<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-06-01 04:35:36"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-08 09:55:00" d="2020-06-08 10:30:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped XI (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>75% Jimmy, Kate and Matt uncover more food secrets. Could squid and chips replace fish and chips as our national dish? Where do multivitamins come from? Why is clotted cream yellow?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-08 10:30:00" d="2020-06-08 11:25:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Summer Sun
With a budget of ?300,000, Laura Hamilton sets out to help Ruth and Philip Trinder from Northamptonshire buy a contemporary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-08 11:25:00" d="2020-06-08 12:25:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Leeds and Preston, Henry Cole makes an international set of clocks out of dashboard time pieces, while Simon O'Brien builds an eccentric chandelier from car headlights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-08 12:25:00" d="2020-06-08 13:25:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Cheshire and the Wirral, Henry and Simon restore a 1920s dance-hall lighting system, an antique butter churn, a huge theatre light and an old enamel advertising sign</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-08 13:25:00" d="2020-06-08 14:25:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY III</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Donna and Paul are hard at work on their most ambitious project yet: creating a tea room. Alex and Ithaca need to raise cash to help repair their 300-year-old roof. Ep14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-08 14:25:00" d="2020-06-08 15:30:00"><n u="Building the Dream">Building the Dream VIII</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Charlie Luxton travels to Essex, where Carla and Elliot are striving to deliver a smart, contemporary home in a woodland clearing for themselves and their five daughters. Ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-08 15:30:00" d="2020-06-08 16:05:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Alan and Sylvie host first, at Watersedge Guest House in Barton on Sea. Mike and Danny waste no time in grumbling about the grime in their room</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-08 16:05:00" d="2020-06-08 16:35:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Tim and Amelia host the rival B&amp;B owners at their non-star-rated boutique accommodation, Nearwater, on the south Cornish coast. But Sylvie and Alan aren't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-08 16:35:00" d="2020-06-08 17:05:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Austrian-born artist Eva hosts in her cosmopolitan B&amp;B, Roundhouse Hotel, on Weymouth seafront. Mike and Danny are shocked by the exposed shower</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-08 17:05:00" d="2020-06-08 17:35:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Showmen Mike and Danny host at the four-star Homecliffe Hotel in Blackpool. Sylvie and Alan have a great view. of the local car wash. And at breakfast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-08 17:35:00" d="2020-06-08 18:05:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the final day and all the B&amp;B hosts meet one last time to find out how much they've been paid. Only one establishment can take the title of best value for money B&amp;B. Who will it be?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-08 18:05:00" d="2020-06-08 19:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It III</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien are in Surrey and Middlesex, where Henry restores a pair of racing go-karts, and Simon repurposes an old butcher's block</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-08 19:05:00" d="2020-06-08 19:55:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Dr Linda Papadopoulos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-08 19:55:00" d="2020-06-08 20:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY III</n><e>TF</e>    <k>The Strawbridge family head to the beaches of Saint-Malo to seek out chateau inspiration. Donna and Paul invite the mayor to the grand opening of their new tea room. Ep15)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-08 20:55:00" d="2020-06-08 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kevin McCloud revisits Alan and Judith, who built a prototype prefab in Cumbria. Did Alan's innovative building system work? And did he realise his dream</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-08 22:00:00" d="2020-06-08 23:00:00"><n>New: The Yorkshire Dales and...</n><e>F</e>    <k>. he Lakes: In Summer - Brand new: A look back on stories from summers gone by in the Yorkshire Dales and the Lakes, featuring sheep shearing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-08 23:00:00" d="2020-06-09 00:00:00"><n u="Nazi Megastructures">Nazi Megastructures V</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Nazi Megastructures
Brand new series - Fortress Japan: While they were in retreat across the Pacific, the Japanese military went to huge lengths</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-09 00:00:00" d="2020-06-09 01:05:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XIV (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Jon Richardson and Cariad Lloyd take on Alan Carr and Kevin Bridges. Elis James and John Robins are in Dictionary Corner with Susie Dent. Plus Rachel Riley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-09 01:05:00" d="2020-06-09 01:55:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Dr Linda Papadopoulos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-09 01:55:00" d="2020-06-09 02:25:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>85% The Passion of St Tibulus: A film that has been denounced by the Pope is due to be shown on Craggy Island, causing conflict between Bishop Brennan and Father Ted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-09 02:25:00" d="2020-06-09 03:00:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted I (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>85% Competition Time: It's the All-Priests-Look-Alike competition and Ted is determined that this year he will defeat his fellow priests from Rugged Island</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-09 03:00:00" d="2020-06-09 04:00:00"><n u="It Was Alright in the...">It Was Alright in the... II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>It Was Alright in the 1990s
Matt Lucas narrates another set of eye-popping clips, this time from the era of cool Britannia, when telly boundaries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-09 04:00:00" d="2020-06-09 07:00:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XIV (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Jon Richardson and Cariad Lloyd take on Alan Carr and Kevin Bridges. Elis James and John Robins are in Dictionary Corner with Susie Dent. Plus Rachel Riley</k>  </p>
</a>
