<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2020-04-12 04:32:45"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-19 09:55:00" d="2020-04-19 10:55:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S IV (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>AC Aceca: Tim Shaw and Fuzz Townshend are in Leeds to restore a rare AC Aceca, a beautiful but little-known British sports car that has been rotting away in a garage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-19 10:55:00" d="2020-04-19 11:55:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S IV (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Datsun 240z: Tim Shaw and Fuzz Townshend are in West Sussex to rescue an iconic 1970s motor, a mighty Datsun 240z, which has been languishing in a retired</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-19 11:55:00" d="2020-04-19 12:55:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S VII (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Triumph TR4: Tim Shaw and Fuzz Townshend steal away a 1962 Triumph TR4 - a great British classic that turns out to be one of their biggest ever rebuilds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-19 12:55:00" d="2020-04-19 13:25:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>Surrey. Will planning enforcement officer Becky's crispy croutons and lamb shank stew impress her guests Petrina, Rob, Shoba and Giovanni? (Ep1/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-19 13:25:00" d="2020-04-19 14:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>Surrey. Shoba serves an Indian menu, but her guests aren't impressed with the frozen fish curry; can some Bollywood-style belly dancing save the day? (Ep2/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-19 14:00:00" d="2020-04-19 14:35:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>Surrey. Drum tutor Rob hopes his Thai-tastic menu will impress his guests and snare him the prize, as well as impressing the object of his affections: Petrina. (Ep3/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-19 14:35:00" d="2020-04-19 15:05:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>Surrey. Petrina hopes her experience entertaining on cruise ships will give her the edge. Or will her dessert, a salted caramel chocolate crunch surprise, win it for her? (Ep4/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-19 15:05:00" d="2020-04-19 15:35:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>Surrey. Giovanni hosts the final night and wants to fly the flag for Sicily with some family-inspired recipes. But a tagliatelle tragedy leaves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-19 15:35:00" d="2020-04-19 16:10:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Jon Shorrock and his wife Julia run the four-star B&amp;B Derwent House in West Sussex. They take the boys to the local shooting range, while the girls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-19 16:10:00" d="2020-04-19 16:40:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Soulmates Peter and Sharron Sorsky share the warmth of their Liverpool home, Kirkby Park B&amp;B, with their guests. They've got a trip to Knowsley Safari</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-19 16:40:00" d="2020-04-19 17:10:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Andy and Julian Banner-Price host the competition at their swanky Plas Dinas Country House in Snowdonia, where they've allocated their guests their priciest rooms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-19 17:10:00" d="2020-04-19 17:45:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>The final B&amp;B of the competition is Annette McAnespie's Hazelwood Farm in Crake, Yorkshire. Hyperactive Annette has lined up her idea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-19 17:45:00" d="2020-04-19 18:15:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>It's been a week of waterworks, tall tales and breakfast scrambles, but who is going to end up with the final prize? And with the competition over</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-19 18:15:00" d="2020-04-19 18:50:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>In and around Guildford. Glamorous 22-year-old Shanice hopes to show she is more than just a pretty face by serving up sumptuous food and dazzling conversation. (Ep1/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-19 18:50:00" d="2020-04-19 19:25:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>In and around Guildford. Retired estate agent Vivi offers a feast inspired by her homeland. And she doesn't disappoint with Norwegian fish soup, singing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-19 19:25:00" d="2020-04-19 19:55:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>In and around Guildford. It's Charlotte's turn to host. She's taken a risk with her Asian-inspired menu and worries that entertainments manager David</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-19 19:55:00" d="2020-04-19 20:25:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>In and around Guildford. It's the turn of entertainments manager David to host. And with his simple food, it's David's fun, excitement and entertainment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-19 20:25:00" d="2020-04-19 21:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>In and around Guildford. Neil hopes to land the prize with his sophisticated menu of a caviar starter, Moroccan lamb main and an artistically angled panna</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-19 21:00:00" d="2020-04-19 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>R</e>    <k>Paul Rimmer has worked with bricks for 40 years, renovating Victorian houses in Bolton. But now he plans to hand-build a state-of-the-art wooden home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-19 22:00:00" d="2020-04-20 00:00:00"><n u="999: On the Front Line">999: On the Front Line IV</n><e>R</e>    <k>West Midlands paramedics treat a man who has taken a heroin overdose, a 73-year-old man with slurred speech, and a toddler with breathing difficulties. Ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-20 00:00:00" d="2020-04-20 01:05:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E X (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Daisy, who's 22 months old, has serious injuries after being kicked in the head by a racehorse at her family's stables. Florence, who's 100, has had a suspected stroke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-20 01:05:00" d="2020-04-20 02:10:00"><n u="999: On the Front Line">999: On the Front Line IV</n><e>R</e>    <k>West Midlands paramedics treat a man who has taken a heroin overdose, a 73-year-old man with slurred speech, and a toddler with breathing difficulties. Ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-20 02:10:00" d="2020-04-20 04:00:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>R</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay revisits some of the restaurants he set out to save, including The Mixing Bowl, The Olde Stone Mill, Peter's and Campania. Have they pulled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-20 04:00:00" d="2020-04-20 07:00:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted II (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>85% Think Fast, Father Ted: Ted receives a car from Bishop Brennan to raffle to raise funds to fix the leaky roof. But, as usual, things go horribly wrong</k>  </p>
</a>
