<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2021-07-11 04:59:53"><p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-18 09:55:00" d="2021-07-18 10:30:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped XIV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Can coffee help you sober up? Kate investigates trendy drink kombucha and meets people who are turning it into clothes! And which cut of beef do thin-cut</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-18 10:30:00" d="2021-07-18 11:30:00"><n>George Clarke's Amazing Spaces</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>George visits a stunning log farmhouse in Canada's Rocky Mountains, an epic panoramic beach house in New Zealand and, in Japan, what could be the world's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-18 11:30:00" d="2021-07-18 12:35:00"><n u="Ugly House to Lovely House with George Clarke">Ugly House to Lovely House with George Clarke II (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Ugly House to Lovely House with. 
. eorge Clarke: Martijn and Sally are desperate to do something to their impractical upside-down 1980s house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-18 12:35:00" d="2021-07-18 13:35:00"><n u="George Clarke's Old House, New Home">George Clarke's Old House, New Home II (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>George Clarke's Old House New Home
George makes a tall, slim Victorian terrace in Stratford-upon-Avon fit for a 21st-century single dad. In Hastings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-18 13:35:00" d="2021-07-18 14:10:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The competition starts at The Oak Tree Cottage in Burley, where Jacqui hopes that her homely approach will win the day. But her communal breakfast doesn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-18 14:10:00" d="2021-07-18 14:40:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The second visit is to The Rising Sun Inn in Bath, where owners Lorraine Hawkins and Norman Butcher impose a dress code for dinner. Some of their guests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-18 14:40:00" d="2021-07-18 15:10:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Martin and Catherine Crosswaite pride themselves on their great Yorkshire hospitality at The Busfeild Arms in East Morton. But Martin's past shocks their guests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-18 15:10:00" d="2021-07-18 15:40:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The final visit is to Epstein House in Liverpool, where there's a competitive Beatles-themed game of charades and some shocking revelations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-18 15:40:00" d="2021-07-18 16:15:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the last day and Patrick has some questions for Jacqui and Jane, while Martin and Catherine have some explaining to do, before the payments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-18 16:15:00" d="2021-07-18 17:15:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY II</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Mariam, Johnno and their teenage son Monty arrive at their new chateau to discover that they have no running water and the builders are busy in every room. Ep13)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-18 17:15:00" d="2021-07-18 18:20:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY II</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Emma and Paul urgently need to fill their lake ready for the artists' retreat they're hosting. Angel gives Abbie and Karen tips on how to save money</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-18 18:20:00" d="2021-07-18 18:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The first visit is to The Bell House Hotel in Wiltshire, where owners Chris and Jacqui aim to bring London chic to the shires. But their absence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-18 18:50:00" d="2021-07-18 19:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The second visit is to The Partridge in Oxfordshire, where Matthew Cockman and Paula Szkwarkowska share a passion for organic food. But the self-service</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-18 19:25:00" d="2021-07-18 19:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The third visit is to Strawberry Gardens B&amp;B in Heysham, where David and Susan Speak aim to make their guests feel at home with northern hospitality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-18 19:55:00" d="2021-07-18 20:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The last visit is to The Bateman's Mill near Chesterfield, where Jade Hendon and Diana Yates aim to be the best, but David and Susan are quick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-18 20:25:00" d="2021-07-18 21:00:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's payment day, and fur flies as Jade tackles Matthew over feedback for The Bateman's Mill. The group thrash out their differences before the winner is revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-18 21:00:00" d="2021-07-18 22:00:00"><n u="999: On the Front Line">999: On the Front Line IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Birmingham, paramedics treat a man having a heart attack. In Coventry, a woman mysteriously collapses. And in Worcester, a baby is struggling to breathe. Ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-18 22:00:00" d="2021-07-18 23:00:00"><n u="999: What's Your Emergency?">999: What's Your Emergency? IV</n><e>RF</e>    <k>This episode explores how parents decide on how much freedom to give young children. A mum discovers her eight-year-old has been playing in woods littered</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-18 23:00:00" d="2021-07-19 00:05:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E I (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Omar, who's 88, is brought to King's College Hospital after experiencing severe stomach pains. And staff battle to save an 18-year-old who's been stabbed in a street fight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-19 00:05:00" d="2021-07-19 01:10:00"><n u="Emergency Helicopter Medics">Emergency Helicopter Medics II</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Air ambulance teams rush to help Bill after his car flips. And Malcolm, who has had a cardiac arrest, is put under emergency anaesthetic on a hospital helipad. Ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-19 01:10:00" d="2021-07-19 02:15:00"><n u="999: On the Front Line">999: On the Front Line IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Birmingham, paramedics treat a man having a heart attack. In Coventry, a woman mysteriously collapses. And in Worcester, a baby is struggling to breathe. Ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-19 02:15:00" d="2021-07-19 03:15:00"><n u="999: What's Your Emergency?">999: What's Your Emergency? IV</n><e>RF</e>    <k>This episode explores how parents decide on how much freedom to give young children. A mum discovers her eight-year-old has been playing in woods littered</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-19 03:15:00" d="2021-07-19 04:20:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E I (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Omar, who's 88, is brought to King's College Hospital after experiencing severe stomach pains. And staff battle to save an 18-year-old who's been stabbed in a street fight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-19 04:20:00" d="2021-07-19 09:55:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>86% The Old Grey Whistle Theft: The arrival of a rebellious priest coincides with the theft of the picnic area supervisor's whistle. Is law and order breaking</k>  </p>
</a>
