<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2020-05-30 04:37:56"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-06 09:55:00" d="2020-06-06 10:30:00"><n>Kirstie's Vintage Gems</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp brings the swinging 60s to Amber and Colin's seaside pad in Edinburgh's Portobello, with some cool concrete and a class in screen-printing furniture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-06 10:30:00" d="2020-06-06 11:25:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Summer Sun
Gillian and Paul Clarke from Stockport have their hearts set on a retirement holiday home on Spain's Costa Cálida</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-06 11:25:00" d="2020-06-06 12:35:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Summer Sun
Foster parents Jo and Bill want a family holiday home where they can enjoy quality time in Spain's Orihuela Costa region</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-06 12:35:00" d="2020-06-06 13:35:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Summer Sun
Derek Hansel and Gina Awoko from Birmingham are looking for a property in the unspoiled countryside of Almeria in Spain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-06 13:35:00" d="2020-06-06 14:40:00"><n u="Location, Location, Location">Location, Location, Location XXVI (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp helps Savannah and John find their first home in Maidstone, while Phil Spencer's with Matt and Tricia, who have ?1.5 million to spend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-06 14:40:00" d="2020-06-06 15:40:00"><n u="Bake Off: The Professionals">Bake Off: The Professionals III</n><e>F</e>    <k>The five remaining teams make the classic layered dessert millefeuille, master the art of illusion, and create a bird-themed piece montée adorned with Paris-Brest. Ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-06 15:40:00" d="2020-06-06 16:10:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Reading. Sonya Smith hopes to disguise her lack of cooking ability with her good humour and a 'touch of sparkle'. But with kitchen calamities galore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-06 16:10:00" d="2020-06-06 16:40:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Reading. Cockney Glen Wilkie is confident his menu will be a winner. But his evening goes from disaster to disaster, with tears at the table when he serves his main. (Ep2/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-06 16:40:00" d="2020-06-06 17:15:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Reading. It's all hands on deck as Richard Howse's girlfriend Katy plans his pirate-themed night. But Sonya isn't convinced by the gluten-free</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-06 17:15:00" d="2020-06-06 17:50:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Reading. Sabi Phagura hosts a bhangra-themed evening with traditional Indian food, but can she succeed despite Glen's efforts to wind everyone up? (Ep4/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-06 17:50:00" d="2020-06-06 18:20:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Reading. Corset-maker Serine Daou hopes her burlesque night will end the competition on a high. But her gourmet burgers aren't very gourmet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-06 18:20:00" d="2020-06-06 18:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>The competition kicks off with a stay at The Kings Head and Queens Jules in Suffolk, where hosts Tim and Jules Anderson offer guests a 21st-century party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-06 18:50:00" d="2020-06-06 19:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Poetry and erotic art are all part of the fun at Gordon and Blossom Hoyles' Hotel Continental in the Essex port of Harwich. But their breakfast doesn't go exactly to plan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-06 19:25:00" d="2020-06-06 19:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Following a cleaning crisis, will host Ryan Davies' selection of his own wines be enough to impress the guests at his five-star B&amp;B, Llanerch Vineyard, in south Wales?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-06 19:55:00" d="2020-06-06 20:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>After touring a paint factory and clashing over previous feedback, the guests at Neil and Tracy's Whitehall Hotel in Darwen, Lancashire, end their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-06 20:25:00" d="2020-06-06 21:00:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>The conflict continues as the B&amp;Bers meet for the last time to confront their critics and find out what they've been paid. Who will walk away with the prize?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-06 21:00:00" d="2020-06-06 22:00:00"><n>Princess Diana's 'Wicked' Stepmother</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Princess Diana's 'Wicked'. 
. tepmother: An insight into the turbulent relationship between Princess Diana and her formidable stepmother Raine Spencer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-06 22:00:00" d="2020-06-06 23:00:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XIII (5)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>This episode explores the notions of luck and chance, when a young man is involved in a high-speed car crash and an 18-year-old breaks his leg while playing football</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-06 23:00:00" d="2020-06-07 00:05:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (21)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>This episode meets some of the youngest patients who visit A&amp;E. Eight-year-old Billy has been hit by falling bricks. Luther, who's six, has a metal washer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 00:05:00" d="2020-06-07 00:40:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted I (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>85% Good Luck, Father Ted: Ted is asked to appear on prestigious TV show Faith of Our Fathers. Could this be the opportunity for him to find stardom and escape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 00:40:00" d="2020-06-07 01:10:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>85% Entertaining Father Stone: For six years, Father Stone has been coming to Craggy Island and for Father Ted, Father Dougal and Father Jack, that's seven years too many</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 01:10:00" d="2020-06-07 02:15:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XIII (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Sean Lock and Stephen Mangan take on guest captain Richard Ayoade and Katherine Ryan. Bill Bailey's in Dictionary Corner with Susie Dent. Plus Rachel Riley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 02:15:00" d="2020-06-07 03:20:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XIII (5)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>This episode explores the notions of luck and chance, when a young man is involved in a high-speed car crash and an 18-year-old breaks his leg while playing football</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 03:20:00" d="2020-06-07 04:25:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>This episode meets some of the youngest patients who visit A&amp;E. Eight-year-old Billy has been hit by falling bricks. Luther, who's six, has a metal washer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 04:25:00" d="2020-06-07 09:55:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted I (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>85% Good Luck, Father Ted: Ted is asked to appear on prestigious TV show Faith of Our Fathers. Could this be the opportunity for him to find stardom and escape</k>  </p>
</a>
