<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2020-05-14 04:55:57"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 09:55:00" d="2020-05-21 10:20:00"><n>Kirstie's Vintage Gems</n><e>RF</e>    <k>In this bite-size episode, Kirstie Allsopp looks back to the 1970s for vintage inspiration. With two of the country's most gifted crafters, she makes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 10:20:00" d="2020-05-21 11:15:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2014 &amp; 2015</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Summer Sun
Publicans Chris and Sue from Shropshire are searching for their dream holiday home on Portugal's stunning Silver Coast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 11:15:00" d="2020-05-21 12:15:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It I (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>In this episode, Henry Cole monkeys around with a monkey bike, while Simon O'Brien uses all his skills to restore an old racing bike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 12:15:00" d="2020-05-21 13:15:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It I (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>In this episode, Simon O'Brien leads Henry Cole to a barn that features an amazing collection of replica Rolls-Royce cars, while Henry tries his hand at driving a tractor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 13:15:00" d="2020-05-21 14:15:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Mariam and Johnno create a French parterre garden, Phillip and his wife Janet move into Chateau de la Fare, and Emma and Paul renovate a Charles Rennie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 14:15:00" d="2020-05-21 15:20:00"><n u="Building the Dream">Building the Dream VII (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Charlie Luxton's in Caterham, Surrey, where Ben and Nicola are transforming a dilapidated bungalow into a contemporary split-level home. But the project is a bit hectic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 15:20:00" d="2020-05-21 15:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The competition kicks off at the contemporary Fraoch House in Edinburgh, run by Gareth Houston and his mother Heather Davidson, who hope to impress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 15:50:00" d="2020-05-21 16:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Newly-weds Kevin and Elaine hope the traditional style of The Springfield Hotel in Marple, near Manchester, will be enough to win over their guests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 16:20:00" d="2020-05-21 16:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Suzy Way hopes that her modern, unconventional B&amp;B near Loughborough, plus a spot of wakeboarding and a home-cooked curry, will do the trick for her guests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 16:50:00" d="2020-05-21 17:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>John Benson runs The Benson Hotel in Braintree, Essex. He hopes his charm, a race at a skidpan track and a good old-fashioned singsong will win everyone's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 17:25:00" d="2020-05-21 17:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the final day of the competition and the B&amp;B owners meet for the last time to find out what they've been paid and to settle some scores</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 17:55:00" d="2020-05-21 18:55:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>In this episode, Max McMurdo upcycles a brass propeller into a stylish table lamp, while Henry Cole goes all Victorian with an old pond yacht</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 18:55:00" d="2020-05-21 19:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The final visit is to Robin and Liza's Georgian mansion, Tall John's House, in the Brecon Beacons. The guests gush over their new friendships, but Vicky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 19:25:00" d="2020-05-21 19:55:00"><n>Jamie: Keep Cooking and Carry On</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Jamie Oliver shows us some recipes, tips and hacks tailored for the unique times we're living in, including home-made pasta shapes, chicken fajitas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 19:55:00" d="2020-05-21 20:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY IV</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Phillip and Janet rush to finish the bridal suite for daughter Penny's wedding, Mariam and Johnno prepare to host seven guests, and Emma and Paul complete</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 20:55:00" d="2020-05-21 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kevin McCloud meets university professors Celia and Diana, who plan a state-of-the-art home that will be the world's first computer-cut house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 22:00:00" d="2020-05-21 23:15:00"><n u="Outlander">Outlander IV</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Outlander
Brand new series - The False Bride: After refusing his aunt's plantation, Jamie and Claire set out into the North Carolina wilderness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 23:15:00" d="2020-05-22 00:20:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XI (7)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as David Mitchell and Cariad Lloyd take on Jon Richardson and Russell Howard. Sam Simmons joins Susie Dent in Dictionary Corner. Plus Rachel Riley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 00:20:00" d="2020-05-22 00:55:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>85% A Song for Europe: Ted and Dougal decide to enter the Eurosong contest. With inspired lyrics, a jaunty tune and the right attitude, they stand a good chance. Don't they?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 00:55:00" d="2020-05-22 01:20:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>85% The Plague: Father Dougal is excited about his pet rabbit, Sampras, while Bishop Brennan is due to arrive to investigate a case of suspected</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 01:20:00" d="2020-05-22 02:25:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Nicky's been hit by a car. Doctors rush her for a CT scan. Her husband Richard tries to reassure everyone as her daughter Annie tries to come to terms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 02:25:00" d="2020-05-22 03:30:00"><n>Shocking Emergency Calls</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In California, a woman who's just given birth is threatened by wildfire. And in Georgia, a mother calls to report an attempted murder by her sons. (Ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 03:30:00" d="2020-05-22 04:05:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>85% A Song for Europe: Ted and Dougal decide to enter the Eurosong contest. With inspired lyrics, a jaunty tune and the right attitude, they stand a good chance. Don't they?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 04:05:00" d="2020-05-22 04:30:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>85% The Plague: Father Dougal is excited about his pet rabbit, Sampras, while Bishop Brennan is due to arrive to investigate a case of suspected</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 04:30:00" d="2020-05-22 07:30:00"><n>Food Unwrapped</n><e>R</e>    <k>Jimmy, Kate and Matt present some of their favourite investigations. Is there a wasp in your fig? How do energy drinks give you a boost? Why can't you eat kidney beans raw?</k>  </p>
</a>
