<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2019-08-13 02:20:29"><p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-19 09:55:00" d="2019-08-19 10:20:00"><n>Kirstie's Fill Your House for Free</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and the team come to the rescue of Dave and Kate, whose house has been flooded</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-19 10:20:00" d="2019-08-19 10:50:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped VI (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>76% Jimmy, Kate and Matt uncover more secrets about our food. Are alarming headlines about MSG justified? Are Brazil nuts radioactive? And how is elderflower cordial made?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-19 10:50:00" d="2019-08-19 11:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY I</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>As Jonathan and Michael prepare their chateau for the big wedding, they have a sewage issue that threatens the whole first floor. Mandy and Steve continue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-19 11:55:00" d="2019-08-19 13:00:00"><n u="Bake Off: The Professionals">Bake Off: The Professionals I (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The remaining teams take on a secret recipe challenge as well as a chocolate showpiece inspired by the theme of the four seasons, requiring huge feats of patisserie skill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-19 13:00:00" d="2019-08-19 14:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Leeds and Preston, Henry Cole makes an international set of clocks out of dashboard time pieces, while Simon O'Brien builds an eccentric chandelier from car headlights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-19 14:05:00" d="2019-08-19 14:35:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jon Shorrock and his wife Julia run the four-star B&amp;B Derwent House in West Sussex. They take the boys to the local shooting range, while the girls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-19 14:35:00" d="2019-08-19 15:10:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Soulmates Peter and Sharron Sorsky share the warmth of their Liverpool home, Kirkby Park B&amp;B, with their guests. They've got a trip to Knowsley Safari</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-19 15:10:00" d="2019-08-19 15:40:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Andy and Julian Banner-Price host the competition at their swanky Plas Dinas Country House in Snowdonia, where they've allocated their guests their priciest rooms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-19 15:40:00" d="2019-08-19 16:15:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The final B&amp;B of the competition is Annette McAnespie's Hazelwood Farm in Crake, Yorkshire. Hyperactive Annette has lined up her idea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-19 16:15:00" d="2019-08-19 16:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's been a week of waterworks, tall tales and breakfast scrambles, but who is going to end up with the final prize? And with the competition over</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-19 16:50:00" d="2019-08-19 17:50:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer search for homes for two families. One pair want to recreate their Australian beachside lifestyle in Bournemouth;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-19 17:50:00" d="2019-08-19 18:55:00"><n u="Love It or List It Australia">Love It or List It Australia II</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Con and Rita's four-bedroom house in Preston, a Melbourne suburb, is dated, dark and dreary. Con wants to move, but Rita thinks their home just needs opening out. Ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-19 18:55:00" d="2019-08-19 19:55:00"><n u="The Secret Life of the Zoo">The Secret Life of the Zoo II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Two of Chester Zoo's Grevy's zebras are about to give birth. Meanwhile, Asiatic lioness Kumari seems to be losing interest in her partner Iblis. Plus: warthogs and sloths</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-19 19:55:00" d="2019-08-19 20:55:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick XI (6)</n><t>S</t><e>TF</e>    <k>The Supervet
Sports pundit Lee Dixon brings his beloved rescue dog to see Professor Noel. An owner comes all the way from Guernsey with her injured dog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-19 20:55:00" d="2019-08-19 22:00:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau">Escape to the Chateau V (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Angel creates a series of rooms bursting with beauty in the chateau's pepper-pot turret. Dick opens up a parkour fitness trail in the grounds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-19 22:00:00" d="2019-08-19 23:00:00"><n u="Great Canal Journeys">Great Canal Journeys X</n><t>S</t><e>TF</e>    <k>Great Canal Journeys: Asian. 
. dyssey: Timothy West and Prunella Scales complete their grand tour of South East Asian waterways on Vietnam's Mekong Delta</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-19 23:00:00" d="2019-08-20 00:05:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E II</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>A look at young men being treated at King's, including a 19-year-old fitness fanatic injured in a canal barge accident and a pre-operative transsexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-20 00:05:00" d="2019-08-20 01:05:00"><n u="999: What's Your Emergency?">999: What's Your Emergency? III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>This episode explores the rise in violent crime across the UK and the increase in attacks on our police forces. Cheshire PC Claire Heatley is assaulted by a suspect. Ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-20 01:05:00" d="2019-08-20 02:15:00"><n>Shocking Emergency Calls</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series: In California, a woman who's just given birth is threatened by wildfire. And in Georgia, a mother calls to report an attempted murder by her sons. (Ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-20 02:15:00" d="2019-08-20 03:15:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick XI (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Supervet
Sports pundit Lee Dixon brings his beloved rescue dog to see Professor Noel. An owner comes all the way from Guernsey with her injured dog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-20 03:15:00" d="2019-08-20 04:20:00"><n u="The Secret Life of the Zoo">The Secret Life of the Zoo II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Two of Chester Zoo's Grevy's zebras are about to give birth. Meanwhile, Asiatic lioness Kumari seems to be losing interest in her partner Iblis. Plus: warthogs and sloths</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-20 04:20:00" d="2019-08-20 07:20:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped VI (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>76% Jimmy, Kate and Matt uncover more secrets about our food. Are alarming headlines about MSG justified? Are Brazil nuts radioactive? And how is elderflower cordial made?</k>  </p>
</a>
