<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2020-04-16 04:35:06"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-23 09:55:00" d="2020-04-23 10:20:00"><n>Kirstie's Vintage Gems</n><e>R</e>    <k>In this bite-size episode, Kirstie Allsopp looks back to the seventies for inspiration. With two of the country's most gifted crafters, she creates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-23 10:20:00" d="2020-04-23 11:15:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2014 &amp; 2015</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Home or Away
Marc and Lucy Champ are torn between east Devon - where Marc grew up - and Comares in Andalucia, southern Spain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-23 11:15:00" d="2020-04-23 12:15:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2014 &amp; 2015</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Home or Away
Lisa and Stuart Newby are torn between a holiday home on Yorkshire's 'Dinosaur Coast' or something on the Costa Granadina in Spain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-23 12:15:00" d="2020-04-23 13:15:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It III</n><e>R</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien fix old possessions for profit. Henry restores two quad bikes and a sun lounger while Simon rescues a canoe and turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-23 13:15:00" d="2020-04-23 14:15:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It III</n><e>R</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien are in Essex where Henry restores a car trailer and a 1970s racing bike, and Simon turns his attentions to lovingly restoring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-23 14:15:00" d="2020-04-23 15:20:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau">Escape to the Chateau I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Dick and Angel are due to marry in just a few weeks, expecting 200 guests. But room after room still needs to be restored, decorated and furnished</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-23 15:20:00" d="2020-04-23 15:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Fay and Ray of the Shiralee B&amp;B in Salisbury, with its striking Tunisian inspiration, start this round. But their cluttered decor and CCTV provokes comment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-23 15:50:00" d="2020-04-23 16:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>The second visit is to The Bluebell Woods in Northampton, where David and Donna try to bring a touch of class to their woodland B&amp;B. But the feedback has the hosts fuming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-23 16:20:00" d="2020-04-23 16:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>The third visit is to The Lion Hotel in Pontypool, where manager Marc Harris and chef Wayne Williams aim to deliver a high-end service. But over dinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-23 16:55:00" d="2020-04-23 17:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>The last visit is to The New Inn, Talgarth, where ex-naval officer Damon Lewis is the sole captain of his ship. Wayne and Marc prepare to be honest, while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-23 17:25:00" d="2020-04-23 17:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>It's payment day and the owners are meeting for the last time. Tensions come to a head, as the group air their grievances and find out what they've</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-23 17:55:00" d="2020-04-23 18:55:00"><n>A New Life in the Sun</n><e>R</e>    <k>The owners of a vineyard open a pop up restaurant in a stunning location. Two B&amp;Bers host an unusual event to boost takings. And in Spain, a wannabe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-23 18:55:00" d="2020-04-23 19:55:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S I (9)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Zodiac Come Back: Tim and Fuzz head to Norfolk to revive an ageing Ford Zodiac, but tensions rise when Fuzz changes the paintwork back to its original colour scheme</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-23 19:55:00" d="2020-04-23 20:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau">Escape to the Chateau II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Dick and Angel Strawbridge's adventure turning a shabby French castle into a family home and venue continues. Dick makes a pig roaster and it's their son's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-23 20:55:00" d="2020-04-23 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>R</e>    <k>Architect Ben Hebblethwaite builds a nautically-styled home that floats on stilts for his boat-loving uncle James Strangeways. But a contractor problem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-23 22:00:00" d="2020-04-23 23:00:00"><n u="Great Canal Journeys">Great Canal Journeys X</n><t>S</t>    <k>Great Canal Journeys: Asian. 
. dyssey: Timothy West and Prunella Scales complete their grand tour of South East Asian waterways on Vietnam's Mekong Delta</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-23 23:00:00" d="2020-04-24 00:05:00"><n>It Was Alright in the 1970s</n><e>R</e>    <k>This series revisits the TV decade that taste forgot. This episode features jaw-dropping clips of outrageous sex jokes and smoking in prime-time shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-24 00:05:00" d="2020-04-24 00:40:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>85% A Song for Europe: Ted and Dougal decide to enter the Eurosong contest. With inspired lyrics, a jaunty tune and the right attitude, they stand a good chance. Don't they?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-24 00:40:00" d="2020-04-24 01:10:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>85% The Plague: Father Dougal is excited about his pet rabbit, Sampras, while Bishop Brennan is due to arrive to investigate a case of suspected</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-24 01:10:00" d="2020-04-24 02:15:00"><n>Shocking Emergency Calls</n><e>R</e>    <k>A beautiful September morning in Kent turns to carnage when fog suddenly hits the Sheppey Crossing, creating one of the biggest road traffic accidents in UK history. (Ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-24 02:15:00" d="2020-04-24 03:15:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown VIII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts the panel game. Sean Lock and Jason Manford take on Jon Richardson and Roisin Conaty, while Sam Simmons joins Susie Dent in Dictionary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-24 03:15:00" d="2020-04-24 03:50:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>85% A Song for Europe: Ted and Dougal decide to enter the Eurosong contest. With inspired lyrics, a jaunty tune and the right attitude, they stand a good chance. Don't they?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-24 03:50:00" d="2020-04-24 04:20:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>85% The Plague: Father Dougal is excited about his pet rabbit, Sampras, while Bishop Brennan is due to arrive to investigate a case of suspected</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-24 04:20:00" d="2020-04-24 07:20:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped VI</n><e>R</e>    <k>Why do we have to pay for pistachios that we can't crack open and eat? Are traditional rolled oats better for us than quick-cook porridge? Plus: the trouble with draught Prosecco. Ep5)</k>  </p>
</a>
