<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2019-07-11 00:18:51"><p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-17 09:55:00" d="2019-07-17 10:45:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2015 &amp; 2016</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Winter Sun
Tina Watkins wants to make the most of the incredibly good value property in Spain's Granada Province</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-17 10:45:00" d="2019-07-17 11:45:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau">Escape to the Chateau I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>An extended four-part version of series one. Wanting to create a stunning honeymoon suite, Angel asks Dick to smash a hole in the three-feet-thick castle wall</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-17 11:45:00" d="2019-07-17 13:00:00"><n u="The Great British Bake Off">The Great British Bake Off I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Paul Hollywood and Prue Leith set three tough challenges for the remaining 10 bakers in bread week, including an ambitious sculpture showstopper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-17 13:00:00" d="2019-07-17 14:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It I (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>In this episode, Simon O'Brien leads Henry Cole to a barn that features an amazing collection of replica Rolls-Royce cars, while Henry tries his hand at driving a tractor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-17 14:05:00" d="2019-07-17 14:40:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The first visit of this competition is to Blackthorn Farm on Anglesey, Wales, where best friends Richard and Susan hope to impress, but there are mixed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-17 14:40:00" d="2019-07-17 15:10:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Graham and Barbara pride themselves on offering basic facilities for great value at the White Swan Hotel in West Yorkshire. But will their guests be happy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-17 15:10:00" d="2019-07-17 15:40:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Malcolm and Fiona Piers-Taylor hope to show their guests an alternative way of life at The Old Mill House in Bridport, Dorset. But their guests aren't so sure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-17 15:40:00" d="2019-07-17 16:15:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The final visit of the week is to Rachel and Dan Lonergan's Brighton Inn, where the guests clown around as they learn some circus skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-17 16:15:00" d="2019-07-17 16:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the last day of the competition and the B&amp;B owners come together and confront their rivals. Tensions run high as the payments are finally revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-17 16:50:00" d="2019-07-17 17:50:00"><n u="Kirstie and Phil's Love It or List It">Kirstie and Phil's Love It or List It III (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie and Phil's Love It or. 
. ist It: Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer help the Clayton-Fisher family from Walthamstow, who can't decide if their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-17 17:50:00" d="2019-07-17 18:55:00"><n u="Love It or List It Australia">Love It or List It Australia II</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Love It or List It Australia
Brand new series: Con and Rita's four-bedroom house in Preston, a Melbourne suburb, is dated, dark and dreary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-17 18:55:00" d="2019-07-17 19:55:00"><n u="The Secret Life of the Zoo">The Secret Life of the Zoo III (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Can rhino Kifaru - who has arthritic knees - mate with younger, taller and heavier female rhino Malindi? Tapir Jenny falls ill. Widowed porcupine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-17 19:55:00" d="2019-07-17 20:55:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick IX (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Supervet
Marley the dog is admitted to the clinic with severe dysplasia of the elbow. A Rhodesian ridgeback has a high-risk operation. And Noel treats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-17 20:55:00" d="2019-07-17 22:00:00"><n u="Great Canal Journeys">Great Canal Journeys VIII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Timothy West and Prunella Scales explore the Norfolk Broads, one of Britain's most ancient and picturesque waterways, discovering the area's unique</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-17 22:00:00" d="2019-07-17 23:15:00"><n u="Outlander">Outlander III (2)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Outlander
Brand new series - Surrender: Jamie leads a lonely life until Lallybroch is threatened by Redcoats pursuing an elusive figure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-17 23:15:00" d="2019-07-18 00:15:00"><n>Inside Royal Homes</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Inside Royal Homes
Brand new: Exploring how historic buildings have become modern royal homes, from Kensington Palace to Frogmore Cottage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-18 00:15:00" d="2019-07-18 01:25:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XIV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The series that follows the stories of patients at St George's hospital returns for a new run. Staff try to unravel the mystery of an unknown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-18 01:25:00" d="2019-07-18 02:25:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown X (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts, with guest captain Claudia Winkleman and Johnny Vegas versus Jon Richardson and Reginald D Hunter. Sara Pascoe joins Susie Dent in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-18 02:25:00" d="2019-07-18 03:30:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick IX (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Supervet
Marley the dog is admitted to the clinic with severe dysplasia of the elbow. A Rhodesian ridgeback has a high-risk operation. And Noel treats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-18 03:30:00" d="2019-07-18 04:30:00"><n u="The Secret Life of the Zoo">The Secret Life of the Zoo III (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Can rhino Kifaru - who has arthritic knees - mate with younger, taller and heavier female rhino Malindi? Tapir Jenny falls ill. Widowed porcupine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-18 04:30:00" d="2019-07-18 09:55:00"><n>8 Out of 10 Cats</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>78% 8 Out of 10 Cats: Jimmy, Sean. 
. &amp; Jon's Best Bits: Jimmy Carr and team captains Sean Lock and Jon Richardson select their favourite</k>  </p>
</a>
