<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-05-26 04:37:52"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 09:55:00" d="2020-06-02 10:30:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped X (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>75% How do you farm crocodiles? Kate's in Australia to find out and collect crocodile eggs from under their mothers' noses. Plus, cod liver</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 10:30:00" d="2020-06-02 11:25:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Summer Sun
Ruth Jobey wants to escape from her busy London life to the relaxed town of Oliva on Spain's 'orange blossom coast', Costa Azahar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 11:25:00" d="2020-06-02 12:25:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Simon O'Brien goes military as he converts tank parts into garden furniture, while Henry Cole takes his life in his hands with a motorised skateboard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 12:25:00" d="2020-06-02 13:25:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (19)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Henry and Simon head to a private railway. Simon transforms a lantern into a stylish table, while Henry converts a fire extinguisher into a steampunk lamp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 13:25:00" d="2020-06-02 14:25:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY IV</n><e>R</e>    <k>Wendy and Marcus prepare to host their first official booking. Amy and Marc turn their grounds into an escapist retreat. Ben and Billie start building</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 14:25:00" d="2020-06-02 15:30:00"><n u="Building the Dream">Building the Dream VIII</n><e>R</e>    <k>In Cambridgeshire, Charlie Luxton meets Chris and Philippa, who plan to self-build a four-bed detached home for the price of a tiny terrace</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 15:30:00" d="2020-06-02 16:05:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>First to host are Steve and Beverly Green from Centery Farm in north Devon, whose sheep-herding activity is hit by rain and fog, so the group resort</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 16:05:00" d="2020-06-02 16:35:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>The second visit is to The Little Gloster on the Isle of Wight, where owner and professional chef Ben Cooke shows his guests how to make gravlax</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 16:35:00" d="2020-06-02 17:05:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Stephen hosts at his four-star Old Hall House, where the on-site activities include shooting and archery. And guest Sandie makes a surprising revelation to the group</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 17:05:00" d="2020-06-02 17:35:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>The final visit of the competition is to The House of Agnes in Canterbury, run by ex-hotel inspector Sandie. But could Sandie's former job backfire on her?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 17:35:00" d="2020-06-02 18:05:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>It's the final day and the B&amp;B hosts gather one last time to find out how much they've been paid. Only one establishment can take the title of best value for money B&amp;B. Who will it be?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 18:05:00" d="2020-06-02 19:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It III</n><e>R</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien fix old possessions for profit. Henry restores two quad bikes and a sun lounger, while Simon rescues a canoe and turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 19:05:00" d="2020-06-02 19:55:00"><n>Countdown</n>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Adrian Chiles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 19:55:00" d="2020-06-02 20:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY IV</n>    <k>Ben and Billie get to work on their dilapidated boathouse, Amy and Marc get their barn and café ready for their first yoga class, and Wendy and Marcus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 20:55:00" d="2020-06-02 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>R</e>    <k>Stonemason Adam and his partner Nicola have 12 months in which to convert the engine house of a silver mine in Cornwall into a home. But it quickly becomes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 22:00:00" d="2020-06-02 23:00:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XIII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Shea and Bob are both 17. Shea's been stabbed, while Bob has impaled his leg on a fence. And 33-year-old James arrives by ambulance after fainting at home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 23:00:00" d="2020-06-03 00:05:00"><n u="999: On the Front Line">999: On the Front Line IV</n><e>R</e>    <k>Paramedics treat a teenager with suspected meningitis, a man with diabetes and dangerously high blood sugar levels, and a man with a suspected swollen artery. Ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-03 00:05:00" d="2020-06-03 01:05:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XIII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Jon Richardson and Joe Lycett take on Sean Lock and Michelle Wolf. Adam Riches is in Dictionary Corner, and Rachel Riley looks after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-03 01:05:00" d="2020-06-03 01:55:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>R</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Adrian Chiles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-03 01:55:00" d="2020-06-03 02:55:00"><n u="It Was Alright in the...">It Was Alright in the... II (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>It Was Alright in the 1980s
Matt Lucas narrates this trawl through 80s TV, a time of revolution, big hair, aggressive poets and monkeys playing tennis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-03 02:55:00" d="2020-06-03 04:00:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XIII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Shea and Bob are both 17. Shea's been stabbed, while Bob has impaled his leg on a fence. And 33-year-old James arrives by ambulance after fainting at home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-03 04:00:00" d="2020-06-03 07:00:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XIII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Jon Richardson and Joe Lycett take on Sean Lock and Michelle Wolf. Adam Riches is in Dictionary Corner, and Rachel Riley looks after</k>  </p>
</a>
