<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2019-08-09 01:39:49"><p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-15 09:55:00" d="2019-08-15 10:20:00"><n>Food Unwrapped</n><e>R</e>    <k>Why is maple syrup so expensive? And jelly beans don't contain gelatine, so what is the jelly in a jelly bean?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-15 10:20:00" d="2019-08-15 10:50:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped XVI</n>    <k>How do you milk a camel? Kate Quilton investigates, and explores camel milk's rising popularity. And should we buy supermarkets' standard products or value ranges? Ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-15 10:50:00" d="2019-08-15 11:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY I</n><e>R</e>    <k>Jonathan and Michael face their investors, but their new idea to keep goats does not go down well. And Philip and Angelina contend with broken toilets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-15 11:55:00" d="2019-08-15 13:00:00"><n u="Bake Off: The Professionals">Bake Off: The Professionals I (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The teams are tasked with reinventing the classic Eton mess while also tackling an exceedingly tricky challenge making perfect miniature classics</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-15 13:00:00" d="2019-08-15 14:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (10)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>In this episode, Max McMurdo upcycles a brass propeller into a stylish table lamp, while Henry Cole goes all Victorian with an old pond yacht</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-15 14:05:00" d="2019-08-15 14:35:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Claire of Robertsbrook Guesthouse, Swanage, hosts first and fancies her chances. But her first guests take their bedroom apart searching for dust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-15 14:35:00" d="2019-08-15 15:10:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Quirky Cornish couple Lynn and Ziggy hope to impress with their two-star paradise Eden Lodge. But, from the start, their guests are unimpressed by their surroundings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-15 15:10:00" d="2019-08-15 15:40:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Dexby Townhouse in Cardiff is run by Charlotte Church's parents, James and Maria, who lay on a day of white-water rafting and organise a magic show for the evening</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-15 15:40:00" d="2019-08-15 16:15:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>It is the last stay of the competition and the turn of newly-weds Pip and Nicky, who run Muddifords Court Country House in Devon. Will their guests enjoy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-15 16:15:00" d="2019-08-15 16:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>There are tears, outrage and arguments as the group meet one last time to find out exactly how much they have been paid by their fellow hoteliers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-15 16:50:00" d="2019-08-15 17:50:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>R</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer catch up with house-hunters in East Molesey, Surrey, and a couple hoping to swap Watford for St Albans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-15 17:50:00" d="2019-08-15 18:55:00"><n u="Love It or List It Australia">Love It or List It Australia II</n><e>R</e>    <k>Childhood sweethearts Paul and Michelle have outgrown their three-bed house in Brisbane suburb Boondall. Will they move elsewhere or give their home a makeover? Ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-15 18:55:00" d="2019-08-15 19:55:00"><n u="The Secret Life of the Zoo">The Secret Life of the Zoo I (5)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Boris the chimp takes a moorhen hostage. French crocodile François turns his snout up at British food. The keepers try to spark romance between two turtles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-15 19:55:00" d="2019-08-15 20:55:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick XI (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Supervet
A Labrador puppy needs fitted plates and stem cell injections for elbow disease. And a Russian black terrier has a cancerous growth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-15 20:55:00" d="2019-08-15 22:00:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau">Escape to the Chateau V (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Dick Strawbridge and his partner Angel throw open the shutters of their French chateau for a new season, as they get to work creating a luxury glamping experience</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-15 22:00:00" d="2019-08-15 23:00:00"><n>24 Hour Baby Hospital</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: 24 Hour Baby Hospital
Brand new series: Life at the world's longest-running maternity hospital - The Rotunda in Dublin - where over one million</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-15 23:00:00" d="2019-08-16 00:05:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E I</n><e>R</e>    <k>Doctors Firas and André operate on a 78-year-old, who needs surgery on a life-threatening gut condition. Other patients include a man who twisted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-16 00:05:00" d="2019-08-16 01:10:00"><n u="999: What's Your Emergency?">999: What's Your Emergency? III</n><e>R</e>    <k>Focusing on issues around immigration in Cheshire, this episode features a heated arrest at a supermarket, and explores the rise in racially aggravated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-16 01:10:00" d="2019-08-16 02:10:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XII (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts the words-and-numbers quiz with Sean Lock and Joe Wilkinson who take on Jon Richardson and Jayde Adams. David Baddiel is in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-16 02:10:00" d="2019-08-16 03:15:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick XI (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Supervet
A Labrador puppy needs fitted plates and stem cell injections for elbow disease. And a Russian black terrier has a cancerous growth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-16 03:15:00" d="2019-08-16 04:20:00"><n u="The Secret Life of the Zoo">The Secret Life of the Zoo I (5)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Boris the chimp takes a moorhen hostage. French crocodile François turns his snout up at British food. The keepers try to spark romance between two turtles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-16 04:20:00" d="2019-08-16 09:55:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped XVI</n><e>R</e>    <k>How do you milk a camel? Kate Quilton investigates, and explores camel milk's rising popularity. And should we buy supermarkets' standard products or value ranges? Ep4)</k>  </p>
</a>
