<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2021-07-09 07:08:25"><p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-16 09:55:00" d="2021-07-16 10:15:00"><n>Kirstie's Handmade Treasures</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and cider maker Andy Thomstone show us how to make a winter version of one of our favourite drinks. Plus: a limoncello recipe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-16 10:15:00" d="2021-07-16 11:05:00"><n u="Heir Hunters">Heir Hunters VII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>One heir goes on a journey of discovery to fill in the pieces of his late cousin's secret Cold War involvement. Ep20)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-16 11:05:00" d="2021-07-16 12:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It III</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Nantwich and Stoke-on-Trent, Henry Cole tarts up a 1960s moped once favoured by model Twiggy, and Simon O'Brien restores an early Mirror dinghy. Ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-16 12:05:00" d="2021-07-16 13:10:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It III</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In North Yorkshire and the Midlands, Henry Cole restores a petrol pump and turns a hub cap into a clock, while Simon O'Brien repurposes a copper immersion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-16 13:10:00" d="2021-07-16 14:10:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S IV (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Tim and Fuzz's Greatest Hits: Tim Shaw and Fuzz Townshend take Tim's 1965 Ford Mustang Fastback on a road trip to revisit some of their favourite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-16 14:10:00" d="2021-07-16 15:15:00"><n u="Emergency Helicopter Medics">Emergency Helicopter Medics I (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The medics help an injured horse rider in a forest in Norfolk. Steph is trapped and injured after a bad smash in Northumberland. And Paul sustains burns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-16 15:15:00" d="2021-07-16 15:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The competition kicks off at the 'self B&amp;B' Bove Town House in Glastonbury, where Shannon Slater-Dent and Trevor Tredgett treat their guests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-16 15:50:00" d="2021-07-16 16:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kathryn Langley and Trevor Burnell welcome their rivals to Treberthan B&amp;B in Cornwall, where they nearly come unstuck at breakfast and are left with some explaining to do</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-16 16:20:00" d="2021-07-16 16:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Stevie King and his head chef David Lovett host at SugarBeat Eating House in Swainsthorpe, Norfolk. But there are cleanliness concerns and guests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-16 16:50:00" d="2021-07-16 17:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The final visit is to The Fritton Arms in Norfolk, where Ben Davenport and his partner Sian Dewaal aspire to run the perfect B&amp;B, but</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-16 17:20:00" d="2021-07-16 17:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the final day and the B&amp;Bers meet for the last time to find out how much they've been paid. Tensions run high as issues of hygiene, noise and delayed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-16 17:55:00" d="2021-07-16 18:55:00"><n u="Grand Designs New Zealand">Grand Designs New Zealand III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Mother-of-six Kelly from Helensville, north west of Auckland, hopes to recreate the historic villa she fell in love with as a child, but her husband wants a modern house. Ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-16 18:55:00" d="2021-07-16 19:55:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick IV (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Supervet
Noel pushes the boundaries of life-saving medicine with surgery on an Alsatian puppy. And a young chihuahua with a neck deformity needs delicate surgery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-16 19:55:00" d="2021-07-16 20:55:00"><n>Escape to the Chateau</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Escape to the Chateau:. 
. esigning the Dream: This episode celebrates Angel's creativity with exquisitely designed rooms and bathroom suites</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-16 20:55:00" d="2021-07-16 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>This episode follows actor Sean Simons' epic bid to turn a castle ruins in Ireland into a spectacular fantasy home the hard way: with no architect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-16 22:00:00" d="2021-07-17 00:00:00"><n u="Nordic Murders">Nordic Murders II</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Nordic Murders
Brand new series: Second series of the German crime drama from Walter Presents. After a restaurateur and a perpetrator</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-17 00:00:00" d="2021-07-17 01:00:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E I (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The medical team, patients and their families face the meaning of life and death. One patient, 77-year-old John, faces a dangerous operation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-17 01:00:00" d="2021-07-17 02:05:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E I (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Saturday shift sees a range of sport and drink-related injuries. And when a family party goes horribly wrong, a father and son sustain life-threatening injuries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-17 02:05:00" d="2021-07-17 03:05:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XVIII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Sean Lock and Rob Beckett take on guest team captain Alan Carr and Sarah Millican. Nick Mohammed joins Susie Dent in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-17 03:05:00" d="2021-07-17 04:10:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E I (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The medical team, patients and their families face the meaning of life and death. One patient, 77-year-old John, faces a dangerous operation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-17 04:10:00" d="2021-07-17 07:10:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped XIV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kate meets a tech start-up who hope to feed the world by growing fish flesh in a dish. Plus: how do you make ice cubes that aren't cloudy? And why can't</k>  </p>
</a>
