<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-05-12 04:36:40"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-19 09:55:00" d="2020-05-19 10:20:00"><n>Kirstie's Vintage Gems</n><e>R</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp demonstrates cool tricks for dressing a dining table. She makes a paper napkin rose and a cupcake bouquet, and uses vintage teacups</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-19 10:20:00" d="2020-05-19 11:15:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2014 &amp; 2015</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Summer Sun
Steven and Jennie want a holiday home that can double up as a rental investment on Spain's Costa del Sol</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-19 11:15:00" d="2020-05-19 12:15:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It I (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien fix up unwanted items and sell them to make a profit for their owners. In this episode, Henry gives Simon a motorcycling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-19 12:15:00" d="2020-05-19 13:15:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It I (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien are in the Cotswolds and Somerset, where their finds include a set of milk churns and an old munitions shell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-19 13:15:00" d="2020-05-19 14:15:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Stephanie has big plans for her ground-floor apartment, Sarah and George secure their first wedding and Debbie and Nigel's renovations are halted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-19 14:15:00" d="2020-05-19 15:20:00"><n u="Building the Dream">Building the Dream VII (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Charlie Luxton heads to Woking in Surrey to meet Jason and Philippa, who think they have discovered the perfect refurb project. But will it take them to the brink?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-19 15:20:00" d="2020-05-19 15:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The competition starts at Chimneys B&amp;B in Suffolk, where Carolyn Spilling hopes her guests will like her uptempo personality. But Andrea and John aren't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-19 15:50:00" d="2020-05-19 16:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The second visit is to Neale and Julie Taylor's vegetarian B&amp;B, Copperfields Guest House in Broadstairs, Kent. But parking causes concern for guests Andrea and John</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-19 16:20:00" d="2020-05-19 16:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The third visit is to Andrea Gardner and John Marr's The George and Abbotsford in Melrose, Scotland. Carolyn and Delia have toilet troubles, and Massimo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-19 16:55:00" d="2020-05-19 17:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Italian chef Massimo and his cousin Raf welcome their guests to Massimo's in Seaham, County Durham. Carolyn and Delia are missing a bath, and Andrea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-19 17:25:00" d="2020-05-19 17:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the final day of the competition and the B&amp;B owners meet for the last time. There's fighting talk and some low blows as the payments are revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-19 17:55:00" d="2020-05-19 18:55:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien look for profit potential in some church organ pipes and old leather sports car seats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-19 18:55:00" d="2020-05-19 19:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The second visit is to Raouf and his friend Chrissie at the New Promenade Hotel in Blackpool. There's a teetering toilet seat and Clarkey and Katie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-19 19:25:00" d="2020-05-19 19:55:00"><n>Jamie: Keep Cooking and Carry On</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Jamie Oliver shows us some recipes, tips and hacks tailored for the unique times we're living in, including chocolate cake, squash and spinach pasta rotolo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-19 19:55:00" d="2020-05-19 20:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY IV</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Debbie and Nigel start landscaping their five-acre grounds, Sarah and George run into trouble as they host their first-ever wedding and Stephanie suffers scheduling woes. Ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-19 20:55:00" d="2020-05-19 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kevin McCloud catches up with the story of a daring modernist home that Gil and Hillary Briffa started building ten years previously in the Andalucian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-19 22:00:00" d="2020-05-19 23:00:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XX</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Natai is rushed to A&amp;E with a lacerated wrist after putting his hand through a glass pane. Pauline is struggling to breathe. And 17-year-old Fahad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-19 23:00:00" d="2020-05-20 00:05:00"><n u="999: On the Front Line">999: On the Front Line IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Paramedics treat a 60-year-old patient with severe chest pains, a suspected drunk driver who's crashed his car, and an elderly man who's collapsed at home. Ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 00:05:00" d="2020-05-20 01:05:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XI (5)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Richard Ayoade and Rob Beckett take on Jon Richardson and Claudia Winkleman. Adam Riches joins Susie Dent in Dictionary Corner. With Rachel Riley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 01:05:00" d="2020-05-20 02:05:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay visits Italian restaurant Anna Vincenzo's in Boca Raton, Florida, where owner CeCe has lost her way in the kitchen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 02:05:00" d="2020-05-20 03:10:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XX</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Natai is rushed to A&amp;E with a lacerated wrist after putting his hand through a glass pane. Pauline is struggling to breathe. And 17-year-old Fahad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 03:10:00" d="2020-05-20 04:15:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XI (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Richard Ayoade and Rob Beckett take on Jon Richardson and Claudia Winkleman. Adam Riches joins Susie Dent in Dictionary Corner. With Rachel Riley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 04:15:00" d="2020-05-20 07:15:00"><n>Food Unwrapped</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The team present favourite investigations. Kate reveals the secrets of saffron fraud. Glacé cherry production takes Matt's breath away, but</k>  </p>
</a>
