<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-04-09 04:34:49"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-16 09:55:00" d="2020-04-16 10:20:00"><n>Kirstie's Handmade Treasures</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Queen of crafts Kirstie Allsopp is up against an origami 'black belt' in the 'Something New from Something Old' competition at the Royal Wales Show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-16 10:20:00" d="2020-04-16 11:15:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2014 &amp; 2015</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Winter Sun
Ian and Christine want to buy a holiday home near Sarasota in Florida for up to ?250,000. Jonnie Irwin shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-16 11:15:00" d="2020-04-16 12:15:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2014 &amp; 2015</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Winter Sun
Jonnie Irwin shows Jacky and Peter Kennett how far their ?150,000 budget will stretch in the Tampa Bay area of Florida</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-16 12:15:00" d="2020-04-16 13:15:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien look for profit potential in some church organ pipes and old leather sports car seats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-16 13:15:00" d="2020-04-16 14:15:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>In this episode, Henry Cole calls in a safe-cracker to bring a safe back from the scrapheap, and a ship's wheel is left in splinters when Henry falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-16 14:15:00" d="2020-04-16 15:20:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY III</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Stephanie sets out to restore her chateau's original greenhouse. Lee and Belinda expand their outdoor venue. Jayne and Steve have their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-16 15:20:00" d="2020-04-16 15:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The competition kicks off at The Richard III in Middleham, where Ken and Sharon introduce the group to their racehorse Rosairlie. There's just one problem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-16 15:50:00" d="2020-04-16 16:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The second visit of the week is to the Court House Unique Boutique B&amp;B in Shelsley Walsh, Worcestershire, where Keith and Lisa hold court. Trouble brews</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-16 16:20:00" d="2020-04-16 16:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The third visit is to Castley Camp in Otley, Yorkshire, owned by single mum Jo and her son Louis. Ken and Sharon are horrified by stains on their bedding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-16 16:55:00" d="2020-04-16 17:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The last visit of the week is to the Lion &amp; Swan in Congleton, where owner Paul and manager Matt set out to win. But Lisa and Keith are shocked by their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-16 17:25:00" d="2020-04-16 17:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the final day of the competition and the B&amp;B owners meet for the last time to find out what they've been paid and to settle some scores</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-16 17:55:00" d="2020-04-16 18:55:00"><n>A New Life in the Sun</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Just hours after moving into their new Spanish home, a family battle to avoid eviction. In France, a couple look for clever ways to fund the construction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-16 18:55:00" d="2020-04-16 19:55:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S I (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Fiat Fiasco: Tim Shaw and Fuzz Townshend meet Jeremy, who lost his wife and was unable to work after a car accident. Can they give his Fiat Spider</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-16 19:55:00" d="2020-04-16 20:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY III</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Stephanie's renovations could take longer than anticipated. Lee starts constructing a solar panel system for an outdoor swimming pool. Jayne takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-16 20:55:00" d="2020-04-16 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Matt and Sophie White want to build a giant family house of fun with secret dens, a fireman's pole and a James Bond room. Kevin McCloud can't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-16 22:00:00" d="2020-04-16 23:00:00"><n u="Great Canal Journeys">Great Canal Journeys X</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Great Canal Journeys: Asian. 
. dyssey: National treasures and intrepid 'ancient mariners' Timothy West and Prunella Scales head for South</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-16 23:00:00" d="2020-04-17 00:05:00"><n>The World's Most Beautiful Railway</n><t>S</t><e>TF</e>    <k>Scotland's Scenic Railways
Through vast mountains and across open moorlands, a breathtaking look at Scotland's network - voted the world's most beautiful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-17 00:05:00" d="2020-04-17 01:05:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E IX (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Seventy-year-old part-time DJ Tony arrives at St George's hospital after a high-speed bicycle accident. He was training for a 100-mile charity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-17 01:05:00" d="2020-04-17 02:10:00"><n>Shocking Emergency Calls</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The horrific story of how a chimpanzee made a brutal attack that would change lives forever, plus a chilling call from an online predator. (Ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-17 02:10:00" d="2020-04-17 03:15:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown VII (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Sean Lock and Bill Bailey take on guest captain Joe Wilkinson and Isy Suttie. Joe Lycett is in Dictionary Corner with Susie Dent. Plus Rachel Riley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-17 03:15:00" d="2020-04-17 04:20:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E IX (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Seventy-year-old part-time DJ Tony arrives at St George's hospital after a high-speed bicycle accident. He was training for a 100-mile charity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-17 04:20:00" d="2020-04-17 07:20:00"><n>Food Unwrapped</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Favourite investigations. Matt Tebbutt visits China, the world's biggest oyster producer. Jimmy Doherty looks at dry gin. Kate Quilton asks if herbal</k>  </p>
</a>
