<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-05-27 04:35:46"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-03 09:55:00" d="2020-06-03 10:30:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped X (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>75% Jimmy meets a man whose taste buds are insured for ?1 million, in the inner sanctum of one of Britain's biggest tea producers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-03 10:30:00" d="2020-06-03 11:25:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Summer Sun
Good friends Mike Dawson and Louise Clark want a holiday apartment in the buzzing resort of Sitges, near Barcelona</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-03 11:25:00" d="2020-06-03 12:25:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (20)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Max restores a pair of iconic designer chairs, while Henry transforms a decrepit garden table into a colourful and valuable new one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-03 12:25:00" d="2020-06-03 13:25:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (8)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien turn an old, unloved filing cabinet into a valuable and desirable storage unit, and convert a Bakelite voltmeter into a retro Bluetooth speaker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-03 13:25:00" d="2020-06-03 14:25:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY IV</n><e>R</e>    <k>Ben and Billie get to work on their dilapidated boathouse, Amy and Marc get their barn and café ready for their first yoga class, and Wendy and Marcus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-03 14:25:00" d="2020-06-03 15:30:00"><n u="Building the Dream">Building the Dream VIII</n><e>R</e>    <k>In rural Suffolk, laid-back Steve and Susan's hit-and-hope construction of an oak-framed cottage urgently requires a pep talk from Charlie Luxton to bring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-03 15:30:00" d="2020-06-03 16:05:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>The competition begins at luxury weight-loss and detox retreat Slimmeria in East Sussex, owned by Galia and Michael. But what will their guests make of the 9pm curfew?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-03 16:05:00" d="2020-06-03 16:35:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Jan and William host at their five-star, gold rating establishment, 38 St Giles in Norwich, where guests have the ride of their lives on the race track</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-03 16:35:00" d="2020-06-03 17:05:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Fun-loving Ann and Bill host at their four-star B&amp;B in Bude, north Cornwall, with an indulgent Cornish cream tea, a local stick dance, a drink in their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-03 17:05:00" d="2020-06-03 17:35:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Diane and Max are the last to host at Ombersley Bed &amp; Breakfast in Worcestershire, where there's bickering over gluten-free bread and hand washing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-03 17:35:00" d="2020-06-03 18:05:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>It's the final day and the B&amp;B hosts meet to find out how much they've been paid and who has won the title of best value for money B&amp;B</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-03 18:05:00" d="2020-06-03 19:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It III</n><e>R</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien are in Essex, where Henry restores a car trailer and a 1970s racing bike, and Simon turns his attention to a vintage model aircraft. Ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-03 19:05:00" d="2020-06-03 19:55:00"><n>Countdown</n>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Adrian Chiles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-03 19:55:00" d="2020-06-03 20:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY III</n>    <k>Dick shares his recipe for enjoying the spoils of chateau life. Donna and Paul discover thousands of dead bees in a chimney. Adam's chateau-buying quest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-03 20:55:00" d="2020-06-03 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>R</e>    <k>Claire and Ian try to build a home big enough to include a disco on a small plot at the end of a London mews. But, as angry locals begin to object to their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-03 22:00:00" d="2020-06-03 23:00:00"><n u="Kirstie and Phil's Love It or List It">Kirstie and Phil's Love It or List It V</n><t>S</t>    <k>Kirstie and Phil's Love It. 
. r List It: In North Tyneside, Mark and Suze's emotional ties to their Victorian townhouse have left them in limbo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-03 23:00:00" d="2020-06-04 00:05:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XIII (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>This episode explores the changing nature of relationships between parents and children. Judith, who's 79, has been in a traffic accident, and Mohammad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-04 00:05:00" d="2020-06-04 01:05:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (19)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>A CT scan reveals some unexpected news for lorry driver Neil, who's fallen off a ramp. Ben's dislocated his shoulder in a cycling accident</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-04 01:05:00" d="2020-06-04 01:55:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>R</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Adrian Chiles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-04 01:55:00" d="2020-06-04 02:55:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>R</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay revisits two restaurants - Giuseppi's and Sante La Brea - to find out whether his advice has been put to good use. Plus: an update on Finn McCool's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-04 02:55:00" d="2020-06-04 03:55:00"><n u="It Was Alright in the...">It Was Alright in the... II (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>It Was Alright in the 1960s
Matt Lucas narrates this look back at the wild TV of the 1960s, with extraordinary clips and contributions from Joan Bakewell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-04 03:55:00" d="2020-06-04 06:55:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XIII (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>This episode explores the changing nature of relationships between parents and children. Judith, who's 79, has been in a traffic accident, and Mohammad</k>  </p>
</a>
