<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2019-08-13 02:20:22"><p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 09:55:00" d="2019-08-18 11:00:00"><n>George Clarke's Amazing Spaces</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>George meets a couple in Worcestershire who have just ?50k to build a home using four old portable cabins. And he meets Lauren who's turning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 11:00:00" d="2019-08-18 12:00:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp helps Andy and Jenny find their first home near Warrington, while Phil Spencer helps businesswoman Margot find a forever home in seaside town of Crosby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 12:00:00" d="2019-08-18 13:05:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In the Peak District, Kirstie Allsopp helps single mum Anne and her son Vinnie to find their new home, while Phil Spencer searches for a dream home for Andrea and James</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 13:05:00" d="2019-08-18 13:35:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The first visit is to Newton House in Knaresborough, North Yorkshire, run by organic foodies Denise Carter and Jackie Fennell, who feel confident their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 13:35:00" d="2019-08-18 14:10:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The second visit is to The Highlands Pub in Blackpool, where Mike Hayes and Neal Widdowson are all about value for money. But some North/South snobbery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 14:10:00" d="2019-08-18 14:40:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Tensions are simmering as the guests head to The White House in Brighton, run by Sean Edlin and Kathryn Turnbull, and the group have to decide whether</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 14:40:00" d="2019-08-18 15:10:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The group head to Colchester and Wakes Hall Lodges, where Marianne and Deina hope their brand of luxe will win the day, but some guests think the 'luxury'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 15:10:00" d="2019-08-18 15:40:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's payment day, and grievances are aired before the winner is revealed. Denise and Jackie from Newton House wait to see if high marks can translate into high payments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 15:40:00" d="2019-08-18 16:15:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Colchester. The first host, Richard Massey, is banking on his signature dish 'Drunken Duck' and his cheeky chappy humour. (Ep1/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 16:15:00" d="2019-08-18 16:50:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Colchester. Smooth-talking PR man Darius hosts. He rustles up a menu full of local produce, including his very own blackberry wine. Will his 'Roman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 16:50:00" d="2019-08-18 17:20:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Colchester. The host is American army wife Adrena. She's offering an Armenian menu to reflect her heritage, and plans an Armenian egg fight for her guests' entertainment. (Ep3/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 17:20:00" d="2019-08-18 17:50:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Colchester. It's the turn of money-mad James Coe, whose food is a hit, but what about his hot tub, and one of his guests' pink pants? (Ep4/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 17:50:00" d="2019-08-18 18:20:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Colchester. It's the final day of the competition and vegetarian Jodie Edzekiel is out to wow her guests by giving them what they want: meat! (Ep5/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 18:20:00" d="2019-08-18 18:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The competition starts at No.33 Hunstanton, where Janie Thompson and Gemma Layfield hope their touch of luxury will help win the day. But some unexpected</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 18:55:00" d="2019-08-18 19:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The second visit is to La Tavola Calda in Nuneaton where father-and-son team Mick and Chris Emanuele run their budget B&amp;B, and their George Michael tribute</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 19:25:00" d="2019-08-18 19:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>At The Lansdowne in the Cotswolds, hosts Cheryle and Anthony Katz hope their hospitality expertise will charm their way to the top, but a personal attack leaves them fuming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 19:55:00" d="2019-08-18 20:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Tensions run high in the group as Mark and Jan Rummery welcome their guests to The Ivybridge in Goodwick, Wales, where relationships disintegrate at dinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 20:25:00" d="2019-08-18 21:00:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's payment day, and the group is close to breaking point as they battle through their issues, with dramatic consequences and an admission of game-playing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 21:00:00" d="2019-08-18 22:00:00"><n u="Savage Kingdom">Savage Kingdom I</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Savage Kingdom
Brand new series - The Pale Pack: In Botswana, a family of wild dogs desperately seeks a safe place to raise six puppies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 22:00:00" d="2019-08-18 23:00:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>This episode explores the ways grown men deal with pain and injury, from a cyst on the knee to a dislocated shoulder that takes a five-strong team to pull back into place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 23:00:00" d="2019-08-19 00:05:00"><n>Shocking Emergency Calls</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Shocking Emergency Calls
Brand new series: In California, a woman who's just given birth is threatened by wildfire. And in Georgia, a mother calls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-19 00:05:00" d="2019-08-19 01:10:00"><n u="999: What's Your Emergency?">999: What's Your Emergency? III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>This episode explores the challenges the emergency services face with teenagers, from online bullying and children attacking parents, to teenagers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-19 01:10:00" d="2019-08-19 02:15:00"><n>Egypt's Great Pyramid: The New Evidence</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Egypt's Great Pyramid: The New. 
. vidence: Mystery has long surrounded the construction of Egypt's Great Pyramid, but now new discoveries are revealing its secrets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-19 02:15:00" d="2019-08-19 03:15:00"><n u="Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA">Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA VI (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon visits Greek restaurant Yanni's in Seattle, where he clashes with defiant owner Peter, a chef who hasn't allowed changes to his menu since</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-19 03:15:00" d="2019-08-19 04:15:00"><n u="Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA">Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA VI (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Gordon visits Chappy's Cajun restaurant in Nashville, Tennessee, where the chef/owner's careless methods and less-than-appetising</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-19 04:15:00" d="2019-08-19 09:55:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped VIII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>76% What exactly is processed meat, and is a fresh British banger healthier than a frankfurter? Jimmy investigates dates. And Matt meets a man who grows</k>  </p>
</a>
