<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-05-13 04:35:56"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 09:55:00" d="2020-05-20 10:20:00"><n>Kirstie's Vintage Gems</n><e>RF</e>    <k>In this bite-size episode, crafting champion Kirstie Allsopp enlists the help of super-seamstress Lisa Comfort to help Amber and Colin create a memory quilt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 10:20:00" d="2020-05-20 11:15:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2014 &amp; 2015</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Summer Sun
Deborah Sims, who has long dreamt of relocating permanently to southern Spain, has a budget of ?90,000 and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 11:15:00" d="2020-05-20 12:15:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It I (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien turn unwanted items into hard cash. In Yorkshire, they scour Wensleydale for profitable finds and also celebrate Henry's birthday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 12:15:00" d="2020-05-20 13:15:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It I (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien turn unwanted items into hard cash. This time they're in stitches over some serious sewing machines in Kent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 13:15:00" d="2020-05-20 14:15:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Debbie and Nigel start landscaping their five-acre grounds, Sarah and George run into trouble as they host their first-ever wedding and Stephanie suffers scheduling woes. Ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 14:15:00" d="2020-05-20 15:20:00"><n u="Building the Dream">Building the Dream VII (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Charlie Luxton's in Cambridgeshire, where Darren and Luisa are on a voyage of discovery, building a picture-perfect waterfront home - a project with lots of issues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 15:20:00" d="2020-05-20 15:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The competition kicks off at Ian and Cathy's 'no frills' 13th-century The Swan Inn, located in the picturesque Ceiriog Valley in Wales, where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 15:50:00" d="2020-05-20 16:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>John and Chris welcome their guests to the Bed &amp; Breakfast by the Beach in Bournemouth. But Ian admits he can't stand being near fellow guest Jill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 16:20:00" d="2020-05-20 16:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The competition moves to The Lansbury on the North Yorkshire coast, where Jill's stab at playing tour guide backfires, and the reaction to her breakfast leads to tears</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 16:50:00" d="2020-05-20 17:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the turn of Charlie and Angie to host at Castle House B&amp;B in Denbigh, north Wales, which turns out to be a lot more swish and luxurious than their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 17:25:00" d="2020-05-20 17:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the final day of the competition and the B&amp;B owners meet for the last time to find out what they've been paid and to settle some scores</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 17:55:00" d="2020-05-20 18:55:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>In this episode, Henry Cole calls in a safe-cracker to bring a safe back from the scrapheap, and a ship's wheel is left in splinters when Henry falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 18:55:00" d="2020-05-20 19:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The third visit is to Vicky's aptly named terrace house, The Terrace, in Oxford. Two pairs of guests make some grim discoveries, including hairs and a pre-sucked sweet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 19:25:00" d="2020-05-20 19:55:00"><n>Jamie: Keep Cooking and Carry On</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Jamie Oliver shows us some recipes, tips and hacks tailored for the unique times we're living in, including cheese-topped burgers, super-spinach pancakes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 19:55:00" d="2020-05-20 20:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY IV</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Mariam and Johnno create a French parterre garden, Phillip and his wife Janet move into Chateau de la Fare, and Emma and Paul renovate a Charles Rennie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 20:55:00" d="2020-05-20 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>This episode follows actor Sean Simons' epic bid to turn a castle ruins in Ireland into a spectacular fantasy home the hard way: without an architect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 22:00:00" d="2020-05-20 23:00:00"><n u="Building the Dream">Building the Dream IX</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Building the Dream
Brand new series: Charlie's in Hampshire with Nikki and Darren, who've struck gold with their stunning seaside plot but don't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-20 23:00:00" d="2020-05-21 00:05:00"><n u="Grand Designs Australia">Grand Designs Australia VIII</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Grand Designs Australia
Brand new series: Barbara and Craig embark on their dream home in Dee Why in NSW. They threw out the rule book and decided</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 00:05:00" d="2020-05-21 01:15:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Reggie, who's seven, has broken his arm while doing a cartwheel to celebrate England beating Wales at Euro 2016. John, who's 84, has crashed his car into a road sign</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 01:15:00" d="2020-05-21 02:15:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XI (6)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Sean Lock and Danny Dyer take on Joe Wilkinson and Gabby Logan. David O'Doherty joins Susie Dent in Dictionary Corner. Plus Rachel Riley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 02:15:00" d="2020-05-21 03:20:00"><n u="Building the Dream">Building the Dream IX</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series: Charlie's in Hampshire with Nikki and Darren, who've struck gold with their stunning seaside plot but don't have the budget to match</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 03:20:00" d="2020-05-21 04:25:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Reggie, who's seven, has broken his arm while doing a cartwheel to celebrate England beating Wales at Euro 2016. John, who's 84, has crashed his car into a road sign</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-21 04:25:00" d="2020-05-21 07:25:00"><n>Food Unwrapped</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The team present some favourite investigations. Kate finds out how cheap red wine is made, Jimmy investigates gluten, and Matt wonders which</k>  </p>
</a>
