<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2019-08-15 22:47:01"><p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-22 09:55:00" d="2019-08-22 10:20:00"><n>Kirstie's Fill Your House for Free</n><e>R</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp goes to Staffordshire to help single mum Helen turn her bedroom into a place where she can run her business</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-22 10:20:00" d="2019-08-22 10:50:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped VI (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>76% Jimmy investigates whether it's worth splashing out on expensive vodka, Kate finds out how coffee beans are turned into instant granules, and Matt checks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-22 10:50:00" d="2019-08-22 11:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY I</n><e>R</e>    <k>Dick and Donna's search for the armour in the lake continues. Tim and Krys struggle to convert the attic in time. And Dick and his mother-in-law Jenny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-22 11:55:00" d="2019-08-22 13:00:00"><n u="Bake Off: The Professionals">Bake Off: The Professionals I (9)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>It's the semi-final as the last four teams compete to create an impressive three-tiered cake, while also performing a spectacular piece of gourmet theatre</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-22 13:00:00" d="2019-08-22 14:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien are in Northamptonshire and Coventry, where Henry discovers a very rare limited edition Goldwing motorbike with only 65 miles on the clock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-22 14:05:00" d="2019-08-22 14:35:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Mark and Kathy start the competition at their grandiose Godshill Park Farmhouse on the Isle of Wight. Will the clay pigeon shooting and their award-winning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-22 14:35:00" d="2019-08-22 15:10:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>B&amp;B beginners Teresa and Clive host at the Butterfly Guest House in Porthcawl, south Wales, taking their guests cosmic bowling and throwing a surprise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-22 15:10:00" d="2019-08-22 15:40:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>The competition moves north to Blackpool to Kalpana and Joseph's The Address. Kalpana dresses the ladies in saris, but some of the guests are upset about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-22 15:40:00" d="2019-08-22 16:15:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>The group head to the Cumbrian hillsides to stay at Ruth and Mike's Crake Trees Manor, where the group activity is helping the hosts to repair a drystone wall</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-22 16:15:00" d="2019-08-22 16:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>It's the final day of the competition and all the B&amp;B hosts gather one last time to find out how much they've been paid and who will be named best-value B&amp;B of the week</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-22 16:50:00" d="2019-08-22 17:50:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>R</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer are in the Midlands, helping Hannah and John in Shrewsbury, and assisting Me'sha and Darren to relocate from London to Wolverhampton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-22 17:50:00" d="2019-08-22 18:55:00"><n u="Love It or List It Australia">Love It or List It Australia II</n><e>R</e>    <k>Tracey and Antony have lived in their four-bedroom, single-level home in Tea Tree Gully, Adelaide, for 10 years. She loves its garden, but he wants a new start. Ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-22 18:55:00" d="2019-08-22 19:55:00"><n u="The Secret Life of the Zoo">The Secret Life of the Zoo II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Oana the anoa and capybara Lochley give birth. Tiger mum Kirana's sons are moved to other zoos to start their own families. Young monkey Rocky won't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-22 19:55:00" d="2019-08-22 20:55:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick XII</n><t>S</t>    <k>85% The Supervet
A puppy called Albie has a broken back from being knocked over by a car and needs a complex operation. And a Scottish terrier</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-22 20:55:00" d="2019-08-22 22:00:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau">Escape to the Chateau V (6)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>It's harvest time at the chateau. But also time for family wheelbarrow races, to give the basement a swish makeover, and to convert the old piggery into a chicken coop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-22 22:00:00" d="2019-08-22 23:00:00"><n u="24 Hour Baby Hospital">24 Hour Baby Hospital I</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: 24 Hour Baby Hospital
Brand new series: Dublin mother-of-two Olivia attempts to go through childbirth drug-free. Doctors in Neonatal Intensive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-22 23:00:00" d="2019-08-23 00:05:00"><n u="999: What's Your Emergency?">999: What's Your Emergency? III</n><e>R</e>    <k>This episode explores the challenges and dangers our emergency services face on our roads, from drivers under the influence of drink, drugs and sometimes old age. Ep11)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-23 00:05:00" d="2019-08-23 00:35:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>85% Entertaining Father Stone: For six years, Father Stone has been coming to Craggy Island and for Father Ted, Father Dougal and Father Jack, that's seven years too many</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-23 00:35:00" d="2019-08-23 01:10:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>85% The Passion of St Tibulus: A film that has been denounced by the Pope is due to be shown on Craggy Island, causing conflict between Bishop Brennan and Father Ted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-23 01:10:00" d="2019-08-23 02:15:00"><n>8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown</n><e>R</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts the panel/quiz show mash-up. Jon Richardson and Chris Addison go up against Joe Wilkinson and Katherine Ryan, with David O'Doherty in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-23 02:15:00" d="2019-08-23 03:15:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick XII</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>85% The Supervet
A puppy called Albie has a broken back from being knocked over by a car and needs a complex operation. And a Scottish terrier</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-23 03:15:00" d="2019-08-23 04:20:00"><n u="The Secret Life of the Zoo">The Secret Life of the Zoo II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Oana the anoa and capybara Lochley give birth. Tiger mum Kirana's sons are moved to other zoos to start their own families. Young monkey Rocky won't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-23 04:20:00" d="2019-08-23 07:20:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped VI (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>76% Jimmy investigates whether it's worth splashing out on expensive vodka, Kate finds out how coffee beans are turned into instant granules, and Matt checks</k>  </p>
</a>
