<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2021-07-13 05:02:33"><p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-20 09:55:00" d="2021-07-20 10:15:00"><n>Kirstie's Vintage Gems</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and expert jewellery maker Rachel Jeffrey help a couple to create their own rings for their wedding day. Kirstie also learns new uses for real gold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-20 10:15:00" d="2021-07-20 11:05:00"><n u="Heir Hunters">Heir Hunters VIII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The race is on to find heirs to the ?100,000 estate of a Newcastle man, and the search on another estate opens the fascinating story of chimney sweeps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-20 11:05:00" d="2021-07-20 12:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It III</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien head to Lowestoft, where Henry picks a valuable Lyons Tea enamel sign, while Simon converts a station trolley into a garden sofa. Ep12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-20 12:05:00" d="2021-07-20 13:10:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It III</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The boys rummage through the hangar of a Vulcan bomber. Henry Cole restores a cockpit seat and Simon O'Brien attempts to turn part of a jet engine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-20 13:10:00" d="2021-07-20 14:10:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S VI (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Karmann Ghia: Tim Shaw and Fuzz Townshend restore a 1965 VW Karmann Ghia, a once-stylish German motor that now has accident-damaged body work and a leaking engine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-20 14:10:00" d="2021-07-20 15:15:00"><n u="Emergency Helicopter Medics">Emergency Helicopter Medics II</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Air ambulance teams race to help mountain biker Rob in the Cumbrian mountains. Off-road motorbiker Dean has taken a nasty tumble. Robbie, who's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-20 15:15:00" d="2021-07-20 15:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Rich and Matt host at the Cliff House Hotel in Southbourne, where some guests are blown away by their bathroom but others feel exposed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-20 15:50:00" d="2021-07-20 16:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Stuart and Fiona host at the Hotel Barge Waternimf in Ely, Cambridgeshire. Guest Dave falls hook, line and sinker in love, but some of the feedback gives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-20 16:20:00" d="2021-07-20 16:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Hannah and Ibrahim welcome their rivals to Montpellier Hotel in Llandrindod Wells, Powys, where there's a bothersome bathroom and some guests struggle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-20 16:50:00" d="2021-07-20 17:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Paul and Dave hope to impress their guests with some country class at the Coach and Horses in Compton, West Sussex. But there are decor disagreements</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-20 17:20:00" d="2021-07-20 17:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>TF</e>    <k>It's the final day of the competition. After dramatic discoveries and score-settling on everything from missing bulbs to TV troubles, the payments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-20 17:55:00" d="2021-07-20 18:55:00"><n u="Grand Designs New Zealand">Grand Designs New Zealand III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Sky Mason is building a remote home on Slipper Island, off the Coromandel Peninsula, but all the materials must travel by barge from the mainland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-20 18:55:00" d="2021-07-20 19:55:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick V (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>86% The Supervet
A Great Dane is rushed to the clinic after losing the use of her back legs. A spaniel needs help after being hit by a car. And an owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-20 19:55:00" d="2021-07-20 20:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau">Escape to the Chateau VI (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's winter at the chateau. Dick and Angel build an events kitchen with a half-tonne oven to cater for their busiest year yet. And there's a magical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-20 20:55:00" d="2021-07-20 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Brixton, design-mad couple Mary and Carl want to build a home that resembles a giant stack of glass cubes and offers a Zen retreat from the noise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-20 22:00:00" d="2021-07-20 23:00:00"><n u="My Floating Home">My Floating Home III</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: My Floating Home
Brand new series: Colin, who's 55, is embarking on a bold life adventure. He plans to spend half the year cruising</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-20 23:00:00" d="2021-07-21 00:05:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XXI</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts with Rachel Riley and Susie Dent. Sean Lock and Paul Foot take on Jon Richardson and Angela Barnes. John Cooper Clarke is in Dictionary Corner. Ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-21 00:05:00" d="2021-07-21 01:05:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>King's College Hospital in London has one of Britain's busiest A&amp;E departments. In this episode, two cyclists arrive in A&amp;E, and a retired docker takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-21 01:05:00" d="2021-07-21 02:10:00"><n u="My Floating Home">My Floating Home III</n><t>S</t>    <k>Brand new series: Colin, who's 55, is embarking on a bold life adventure. He plans to spend half the year cruising the UK's waterways on a high-spec</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-21 02:10:00" d="2021-07-21 03:15:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XXI</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts with Rachel Riley and Susie Dent. Sean Lock and Paul Foot take on Jon Richardson and Angela Barnes. John Cooper Clarke is in Dictionary Corner. Ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-21 03:15:00" d="2021-07-21 04:20:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>King's College Hospital in London has one of Britain's busiest A&amp;E departments. In this episode, two cyclists arrive in A&amp;E, and a retired docker takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-21 04:20:00" d="2021-07-21 07:20:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped XV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>What gives fizzy sweets their fizz, and can you harness their explosive power in a rocket? One in five of us lack vitamin D: can mushrooms help? And are breakfast smoothies safe? Ep8)</k>  </p>
</a>
