<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2019-07-11 00:18:50"><p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-16 09:55:00" d="2019-07-16 10:45:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2015 &amp; 2016</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Summer Sun
Neil and Affy are looking for a holiday home on Ibiza where they can escape from their busy lives in Brighton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-16 10:45:00" d="2019-07-16 11:45:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau">Escape to the Chateau I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>An extended four-part version of series one. Dick, Angel and the family move into their crumbling chateau, which they find home to bats, birds and thousands of flies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-16 11:45:00" d="2019-07-16 13:00:00"><n u="The Great British Bake Off">The Great British Bake Off I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's biscuit week. Paul and Prue set the remaining 11 bakers three new challenges, including a tricky filling and a final showstopper that is literally game-changing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-16 13:00:00" d="2019-07-16 14:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It I (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>In this episode, Henry Cole monkeys around with a monkey bike, while Simon O'Brien uses all his skills to restore an old racing bike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-16 14:05:00" d="2019-07-16 14:35:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The competition kicks off at Dunsandles Guest House in New Brighton, Merseyside, where owner Alan Johnson and sidekick Dave Owen hope to be crowned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-16 14:35:00" d="2019-07-16 15:10:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The second visit is to the Lady Teal Hotel Boat on the waterways near Burnley, owned by Nick and Gina Mead, where the afternoon entertainment is a freezing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-16 15:10:00" d="2019-07-16 15:40:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The third visit is to York House in Tetbury, Gloucestershire, where Brock Bergius hopes his cheeky sense of humour and perfectionist nature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-16 15:40:00" d="2019-07-16 16:15:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The final day of the competition is at Heyford House in Lower Heyford, Oxfordshire, owned by veterans of the hospitality trade, Leo and Sonya Brooke-Little</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-16 16:15:00" d="2019-07-16 16:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The B&amp;Bers meet for the last time to thrash out their differences and find out who's the winner. Feedback includes criticism of a badly positioned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-16 16:50:00" d="2019-07-16 17:50:00"><n u="Kirstie and Phil's Love It or List It">Kirstie and Phil's Love It or List It III (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie and Phil's Love It or. 
. ist It: Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer help the Tuck family in Long Eaton, Derbyshire, who can't decide if their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-16 17:50:00" d="2019-07-16 18:55:00"><n u="Love It or List It Australia">Love It or List It Australia II</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Love It or List It Australia
Brand new series: Belinda and Cameron's home in the desirable Melbourne bayside suburb of Brighton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-16 18:55:00" d="2019-07-16 19:55:00"><n u="The Secret Life of the Zoo">The Secret Life of the Zoo III (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>An elephant calf is born at Chester Zoo. Bush dog Franco has got his sister-in-law pregnant. And rhino beetle Sheldon has a damaged wing case;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-16 19:55:00" d="2019-07-16 20:55:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick IX (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Supervet
Professor Noel Fitzpatrick returns, providing cutting-edge care for pets, including complex spinal surgery for a German pointer and cancer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-16 20:55:00" d="2019-07-16 22:00:00"><n u="Great Canal Journeys">Great Canal Journeys VII (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Great Canal Journeys: India
Timothy West and Pru Scales strike out onto the rarely navigated Brahmaputra river in the far north of India where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-16 22:00:00" d="2019-07-16 23:00:00"><n u="Building the Dream">Building the Dream VIII</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Building the Dream
Charlie Luxton is with a Cambridgeshire couple determined to build a huge barn-style home. Problem is, they don't appreciate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-16 23:00:00" d="2019-07-17 00:05:00"><n u="Grand Designs New Zealand">Grand Designs New Zealand III (8)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>A musician and his partner tackle a complex build - a recording studio and performance space that's also a soundproof designer home for their family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-17 00:05:00" d="2019-07-17 01:05:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XIV (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>This shocking episode follows three women who are stabbed in broad daylight in a random attack at a supermarket car park in Surrey and rushed to St George's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-17 01:05:00" d="2019-07-17 02:10:00"><n u="999: What's Your Emergency?">999: What's Your Emergency? VII</n><e>RF</e>    <k>This episode focuses on the people who answer our cries for help, as well as the people who make these calls, and vastly differing interpretations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-17 02:10:00" d="2019-07-17 03:15:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick IX (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Supervet
Professor Noel Fitzpatrick returns, providing cutting-edge care for pets, including complex spinal surgery for a German pointer and cancer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-17 03:15:00" d="2019-07-17 04:20:00"><n u="The Secret Life of the Zoo">The Secret Life of the Zoo III (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>An elephant calf is born at Chester Zoo. Bush dog Franco has got his sister-in-law pregnant. And rhino beetle Sheldon has a damaged wing case;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-17 04:20:00" d="2019-07-17 09:55:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats">8 Out of 10 Cats XVII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts, with team captains Jon Richardson and Sean Lock being joined by guests Jack Dee, Rob Beckett, Radio 1 DJ Gemma Cairney and Jamie Laing. Ep1)</k>  </p>
</a>
