<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2019-08-11 01:29:08"><p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-17 09:55:00" d="2019-08-17 10:20:00"><n>Food Unwrapped</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Jimmy Doherty investigates a potentially devastating by-product of Greek yoghurt production</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-17 10:20:00" d="2019-08-17 11:20:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2016 &amp; 2017</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Winter Sun
Ex-RAF officers Simon and Amanda have been visiting the gorgeous Caribbean island of Antigua for years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-17 11:20:00" d="2019-08-17 12:25:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2016 &amp; 2017</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Summer Sun
Retired couple Denise and Roger have fallen in love with the Breton culture and lifestyle. Laura Hamilton shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-17 12:25:00" d="2019-08-17 13:30:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2016 &amp; 2017</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Summer Sun
Jasmine Harman shows music therapist Sarah Hadley and her best friend Sue five incredible properties for a budget of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-17 13:30:00" d="2019-08-17 14:35:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp helps Stuart and Lara find a property near Amersham in Buckinghamshire. And Phil Spencer helps with Randhir and Sheetal's urgent home search in Berkshire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-17 14:35:00" d="2019-08-17 15:40:00"><n u="Building the Dream">Building the Dream VIII</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>New: In rural Suffolk, laid-back Steve and Susan's hit-and-hope construction of an oak-framed cottage urgently needs a pep talk from Charlie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-17 15:40:00" d="2019-08-17 16:10:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The first visit is to Alston House in Cumbria, where Michael and Carole Allchorne are brimming with confidence. But things get hairy for one guest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-17 16:10:00" d="2019-08-17 16:40:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The second visit is to Scotia House in Harrogate, where host Marie suspects some of her guests are seeking revenge. Can she impress with deluxe teddy bears</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-17 16:40:00" d="2019-08-17 17:15:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Relationships are strained and cracks start to show on the third visit, to The Canberra Guest House in Blackpool. And one of the guests ruffles more than just feathers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-17 17:15:00" d="2019-08-17 17:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The last visit is to The Crown &amp; Kitchen in East Linton in Scotland, where tensions are close to breaking point. Yvonne and Gail leave no mattress unturned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-17 17:50:00" d="2019-08-17 18:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the final day in the competition and tensions run high with allegations of tit-for-tat scoring and a barrage of criticism. The payments are revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-17 18:20:00" d="2019-08-17 18:50:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Shropshire. Zumba instructor Zoe Bailey is first to host. Zoe's soufflé starter impresses, and so does her gargling game for entertainment. (Ep1/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-17 18:50:00" d="2019-08-17 19:25:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Shropshire. Eccentric artist and dairy farmer Penny Timmis is second to host and has roped in a dentist posing as a magician for entertainment. (Ep2/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-17 19:25:00" d="2019-08-17 19:55:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Shropshire. Lighting salesman Richard Mercer hosts. The self-confessed gadget geek cooks paella for dinner, and for entertainment suggests a game of 'Guess the Gadget'. (Ep3/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-17 19:55:00" d="2019-08-17 20:25:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Shropshire. Lad-about-town Josh Sedgley, the youngest of the group, takes to the kitchen. Unfortunately Josh's meringues look a bit suspect. (Ep4/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-17 20:25:00" d="2019-08-17 21:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Shropshire. The final dinner party is hosted by traffic reporter and radio DJ Paul Shuttleworth, who plans to mix wacky outfits, bouncy castles and fun food. (Ep5/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-17 21:00:00" d="2019-08-17 22:00:00"><n>David Jason's Secret Service</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Sir David Jason reveals the incredible true story of Britain's spy history. This episode covers the assassins, saboteurs, playboys, villains and femmes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-17 22:00:00" d="2019-08-17 23:00:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E II</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>King's College Hospital in south London, is one of Britain's busiest A&amp;E departments. In this edition, two cyclists arrive in A&amp;E and a retired docker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-17 23:00:00" d="2019-08-18 00:05:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E II (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The episode focuses on some of the youngest patients treated by King's College Hospital A&amp;E. The programme also meets 27-year-old emergency medicine trainee Matt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 00:05:00" d="2019-08-18 01:10:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XII (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts the words-and-numbers quiz with Jon Richardson and David Mitchell who take on guest captain Joe Wilkinson and Roisin Conaty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 01:10:00" d="2019-08-18 01:45:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted III (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>86% Going to America: Ted accepts a job in the US, with his very own parish in Beverly Hills. But with his ambition about to be realised, Ted's problem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 01:45:00" d="2019-08-18 02:15:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted I (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>86% Good Luck, Father Ted: Ted is asked to appear on prestigious TV show Faith of Our Fathers. Could this be the opportunity for him to find stardom and escape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 02:15:00" d="2019-08-18 03:10:00"><n u="Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA">Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA VI (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon is in Norwalk, Ohio, for the conclusion to the Mill Street Bistro saga as his disagreement with the proprietor erupts into one of his most intense confrontations yet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 03:10:00" d="2019-08-18 04:15:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E II</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>King's College Hospital in south London, is one of Britain's busiest A&amp;E departments. In this edition, two cyclists arrive in A&amp;E and a retired docker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-08-18 04:15:00" d="2019-08-18 09:55:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped VII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>76% Matt Tebbutt makes a surprising discovery about haggis. Can you put dishwasher salt on your chips? And why do chicks have their beaks trimmed?</k>  </p>
</a>
