<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-05-25 04:52:13"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-01 09:55:00" d="2020-06-01 10:30:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped IX (7)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>75% In Italy, Jimmy investigates why Parmesan costs so much. Kate visits Hungary and Spain to find out where paprika comes from. And Matt looks at mass-produced boiled eggs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-01 10:30:00" d="2020-06-01 11:25:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Summer Sun
Rodney and Lynda Palliser from Hertfordshire are looking for an apartment on Mallorca, close to Palma. Can Laura Hamilton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-01 11:25:00" d="2020-06-01 12:25:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (16)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Max McMurdo and Henry Cole visit a motorbike fan. Henry makes table lamps from motorbike engines, while Max turns a pallet and iron wheels into a stylish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-01 12:25:00" d="2020-06-01 13:25:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (17)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>In Newark, Simon O'Brien finds an antique European threshing board, which he turns into a coffee table, and Henry Cole's all at sea with a ship's porthole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-01 13:25:00" d="2020-06-01 14:25:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY IV</n><e>R</e>    <k>Wendy and Marcus prepare for a VIP visit from the local mayor. Amy and Marc have big plans for their restorative retreat centre. And Belinda</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-01 14:25:00" d="2020-06-01 15:30:00"><n u="Building the Dream">Building the Dream VIII</n><e>R</e>    <k>Charlie catches up with Liz and Craig in Leicestershire. After much pain and hassle, the couple have finally finished the home in their garden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-01 15:30:00" d="2020-06-01 16:05:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>First hosts Paul and Flora aim to impress their guests at Silverwood Lodge in Cambridgeshire by taking them punting. But the couple get a grilling about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-01 16:05:00" d="2020-06-01 16:35:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>At Sue's canine-friendly Seashells Guesthouse in Great Yarmouth, the controversial issues of allowing dogs to sleep in the beds and guests to smoke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-01 16:35:00" d="2020-06-01 17:05:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>The converted prison cell rooms at The Old Court Guesthouse in Bath leave one claustrophobic guest feeling caged, so host Nancy organises a historical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-01 17:05:00" d="2020-06-01 17:35:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>At The Dean B&amp;B in Scotland, Caroline's two acres of gardens and breathtaking views across the Firth of Forth win over the guests. But a fine dining</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-01 17:35:00" d="2020-06-01 18:05:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>The hosts reconvene for one last time to thrash out the feedback, reveal the payments and find out which establishment has been crowned the best value B&amp;B of the week</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-01 18:05:00" d="2020-06-01 19:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It III</n><e>R</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien seek out items to repair and sell. In this episode, they visit a Norman castle, restore a Fiat 500 and build a table</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-01 19:05:00" d="2020-06-01 19:55:00"><n>Countdown</n>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Adrian Chiles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-01 19:55:00" d="2020-06-01 20:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY IV</n>    <k>Wendy and Marcus prepare to host their first official booking. Amy and Marc turn their grounds into an escapist retreat. Ben and Billie start building</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-01 20:55:00" d="2020-06-01 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>R</e>    <k>Ed and Rowena Waghorn are building an organic, timber-framed, curvy house on their smallholding in Herefordshire using recycled materials. But the budget</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-01 22:00:00" d="2020-06-01 23:00:00"><n>The Dambusters' Great Escape: Secret History</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Dambusters' Great Escape:. 
. ecret History: The extraordinary story of how two RAF squadrons finally sank Tirpitz, Germany's most powerful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-01 23:00:00" d="2020-06-02 00:00:00"><n u="Nazi Megastructures">Nazi Megastructures V</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Nazi Megastructures
Brand new series - D-Day: In 1944, Hitler prepared for invasion with an arms race of invention and innovation that culminated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 00:00:00" d="2020-06-02 01:05:00"><n>8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown</n><e>R</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Jon Richardson and James Acaster take on Lee Mack and Sarah Millican, with John Cooper Clarke in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 01:05:00" d="2020-06-02 01:55:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>R</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Adrian Chiles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 01:55:00" d="2020-06-02 02:25:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted III (5)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>85% Escape from Victory: At the annual All-Priests Over 75s Five-a-Side Football Challenge Match against Rugged Island, Ted realises Father Dick Byrne</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 02:25:00" d="2020-06-02 02:55:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted III (6)</n><e>: AlostbemanhTdkicBp</e>    <k>Kicking Bishop Brennan Up the Ar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 02:55:00" d="2020-06-02 04:00:00"><n u="It Was Alright in the...">It Was Alright in the... II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>It Was Alright in the 1970s
Series featuring TV of the past, narrated by Matt Lucas. This episode offers a 70s-style education and reveals the toe-curling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-02 04:00:00" d="2020-06-02 07:00:00"><n>8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown</n><e>R</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Jon Richardson and James Acaster take on Lee Mack and Sarah Millican, with John Cooper Clarke in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
</a>
