<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2021-07-09 07:08:09"><p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-14 09:55:00" d="2021-07-14 10:15:00"><n>Kirstie's Handmade Treasures</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp's in sweet tooth heaven as she learns how to make candy in Manhattan and, back in the UK, creates perfect passion fruit marshmallows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-14 10:15:00" d="2021-07-14 11:05:00"><n u="Heir Hunters">Heir Hunters VII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>When a much-loved lady dies without leaving a will, the heir hunters begin the search for her relative, and soon discover that her husband was a World</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-14 11:05:00" d="2021-07-14 12:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It III</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien head to Middlesex and Surrey, where Simon repurposes a 1950s hairdryer and an old school desk, and Henry restores a child's motorbike. Ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-14 12:05:00" d="2021-07-14 13:10:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It III</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien are on the south coast, where Henry gets to work on an aircraft fuel tank, and Simon's obsessed with an iconic 1960s speedboat. Ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-14 13:10:00" d="2021-07-14 14:10:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S IV (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Vauxhall Astra GTE: Tim Shaw and Fuzz Townshend head to south Wales to rescue former boy racer Huw's rusty Vauxhall Astra GTE, which has</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-14 14:10:00" d="2021-07-14 15:15:00"><n u="Emergency Helicopter Medics">Emergency Helicopter Medics I (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The medics help Mick, who's put into an induced coma after going into cardiac arrest on a tennis court, and fell-runner Michael, who's been seriously</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-14 15:15:00" d="2021-07-14 15:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The competition kicks off at Wharfe House in Wetherby with B&amp;B newbie Pauline Cox, who has a full house for the very first time. But the narrow antique</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-14 15:50:00" d="2021-07-14 16:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The second visit is to Wortwell Hall Barn in Norfolk, where husband-and-wife team Jenny and Clive Aylett strive for perfection. But a kitchen meltdown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-14 16:20:00" d="2021-07-14 16:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Karen and Mike Hepker host at Bath Lodge Castle in Somerset, where they offer a luxurious experience. Their guests are wowed by the opulence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-14 16:50:00" d="2021-07-14 17:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The final visit is to The Old Lodge Hotel in Gosport, Hampshire, where Mike and Tash like to mix business with pleasure, but one guest is disappointed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-14 17:20:00" d="2021-07-14 17:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the last day of the competition and accusations fly, tensions run high and guests walk out, as the payments are revealed and the winner is announced</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-14 17:55:00" d="2021-07-14 18:55:00"><n u="Grand Designs New Zealand">Grand Designs New Zealand VI</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Grand Designs New Zealand
Brand new series: Heritage building enthusiasts Ted and Ita Daniels create an ultra-modern rooftop apartment in Dunedin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-14 18:55:00" d="2021-07-14 19:55:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick IV (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>86% The Supervet
Nurse Steph's cat is brought in after being poisoned. A Polish sheepdog needs an elbow replacement. And a self-confessed 'crazy cat lady'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-14 19:55:00" d="2021-07-14 20:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau">Escape to the Chateau V (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's harvest time at Dick and Angel's chateau. But the family also find time to make over the basement, convert the old piggery into a chicken</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-14 20:55:00" d="2021-07-14 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Confirmed city dwellers Michael Butcher and Phil Palmer have moved to the country to run a farm, start a microbrewery and create a vast, dramatic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-14 22:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:00:00"><n>Emergency Helicopter Medics</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Emergency Helicopter. 
. edics: Mountain Emergencies - Brand new series: The air ambulance team race to a walker who's in cardiac arrest on the banks of Ullswater</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-14 23:00:00" d="2021-07-15 00:05:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E I (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Charlie, who's 65, is back for the second time in two weeks after previously being discharged following a crash. And Peggy, who's 89, is rushed in with a suspected stroke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-15 00:05:00" d="2021-07-15 01:05:00"><n u="999: On the Front Line">999: On the Front Line I (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A 71-year-old man is left with a broken ankle when he is knocked off his bike by a dog. And the paramedics help a man who's been trapped for over 20 hours with a broken leg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-15 01:05:00" d="2021-07-15 02:10:00"><n>Emergency Helicopter Medics</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Emergency Helicopter Medics:. 
. ountain Emergencies - Brand new series: The air ambulance team race to a walker who's in cardiac arrest on the banks of Ullswater</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-15 02:10:00" d="2021-07-15 03:15:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E I (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Charlie, who's 65, is back for the second time in two weeks after previously being discharged following a crash. And Peggy, who's 89, is rushed in with a suspected stroke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-15 03:15:00" d="2021-07-15 04:20:00"><n u="999: On the Front Line">999: On the Front Line I (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A 71-year-old man is left with a broken ankle when he is knocked off his bike by a dog. And the paramedics help a man who's been trapped for over 20 hours with a broken leg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2021-07-15 04:20:00" d="2021-07-15 07:20:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped XIV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Could a threat to British juniper berries spell the end of the gin resurgence? Kate checks out macadamia nuts, and Matt finds out what's so bad about</k>  </p>
</a>
