<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2019-07-11 00:18:49"><p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-15 09:55:00" d="2019-07-15 10:45:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2015 &amp; 2016</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Summer Sun
Derek Hansel and Gina Awoko from Birmingham are looking for a property in the unspoiled countryside of Almeria in Spain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-15 10:45:00" d="2019-07-15 11:45:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau">Escape to the Chateau I (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>An extended four-part version of series one. Dick Strawbridge and Angel buy a fairy-tale French chateau and set about bringing the abandoned building back to life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-15 11:45:00" d="2019-07-15 13:00:00"><n u="The Great British Bake Off">The Great British Bake Off I (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Over 10 weeks,12 contestants knead, bake and ice to impress judges Paul Hollywood and Prue Leith, hosted by Noel Fielding and Sandi Toksvig. First up: cake week</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-15 13:00:00" d="2019-07-15 14:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It I (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien turn unwanted items into hard cash. This time they're in stitches over some serious sewing machines in Kent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-15 14:05:00" d="2019-07-15 14:35:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The first visit is to the Isle of Man, where, at Knockaloe Beg Farm, hosts Fiona and John Anderson want to convert their guests to their green way of thinking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-15 14:35:00" d="2019-07-15 15:10:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The second B&amp;B is the ultra-modern The Arches on the Isle of Man, where ex-demolition man Phil Routledge hopes to blow his guests away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-15 15:10:00" d="2019-07-15 15:40:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>At The Trafford, Robbie and John hope their 'typical' Blackpool B&amp;B will hit the mark with their well-heeled rivals. The guests spend an afternoon learning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-15 15:40:00" d="2019-07-15 16:15:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The last visit of the week is to the grand Sheepy Lodge in Warwickshire, where globetrotting host Julie Brogan must face her worst fear: cooking poached</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-15 16:15:00" d="2019-07-15 16:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the final day of the competition and the rival B&amp;B owners meet to settle some scores and discover what they've been paid, before the winner is revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-15 16:50:00" d="2019-07-15 17:50:00"><n u="Kirstie and Phil's Love It or List It">Kirstie and Phil's Love It or List It III (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie and Phil's Love It or. 
. ist It: Phil Spencer and Kirstie Allsopp head for Stenhousemuir as they compete to convince couple Steven and Mhairi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-15 17:50:00" d="2019-07-15 18:55:00"><n u="Love It or List It Australia">Love It or List It Australia II</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Love It or List It Australia
Brand new series: Childhood sweethearts Paul and Michelle have outgrown their three-bed house in Brisbane suburb Boondall</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-15 18:55:00" d="2019-07-15 19:55:00"><n u="The Secret Life of the Zoo">The Secret Life of the Zoo III (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The arrival of a new female chimp causes upheaval at Chester Zoo, baby otter Bo goes missing, cheetah mum Kinky Tail is on the operating table</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-15 19:55:00" d="2019-07-15 20:55:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick VIII (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Supervet
A Labrador is rushed to surgery after being hit by a car. A cocker spaniel has a bulging disc in her spine. And basset hound Elmer needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-15 20:55:00" d="2019-07-15 22:00:00"><n u="Great Canal Journeys">Great Canal Journeys VII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Great Canal Journeys: India
Timothy West and Prunella Scales embark on their most ambitious voyage ever, travelling the waterways of India. In this show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-15 22:00:00" d="2019-07-15 23:00:00"><n>Ghosts of the Deep: Ancient Shipwrecks</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Ghosts of the Deep. 
. ncient Shipwrecks: Brand new: Cores from the seabed are analysed and dated to see how and when the Black Sea formed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-15 23:00:00" d="2019-07-16 00:05:00"><n>Egypt's Great Pyramid: The New Evidence</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Egypt's Great Pyramid: The New. 
. vidence: Mystery has long surrounded the construction of Egypt's Great Pyramid, but now new discoveries are revealing its secrets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-16 00:05:00" d="2019-07-16 01:05:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XIII (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>This episode explores the power of love. A woman rushes from Italy when her fiancé is involved in a serious bicycle collision. And an elderly lady becomes unwell at home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-16 01:05:00" d="2019-07-16 02:10:00"><n>Shocking Emergency Calls</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series: The horrific story of how a chimpanzee made a brutal attack that would change lives forever, plus a chilling call from an online predator. (Ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-16 02:10:00" d="2019-07-16 03:15:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick VIII (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Supervet
A Labrador is rushed to surgery after being hit by a car. A cocker spaniel has a bulging disc in her spine. And basset hound Elmer needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-16 03:15:00" d="2019-07-16 04:20:00"><n u="The Secret Life of the Zoo">The Secret Life of the Zoo III (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The arrival of a new female chimp causes upheaval at Chester Zoo, baby otter Bo goes missing, cheetah mum Kinky Tail is on the operating table</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2019-07-16 04:20:00" d="2019-07-16 09:55:00"><n>8 Out of 10 Cats</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>78% 8 Out of 10 Cats Uncut
An extended edition of the panel show. Jimmy Carr and team captains Sean Lock and Jon Richardson are joined by guests Alex Brooker</k>  </p>
</a>
