<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-05-28 04:39:46"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-04 09:55:00" d="2020-06-04 10:30:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped X (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>75% Should we keep coffee, tomatoes, potatoes and even red wine in the fridge? Kate finds out why eucalyptus is so good at clearing our air passages. Plus: sauerkraut</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-04 10:30:00" d="2020-06-04 11:25:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Summer Sun
Pia and Stephen Abbott have been married for 35 years and have long dreamed of owning a property in Spain. Jasmine Harman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-04 11:25:00" d="2020-06-04 12:25:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (21)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien look for profit potential in some church organ pipes and old leather sports car seats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-04 12:25:00" d="2020-06-04 13:25:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>In this episode, Henry Cole calls in a safe-cracker to bring a safe back from the scrapheap, and a ship's wheel is left in splinters when Henry falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-04 13:25:00" d="2020-06-04 14:25:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY III</n><e>R</e>    <k>Dick shares his recipe for enjoying the spoils of chateau life. Donna and Paul discover thousands of dead bees in a chimney. Adam's chateau-buying quest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-04 14:25:00" d="2020-06-04 15:30:00"><n u="Building the Dream">Building the Dream VIII</n><e>R</e>    <k>Charlie Luxton is in Shrewsbury with Dave and Elly, who are aiming to stamp their mark on a suburban street with a modern take on a Victorian terrace. Ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-04 15:30:00" d="2020-06-04 16:05:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Former pop star and Lamborghini lover Danny Karne - aka Danny Lambo - hosts first at his 'fashion and rock 'n' roll hotel' The Pavilion, in London</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-04 16:05:00" d="2020-06-04 16:35:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>At the Fox and Duck in Therfield, Hertfordshire, hosts John and Pat treat their guests to a lesson in pitch and putt and a late-night sing-song</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-04 16:35:00" d="2020-06-04 17:05:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>The third visit is to the New Inn in Newbridge-on-Wye, run by Dave and Debbie Lang. As a keen pig breeder, Dave makes sure his guests are given a suitably</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-04 17:05:00" d="2020-06-04 17:35:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>The final visit of the week is to Robert and Kerstin's Westleigh Farm in Somerset, where they lay on a beekeeping lesson, snooker and some generous helpings for breakfast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-04 17:35:00" d="2020-06-04 18:05:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>As the group meet for the last time, the payments are revealed and the winning B&amp;B announced. But old tensions surface and there are heated exchanges around the table</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-04 18:05:00" d="2020-06-04 19:05:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It III</n><e>R</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien head to Middlesex and Surrey, where Simon repurposes a 1950s hairdryer and an old school desk, and Henry restores a child's motorbike. Ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-04 19:05:00" d="2020-06-04 19:55:00"><n>Countdown</n>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Dr Linda Papadopoulos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-04 19:55:00" d="2020-06-04 20:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY III</n>    <k>Dick enlists the help of his children Arthur and Dorothy to rescue baby toads in their chateau grounds. Alex and Ithaca struggle with the upkeep of their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-04 20:55:00" d="2020-06-04 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>R</e>    <k>Kevin McCloud revisits Robert and Milla a year after their ambitious Lake District eco-home was on the verge of running out of money</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-04 22:00:00" d="2020-06-04 23:10:00"><n u="Outlander">Outlander IV</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Outlander
Brand new series - Savages: Jamie's trip to find settlers for Fraser's Ridge reveals anti-British sentiment. Claire struggles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-04 23:10:00" d="2020-06-05 00:15:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XIII (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Jon Richardson and Jonathan Ross take on Lee Mack and Victoria Coren Mitchell. Jessie Cave joins Susie Dent in Dictionary Corner. Plus Rachel Riley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-05 00:15:00" d="2020-06-05 00:50:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted III (7)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>85% Night of the Nearly Dead: Singing sensation Eoin McLove, at No 1 for 27 weeks with 'My Lovely Mayo Mammy', secretly visits Mrs Doyle for tea after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-05 00:50:00" d="2020-06-05 01:20:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted III (8)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>85% Going to America: Ted accepts a job in the US, with his very own parish in Beverly Hills. But with his ambition about to be realised, Ted's problem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-05 01:20:00" d="2020-06-05 02:05:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>R</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Dr Linda Papadopoulos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-05 02:05:00" d="2020-06-05 03:05:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (18)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>This episode explores unexpected events that make us value the people we love. Hayley and her wife Emma discuss Hayley's leukaemia. Antonio has had a motorcycle accident</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-05 03:05:00" d="2020-06-05 04:10:00"><n>Shocking Emergency Calls</n><e>R</e>    <k>A tense 911 call reveals one woman's desperate bid to escape her abductor, whispering to the operator while the predator Shawn Grate was asleep next to her. (Ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-05 04:10:00" d="2020-06-05 07:10:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted III (7)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>85% Night of the Nearly Dead: Singing sensation Eoin McLove, at No 1 for 27 weeks with 'My Lovely Mayo Mammy', secretly visits Mrs Doyle for tea after</k>  </p>
</a>
