<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2020-05-16 04:54:18"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 09:55:00" d="2020-05-23 10:25:00"><n>Kirstie's Handmade Treasures</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp learns paper sculpture, decoupage and paper embroidery for greeting cards. She feels she has found her calling, but will the judges</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 10:25:00" d="2020-05-23 11:25:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2014 &amp; 2015</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Summer Sun
Brenda and Nick Kennett want to buy a family holiday home in the Correze region of France. Sara Damergi searches the local</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 11:25:00" d="2020-05-23 12:35:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2014 &amp; 2015</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Summer Sun
Sara Damergi helps to find the perfect holiday pad to be shared by three sisters and their brother in the Poitou-Charentes region of France</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 12:35:00" d="2020-05-23 13:35:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2014 &amp; 2015</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Summer Sun
Paula dreams of retiring to the Vendée region of western France, where she can live the good life, growing vegetables</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 13:35:00" d="2020-05-23 14:40:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie and Phil help two sets of first-time buyers. Lucy and Joe have their hearts set on a chocolate box Cotswolds cottage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 14:40:00" d="2020-05-23 15:40:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer are in Edinburgh with motor-mad Ian, who's more interested in finding a shed than a house, and Jane and Rogan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 15:40:00" d="2020-05-23 16:15:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Ipswich. First to host is theatre lover Claire, who aims to impress with her panto-themed night. But with one guest reluctant to join in</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 16:15:00" d="2020-05-23 16:45:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Ipswich. Millwall fan Kerrie Pankhurst plays host with a football-themed evening. Kerrie contends with fish-hating Dave and a guest's snub of her beloved club. (Ep2/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 16:45:00" d="2020-05-23 17:15:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Ipswich. Host David J Marks needs to win over Kerrie after offending her last night. His salmon starter impresses all but DJ Dave, who details the things</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 17:15:00" d="2020-05-23 17:50:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Ipswich. DJ Dave James prepares a showbiz-themed evening for his guests and asks them to come dressed as pop stars. Later, a shock revelation leaves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 17:50:00" d="2020-05-23 18:20:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Ipswich. It's the final day and speed-dating expert Nicki Yucel is determined to spread a little love. One contestant reveals their feelings for another</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 18:20:00" d="2020-05-23 18:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Alan and Sylvie host first, at Watersedge Guest House in Barton on Sea. Mike and Danny waste no time in grumbling about the grime in their room</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 18:50:00" d="2020-05-23 19:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Tim and Amelia host the rival B&amp;B owners at their non-star-rated boutique accommodation, Nearwater, on the south Cornish coast. But Sylvie and Alan aren't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 19:25:00" d="2020-05-23 19:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Austrian-born artist Eva hosts in her cosmopolitan B&amp;B, Roundhouse Hotel, on Weymouth seafront. Mike and Danny are shocked by the exposed shower</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 19:55:00" d="2020-05-23 20:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Showmen Mike and Danny host at the four-star Homecliffe Hotel in Blackpool. Sylvie and Alan have a great view. of the local car wash. And at breakfast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 20:25:00" d="2020-05-23 21:00:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the final day and all the B&amp;B hosts meet one last time to find out how much they've been paid. Only one establishment can take the title of best value for money B&amp;B. Who will it be?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 21:00:00" d="2020-05-23 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Lysette and Nigel's plan to build a dramatic new cutting-edge home by the River Thames proves difficult, costly, and not very popular with their neighbours. (Ep4/12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 22:00:00" d="2020-05-23 23:00:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>This episode meets three different sets of friends who have been there for each other through thick and thin. Phil has suffered multiple injuries after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 23:00:00" d="2020-05-24 00:05:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Corey, who's 27, is rushed to St George's after suffering a cardiac arrest during a game of ice hockey. His wife of seven days, Alice, was watching</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-24 00:05:00" d="2020-05-24 00:40:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted II (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>85% Rock-a-Hula Ted: A feminist protest singer arrives on the island just as Ted is about to judge the Lovely Girls competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-24 00:40:00" d="2020-05-24 01:15:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted II (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>85% Cigarettes and Alcohol and Rollerblading: Easter is fast approaching, so Ted decides to get on with the important business of working out what to sacrifice for Lent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-24 01:15:00" d="2020-05-24 02:15:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Sean Lock and Stephen Mangan take on Noel Fielding and Fay Ripley. The Brett Domino Trio are in Dictionary Corner with Susie Dent. Plus Rachel Riley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-24 02:15:00" d="2020-05-24 03:15:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon visits a high-end bistro in Florida. Owner Andy has cooked for top chefs in the past, but since opening Le Bistro, he's lost his passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-24 03:15:00" d="2020-05-24 04:20:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>This episode meets three different sets of friends who have been there for each other through thick and thin. Phil has suffered multiple injuries after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-24 04:20:00" d="2020-05-24 09:55:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted II (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>85% Rock-a-Hula Ted: A feminist protest singer arrives on the island just as Ted is about to judge the Lovely Girls competition</k>  </p>
</a>
