<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2020-05-10 04:34:35"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-17 09:55:00" d="2020-05-17 10:30:00"><n>Kirstie's Handmade Treasures</n><e>RF</e>    <k>What will the judges in the afternoon tea tent at the Devon County Show think of Kirstie Allsopp's unconventional kumquat éclairs?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-17 10:30:00" d="2020-05-17 11:25:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S V (5)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Mercedes-Benz 230SL: Tim and Fuzz pull out all the stops to restore a 1965 classic car that was left in storage after its owner John had a heart attack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-17 11:25:00" d="2020-05-17 12:25:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S V (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Aston Martin DB6: Tim and Fuzz restore a 1967 British classic for oil worker Steve, who bought it for a bargain price over 20 years ago</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-17 12:25:00" d="2020-05-17 13:25:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S V (6)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Renault 5 GT Turbo: Tim and Fuzz tackle a 1980s French hot hatch that has been gathering dust in a garage: a Renault 5 GT Turbo that is owner Ben's dream car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-17 13:25:00" d="2020-05-17 14:30:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>R</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer catch up with long-distance lovebirds Annmarie and Robert, and Alison and Martin, who wanted properties that would bring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-17 14:30:00" d="2020-05-17 15:35:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>R</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer catch up with a pair of period property lovers. Ian wanted a Regency property in Cheltenham, while Sehyr was after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-17 15:35:00" d="2020-05-17 16:05:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Dan and Mardi Leonard host at their funky Brighton B&amp;B, Guest and the City, where their guests have mixed reactions to the establishment's contemporary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-17 16:05:00" d="2020-05-17 16:40:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>At The Farmer's Boy Inn in Gloucestershire, owner and pie entrepreneur Phil sets his guests a pie-making challenge. In the morning, there's a session</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-17 16:40:00" d="2020-05-17 17:10:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Hosts Alan and Jane welcome aboard their first-ever guests for a night on their brand-new, purpose-built hotel boat, the Geanna, as well as a champagne</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-17 17:10:00" d="2020-05-17 17:45:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>The final hosts are B&amp;B connoisseurs Sarah Langford and Jean-Pierre Kujawa, who serve a five-star dinner and breakfast at their B&amp;B, Sentry Mead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-17 17:45:00" d="2020-05-17 18:15:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>It's the final day and the B&amp;B hosts gather for one last time to find out how much they've been paid. Unfortunately, some of the hosts' emotions run away with them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-17 18:15:00" d="2020-05-17 18:50:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>East Lancashire. Vicki Fairbrother cooks up 'sexy' steak and banging banoffee cake. She also has a game in store for her guests involving a helmet and water. (Ep1/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-17 18:50:00" d="2020-05-17 19:25:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>East Lancashire. Burnley businesswoman Jenna Tattersall plans a party night with an all-white dress code. But is it wise to end the evening on a bouncy castle? (Ep2/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-17 19:25:00" d="2020-05-17 19:55:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>East Lancashire. Perfectionist Chris Slater tries his hardest to add a touch of class to the week. But his food and one of his habits don't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-17 19:55:00" d="2020-05-17 20:25:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>East Lancashire. Chelsea's Mediterranean evening begins with the boys having a punch-up over a punch bag. And then the girls discover a secret Chelsea's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-17 20:25:00" d="2020-05-17 21:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>East Lancashire. Hairdresser Nigel Womack hosts an Epicurean evening of love, featuring a mix of aphrodisiacs that he hopes will get his guests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-17 21:00:00" d="2020-05-17 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kevin McCloud meets Kevin McCabe, the leading exponent of the ancient art of cob building, who wants to construct a castle entirely of mud. The huge scale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-17 22:00:00" d="2020-05-17 23:00:00"><n u="999: On the Front Line">999: On the Front Line IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Paramedics treat a 60-year-old patient with severe chest pains, a suspected drunk driver who's crashed his car, and an elderly man who's collapsed at home. Ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-17 23:00:00" d="2020-05-18 00:05:00"><n>Inside Birmingham Children's Hospital</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Inside Birmingham Children's. 
. ospital: Rob has swapped life on the road as a long-haul trucker to become the primary carer for his daughter Chelsea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-18 00:05:00" d="2020-05-18 01:10:00"><n u="999: What's Your Emergency?">999: What's Your Emergency? VI</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Behind the scenes with the emergency services. This episode explores loneliness, from pensioners who need someone to talk to, to teens struggling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-18 01:10:00" d="2020-05-18 02:15:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Mark, who's 52, fights for his life after being thrown from his motorbike in a crash. Kayley, who's 25, has fallen from her horse and doctors worry she's dislocated her hip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-18 02:15:00" d="2020-05-18 03:15:00"><n u="999: On the Front Line">999: On the Front Line IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Paramedics treat a 60-year-old patient with severe chest pains, a suspected drunk driver who's crashed his car, and an elderly man who's collapsed at home. Ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-18 03:15:00" d="2020-05-18 04:15:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay visits Lido Di Manhattan in California. Ambitious business graduate Lisa bought the restaurant at just 23 but, five years later, she's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-18 04:15:00" d="2020-05-18 07:15:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted II (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>85% Think Fast, Father Ted: To raise funds to fix the leaky roof, Ted receives a car from Bishop Brennan to raffle. But, as usual, things go horribly wrong</k>  </p>
</a>
