<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-05-15 04:47:58"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 09:55:00" d="2020-05-22 10:20:00"><n>Kirstie's Vintage Gems</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and expert jewellery maker Rachel Jeffrey help a couple to create their own rings for their wedding day. Kirstie also learns new uses for real gold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 10:20:00" d="2020-05-22 11:15:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2014 &amp; 2015</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Summer Sun
Richard and Felicity want a second home in the Coimbra region of Portugal and are looking to spend ?40,000 on a renovation project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 11:15:00" d="2020-05-22 12:15:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It I (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>In York, Henry Cole struggles to squeeze into some motorcycle leathers, and Simon O'Brien gets into deep water when he tries to restore an aluminium boat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 12:15:00" d="2020-05-22 13:15:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It I (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien turn unwanted possessions into hard cash. Simon takes Henry to a stately home in Somerset, where he thinks he's unearthed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 13:15:00" d="2020-05-22 14:15:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Phillip and Janet rush to finish the bridal suite for daughter Penny's wedding, Mariam and Johnno prepare to host seven guests, and Emma and Paul complete</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 14:15:00" d="2020-05-22 15:20:00"><n u="Building the Dream">Building the Dream VII (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Charlie Luxton returns to East Sussex to catch up with Steve and an eco-efficient, straw-baled, self-built home set in a woodland glade</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 15:20:00" d="2020-05-22 15:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>First host Claire welcomes her guests to Robertsbrook Guesthouse in Swanage. Lynn and Ziggy are on the hunt for dust in their bedroom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 15:50:00" d="2020-05-22 16:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Quirky Cornish couple Lynn and Ziggy hope to impress with their two-star paradise Eden Lodge. But their guests find fault from the get-go, from peeling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 16:20:00" d="2020-05-22 16:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Charlotte Church's parents James and Maria welcome the group to Dexby Townhouse in Cardiff for a day of white-water rafting and magic tricks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 16:50:00" d="2020-05-22 17:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the final stay of the competition and the turn of newly-weds Pip and Nicky, who run Muddifords Court Country House in Devon. Will their guests enjoy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 17:25:00" d="2020-05-22 17:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>There are tears, outrage and arguments as the group meet one last time to find out exactly how much they have been paid by their fellow hoteliers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 17:55:00" d="2020-05-22 18:55:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Near the Malvern Hills, Henry picks two saddles and converts them into bar stools, while Simon makes a profit on a 1960s kitchen cupboard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 18:55:00" d="2020-05-22 19:55:00"><n u="Great Canal Journeys">Great Canal Journeys II (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Timothy West and Prunella Scales explore the most picturesque stretch of the Canal du Midi in the south of France, eating lamb's brain fritters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 19:55:00" d="2020-05-22 20:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY IV</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Emma and Paul prepare for their biggest-ever booking, Mariam and Johnno transform their chateau's grand salon, and Karen and Paul aim to renovate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 20:55:00" d="2020-05-22 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Brixton, south London, design-mad couple Mary and Carl want to build a home that resembles a giant stack of glass cubes and offers a Zen retreat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 22:00:00" d="2020-05-22 23:15:00"><n u="Thou Shalt Not Kill">Thou Shalt Not Kill II</n><t>S</t><e>TF</e>    <k>New: Thou Shalt Not Kill
Brand new series: Second series of the haunting detective drama from Walter Presents. The military interfere in an investigation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-22 23:15:00" d="2020-05-23 00:20:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>George, who's 70, has impaled his eye on a piece of driftwood. Debby, who's 59, has cut her hand on her lawnmower. And eight-year-old Phoebe has scissors stuck in her thigh</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 00:20:00" d="2020-05-23 01:20:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>This episode meets three different sets of friends who have been there for each other through thick and thin. Phil has suffered multiple injuries after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 01:20:00" d="2020-05-23 02:20:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay heads to Mexican restaurant Mama Rita's in Newbury Park, southern California, to try to bring new ideas to the business</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 02:20:00" d="2020-05-23 03:20:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>George, who's 70, has impaled his eye on a piece of driftwood. Debby, who's 59, has cut her hand on her lawnmower. And eight-year-old Phoebe has scissors stuck in her thigh</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 03:20:00" d="2020-05-23 04:25:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XII (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>This episode meets three different sets of friends who have been there for each other through thick and thin. Phil has suffered multiple injuries after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-05-23 04:25:00" d="2020-05-23 07:25:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped IX (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>75% Jimmy finds out how Kenyan farmers get their green beans so straight. Matt learns about scallop procreation. Kate checks out which ingredients should</k>  </p>
</a>
