<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-04-15 04:34:40"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-22 09:55:00" d="2020-04-22 10:20:00"><n>Kirstie's Vintage Gems</n><e>R</e>    <k>In this bite-size episode, crafting champion Kirstie Allsopp enlists the help of super-seamstress Lisa Comfort to help Amber and Colin create a memory quilt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-22 10:20:00" d="2020-04-22 11:15:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2014 &amp; 2015</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Home or Away
Neil and Steph are torn between moving full-time to either Fuerteventura, and its guaranteed sunshine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-22 11:15:00" d="2020-04-22 12:15:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2014 &amp; 2015</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Home or Away
Kim Smith is desperate to start a new life in southern Spain, near Antequera. But her husband Pete doesn't feel ready</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-22 12:15:00" d="2020-04-22 13:15:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (7)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Simon O'Brien finds some night vision goggles and an antique snooker table that's seen better days, while Henry Cole chooses an enormous US army truck as one of his picks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-22 13:15:00" d="2020-04-22 14:15:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It III</n><e>R</e>    <k>Henry Cole and Simon O'Brien are seeking more items to repair and sell. In this episode they visit a Norman castle, restore a Fiat 500 and build a table</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-22 14:15:00" d="2020-04-22 15:20:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau">Escape to the Chateau I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Dick Strawbridge and his partner Angel are doing up an abandoned French chateau. With just ?20,000 left in the coffers the refurb problems feel endless</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-22 15:20:00" d="2020-04-22 15:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>The competition starts at the Park Hotel in Gloucestershire, where couple Lauren Abraham and Callum Hogg make their bid for the prize, but some robust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-22 15:50:00" d="2020-04-22 16:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>The second visit is to Sue's B&amp;B in Trowbridge where, despite the home-from-home approach, cracks in the group start to show and a communal table has its awkward moments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-22 16:20:00" d="2020-04-22 16:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>The third visit is to The Talbot in Dorset, where Erika Watt and Ellie Gill's rooms don't live up to first impressions. And some of the feedback sends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-22 16:55:00" d="2020-04-22 17:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>The final visit is to The Old Rectory in south Wales, where Cameron Thomas has to show more than just his professional side, and the competition heats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-22 17:25:00" d="2020-04-22 17:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>It's the final day and the B&amp;B owners meet for the last time to settle some scores. Tensions are in the air and issues are debated before the winner is revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-22 17:55:00" d="2020-04-22 18:55:00"><n>A New Life in the Sun</n><e>R</e>    <k>A couple of expats attempt to run a new fishing charter, two B&amp;Bers in France cope with their biggest challenge yet, and a family tries to rescue their Spanish dream</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-22 18:55:00" d="2020-04-22 19:55:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S I (8)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Austin Re-Powered: Tim Shaw and Fuzz Townshend head to Suffolk to secretly restore a charismatic but worn-out 1928 Austin 12 Tourer - a 'mobster's car', as Tim puts it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-22 19:55:00" d="2020-04-22 20:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau">Escape to the Chateau I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Dick and Angel are due to marry in just a few weeks, expecting 200 guests. But room after room still needs to be restored, decorated and furnished</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-22 20:55:00" d="2020-04-22 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>R</e>    <k>Kevin McCloud meets Clinton from West Sussex who's willing to spend whatever it takes to build one of the largest homes ever featured on Grand Designs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-22 22:00:00" d="2020-04-22 23:00:00"><n u="Building the Dream">Building the Dream IX</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Building the Dream
Brand new series: Charlie's in Berkshire with Tom and Georgina who plan to renovate a run-down bungalow. Will they reach breaking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-22 23:00:00" d="2020-04-23 00:05:00"><n u="Grand Designs Australia">Grand Designs Australia VIII</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Grand Designs Australia
Brand new series: Tabitha and Chris always dreamt of living in the forest. They bought 120 acres of rainforest in Toolangi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-23 00:05:00" d="2020-04-23 01:10:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E X</n><e>R</e>    <k>Ten-year-old Josh arrives at A&amp;E after an accident at school, unaware that his finger was cut off in the incident. Doctors must work out how to reattach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-23 01:10:00" d="2020-04-23 02:15:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown VIII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts the panel game. Sean Lock and Jason Manford take on Jon Richardson and Roisin Conaty, while Sam Simmons joins Susie Dent in Dictionary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-23 02:15:00" d="2020-04-23 03:20:00"><n u="Building the Dream">Building the Dream IX</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Brand new series: Charlie's in Berkshire with Tom and Georgina who plan to renovate a run-down bungalow. Will they reach breaking point when their project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-23 03:20:00" d="2020-04-23 04:25:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E X</n><e>R</e>    <k>Ten-year-old Josh arrives at A&amp;E after an accident at school, unaware that his finger was cut off in the incident. Doctors must work out how to reattach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-23 04:25:00" d="2020-04-23 07:25:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped VI (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>76% Jimmy investigates whether it's worth splashing out on expensive vodka, Kate finds out how coffee beans are turned into instant granules, and Matt checks</k>  </p>
</a>
