<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-04-10 04:35:27"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-17 09:55:00" d="2020-04-17 10:20:00"><n>Kirstie's Handmade Treasures</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp enters the single-cake class at the Devon County Show, where a beetroot cake raises some eyebrows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-17 10:20:00" d="2020-04-17 11:15:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2014 &amp; 2015</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Winter Sun
Jonnie Irwin helps David and Christina, who have ?150,000 to spend on a holiday home in Orlando, Florida, where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-17 11:15:00" d="2020-04-17 12:15:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2014 &amp; 2015</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Winter Sun
Rob and Jan want to buy a holiday home in Florida's Sarasota Bay, where they can escape rainy England. Jonnie Irwin shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-17 12:15:00" d="2020-04-17 13:15:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>In this episode, Max McMurdo upcycles a brass propeller into a stylish table lamp, while Henry Cole goes all Victorian with an old pond yacht</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-17 13:15:00" d="2020-04-17 14:15:00"><n u="Find It, Fix It, Flog It">Find It, Fix It, Flog It II (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Near the Malvern Hills, Henry picks two saddles and converts them into bar stools, while Simon makes a profit on a 1960s kitchen cupboard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-17 14:15:00" d="2020-04-17 15:20:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY III</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Stephanie's renovations could take longer than anticipated. Lee starts constructing a solar panel system for an outdoor swimming pool. Jayne takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-17 15:20:00" d="2020-04-17 15:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The competition starts at The Oak Tree Cottage in Burley, where Jacqui Castle hopes her homely approach will win the day, but her communal breakfast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-17 15:50:00" d="2020-04-17 16:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The second visit is to The Rising Sun Inn in Bath, where owners Lorraine Hawkins and Norman Butcher impose a dress code for dinner. Some of the guests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-17 16:20:00" d="2020-04-17 16:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The third visit is to The Busfeild Arms in East Morton, where hosts Martin and Catherine Crosswaite pride themselves on Yorkshire hospitality, but Martin's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-17 16:55:00" d="2020-04-17 17:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The final visit is to Epstein House in Liverpool, where there's a competitive Beatles-themed game of charades and some shocking revelations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-17 17:25:00" d="2020-04-17 17:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the last day and Patrick has some serious questions for Jacqui and Jane, while Martin and Catherine have some explaining to do. Payments are revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-17 17:55:00" d="2020-04-17 18:55:00"><n>A New Life in the Sun</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Spain, two best friends reveal their business plans at the end of a successful summer. A bar inches dangerously close to failure. And a rookie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-17 18:55:00" d="2020-04-17 19:55:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S I (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Anglia Angels: Tim Shaw and Fuzz Townshend meet the Hutchings-Clarke family, who all drive Ford Anglias - except James, whose car hasn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-17 19:55:00" d="2020-04-17 20:55:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY III</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Laying electrical cable proves tricky at Dick and Angel's chateau. Brand new chateau owners Donna and Paul move into their new home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-17 20:55:00" d="2020-04-17 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Tom and Danielle use their steam-bending skills to build a wavy wooden house full of twisty furniture in Cornwall. But with a relatively modest budget</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-17 22:00:00" d="2020-04-17 23:20:00"><n u="Thou Shalt Not Kill">Thou Shalt Not Kill II</n><t>S</t><e>TF</e>    <k>New: Thou Shalt Not Kill
Brand new series: Second series of the haunting detective drama from Walter Presents. A young woman's death during a complicated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-17 23:20:00" d="2020-04-18 00:20:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E IX (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>This episode focuses on the importance of having someone to love and support us when life gets tough. Gerald, who's 66, has fallen from</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-18 00:20:00" d="2020-04-18 01:25:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XI</n><e>R</e>    <k>Tony has fallen head-first onto a tiled floor while doing DIY. Charlie was assaulted on his way home from a night out. And 10-year-old Lucy has been having</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-18 01:25:00" d="2020-04-18 02:20:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay visits the upmarket Cafe 36 in Chicago, where husband-and-wife team Terry and Carol are stuck in the past and their head chef's cavalier</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-18 02:20:00" d="2020-04-18 03:25:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E IX (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>This episode focuses on the importance of having someone to love and support us when life gets tough. Gerald, who's 66, has fallen from</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-18 03:25:00" d="2020-04-18 04:30:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XI</n><e>R</e>    <k>Tony has fallen head-first onto a tiled floor while doing DIY. Charlie was assaulted on his way home from a night out. And 10-year-old Lucy has been having</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-04-18 04:30:00" d="2020-04-18 07:30:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped VI (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>76% Jimmy, Kate and Matt uncover more secrets about our food. Are alarming headlines about MSG justified? Are Brazil nuts radioactive? And how is elderflower cordial made?</k>  </p>
</a>
