<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2020-05-31 04:35:44"><p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 09:55:00" d="2020-06-07 10:30:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped X (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>75% What are those worms doing in bottles of tequila? How do you stop carp tasting of mud? And what's the difference between tangerines, mandarins, satsumas and clementines?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 10:30:00" d="2020-06-07 11:25:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S VI (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Karmann Ghia: Tim and Fuzz toil to restore a 1965 VW Karmann Ghia, a once-stylish German motor that now has accident-damaged body work and a leaking engine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 11:25:00" d="2020-06-07 12:25:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S VI (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Lancia Delta Integrale: The boys tackle a rusty, four-wheel-drive world rally champ but, as tragedy strikes, the restoration takes on a very different meaning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 12:25:00" d="2020-06-07 13:30:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S VI (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Peugeot 205 GTi: Tim Shaw and Fuzz Townshend take on a 1989 Peugeot 205 GTi, with help from former Monte Carlo winner and racing legend Paddy Hopkirk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 13:30:00" d="2020-06-07 14:35:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau">Escape to the Chateau I (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Dick Strawbridge and Angel embark on their French fairy tale, swapping their two-bed Southend flat for a 19th-century chateau. But, abandoned for years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 14:35:00" d="2020-06-07 15:40:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau">Escape to the Chateau I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Dick Strawbridge and Angel have moved to France to do up an abandoned chateau. With just ?20,000 left in the coffers, the refurb problems feel endless</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 15:40:00" d="2020-06-07 16:10:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Julie Janes and Yvonne Quinsey hope to impress their guests at their African-themed Foxholm B&amp;B in North Yorkshire. Things start harmoniously but soon descend into chaos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 16:10:00" d="2020-06-07 16:40:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Wendy Johnson and John Shields welcome their rivals to their American diner-themed B&amp;B, the Pack Horse in Lincolnshire, where the guests enjoy an afternoon of horse riding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 16:40:00" d="2020-06-07 17:15:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>At Glenwalden B&amp;B in Blackpool, hosts Steve and Sigrid take their guests ballroom dancing, but there are suspicions of tactical behaviour and accusations of back-stabbing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 17:15:00" d="2020-06-07 17:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Expectations start high at the five-star Winder Hall Country House B&amp;B in the Lake District. But things soon turn sour when Nick offers a crash course</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 17:50:00" d="2020-06-07 18:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>R</e>    <k>It's crunch time for the B&amp;Bers as they meet for the last time and are soon squabbling about stolen milk, dusty bathrooms and dirty toilet brushes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 18:20:00" d="2020-06-07 18:50:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Belfast. First to host is make-up artist and female impersonator Marcus Hunter-Neill - aka Lady Portia Diamante - who steals the limelight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 18:50:00" d="2020-06-07 19:25:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Belfast. Jamaican lifeguard Lenny Irving serves up some authentic Caribbean cuisine in a bid to win over his guests - particularly glamorous navy officer Fiona. (Ep2/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 19:25:00" d="2020-06-07 19:55:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Belfast. Feminist writer Cat Anderson hopes to raise the bar with a home-cooked feast and attentive service. But will her bohemian chic style</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 19:55:00" d="2020-06-07 20:25:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Belfast. Next to host is charity worker and confident cook Rosie Smyth, who hopes to win over fussy Fiona and new best friend Cat with a 'come</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 20:25:00" d="2020-06-07 21:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Belfast. It's the final day and merchant navy officer Fiona Rush dishes up a nautical-themed evening, featuring maritime entertainment and a very fishy menu. (Ep5/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 21:00:00" d="2020-06-07 22:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kevin McCloud revisits Denise and Bruno Del Tufo who set about transforming a concrete water tower in their back garden into an avant-garde contemporary home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 22:00:00" d="2020-06-07 23:00:00"><n u="999: On the Front Line">999: On the Front Line IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Paramedics treat a man with a crippling cluster headache, a woman suffering from the effects of alcohol withdrawal and a woman who's collapsed in a sauna. Ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-07 23:00:00" d="2020-06-08 00:05:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XIII (6)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>This episode explores how grief can test the strongest marriages and how finding love for a second time can save you. Kim has been hit by a lorry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-08 00:05:00" d="2020-06-08 01:05:00"><n u="999: What's Your Emergency?">999: What's Your Emergency? VII</n><e>RF</e>    <k>This episode joins the emergency services as they respond to accidents, from car crashes to sports injuries and a man who's chopped through his foot while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-08 01:05:00" d="2020-06-08 02:05:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>The saga of Boston eatery La Galleria 33 comes to a dramatic conclusion, as Gordon Ramsay gives restaurant owners and sisters Rita and Lisa an ultimatum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-08 02:05:00" d="2020-06-08 03:10:00"><n u="999: On the Front Line">999: On the Front Line IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Paramedics treat a man with a crippling cluster headache, a woman suffering from the effects of alcohol withdrawal and a woman who's collapsed in a sauna. Ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-08 03:10:00" d="2020-06-08 04:15:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XIII (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>This episode explores how grief can test the strongest marriages and how finding love for a second time can save you. Kim has been hit by a lorry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1000" o="2020-06-08 04:15:00" d="2020-06-08 09:55:00"><n u="Father Ted">Father Ted I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>85% Entertaining Father Stone: For six years, Father Stone has been coming to Craggy Island and for Father Ted, Father Dougal and Father Jack, that's seven years too many</k>  </p>
</a>
