<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-05-14 04:52:41"><p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-21 12:00:00" d="2020-05-21 13:50:00"><n>The Naked Truth</n><e>R</e>    <k>Black comedy with Peter Sellers, Terry-Thomas and Dennis Price. A group of celebrities decide to murder the extortionist who's threatening to publish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-21 13:50:00" d="2020-05-21 15:30:00"><n>The Spy in Black</n><e>R</e>    <k>Michael Powell's thriller stars Conrad Veidt as a First World War German spy sent to Orkney, where he is pursued by a double agent (Valerie Hobson)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-21 15:30:00" d="2020-05-21 17:40:00"><n>The Man in the Iron Mask</n><e>R</e>    <k>Richard Chamberlain stars in the dual role of the wicked Louis XIV of France and his noble twin brother Philippe, who is imprisoned with his identity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-21 17:40:00" d="2020-05-21 19:45:00"><n>Three Violent People</n><e>R</e>    <k>Western starring Charlton Heston and Anne Baxter. A Confederate officer returning home from the Civil War has to fight to save his ranch from corrupt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-21 19:45:00" d="2020-05-21 22:00:00"><n>Cowboys &amp; Aliens</n><e>R</e>    <k>Sci-fi western starring Daniel Craig and Harrison Ford. A brutal cattle baron and his amnesiac enemy must cease their feuding when a town is attacked by aliens. Violence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-21 22:00:00" d="2020-05-22 00:05:00"><n>A Walk in the Woods</n><e>R</e>    <k>Fact-based comedy-drama starring Robert Redford, Nick Nolte and Emma Thompson. Ageing travel writer Bill Bryson attempts to walk the 2000-mile Appalachian Trail. Strong language</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-22 00:05:00" d="2020-05-22 02:20:00"><n u="The Family">The Family (2013)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Family
(2013) Comedy thriller with Robert De Niro and Michelle Pfeiffer. A New York Mafia family relocate to a small French village under the Witness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-22 02:20:00" d="2020-05-22 05:20:00"><n u="Child">Child 44</n><e>R</e>    <k>Thriller with Tom Hardy and Noomi Rapace. In 1950s Russia, a demoted security services agent realises that a serial killer is targeting young boys</k>  </p>
</a>
