<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-05-27 04:35:30"><p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-03 12:00:00" d="2020-06-03 14:10:00"><n>Esther Waters</n><e>R</e>    <k>Period melodrama with Kathleen Ryan. After a tough childhood, Esther is sent away to become a maid, but gets pregnant when seduced by a servant (Dirk Bogarde)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-03 14:10:00" d="2020-06-03 15:55:00"><n>Appointment with Danger</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Noir thriller starring Alan Ladd, Phyllis Calvert and Paul Stewart. A postal inspector infiltrates a gang planning a huge heist. But he must also protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-03 15:55:00" d="2020-06-03 18:00:00"><n>The Man from Laramie</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Classic western. James Stewart plays a stranger who arrives in a remote New Mexico town secretly seeking his brother's killer. With Donald Crisp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-03 18:00:00" d="2020-06-03 20:10:00"><n>The Way to the Stars</n><e>R</e>    <k>John Mills, Michael Redgrave and Trevor Howard star in this Second World War drama exploring the relationships that form on an RAF base when a US squadron arrives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-03 20:10:00" d="2020-06-03 22:00:00"><n>Enough Said</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Comedy-drama with James Gandolfini and Julia Louis-Dreyfus. Two divorcees start to date. But she also begins a secret friendship that may threaten the relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-03 22:00:00" d="2020-06-04 00:15:00"><n>The Bank Job</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Bank heist thriller. Jason Statham stars as the leader of a gang of thieves whose lucrative job lands them in grave danger. Very strong language/violence/sexual scenes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-04 00:15:00" d="2020-06-04 02:20:00"><n>Gemma Bovery</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Comedy-drama with Gemma Arterton and Jason Flemyng. An English couple move to a French village, where a book-loving baker fears they are headed for tragedy. Sexual scenes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-04 02:20:00" d="2020-06-04 05:20:00"><n>The Love Witch</n><e>R</e>    <k>Stylised thriller with Samantha Robinson. In 1960s California, a woman uses occult potions and spells in her troubled quest for love. Nudity/sex/violence/gory images</k>  </p>
</a>
