<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-05-10 04:33:09"><p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-17 12:00:00" d="2020-05-17 14:10:00"><n>Kidnapped</n><e>R</e>    <k>Drama. After the Battle of Culloden in 1746, a young and naive lad, Lawrence Douglas, has a succession of dangerous adventures with a fleeing Jacobite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-17 14:10:00" d="2020-05-17 16:15:00"><n>The Perfect Catch</n><e>R</e>    <k>Comedy. Ben (Jimmy Fallon) must choose between his love for Lindsey (Drew Barrymore) and the baseball team he supports, the Boston Red Sox</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-17 16:15:00" d="2020-05-17 18:15:00"><n>Hotel for Dogs</n><e>R</e>    <k>Family comedy starring Emma Roberts and Jake T Austin. A neglected teenager and her brother secretly set up a refuge for stray dogs in an abandoned building</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-17 18:15:00" d="2020-05-17 20:15:00"><n u="Home Alone">Home Alone 3</n><e>R</e>    <k>Comedy sequel. Alex D Linz stars as a resourceful boy who's stranded at home with chickenpox when a top-secret military microchip comes his way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-17 20:15:00" d="2020-05-17 22:00:00"><n>Europa Report</n><e>R</e>    <k>Scary sci-fi thriller. A manned spaceship heads to Jupiter's ice moon Europa in search of life, but things don't go according to plan. Starring Michael</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-17 22:00:00" d="2020-05-18 00:05:00"><n>Jack Ryan: Shadow Recruit</n><e>R</e>    <k>Thriller starring Chris Pine, Keira Knightley, Kevin Costner and Kenneth Branagh. A CIA agent is sent on a dangerous mission to Moscow to investigate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-18 00:05:00" d="2020-05-18 02:25:00"><n>Rush</n><e>R</e>    <k>Fact-based drama about the intense rivalry between 1970s F1 racing drivers James Hunt (Chris Hemsworth) and Niki Lauda (Daniel Brühl)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-18 02:25:00" d="2020-05-18 05:25:00"><n>Good Kill</n><e>R</e>    <k>Drama starring Ethan Hawke. A US combat pilot struggles to cope when he's reassigned to remotely controlling military assault drones. Strong language/sexual violence/sex</k>  </p>
</a>
