<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-05-31 04:35:17"><p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-07 12:00:00" d="2020-06-07 13:55:00"><n>Baggage Claim</n><e>R</e>    <k>Romcom starring Paula Patton. A flight attendant desperately tries to find herself a husband before her younger sister gets married. With Derek Luke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-07 13:55:00" d="2020-06-07 15:55:00"><n u="Rio">Rio 2</n><e>R</e>    <k>Animated family adventure. Rare Spix's macaws Blu, Jewel and their kids embark on an eventful journey deep into the Amazon to find more of their kind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-07 15:55:00" d="2020-06-07 17:40:00"><n>Shrek Forever After</n><e>R</e>    <k>Animated adventure. In the ogre's fourth feature-length escapade, Shrek makes an unwise bargain with Rumpelstiltskin. With the voices of Mike Myers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-07 17:40:00" d="2020-06-07 19:45:00"><n>Dante's Peak</n><e>R</e>    <k>Action thriller starring Pierce Brosnan and Linda Hamilton. A scientist's warning that a volcano is set to erupt is unwisely ignored by the inhabitants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-07 19:45:00" d="2020-06-07 22:00:00"><n>G.I. Joe: The Rise of Cobra</n><e>R</e>    <k>Violent action-adventure with Channing Tatum, Sienna Miller and Christopher Eccleston. Terrorists steal a devastating weapon and only the USA's finest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-07 22:00:00" d="2020-06-08 00:25:00"><n>Stargate</n><e>R</e>    <k>James Spader and Kurt Russell go through a Stargate to a distant planet where the evil god Ra (Jaye Davidson), who created humanity, is planning his return</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-08 00:25:00" d="2020-06-08 02:35:00"><n>Dumb and Dumber To</n><e>R</e>    <k>Gross-out comedy sequel with Jim Carrey and Jeff Daniels. Two decades after their first one, Harry and Lloyd take another idiocy-and-incident-packed road trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-08 02:35:00" d="2020-06-08 09:00:00"><n>Quadrophenia</n><e>R</e>    <k>Drama with Phil Daniels. A youth finds excitement and a sense of belonging in 1960s mod culture. But the scene has its darker side. Violence/very strong</k>  </p>
</a>
