<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2019-07-11 00:18:49"><p id_tv="1001" o="2019-07-15 09:00:00" d="2019-07-15 12:00:00"><n u="BSL Zone: Up For It?">BSL Zone: Up For It? I</n><e>R</e>    <k>Children's series: We meet Mia, Rosie, Nadeem and their dog Twiks. and two mystery guests! Ep 1/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-07-15 12:00:00" d="2019-07-15 14:15:00"><n>Houseboat</n><e>R</e>    <k>Romcom starring Cary Grant and Sophia Loren. An inept single father offers a beautiful Italian woman a job as a maid, which she accepts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-07-15 14:15:00" d="2019-07-15 15:55:00"><n>The Tall Stranger</n><e>R</e>    <k>Western. A Union officer (Joel McCrea), wounded in battle and left for dead, is rescued by a wagon train. Nursed back to health, he offers to guide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-07-15 15:55:00" d="2019-07-15 17:45:00"><n>Run for Cover</n><e>R</e>    <k>Western with James Cagney and John Derek. Two cowboys are made sheriff and deputy by the townsfolk who initially mistook them for armed bandits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-07-15 17:45:00" d="2019-07-15 19:50:00"><n>Master of the World</n><e>R</e>    <k>Sci-fi fantasy starring Vincent Price. A 19th-century scientist flies his airship around the globe, threatening mass destruction from the clouds unless</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-07-15 19:50:00" d="2019-07-15 22:00:00"><n>Hail, Caesar!</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Coen brothers' 1950s-set comedy-drama. A Hollywood fixer sets out to find a star who disappeared during a film shoot. With Josh Brolin, George Clooney</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-07-15 22:00:00" d="2019-07-16 00:25:00"><n>Sicario</n><e>R</e>    <k>Summer of Action: Violent thriller with Emily Blunt, Benicio Del Toro and Josh Brolin. An FBI agent takes part in a mission to disrupt a brutal Mexican drug cartel. Strong language</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-07-16 00:25:00" d="2019-07-16 02:15:00"><n u="Nico">Nico, 1988</n><t>S</t>    <k>67% NIco, 1988
(2017) Drama following the singer Nico in her final years, as she tours Europe, lives in Manchester and struggles with heroin addiction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-07-16 02:15:00" d="2019-07-16 12:00:00"><n>Joe Strummer: The Future Is Unwritten</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>77% Joe Strummer: The Future Is. 
. nwritten: (2007) Documentary. Julien Temple's tribute to Joe Strummer, one of Britain's most influential musicians</k>  </p>
</a>
