<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2019-08-11 01:29:08"><p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-17 12:00:00" d="2019-08-17 13:45:00"><n>Coneheads</n><e>R</e>    <k>Sci-fi comedy with Dan Aykroyd and Jane Curtin. When their spacecraft crashes, two humanoid aliens with bald, pointed heads try to fit into society</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-17 13:45:00" d="2019-08-17 15:35:00"><n>Paddington</n><e>R</e>    <k>Part-animated family fun. Hugh Bonneville, Sally Hawkins and Nicole Kidman star in this adaptation of Michael Bond's tales of the adventures of a small</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-17 15:35:00" d="2019-08-17 17:40:00"><n u="Home Alone">Home Alone 3</n><e>R</e>    <k>Comedy sequel. Alex D Linz stars as a resourceful boy who's stranded at home with chickenpox when a top-secret military microchip comes his way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-17 17:40:00" d="2019-08-17 19:45:00"><n>Volcano</n><e>R</e>    <k>Action-thriller with Tommy Lee Jones, Anne Heche and Don Cheadle. Los Angeles is threatened by an erupting volcano. Can the catastrophe be averted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-17 19:45:00" d="2019-08-17 22:00:00"><n>Bend It Like Beckham</n><e>R</e>    <k>Comedy starring Parminder Nagra and Keira Knightley. A pair of teenage friends join an all-female football team. But Jess's Sikh parents don't approve</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-17 22:00:00" d="2019-08-18 00:20:00"><n u="Spy">Spy (2015)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Spy
(2015) Comedy action-thriller starring Melissa McCarthy. A CIA intelligence officer abandons her desk job to track down a stolen nuclear weapon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-18 00:20:00" d="2019-08-18 02:55:00"><n>The Mortal Instruments: City of Bones</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>60% The Mortal Instruments: City of. 
. ones: (2013) Supernatural fantasy action-adventure starring Lily Collins. A teenager discovers that the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-18 02:55:00" d="2019-08-18 12:00:00"><n>The Windmill Massacre</n><e>R</e>    <k>Gory horror with Charlotte Beaumont, Noah Taylor and Patrick Baladi. A tour of Holland's historic windmills turns into a bloodbath for a group</k>  </p>
</a>
