<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-05-25 04:49:33"><p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-01 09:00:00" d="2020-06-01 12:00:00"><n>BSL Zone: Punk Chef on the Road</n><e>F</e>    <k>Punk Chef Scott Garthwaite travels to Gloucestershire to find top-quality produce. Scott finds inspiration at a service station and meets a pioneering deaf cook</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-01 12:00:00" d="2020-06-01 13:50:00"><n>Hell Below Zero</n><e>R</e>    <k>Thriller with Joan Tetzel and Alan Ladd. When her father is killed, a whaling-boat skipper teams up with a crewman to track the murderer. Whaling footage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-01 13:50:00" d="2020-06-01 16:30:00"><n>A Night to Remember</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Kenneth More stars in director Roy Ward Baker's acclaimed drama about the fateful final night of the RMS Titanic's maiden voyage. With Honor Blackman and Ronald Allen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-01 16:30:00" d="2020-06-01 18:10:00"><n>Hondo</n><e>R</e>    <k>Western starring John Wayne and Geraldine Page. A US cavalryman takes a rancher who's been abandoned by her husband under his wing, protecting her from Apache aggression</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-01 18:10:00" d="2020-06-01 19:55:00"><n>The Weaker Sex</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Ursula Jeans stars in a home front drama that examines the pressures that women were under during World War II and also in the years of austerity that followed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-01 19:55:00" d="2020-06-01 22:00:00"><n>Dante's Peak</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Action thriller starring Pierce Brosnan and Linda Hamilton. A scientist's warning that a volcano is set to erupt is unwisely ignored by the inhabitants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-01 22:00:00" d="2020-06-02 00:25:00"><n>Stargate</n><e>F</e>    <k>James Spader and Kurt Russell go through a Stargate to a distant planet where the evil god Ra (Jaye Davidson), who created humanity, is planning his return</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-02 00:25:00" d="2020-06-02 03:15:00"><n>The Great Beauty</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Tony Servillo stars in Paolo Sorrentino's Oscar-winning comedy-drama about a 65-year-old society journalist looking back on his life with a critical eye</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-02 03:15:00" d="2020-06-02 06:15:00"><n>Little Men</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Drama about two very different 13-year-old boys who become close friends - only for a dispute between their parents to threaten their relationship</k>  </p>
</a>
