<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-04-09 04:32:48"><p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-16 12:00:00" d="2020-04-16 13:50:00"><n>The SpongeBob Movie: Sponge Out...</n><e>R</e>    <k>. f Water: (2015) Surreal animated adventure. When the recipe for Mr Krabs' Krabby Patties vanishes, Bikini Bottom is plunged into anarchy. So SpongeBob</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-16 13:50:00" d="2020-04-16 15:55:00"><n>Mary and the Witch's Flower</n><e>R</e>    <k>Fans of Studio Ghibli will be enchanted by this animated tale about a girl who gains magical powers from a mysterious flower, based on Mary Stewart's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-16 15:55:00" d="2020-04-16 17:40:00"><n>Carry On Nurse</n><e>R</e>    <k>Classic Carry On comedy, with high jinks on a men's surgical ward, where no entendre is left undoubled, starring Kenneth Williams, Hattie Jacques, Leslie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-16 17:40:00" d="2020-04-16 19:50:00"><n>Young Sherlock Holmes</n><e>R</e>    <k>Barry Levinson's scary, darkly Gothic family drama stars Nicholas Rowe and Alan Cox as the young Holmes and Watson, who investigate a series of mysterious and grisly murders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-16 19:50:00" d="2020-04-16 22:00:00"><n>The League of Extraordinary...</n><e>R</e>    <k>. entlemen: (2003) Fantasy with Sean Connery. In an alternative Victorian age, Allan Quatermain, Dorian Gray, Captain Nemo, Mina Harker and the Invisible</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-16 22:00:00" d="2020-04-17 00:20:00"><n>Independence Day: Resurgence</n><e>R</e>    <k>Sci-fi blockbuster sequel starring Jeff Goldblum. Twenty years after Earth repelled a devastating alien invasion, the extraterrestrials return to finish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-17 00:20:00" d="2020-04-17 02:10:00"><n>The Witch</n><e>R</e>    <k>Supernatural horror with Anya Taylor-Joy, Ralph Ineson and Kate Dickie. In 1630s New England a family suffers troubling events after being expelled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-17 02:10:00" d="2020-04-17 05:10:00"><n>A Field in England</n><e>R</e>    <k>Drama. A psychedelic trip into magic and madness during the English Civil War. Starring Michael Smiley and Reece Shearsmith. Nudity/very strong</k>  </p>
</a>
