<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2019-08-10 01:39:09"><p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-16 12:00:00" d="2019-08-16 14:10:00"><n>Congo</n><e>R</e>    <k>Action adventure with Laura Linney. An expedition deep into central Africa encounters dangers that include a troop of intelligent killer apes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-16 14:10:00" d="2019-08-16 16:15:00"><n>Edward Scissorhands</n><e>R</e>    <k>Tim Burton's fantasy drama stars Johnny Depp as a young man who, created but not completed by his inventor (Vincent Price), is left with shears for hands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-16 16:15:00" d="2019-08-16 18:00:00"><n>Shrek Forever After</n><e>R</e>    <k>Animated adventure. In the ogre's fourth feature-length escapade, Shrek makes an unwise bargain with Rumpelstiltskin. With the voices of Mike Myers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-16 18:00:00" d="2019-08-16 20:15:00"><n u="Last Holiday">Last Holiday (2006)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Last Holiday
(2006) Comedy starring Queen Latifah. Diagnosed with a fatal illness, a US woman cashes in her life savings and takes a luxury European holiday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-16 20:15:00" d="2019-08-16 22:00:00"><n>Max Steel</n><e>R</e>    <k>Family sci-fi adventure starring Ben Winchell. A 16-year-old is shocked to discover that he can emit increasingly powerful energy from his fingers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-16 22:00:00" d="2019-08-16 23:50:00"><n>American Ultra</n><e>R</e>    <k>Action-comedy with Jesse Eisenberg and Kristen Stewart. A perpetually stoned slacker learns he's actually a deadly CIA sleeper agent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-16 23:50:00" d="2019-08-17 02:05:00"><n>World War Z</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Tarantino Connection: Horror with Brad Pitt. A retired UN investigator joins an armed research team that's searching for a cure to a virulent zombie plague. Gory violence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-17 02:05:00" d="2019-08-17 05:05:00"><n>Evil Dead</n><e>R</e>    <k>Gory horror. Friends stay in a remote cabin to help one of them (Jane Levy) kick her drug habit. But they accidentally unleash a demonic force</k>  </p>
</a>
