<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2019-08-15 22:31:45"><p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-21 12:00:00" d="2019-08-21 13:50:00"><n>The SpongeBob Movie: Sponge Out...</n><e>RF</e>    <k>. f Water: (2015) Surreal animated adventure. When the recipe for Mr Krabs' Krabby Patties vanishes, Bikini Bottom is plunged into anarchy. So SpongeBob</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-21 13:50:00" d="2019-08-21 15:40:00"><n>A Thousand Words</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Comedy. Eddie Murphy stars as a truth-bending literary agent who finds himself in danger of literally talking himself to death after he's cursed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-21 15:40:00" d="2019-08-21 17:50:00"><n>The Princess Bride</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Fantasy adventure with Cary Elwes and Robin Wright. A lowly farmhand sets out to prove himself worthy of the princess he has fallen in love with</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-21 17:50:00" d="2019-08-21 19:35:00"><n>The Simpsons Movie</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Animated comedy. Homer's love for a pig causes world-threatening pollution and Springfield to be enclosed by a huge dome. D'oh! Will he do the decent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-21 19:35:00" d="2019-08-21 22:00:00"><n>Mrs Doubtfire</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Comedy starring Robin Williams and Sally Field. A failing actor dresses in drag to fool his estranged wife into hiring him as a housekeeper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-21 22:00:00" d="2019-08-21 23:50:00"><n>Sleepless</n><e>F</e>    <k>Violent action-thriller with Jamie Foxx. When a corrupt cop steals a cocaine shipment, it prompts the kidnapping of his son and interest from Internal Affairs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-21 23:50:00" d="2019-08-22 02:00:00"><n u="True Grit">True Grit (2010)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>True Grit
(2010) Western. When a farmer is murdered, his daughter seeks the help of a US Marshal to track down the culprit. With Hailee Steinfeld</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-22 02:00:00" d="2019-08-22 05:00:00"><n>The Midnight Meat Train</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Gory horror starring Bradley Cooper and Vinnie Jones. A New York photographer investigates disappearances on the subway and discovers a serial killer</k>  </p>
</a>
