<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2019-08-15 22:41:46"><p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-22 12:00:00" d="2019-08-22 14:10:00"><n>Edward Scissorhands</n><e>R</e>    <k>Tim Burton's fantasy drama stars Johnny Depp as a young man who, created but not completed by his inventor (Vincent Price), is left with shears for hands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-22 14:10:00" d="2019-08-22 16:10:00"><n>Megamind</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Animated adventure. There are unexpected consequences when a blue-skinned, large-headed alien supervillain outwits and defeats his superhero enemy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-22 16:10:00" d="2019-08-22 18:00:00"><n>How to Train Your Dragon</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Oscar-nominated animation. The young Viking Hiccup and his friend Astrid inhabit a village that lives in fear of fire-breathing dragons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-22 18:00:00" d="2019-08-22 20:05:00"><n>Monster Trucks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Comedy starring Lucas Till and Rob Lowe. A car-obsessed teenager attempts to save three strange creatures after an oil company accidentally frees</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-22 20:05:00" d="2019-08-22 22:00:00"><n>Max Steel</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Family sci-fi adventure starring Ben Winchell. A 16-year-old is shocked to discover that he can emit increasingly powerful energy from his fingers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-22 22:00:00" d="2019-08-22 23:50:00"><n>Stratton</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Action-thriller. Dominic Cooper stars as a Special Boat Service officer who is tasked with tracking down stolen WMDs and preventing a terrorist attack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-22 23:50:00" d="2019-08-23 01:45:00"><n>Crank 2: High Voltage</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Outrageous comedy starring Jason Statham as a hitman with an artificial heart that requires regular electrical kick-starts. Violence/strong, offensive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-23 01:45:00" d="2019-08-23 04:45:00"><n>Bully</n><e>R</e>    <k>Larry Clark's drama stars Brad Renfro and Rachel Milner as teens who plan violent revenge on a bully (Nick Stahl). Adults only: very strong</k>  </p>
</a>
