<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2019-08-13 02:13:04"><p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-19 09:00:00" d="2019-08-19 12:00:00"><n u="BSL Zone: Up For It?">BSL Zone: Up For It? II</n><e>R</e>    <k>Cameron and Zachary show off their triathlon skills. Orion longs to be a TV chef. Plus sketches and VV. Ep 1/2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-19 12:00:00" d="2019-08-19 14:05:00"><n>Short Circuit</n><e>R</e>    <k>Family sci-fi comedy-adventure. When a military robot is struck by lightning it gains the power of independent thought, begins to develop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-19 14:05:00" d="2019-08-19 15:40:00"><n>Garfield 2: A Tale of Two Kitties</n><e>R</e>    <k>Part-animated family comedy. Garfield (voiced by Bill Murray) inherits a stately home in England, to the fury of an evil aristocrat (Billy Connolly)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-19 15:40:00" d="2019-08-19 17:40:00"><n>Baby's Day Out</n><e>R</e>    <k>Comedy starring Joe Mantegna, Joe Pantoliano and Brian Haley. Inept criminals kidnap a millionaire's baby. But when the boy escapes, there's mayhem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-19 17:40:00" d="2019-08-19 19:55:00"><n>Big Eyes</n><e>R</e>    <k>Amy Adams stars in Tim Burton's fact-based drama about the US artist Margaret Keane. A single mother meets a man who enthusiastically promotes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-19 19:55:00" d="2019-08-19 22:00:00"><n>X-Men: The Last Stand</n><e>R</e>    <k>Fantasy adventure. The X-Men face a new threat: the development of an enforced cure for mutants. Starring Famke Janssen, Halle Berry, Ian McKellen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-19 22:00:00" d="2019-08-20 00:15:00"><n>RED</n><e>R</e>    <k>Comedy thriller. Bruce Willis stars as a retired CIA hitman who knows too much about their operations and is targeted for elimination. With Helen Mirren</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-20 00:15:00" d="2019-08-20 02:00:00"><n>Paranormal Activity: The Ghost Dimension</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>46% 
. imension: (2015)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-20 02:00:00" d="2019-08-20 05:00:00"><n>Adore</n><e>R</e>    <k>Romantic drama starring Naomi Watts, Robin Wright, Xavier Samuel and James Frecheville. Two lifelong female friends start relationships with each other's sons</k>  </p>
</a>
