<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2019-08-13 02:13:02"><p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-18 12:00:00" d="2019-08-18 13:55:00"><n>Megamind</n><e>R</e>    <k>Animated adventure. There are unexpected consequences when a blue-skinned, large-headed alien supervillain outwits and defeats his superhero enemy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-18 13:55:00" d="2019-08-18 15:45:00"><n>How to Train Your Dragon</n><e>R</e>    <k>Oscar-nominated animation. The young Viking Hiccup and his friend Astrid inhabit a village that lives in fear of fire-breathing dragons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-18 15:45:00" d="2019-08-18 17:55:00"><n>Monster Trucks</n><e>R</e>    <k>Comedy starring Lucas Till and Rob Lowe. A car-obsessed teenager attempts to save three strange creatures after an oil company accidentally frees</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-18 17:55:00" d="2019-08-18 20:00:00"><n>Night at the Museum: Secret of the Tomb</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>63% Night at the Museum: Secret of. 
. he Tomb: (2014) Ben Stiller stars in the third part of the adventure comedy franchise. Larry the nightwatchman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-18 20:00:00" d="2019-08-18 22:00:00"><n>X-Men</n><e>R</e>    <k>Violent superhero fantasy starring Patrick Stewart and Ian McKellen. Superpowered mutants fight over whether to control or co-exist with regular humans. With Hugh Jackman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-18 22:00:00" d="2019-08-19 00:05:00"><n>Solace</n><e>R</e>    <k>Thriller starring Anthony Hopkins. A psychic former FBI analyst joins the hunt to catch a serial killer who also has psychic powers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-19 00:05:00" d="2019-08-19 01:50:00"><n>I, Frankenstein</n><e>R</e>    <k>Action fantasy with Aaron Eckhart, Bill Nighy and Miranda Otto. Dr Frankenstein's creation is caught between the demons and the gargoyles in a battle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-19 01:50:00" d="2019-08-19 09:00:00"><n>Night Moves</n><e>R</e>    <k>Drama starring Jesse Eisenberg, Dakota Fanning and Peter Sarsgaard. Three people take violent action to stop the environmental damage caused by a local dam</k>  </p>
</a>
