<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-04-10 04:33:47"><p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-17 12:00:00" d="2020-04-17 13:50:00"><n>The Three Stooges</n><e>R</e>    <k>Comedy recreating classic anarchic slapstick from the 1940s and 50s. Three brothers try to save the orphanage that raised them. Do not try to copy these</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-17 13:50:00" d="2020-04-17 15:25:00"><n>Garfield 2: A Tale of Two Kitties</n><e>R</e>    <k>Part-animated family comedy. Garfield (voiced by Bill Murray) inherits a stately home in England, to the fury of an evil aristocrat (Billy Connolly)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-17 15:25:00" d="2020-04-17 17:30:00"><n>Rise of the Guardians</n><e>R</e>    <k>Animated adventure with Alec Baldwin and Hugh Jackman. When evil spirit Pitch taints the dreams of Earth's children, the Guardians, including Santa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-17 17:30:00" d="2020-04-17 19:20:00"><n>Before We Go</n><e>R</e>    <k>Drama. Chris Evans directs and stars alongside Alice Eve in a story about two strangers who become confidantes after a chance meeting one night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-17 19:20:00" d="2020-04-17 22:00:00"><n>X-Men: Days of Future Past</n><e>R</e>    <k>Violent action fantasy. In a post-apocalyptic future, mutants are being hunted to extinction by giant robots, so Wolverine's consciousness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-17 22:00:00" d="2020-04-18 00:20:00"><n>Four Weddings and a Funeral</n><e>R</e>    <k>Drama. Hugh Grant and Andie MacDowell star as people who should obviously be a couple, but who only meet at weddings and funerals. Contains strong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-18 00:20:00" d="2020-04-18 02:30:00"><n>Border</n>    <k>Fantasy drama. A border patrolwoman with heightened senses believes herself alone until she meets someone just like her. Adults only:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-18 02:30:00" d="2020-04-18 05:30:00"><n>Sightseers</n><e>R</e>    <k>Dark comedy-drama. An innocent tour of Britain's countryside turns into a disturbing odyssey for two lovers (Alice Lowe and Steve Oram). Sex/drugs/strong</k>  </p>
</a>
