<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-04-15 04:27:42"><p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-22 12:00:00" d="2020-04-22 14:15:00"><n>Houseboat</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Romcom starring Cary Grant and Sophia Loren. An inept single father offers a beautiful Italian woman a job as a maid, which she accepts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-22 14:15:00" d="2020-04-22 16:00:00"><n>Carry On Nurse</n><e>R</e>    <k>Classic Carry On comedy, with high jinks on a men's surgical ward, where no entendre is left undoubled, starring Kenneth Williams, Hattie Jacques, Leslie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-22 16:00:00" d="2020-04-22 17:50:00"><n>All That Heaven Allows</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Romantic drama with Jane Wyman and Rock Hudson. A wealthy widow decides to restart her life. But her children and her social set disapprove of her lover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-22 17:50:00" d="2020-04-22 19:45:00"><n>Baggage Claim</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Romcom starring Paula Patton. A flight attendant desperately tries to find herself a husband before her younger sister gets married. With Derek Luke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-22 19:45:00" d="2020-04-22 22:00:00"><n>Wonder</n><e>F</e>    <k>Heart-warming drama starring Julia Roberts. A young boy with an extensive facial deformity gets to grips with the outside world as he attends middle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-22 22:00:00" d="2020-04-23 00:35:00"><n>Midnight Run</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Action comedy. Robert De Niro stars as a bounty hunter transporting a criminal from New York to Los Angeles with the FBI and the mob on their tail. Strong language</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-23 00:35:00" d="2020-04-23 02:40:00"><n>Ashby</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Comedy drama with Mickey Rourke, Nat Wolff, Emma Roberts and Sarah Silverman. A high-school student discovers that his neighbour was once a CIA hitman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-23 02:40:00" d="2020-04-23 05:40:00"><n>Kaleidoscope</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Unsettling and enigmatic psychological thriller. Toby Jones plays a man confronted by a shocking sight in his flat. With Anne Reid and Sinead Matthews</k>  </p>
</a>
