<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2021-07-09 06:57:14"><p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-14 12:00:00" d="2021-07-14 14:15:00"><n>Esther Waters</n><e>R</e>    <k>Period melodrama with Kathleen Ryan. After a tough childhood, Esther is sent away to become a maid, but gets pregnant when seduced by a servant (Dirk Bogarde)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-14 14:15:00" d="2021-07-14 16:10:00"><n>Last Train from Gun Hill</n><e>R</e>    <k>Kirk Douglas and Anthony Quinn star in John Sturges's western. A US Marshal sets out to arrest the men who raped and murdered his wife - only to discover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-14 16:10:00" d="2021-07-14 17:55:00"><n>The Red Pony</n><e>R</e>    <k>Drama. Peter Miles plays a lonely farm boy who takes refuge from his squabbling parents in his love for a beautiful red foal. Based on John Steinbeck's stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-14 17:55:00" d="2021-07-14 19:50:00"><n>The Rare Breed</n><e>R</e>    <k>Western with Maureen O'Hara and James Stewart. With the help of a drifter, a woman strives to fulfil her dead husband's desire to introduce rare cattle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-14 19:50:00" d="2021-07-14 22:00:00"><n>The Maze Runner</n><e>R</e>    <k>Intense, scary dystopian action-thriller. Teenagers are imprisoned in a large forest glade surrounded by a high-walled maze that's home to fearsome beasts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-14 22:00:00" d="2021-07-15 00:40:00"><n>The Hate U Give</n>    <k>Drama with Amanda Stenberg. A young Black woman's friend is killed after they are pulled over. Can she speak out against the police? Violence/strong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-15 00:40:00" d="2021-07-15 02:55:00"><n>Total Recall</n><e>R</e>    <k>Violent sci-fi remake starring Colin Farrell as a factory worker who has fake memories implanted of life as a spy. But it turns out he really</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-15 02:55:00" d="2021-07-15 05:55:00"><n>Goat</n><e>R</e>    <k>Ben Schnetzer and Nick Jonas star as brothers in a fact-based drama about the brutality and toxic machismo of US college fraternities</k>  </p>
</a>
