<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2021-07-08 05:00:49"><p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-13 12:00:00" d="2021-07-13 14:10:00"><n>Tiger Bay</n><e>R</e>    <k>Drama with John Mills, Horst Buchholz and Hayley Mills. A policeman's attempt to catch a killer is hampered when a girl who witnessed the homicide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-13 14:10:00" d="2021-07-13 15:55:00"><n>Appointment with Danger</n><e>R</e>    <k>Noir thriller starring Alan Ladd, Phyllis Calvert and Paul Stewart. A postal inspector infiltrates a gang planning a huge heist. But he must also protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-13 15:55:00" d="2021-07-13 17:45:00"><n>The Black Tent</n><e>R</e>    <k>World War II drama. Anthony Steel stars as a British soldier who disappears while fighting in Libya. Donald Sinden plays his brother, who travels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-13 17:45:00" d="2021-07-13 19:40:00"><n>The Far Country</n><e>R</e>    <k>Western starring James Stewart. A self-centred drover looks to buy a ranch in Alaska during the 1896 Klondike gold rush but runs into problems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-13 19:40:00" d="2021-07-13 22:00:00"><n>The Second Best Exotic Marigold...</n><e>R</e>    <k>. otel: (2015) Comedy drama sequel set in India. Sonny and Muriel want to open a second hotel for western retirees. With Dev Patel, Maggie Smith, Richard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-13 22:00:00" d="2021-07-14 00:25:00"><n>Miss Peregrine's Home for...</n><e>R</e>    <k>. eculiar Children: (2016) Eva Green and Asa Butterfield star in Tim Burton's fantasy adventure. A teenager enters the magical, but scary and violent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-14 00:25:00" d="2021-07-14 02:35:00"><n>Beast</n><e>R</e>    <k>BAFTA-winning drama starring Jessie Buckley. A fragile young woman begins a potentially dangerous relationship with an outsider. Disturbing violence/some strong language</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-14 02:35:00" d="2021-07-14 05:35:00"><n>The Endless</n><e>R</e>    <k>Hypnotic sci-fi thriller. Struggling with real life, two brothers return to a 'UFO death cult' that they escaped years before. Was it really so bad? Strong language/self-harm/drugs</k>  </p>
</a>
