<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2021-07-09 06:57:20"><p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-16 12:00:00" d="2021-07-16 14:05:00"><n>The Blue Dahlia</n><e>R</e>    <k>Classic noir thriller. A man returns home after WWII to find his wife's been unfaithful. When she's murdered, he turns detective. Language and attitudes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-16 14:05:00" d="2021-07-16 15:40:00"><n>The Duel at Silver Creek</n><e>R</e>    <k>Western starring Audie Murphy, Stephen McNally, Faith Domergue and Susan Cabot. A gunslinger and a marshal join forces to hunt a violent gang of claim jumpers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-16 15:40:00" d="2021-07-16 17:25:00"><n>Texas Lady</n><e>R</e>    <k>Claudette Colbert plays the new newspaper proprietor in a tough Texan town whose crusade against crooked cattle barons makes her a vulnerable target</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-16 17:25:00" d="2021-07-16 19:05:00"><n>Sword of Sherwood Forest</n><e>R</e>    <k>Adventure with Richard Greene, Peter Cushing and a young Oliver Reed. Can Robin Hood foil the villainous Sheriff of Nottingham's evil plan to murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-16 19:05:00" d="2021-07-16 22:00:00"><n>Transformers: Revenge of the...</n><e>R</e>    <k>. allen: (2009) Raucous, violent sci-fi action sequel in which a couple (Shia LaBeouf and Megan Fox) must try to prevent the Decepticon robots</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-16 22:00:00" d="2021-07-17 00:50:00"><n>X-Men: Apocalypse</n><e>R</e>    <k>Action fantasy sequel. Can Charles Xavier and his young mutants prevent god-like Apocalypse and his allies from destroying the world? With James McAvoy and Oscar Isaac</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-17 00:50:00" d="2021-07-17 03:00:00"><n>The Purge: Election Year</n><e>R</e>    <k>Gory horror-thriller starring Elizabeth Mitchell. In the third chapter of the dystopian tale, a senator attempts to stop the night of slaughter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-17 03:00:00" d="2021-07-17 06:00:00"><n>Feedback</n><e>R</e>    <k>Thriller with Eddie Marsan. A radio talk show host is taken hostage before going live on air. He must broadcast, but the script will not be his</k>  </p>
</a>
