<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-05-12 04:34:34"><p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-19 12:00:00" d="2020-05-19 13:40:00"><n>Three Faces West</n><e>R</e>    <k>Western starring Charles Coburn, Sigrid Gurie and John Wayne. An Austrian doctor and his daughter flee the Nazis to America, before a natural disaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-19 13:40:00" d="2020-05-19 15:25:00"><n>The Million Pound Note</n><e>R</e>    <k>Comedy. A penniless sailor (Gregory Peck) is given a ?1,000,000 note, but is told he must not spend it. Will just showing it to people give him enough</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-19 15:25:00" d="2020-05-19 17:35:00"><n>Tiger Bay</n><e>R</e>    <k>Drama with John Mills, Horst Buchholz and Hayley Mills. A policeman's attempt to catch a killer is hampered when a girl who witnessed the homicide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-19 17:35:00" d="2020-05-19 19:40:00"><n>The Lady Vanishes</n><e>R</e>    <k>Elliott Gould and Cybill Shepherd star in this remake of Hitchcock's thriller as two people who are thrown into a world of political intrigue on a train in pre-war Germany</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-19 19:40:00" d="2020-05-19 22:00:00"><n>Warcraft</n><e>R</e>    <k>Fantasy adventure. The planet Azeroth - a peaceful, magical world where humans co-exist with mythological beings - is invaded by a horde of orcs. Violence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-19 22:00:00" d="2020-05-20 00:00:00"><n>The Grand Budapest Hotel</n><e>R</e>    <k>Ralph Fiennes and Tony Revolori star in Wes Anderson's comedy-drama about a man's youthful misadventures, and how he came to own a hotel. Strong language/violence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-20 00:00:00" d="2020-05-20 02:10:00"><n>My Friend Dahmer</n><e>R</e>    <k>Ross Lynch portrays serial killer Jeffrey Dahmer at high school in this biographical drama based on John 'Derf' Backderf's graphic novel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-20 02:10:00" d="2020-05-20 05:10:00"><n>Mona Lisa</n><e>R</e>    <k>Crime drama starring Bob Hoskins and Cathy Tyson. An ex-con is hired to guard a high-class prostitute. But they're both soon in danger. Strong, offensive</k>  </p>
</a>
