<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2021-07-13 04:50:42"><p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-20 12:00:00" d="2021-07-20 13:50:00"><n>The Black Tent</n><e>RF</e>    <k>World War II drama. Anthony Steel stars as a British soldier who disappears while fighting in Libya. Donald Sinden plays his brother, who travels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-20 13:50:00" d="2021-07-20 16:00:00"><n>Esther Waters</n><e>R</e>    <k>Period melodrama with Kathleen Ryan. After a tough childhood, Esther is sent away to become a maid, but gets pregnant when seduced by a servant (Dirk Bogarde)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-20 16:00:00" d="2021-07-20 17:55:00"><n>The Rare Breed</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Western with Maureen O'Hara and James Stewart. With the help of a drifter, a woman strives to fulfil her dead husband's desire to introduce rare cattle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-20 17:55:00" d="2021-07-20 19:45:00"><n>The Hound of the Baskervilles</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Classic version of Arthur Conan Doyle's scary Gothic mystery. Peter Cushing is Sherlock Holmes, investigating a chilling death on Dartmoor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-20 19:45:00" d="2021-07-20 22:00:00"><n>The Imitation Game</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Benedict Cumberbatch's Oscar-nominated role as Alan Turing, the socially awkward mathematician, WWII codebreaker, father of the modern computer and demonised homosexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-20 22:00:00" d="2021-07-21 00:40:00"><n>Maze Runner: The Scorch Trials</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Young adult sci-fi thriller sequel starring Dylan O'Brien, Kaya Scodelario and Aidan Gillen. The young abductees face more dark threats and another</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-21 00:40:00" d="2021-07-21 03:15:00"><n>Snowpiercer</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Violent sci-fi thriller with Chris Evans. Survivors from a global disaster take refuge on a train with a severely defined class system. But the oppressed will rebel. Strong language</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-21 03:15:00" d="2021-07-21 06:15:00"><n>The Guilty</n><e>F</e>    <k>Crime drama. Jakob Cedergren stars as a troubled cop confined to the office who finds himself in a race against time to help a distressed woman. Danish/subs. Strong language</k>  </p>
</a>
