<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-04-11 04:32:45"><p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-18 12:00:00" d="2020-04-18 13:40:00"><n>Rugrats Go Wild</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Family animation. The children and their parents get stranded on a desert island. But help is at hand from the Thornberry family, who travel the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-18 13:40:00" d="2020-04-18 15:45:00"><n>Hotel for Dogs</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Family comedy starring Emma Roberts and Jake T Austin. A neglected teenager and her brother secretly set up a refuge for stray dogs in an abandoned building</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-18 15:45:00" d="2020-04-18 17:40:00"><n>Shrek the Third</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Mike Myers' animated ogre returns. When Shrek's in danger of becoming king, he enlists Donkey (Eddie Murphy) and Puss in Boots (Antonio Banderas) to get him out of it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-18 17:40:00" d="2020-04-18 19:50:00"><n>The Rewrite</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Romcom with Hugh Grant, Marisa Tomei and Bella Heathcote. When his movie career stalls, an Oscar-winning screenwriter takes a university teaching job</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-18 19:50:00" d="2020-04-18 22:00:00"><n>The League of Extraordinary...</n><e>RF</e>    <k>. entlemen: (2003) Fantasy with Sean Connery. In an alternative Victorian age, Allan Quatermain, Dorian Gray, Captain Nemo, Mina Harker and the Invisible</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-18 22:00:00" d="2020-04-19 00:10:00"><n>Assassin's Creed</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Sci-fi action-thriller with Michael Fassbender. A modern-day American is transported back to 15th-century Spain to help the Knights Templar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-19 00:10:00" d="2020-04-19 01:55:00"><n>Blair Witch</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Supernatural horror sequel. Twenty years after her disappearance, Heather's brother James investigates eerie online footage of someone resembling her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-04-19 01:55:00" d="2020-04-19 12:00:00"><n>Thelma</n><e>R</e>    <k>Supernatural thriller. A young woman discovers she has worrying powers that endanger those closest to her. In Norwegian/subs. Sex/very strong</k>  </p>
</a>
