<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2019-08-13 02:13:07"><p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-20 12:00:00" d="2019-08-20 13:35:00"><n>Rugrats Go Wild</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Family animation. The children and their parents get stranded on a desert island. But help is at hand from the Thornberry family, who travel the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-20 13:35:00" d="2019-08-20 15:25:00"><n>The Boxtrolls</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Oscar-nominated animation. Grotesque and badly behaved (but harmless) trolls living below a hilltop town face extermination by its inhabitants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-20 15:25:00" d="2019-08-20 17:35:00"><n>Young Sherlock Holmes</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Barry Levinson's scary, darkly Gothic family drama stars Nicholas Rowe and Alan Cox as the young Holmes and Watson, who investigate a series of mysterious and grisly murders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-20 17:35:00" d="2019-08-20 19:45:00"><n>Splash</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Family fantasy romance starring Darryl Hannah and Tom Hanks. A mermaid falls in love with a man after twice saving him from drowning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-20 19:45:00" d="2019-08-20 22:00:00"><n u="Crocodile Dundee">Crocodile Dundee II</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Comedy. Paul Hogan returns as Mick 'Crocodile' Dundee, who uses his bushcraft skills to save his journalist girlfriend (Linda Kozlowski) when she's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-20 22:00:00" d="2019-08-21 00:10:00"><n>Deadpool</n>    <k>Action-comedy with Ryan Reynolds. A wisecracking ex-soldier seeks vengeance against the mutants who gave him superhuman powers. Not for children</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-21 00:10:00" d="2019-08-21 02:00:00"><n>American Ultra</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Action-comedy with Jesse Eisenberg and Kristen Stewart. A perpetually stoned slacker learns he's actually a deadly CIA sleeper agent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-08-21 02:00:00" d="2019-08-21 05:00:00"><n>Bad Lieutenant: Port of Call New Orleans</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% 
. ew Orleans: (2009)</k>  </p>
</a>
