<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-05-15 04:53:02"><p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-22 12:00:00" d="2020-05-22 13:50:00"><n>Sorry, Wrong Number</n><e>R</e>    <k>Noir thriller starring Barbara Stanwyck and Burt Lancaster. A wealthy bedridden woman is trapped alone in her apartment when she overhears a murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-22 13:50:00" d="2020-05-22 15:55:00"><n>Destroyer</n><e>R</e>    <k>Second World War drama about a warship assigned to mail runs but that ends up engaged in battle anyway, starring Edward G Robinson, Glenn Ford and Marguerite Chapman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-22 15:55:00" d="2020-05-22 18:00:00"><n>The Malta Story</n><e>R</e>    <k>Second World War drama. Alec Guinness plays an RAF reconnaissance pilot in this tribute to the people and defenders of the besieged island of Malta</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-22 18:00:00" d="2020-05-22 19:55:00"><n>40 Guns to Apache Pass</n><e>R</e>    <k>Western starring Audie Murphy. A cavalry captain tries to protect a wagon train and a shipment of rifles from the Apaches. But he faces treachery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-22 19:55:00" d="2020-05-22 22:00:00"><n u="Home Alone">Home Alone 3</n><e>R</e>    <k>Comedy sequel. Alex D Linz stars as a resourceful boy who's stranded at home with chickenpox when a top-secret military microchip comes his way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-22 22:00:00" d="2020-05-23 01:20:00"><n>Heat</n><e>R</e>    <k>Al Pacino and Robert De Niro star in Michael Mann's crime thriller. A cop sets out to track down a career criminal and his gang of armed robbers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-23 01:20:00" d="2020-05-23 03:10:00"><n>Momentum</n><e>R</e>    <k>Brutally violent adult thriller with Olga Kurylenko, Morgan Freeman and James Purefoy. A thief gets caught up in a deadly conspiracy. Very strong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-23 03:10:00" d="2020-05-23 06:10:00"><n>Last Night</n><e>R</e>    <k>Drama. There are just six hours left until the end of the world and Toronto's citizens must decide how they will spend them. With David Cronenberg and Sandra Oh. Strong Language</k>  </p>
</a>
