<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2019-07-11 00:18:50"><p id_tv="1001" o="2019-07-16 12:00:00" d="2019-07-16 14:25:00"><n u="Stalag">Stalag 17</n><e>R</e>    <k>Classic prisoner of war comedy-drama. Oscar-winning William Holden stars as an opportunistic American POW suspected of spying for the Germans. Directed by Billy Wilder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-07-16 14:25:00" d="2019-07-16 16:00:00"><n>Sword of Sherwood Forest</n><e>R</e>    <k>Adventure. A reworking of the exploits of the legendary outlaw Robin Hood (Richard Greene), who foils the villainous Sheriff of Nottingham (Peter Cushing)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-07-16 16:00:00" d="2019-07-16 17:40:00"><n>The Great Sioux Uprising</n><e>R</e>    <k>Western starring Jeff Chandler. An ex-army doctor arrives at a frontier outpost and walks straight into a conflict between Native Americans and the town's horse traders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-07-16 17:40:00" d="2019-07-16 19:50:00"><n>Mysterious Island</n><e>R</e>    <k>Sci-fi adventure based on Jules Verne's novel. Two men fleeing the US Civil War find an island inhabited by monsters (animated by Ray Harryhausen)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-07-16 19:50:00" d="2019-07-16 22:00:00"><n>Risen</n><e>R</e>    <k>Biblical drama with Joseph Fiennes. A Roman legionary officer is ordered to find the missing body of the crucified Yeshua, who is rumoured to be a Jewish messiah. Violence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-07-16 22:00:00" d="2019-07-16 23:50:00"><n u="Commando">Commando (1985)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Commando
(1985) Summer of Action: Violent thriller starring Arnold Schwarzenegger. To free his kidnapped daughter, an ex US commando agrees</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-07-16 23:50:00" d="2019-07-17 01:50:00"><n u="Bad Neighbours">Bad Neighbours 2</n><e>R</e>    <k>Crude comedy sequel with Seth Rogen, Rose Byrne and Chloë Grace Moretz. A couple want to sell their home when a riotous sorority rents the house next door</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2019-07-17 01:50:00" d="2019-07-17 04:50:00"><n>The Best Man Holiday</n><e>R</e>    <k>Comedy-drama sequel with Taye Diggs, Sanaa Lathan, Morris Chestnut and Monica Calhoun. A group of old friends reunite for an eventful Christmas celebration</k>  </p>
</a>
