<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-05-16 04:51:33"><p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-23 12:00:00" d="2020-05-23 13:35:00"><n>Arthur's Hallowed Ground</n><e>R</e>    <k>Comedy drama. Jimmy Jewell stars as a cricket groundsman whose dream is to produce a pitch of billiard-table perfection. But he finds himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-23 13:35:00" d="2020-05-23 15:40:00"><n>Hotel for Dogs</n><e>R</e>    <k>Family comedy starring Emma Roberts and Jake T Austin. A neglected teenager and her brother secretly set up a refuge for stray dogs in an abandoned building</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-23 15:40:00" d="2020-05-23 17:40:00"><n>A Dog's Purpose</n><e>R</e>    <k>Lasse Hallström's comedy drama about the adventures of a dog who gets reincarnated as different breeds and has many different owners over the decades</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-23 17:40:00" d="2020-05-23 19:55:00"><n>Chasing Mavericks</n><e>R</e>    <k>Jonny Weston and Gerard Butler star in this fact based drama about surfing and coming of age in California. Also starring Elisabeth Shue and Leven Rambin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-23 19:55:00" d="2020-05-23 22:00:00"><n>Non-Stop</n><e>R</e>    <k>Action thriller with Liam Neeson, Julianne Moore, Scoot McNairy and Michelle Dockery. A terrorist threatens to murder passengers on a transatlantic flight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-23 22:00:00" d="2020-05-24 01:40:00"><n>The Green Mile</n><e>R</e>    <k>Drama. Tom Hanks stars as a prison warder who takes charge of a death row prisoner with mysterious healing powers. Violence/strong language/scenes viewers may find upsetting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-24 01:40:00" d="2020-05-24 03:20:00"><n>Slow West</n><e>R</e>    <k>Violent offbeat western starring Kodi Smit-McPhee and Michael Fassbender. A 16-year-old Scottish lad travels to 1870s Colorado on the trail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-24 03:20:00" d="2020-05-24 12:00:00"><n>A Young Man with High Potential</n><e>R</e>    <k>Thriller. Two IT students collaborate on an assignment. But things turn dark when she rebuffs his romantic advances. Adults only: sexual violence/graphic</k>  </p>
</a>
