<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-05-13 04:34:39"><p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-20 12:00:00" d="2020-05-20 14:25:00"><n>The Professionals</n><e>R</e>    <k>Action-packed western. Burt Lancaster, Lee Marvin, Robert Ryan and Woody Strode star as soldiers of fortune hired by a wealthy rancher (Ralph Bellamy)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-20 14:25:00" d="2020-05-20 16:45:00"><n>How Green Was My Valley</n><e>R</e>    <k>Walter Pidgeon, Maureen O'Hara and Roddy McDowall star in John Ford's multi-Oscar-winning period drama set in the mining communities of the South Wales</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-20 16:45:00" d="2020-05-20 16:55:00"><n>The Martian Interview Special</n><e>R</e>    <k>Director Ridley Scott talks about making his science-fiction survival adventure starring Matt Damon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-20 16:55:00" d="2020-05-20 19:10:00"><n>Gallipoli</n><e>R</e>    <k>First World War drama. Mel Gibson and Mark Lee star as two young Australian soldiers caught up in the disastrous, bloody attack on Turkish positions at Gallipoli</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-20 19:10:00" d="2020-05-20 21:50:00"><n>A Beautiful Mind</n><e>R</e>    <k>Russell Crowe stars in the multi-Oscar-winning biopic of John Nash, the mathematician who battled paranoid schizophrenia and won the Nobel Prize in Economics. Upsetting scenes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-20 21:50:00" d="2020-05-20 22:00:00"><n>The Martian Interview Special</n><e>R</e>    <k>Director Ridley Scott talks about making his science-fiction survival adventure starring Matt Damon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-20 22:00:00" d="2020-05-21 00:45:00"><n>The Martian</n><e>R</e>    <k>Matt Damon stars in Ridley Scott's drama about a NASA astronaut who's left behind on Mars when his mission is aborted and his crewmates think</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-21 00:45:00" d="2020-05-21 02:35:00"><n>The Daughter</n>    <k>Geoffrey Rush leads an ensemble cast in Simon Stone's drama about a secret that threatens to tear a family apart years later, based on Ibsen's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-05-21 02:35:00" d="2020-05-21 05:35:00"><n>The Possibilities Are Endless</n><e>R</e>    <k>A moving, impressionistic documentary about how singer Edwyn Collins and his wife Grace Maxwell put his life back together after he suffered</k>  </p>
</a>
