<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-05-29 04:35:48"><p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-05 12:00:00" d="2020-06-05 13:45:00"><n>The Weaker Sex</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Ursula Jeans stars in a home front drama that examines the pressures that women were under during World War II and also in the years of austerity that followed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-05 13:45:00" d="2020-06-05 15:50:00"><n>The Fighting Seabees</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Drama. John Wayne stars in this wartime tribute to the US Navy's Construction Battalions and their role in defeating the Japanese in the Pacific</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-05 15:50:00" d="2020-06-05 17:55:00"><n>Track of the Cat</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Western with Robert Mitchum. In 1880s northern California, an isolated, dysfunctional family find their lives changed forever when a mountain lion starts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-05 17:55:00" d="2020-06-05 19:50:00"><n>The Naked Jungle</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Drama starring Charlton Heston and Eleanor Parker. The owner of a cocoa plantation and his mail-order bride are threatened by an immense</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-05 19:50:00" d="2020-06-05 22:00:00"><n>27 Dresses</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Romcom. Katherine Heigl stars as an amateur wedding planner who thinks she'll be the blushing bride one day soon, until her sister steals the man she's got her eye on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-05 22:00:00" d="2020-06-05 23:45:00"><n>The Take</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Violent thriller with Idris Elba, Richard Madden and Charlotte Le Bon. A pickpocket, an anti-fascist and a CIA agent uncover a conspiracy in Paris</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-05 23:45:00" d="2020-06-06 01:50:00"><n>Punisher: War Zone</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Ray Stevenson is Marvel anti-hero Punisher taking on Dominic West, who relishes playing the wise guy turned arch-nemesis Jigsaw in this gory, violent thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-06 01:50:00" d="2020-06-06 04:50:00"><n u="Kill Zone">Kill Zone 2</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Martial arts action-thriller. A Hong Kong cop investigates a gang trafficking human organs. In Mandarin/Cantonese/Thai/English subs</k>  </p>
</a>
