<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2021-07-09 06:57:17"><p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-15 12:00:00" d="2021-07-15 13:55:00"><n>Timberjack</n><e>R</e>    <k>Joseph Kane's western with Sterling Hayden as Tim Chipman, an honest lumberman who returns home to avenge the murder of his father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-15 13:55:00" d="2021-07-15 16:05:00"><n>The Furies</n><e>R</e>    <k>Barbara Stanwyck and Walter Huston star in Anthony Mann's western. A clash between a self-made cattle baron and his equally strong-willed daughter leads to tragedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-15 16:05:00" d="2021-07-15 17:50:00"><n>The Hound of the Baskervilles</n><e>R</e>    <k>Classic version of Arthur Conan Doyle's scary Gothic mystery. Peter Cushing is Sherlock Holmes, investigating a chilling death on Dartmoor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-15 17:50:00" d="2021-07-15 19:35:00"><n>Carry On Spying</n><e>R</e>    <k>Comedy with Kenneth Williams, Bernard Cribbins, Charles Hawtrey and Barbara Windsor. An undercover agent and his bumbling trainees are sent to track</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-15 19:35:00" d="2021-07-15 22:00:00"><n>The Imitation Game</n><e>R</e>    <k>Benedict Cumberbatch's Oscar-nominated role as Alan Turing, the socially awkward mathematician, WWII codebreaker, father of the modern computer and demonised homosexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-15 22:00:00" d="2021-07-16 00:55:00"><n>Mission: Impossible - Fallout</n><e>R</e>    <k>Tom Cruise stars in part six of the action-thriller series. Ethan Hunt and his team attempt to stop a terrorist cell from acquiring several easily</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-16 00:55:00" d="2021-07-16 02:55:00"><n>Prospect</n><e>R</e>    <k>Sci-fi thriller starring Sophie Thatcher, Jay Duplass and Pedro Pascal. A father and daughter run into trouble while prospecting for gems on a forested alien planet. Violence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2021-07-16 02:55:00" d="2021-07-16 05:55:00"><n>Fire Will Come</n>    <k>Oliver Laxe's psychological drama follows the story of Amador, a convicted arsonist, as he returns home from prison to his small community. Galician and Spanish/subs</k>  </p>
</a>
