<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-05-26 04:35:47"><p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-02 12:00:00" d="2020-06-02 13:50:00"><n>The Sound of Fury</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Film noir starring Frank Lovejoy and Lloyd Bridges. When two down-and-outs murderously bungle a kidnap plot and end up in prison, a newspaper dangerously</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-02 13:50:00" d="2020-06-02 16:15:00"><n u="Stalag">Stalag 17</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Classic prisoner of war comedy-drama. Oscar-winning William Holden stars as an opportunistic American POW suspected of spying for the Germans. Directed by Billy Wilder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-02 16:15:00" d="2020-06-02 18:05:00"><n>The Black Tent</n><e>R</e>    <k>World War II drama. Anthony Steel stars as a British soldier who disappears while fighting in Libya. Donald Sinden plays his brother, who travels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-02 18:05:00" d="2020-06-02 19:45:00"><n>Death Drums Along the River</n><e>R</e>    <k>Thriller. Richard Todd stars as Inspector Sanders, a colonial policeman investigating diamond smuggling and murder in West Africa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-02 19:45:00" d="2020-06-02 22:00:00"><n>G.I. Joe: The Rise of Cobra</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Violent action-adventure with Channing Tatum, Sienna Miller and Christopher Eccleston. Terrorists steal a devastating weapon and only the USA's finest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-02 22:00:00" d="2020-06-03 00:15:00"><n>American Made</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Tom Cruise stars in Doug Liman's comedy thriller charting the improbable but true story of an airline pilot who ends up working undercover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-03 00:15:00" d="2020-06-03 02:20:00"><n>Alone in Berlin</n><e>RF</e>    <k>WWII drama with Emma Thompson and Brendan Gleeson. After their son is killed in battle, a German couple start to leave postcards around Berlin denouncing the Nazi regime. Violence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1001" o="2020-06-03 02:20:00" d="2020-06-03 05:20:00"><n>Devil's Knot</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Colin Firth and Reese Witherspoon star in a fact-based drama about a triple child murder in Arkansas. With James Hamrick, Seth Meriwether</k>  </p>
</a>
