<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2020-05-16 04:55:20"><p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 05:00:00" d="2020-05-23 05:30:00"><n u="Motorway Patrol">Motorway Patrol XI (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series from New Zealand following the madness and mayhem faced by intrepid officers as they pull over motorists for a variety of suspected offences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 05:30:00" d="2020-05-23 06:00:00"><n u="Motorway Patrol">Motorway Patrol XI (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series from New Zealand following the madness and mayhem faced by intrepid officers as they pull over motorists for a variety of suspected offences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 06:00:00" d="2020-05-23 06:30:00"><n u="Highway Patrol">Highway Patrol IX (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Documentary series following Australia's traffic enforcers. Officers face high-speed chases, defiant hooligans, explosive crashes and out-of-control drunk drivers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 06:30:00" d="2020-05-23 07:00:00"><n u="Highway Patrol">Highway Patrol IX (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Documentary series following Australia's traffic enforcers. Officers face high-speed chases, defiant hooligans, explosive crashes and out-of-control drunk drivers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 07:00:00" d="2020-05-23 07:30:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare VII (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Documentary following the officers protecting Australia's borders. Cameras capture first-hand how they deal with drug-runners, smugglers and strange creepy-crawlies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 07:30:00" d="2020-05-23 08:00:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare VII (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% The fly-on-the-wall documentary joins the men and women who enforce Australia's customs, quarantine and immigration laws at the nation's airports and harbours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 08:00:00" d="2020-05-23 08:30:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare UK">Nothing To Declare UK III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Observational documentary series following customs officials as they search and seize illegal drugs and contraband in their continued fight to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 08:30:00" d="2020-05-23 09:00:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare UK">Nothing To Declare UK III (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Observational documentary series following customs officials as they search and seize illegal drugs and contraband in their continued fight to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 09:00:00" d="2020-05-23 10:00:00"><n u="Merlin">Merlin I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Dragon's Call
Merlin, a teenage warlock, is sent to Camelot and tasked with protecting a young Arthur until he becomes king. But Merlin thinks Arthur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 10:00:00" d="2020-05-23 11:00:00"><n u="Merlin">Merlin I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Valiant
When Knight Valiant takes devious measures to win Camelot's annual sword tournament, Merlin attempts to expose him and save Arthur's life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 11:00:00" d="2020-05-23 12:00:00"><n u="Merlin">Merlin I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Poisoned Chalice
Merlin becomes dangerously ill when he is targeted by the evil sorceress Nimueh. As Arthur tries to save him, he unwittingly enters a trap</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 12:00:00" d="2020-05-23 13:00:00"><n u="Merlin">Merlin I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lancelot
When a brave stranger named Lancelot saves Merlin from a flying beat, Merlin attempts to have him made a Knight of Camelot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 13:00:00" d="2020-05-23 14:00:00"><n u="Merlin">Merlin I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Remedy To Cure All Ills
As Lady Morgana battles a mysterious illness, a new physician offers a helping hand. but Gaius isn't convinced</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 14:00:00" d="2020-05-23 15:00:00"><n u="Merlin">Merlin I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Gates Of Avalon
Arthur puts himself in danger as he rescues a damsel in distress and her father, and there's more to the mysterious pair than meets the eye</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 15:00:00" d="2020-05-23 16:00:00"><n u="Merlin">Merlin I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Beginning Of The End
Arthur finds an unlikely ally in Morgana when the pair team up and put their lives on the line to help a magical young fugitive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 16:00:00" d="2020-05-23 17:00:00"><n u="Merlin">Merlin I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Excalibur
A mysterious black knight rides into Camelot and challenges the Knights to mortal combat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 17:00:00" d="2020-05-23 18:00:00"><n u="Merlin">Merlin I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Moment Of Truth
Merlin has a difficult choice to make as he races home to help save his village from a fearsome raider, with the help of Arthur, Gwen and Morgana</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 18:00:00" d="2020-05-23 19:00:00"><n u="Merlin">Merlin I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Labyrinth Of Gedref
Arthur curses the whole of Camelot when he kills a unicorn and takes desperate measures to make amends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 19:00:00" d="2020-05-23 20:00:00"><n u="Merlin">Merlin I (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>To Kill The King
Merlin uncovers Mogana's plot to kill the king and grapples with whether he should stop her or do nothing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 20:00:00" d="2020-05-23 21:00:00"><n u="Merlin">Merlin I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Le Morte D'arthur
Sightings of a deadly beast in Camelot spell trouble for Merlin as he is forced to choose between his loved ones and make a difficult sacrifice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 21:00:00" d="2020-05-23 21:35:00"><n u="New: Caught Red Handed S6">New: Caught Red Handed S6 VI (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A hairdressing salon owner races to confront his thieves in action, while a burglar is caught in the act by an eagle-eyed neighbour and another thief makes a rookie mistake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 21:35:00" d="2020-05-23 22:15:00"><n u="New: Caught Red Handed S6">New: Caught Red Handed S6 VI (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A burglar tries to rob a house with no idea of what's waiting to confront him inside. A man gets more than he bargained for when he breaks into a garage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 22:15:00" d="2020-05-23 23:15:00"><n u="Micky Flanagan's Detour De France">Micky Flanagan's Detour De France I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bon voyage, Micky! Join the funnyman as he heads across the Channel to put his own spin on the Tour de France. Along for the ride is his mate Noel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2020-05-23 23:15:00" d="2020-05-24 02:15:00"><n u="Micky Flanagan's Detour De France">Micky Flanagan's Detour De France I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>France is famous for its fizz and food, so it would be rude of Micky and Noel not to indulge in both. Noel also takes on a huge cycling challenge</k>  </p>
</a>
