<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="35" t="2019-08-15 22:49:19"><p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 05:00:00" d="2019-08-22 05:30:00"><n u="Highway Patrol">Highway Patrol IX (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Documentary series following Australia's traffic enforcers. Officers face high-speed chases, defiant hooligans, explosive crashes and out-of-control drunk drivers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 05:30:00" d="2019-08-22 06:00:00"><n u="Motorway Patrol">Motorway Patrol VII (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series from New Zealand following the madness and mayhem faced by intrepid officers as they pull over motorists for a variety of suspected offences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 06:00:00" d="2019-08-22 06:30:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare VIII (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% The fly-on-the-wall documentary joins the men and women who enforce Australia's customs, quarantine and immigration laws at the nation's airports and harbours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 06:30:00" d="2019-08-22 07:00:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare VIII (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% The observational documentary series goes to the frontline of Australia's defence against customs, quarantine and immigration violations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 07:00:00" d="2019-08-22 07:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 07:30:00" d="2019-08-22 08:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 08:00:00" d="2019-08-22 08:30:00"><n u="Border Patrol">Border Patrol IX (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. New Zealand reality series following the work of customs officers as they prevent drug smuggling, illegal immigrants and more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 08:30:00" d="2019-08-22 09:00:00"><n u="Border Patrol">Border Patrol IX (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. New Zealand reality series following the work of customs officers as they prevent drug smuggling, illegal immigrants and more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 09:00:00" d="2019-08-22 09:30:00"><n u="Highway Patrol Australia">Highway Patrol Australia VII (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series following Australia's traffic enforcers. Officers face high-speed chases, defiant hooligans, explosive crashes and out-of-control drunk drivers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 09:30:00" d="2019-08-22 10:00:00"><n u="Highway Patrol Australia">Highway Patrol Australia VII (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series following Australia's traffic enforcers. Officers face high-speed chases, defiant hooligans, explosive crashes and out-of-control drunk drivers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 10:00:00" d="2019-08-22 10:45:00"><n>Caught Red Handed</n>    <k>The victims of an armed robbery turn the tables on their attackers.(S2, ep 6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 10:45:00" d="2019-08-22 11:30:00"><n u="Caught Red Handed">Caught Red Handed II (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Dom presents a series of videos showing carers stealing from those they are supposed to be looking after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 11:30:00" d="2019-08-22 12:00:00"><n u="Highway Cops">Highway Cops IV (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A fisherman finds himself in hot water and so does a drunk driver who can barely stand, as the Highway Cops continue their patrol of New Zealand's busiest roads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 12:00:00" d="2019-08-22 12:30:00"><n u="Police Force Australia">Police Force Australia VIII (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series joining police forces across Australia as they deal with everything from dramatic siege situations and major drug busts to murder investigations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 12:30:00" d="2019-08-22 13:00:00"><n u="Police Force Australia">Police Force Australia VIII (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series joining police forces across Australia as they deal with everything from dramatic siege situations and major drug busts to murder investigations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 13:00:00" d="2019-08-22 14:00:00"><n u="Brit Cops: Rapid Response">Brit Cops: Rapid Response III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Action-packed documentary following rapid response officers, the fastest cops in Britain, as they crack down on crime. Time is of the essence!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 14:00:00" d="2019-08-22 14:30:00"><n u="999 Frontline">999 Frontline I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>We check in on the doctors and nurses of Peterborough General Hospital's Accident and Emergency Department and douse some flames with Northamptonshire fire fighters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 14:30:00" d="2019-08-22 15:00:00"><n u="999 Frontline">999 Frontline I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>This time on 999 Front Line we're enforcing the law on the M1 with Bedfordshire Traffic Cops, and up at the front with Green Watch fighting fires in Ipswich</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 15:00:00" d="2019-08-22 15:30:00"><n u="Border Security: Australia's Front Line">Border Security: Australia's Front Line IX (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series following Australian Customs and Border Protection officers as they attempt to enforce the country's customs, quarantine and immigration laws</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 15:30:00" d="2019-08-22 16:00:00"><n u="Border Security: Canada's Front Line">Border Security: Canada's Front Line I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cameras follow Canadian border services officers on the frontlines of national security. In this opening episode, an American learns about Canada's drug laws</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 16:00:00" d="2019-08-22 16:30:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare VI (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 16:30:00" d="2019-08-22 17:15:00"><n u="Caught Red Handed">Caught Red Handed II (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A window fitter is caught stealing from the house he is supposed to be securing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 17:15:00" d="2019-08-22 18:00:00"><n u="Caught Red Handed">Caught Red Handed II (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A sleepy thief is caught stealing from a bar before nodding off at the scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 18:00:00" d="2019-08-22 19:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In Extremis
When a doctor of Saudi Arabian descent with an exemplary record mysteriously vanishes, Martin is quick to suspect the man of having terrorist connections</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 19:00:00" d="2019-08-22 20:00:00"><n u="Stargate SG-1">Stargate SG-1 I (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Tin Man
A strange man implants the consciousness of the SG-1 team into robots</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 20:00:00" d="2019-08-22 21:00:00"><n u="New: Supergirl">New: Supergirl III (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>For Good
Supergirl steps in to help Lena when the fight between her and Morgan Edge takes a rather deadly turn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 21:00:00" d="2019-08-22 22:00:00"><n u="New: The Flash">New: The Flash IV (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Subject 9
As DeVoe goes after the remaining metas, Barry meets a powerful woman who might just help to stop him. Meanwhile, Ralph starts to fear for his life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 22:00:00" d="2019-08-22 23:00:00"><n u="An Idiot Abroad">An Idiot Abroad (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>82% China
Karl Pilkington's journey begins in the Far East. As well as casting his verdict on The Great Wall of China, he immerses himself in the culture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-22 23:00:00" d="2019-08-23 00:00:00"><n u="Karl Pilkington: The Moaning of Life">Karl Pilkington: The Moaning of Life (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Happiness
Karl sets off to see how other people achieve happiness, starting off in Mexico</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-23 00:00:00" d="2019-08-23 01:00:00"><n u="Murders That Shocked The Nation">Murders That Shocked The Nation I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ruth Ellis - Last Woman Hanged
In 1955, Ruth Ellis hanged for the murder of her estranged lover. But what would her punishment have been today?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-23 01:00:00" d="2019-08-23 02:00:00"><n u="Banged Up Abroad">Banged Up Abroad VII (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Son Of Saddam
The shocking story of Iraqi soldier Latif Yahia, who witnessed terrible atrocities after he was forced to become a body double for Saddam Hussein's son</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-23 02:00:00" d="2019-08-23 03:00:00"><n u="Brit Cops: Frontline Crime">Brit Cops: Frontline Crime I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Wales
Adrenaline-fuelled documentary following Britain's police as they wage war against crime. This time, cameras chart the admirable efforts of police teams from Wales</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-23 03:00:00" d="2019-08-23 04:00:00"><n u="Ultimate Road Wars">Ultimate Road Wars VIII (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>This two-part special skids onto screens to celebrate Road Wars' best bits, from rubber-burning pursuits and dangerous drug raids to explosive kerbside arrests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-23 04:00:00" d="2019-08-23 04:30:00"><n u="Border Patrol">Border Patrol III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Follow the work of the New Zealand Customs agents in their quest to prevent illegal items passing through the country's borders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1002" o="2019-08-23 04:30:00" d="2019-08-23 05:00:00"><n u="Border Patrol">Border Patrol III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Follow the work of the New Zealand Customs agents in their quest to prevent illegal items passing through the country's borders</k>  </p>
</a>
