<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2021-07-13 05:03:53"><p id_tv="1042" o="2021-07-20 05:30:00" d="2021-07-20 07:10:00" c="1"><n u="Bulletproof">Bulletproof 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>35% Mayhem ensues in this action-comedy sequel as Jack Carter is tasked to take down a powerful South African cartel - undercover. Faizon Love and Kirk Fox star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2021-07-20 07:10:00" d="2021-07-20 09:00:00" c="1"><n>Elektra</n><t>F</t>    <k>49% Jennifer Garner sizzles as the sultry assassin who battles against supernatural ninjas. Daredevil spin-off with Goran Visnjic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2021-07-20 09:00:00" d="2021-07-20 11:05:00" c="1"><n>Gemini Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% Will Smith stars as an aging assassin who becomes targeted by a mysterious enemy that seems able to anticipate his every move. Ang Lee directs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2021-07-20 11:05:00" d="2021-07-20 13:10:00" c="1"><n>The Wolf's Call</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% When a group of terrorists steal a submarine and simulate a deadly attack, a gifted sonar officer uses his abilities to end the threat of war. French with subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2021-07-20 13:10:00" d="2021-07-20 15:15:00" c="1"><n>The Sweeney</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% Ray Winstone and Ben 'Plan B' Drew head up a strong-armed police team on the trail of a gang of vicious armed robbers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2021-07-20 15:15:00" d="2021-07-20 17:20:00" c="1"><n>Cliffhanger</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% Climber Sylvester Stallone is forced by John Lithgow's gang of thieves to help recover lost loot in the mountains. Action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2021-07-20 17:20:00" d="2021-07-20 19:15:00" c="1"><n>Brothers In Arms</n><t>F</t>    <k>A by-the-book police officer is driven to take drastic measures when his brother is jailed unfairly. Tense thriller starring Jai Courtney and Leighton Meester</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2021-07-20 19:15:00" d="2021-07-20 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Elektra</n><t>F</t>    <k>49% Jennifer Garner sizzles as the sultry assassin who battles against supernatural ninjas. Daredevil spin-off with Goran Visnjic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2021-07-20 21:00:00" d="2021-07-20 23:00:00" c="1"><n>Gemini Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% Will Smith stars as an aging assassin who becomes targeted by a mysterious enemy that seems able to anticipate his every move. Ang Lee directs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2021-07-20 23:00:00" d="2021-07-21 02:00:00" c="1"><n>Mad Max: Fury Road</n><t>F</t>    <k>80% Tom Hardy and Charlize Theron star in George Miller's action adventure about a rebel and a drifter who team up in post-apocalyptic Australia</k>  </p>
</a>
