<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-05-14 04:53:53"><p id_tv="1042" o="2020-05-21 06:30:00" d="2020-05-21 07:00:00"><n>Sky Cinema Preview</n>    <k>Previews of the great films now playing on Sky Cinema plus other highlights showing on Sky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2020-05-21 07:00:00" d="2020-05-21 08:50:00" c="1"><n>The Hurricane Heist</n><t>F</t>    <k>51% Full-throttle thriller about a team of hackers using a devastating hurricane as cover to steal millions. Sky Cinema Original Film from Rob Cohen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2020-05-21 08:50:00" d="2020-05-21 10:35:00" c="1"><n>Hudson Hawk</n><t>F</t>    <k>59% Eccentric billionaire Richard E Grant forces suave cat burglar Bruce Willis to steal Leonardo Da Vinci's most valuable works. Barmy comedy caper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2020-05-21 10:35:00" d="2020-05-21 13:15:00" c="1"><n>2012</n><t>F</t>    <k>John Cusack battles to save his family as the end of the world closes in. Disaster epic from director Roland Emmerich, with Danny Glover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2020-05-21 13:15:00" d="2020-05-21 15:05:00" c="1"><n>Broken Arrow</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% John Travolta stars as a renegade pilot who steals two nuclear warheads, but former partner Christian Slater is on his trail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2020-05-21 15:05:00" d="2020-05-21 17:30:00" c="1"><n>The Karate Kid</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Moving to China, young Jaden Smith is bullied by local kids, until martial arts master Jackie Chan teaches him to fight back. Family action remake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2020-05-21 17:30:00" d="2020-05-21 19:20:00" c="1"><n>Final Score</n><t>F</t>    <k>57% An ex-soldier (Dave Bautista) is forced into action when terrorists take control of a football stadium. Sky Cinema Original Film with Pierce Brosnan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2020-05-21 19:20:00" d="2020-05-21 22:00:00" c="1"><n>2012</n><t>F</t>    <k>John Cusack battles to save his family as the end of the world closes in. Disaster epic from director Roland Emmerich, with Danny Glover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2020-05-21 22:00:00" d="2020-05-22 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Bad Boys</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Wise-cracking Miami cops Will Smith and Martin Lawrence fight to protect a witness and bring down a heroin crook. Action comedy</k>  </p>
</a>
