<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2021-07-09 07:14:49"><p id_tv="1042" o="2021-07-14 05:15:00" d="2021-07-14 07:00:00" c="1"><n>Skyfire</n><t>F</t>    <k>Chaos ensues on an idyllic resort when the once-dormant volcano on the tropical island begins to erupt. In Mandarin with subtitles. Gripping disaster action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2021-07-14 07:00:00" d="2021-07-14 09:10:00" c="1"><n u="Mission: Impossible">Mission: Impossible II</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Action sequel starring Tom Cruise as a secret agent in a race to stop a deadly virus and villainous Dougray Scott</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2021-07-14 09:10:00" d="2021-07-14 11:45:00" c="1"><n>Gladiator</n><t>F</t>    <k>85% Russell Crowe is the Roman general turned vengeful gladiator in this spectacular Oscar-winning epic from director Ridley Scott</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2021-07-14 11:45:00" d="2021-07-14 13:50:00" c="1"><n>The Iron Mask</n><t>F</t>    <k>Cartographer Jonathan Green returns - and this time he is off on another supernatural journey to the Far East. Arnold Schwarzenegger, Jackie Chan and Charles Dance star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2021-07-14 13:50:00" d="2021-07-14 15:45:00" c="1"><n>Twister</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Helen Hunt and the late Bill Paxton star in this FX-filled action movie about rival teams of scientists competing to investigate a series of destructive tornadoes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2021-07-14 15:45:00" d="2021-07-14 17:25:00" c="1"><n>Narco Soldiers</n><t>F</t>    <k>Action-packed crime thriller following a couple's rise to power in a Caribbean drug gang and the deadly turf war that ensues as a result of their scheming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2021-07-14 17:25:00" d="2021-07-14 19:25:00" c="1"><n>The Wolf's Call</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% When a group of terrorists steal a submarine and simulate a deadly attack, a gifted sonar officer uses his abilities to end the threat of war. French with subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2021-07-14 19:25:00" d="2021-07-14 21:35:00" c="1"><n u="Mission: Impossible">Mission: Impossible II</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Action sequel starring Tom Cruise as a secret agent in a race to stop a deadly virus and villainous Dougray Scott</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2021-07-14 21:35:00" d="2021-07-15 00:15:00" c="1"><n>Gladiator</n><t>F</t>    <k>85% Russell Crowe is the Roman general turned vengeful gladiator in this spectacular Oscar-winning epic from director Ridley Scott</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2021-07-15 00:15:00" d="2021-07-15 03:00:00" c="1"><n u="Le Mans">Le Mans 66</n><t>F</t>    <k>Car designer Carroll Shelby and driver Ken Miles battle to build a revolutionary race car for Ford. Oscar-winning drama starring Matt Damon and Christian Bale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2021-07-15 03:00:00" d="2021-07-15 04:50:00" c="1"><n>The Tax Collector</n><t>F</t>    <k>The family of a gangster's tax collector are put in danger when a rival gang leader takes over LA. Shia LaBeouf stars in this action-packed thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2021-07-15 04:50:00" d="2021-07-15 07:00:00" c="1"><n>Twister</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Helen Hunt and the late Bill Paxton star in this FX-filled action movie about rival teams of scientists competing to investigate a series of destructive tornadoes</k>  </p>
</a>
