<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="11" t="2019-08-09 01:41:38"><p id_tv="1042" o="2019-08-15 06:30:00" d="2019-08-15 07:00:00"><n>Solo: A Star Wars Story: Special</n>    <k>Sky Cinema takes a special look at the spin-off adventure, directed by Ron Howard and starring Alden Ehrenreich (Hail, Caesar!) as a young Han Solo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2019-08-15 07:00:00" d="2019-08-15 09:30:00" c="1"><n>Solo: A Star Wars Story</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Alden Ehrenreich steps into the Millennium Falcon hot seat as legendary intergalactic smuggler Han Solo. Breezy Star Wars spin-off with Game of Thrones star Emilia Clarke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2019-08-15 09:30:00" d="2019-08-15 11:45:00" c="1"><n>Star Wars: A New Hope</n><t>F</t>    <k>Luke Skywalker joins forces with Jedi Knight Obi-Wan Kenobi and cocky pilot Han Solo to rescue Princess Leia (the late Carrie Fisher). Iconic sci-fi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2019-08-15 11:45:00" d="2019-08-15 14:00:00" c="1"><n>Star Wars: The Empire Strikes Back</n><t>F</t>    <k>Luke Skywalker travels to a distant planet to train with Jedi master Yoda while Han and Leia (the late Carrie Fisher) are pursued by the Empire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2019-08-15 14:00:00" d="2019-08-15 16:30:00" c="1"><n>Star Wars: Return Of The Jedi</n><t>F</t>    <k>The Empire and the Rebellion prepare for a final stand-off as Luke confronts Darth Vader. With Mark Hamill, Harrison Ford and the late Carrie Fisher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2019-08-15 16:30:00" d="2019-08-15 16:45:00"><n>The 2019 Top Ten Show</n>    <k>Which movies are doing the best business at home and across the pond? Clips from the UK and US Top Ten show you the best of what's on offer on the big screen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2019-08-15 16:45:00" d="2019-08-15 19:30:00" c="1"><n>Star Wars: The Last Jedi</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% With the Resistance cornered, aspiring Jedi Rey must persuade the great Luke Skywalker to save the galaxy once more. Epic eighth instalment in the blockbuster sci-fi saga</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2019-08-15 19:30:00" d="2019-08-15 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Star Wars: The Phantom Menace</n><t>F</t>    <k>Two Jedi Knights (Ewan McGregor and Liam Neeson) discover a boy who may bring balance to the Force just as the evil Sith resurface. Sci-fi prequel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2019-08-15 22:00:00" d="2019-08-16 00:30:00" c="1"><n>Star Wars: Attack Of The Clones</n><t>F</t>    <k>A Jedi Knight (Ewan McGregor) and his young apprentice (Hayden Christensen) battle to protect the Republic from separatist leader Count Dooku</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2019-08-16 00:30:00" d="2019-08-16 03:00:00" c="1"><n>Star Wars: Revenge Of The Sith</n><t>F</t>    <k>Anakin Skywalker becomes closer with Chancellor Palpatine and begins to succumb to the temptations of the dark side. Epic sci-fi adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2019-08-16 03:00:00" d="2019-08-16 05:00:00" c="1"><n>12 Rounds</n><t>F</t>    <k>57% When his girlfriend is kidnapped, cop John Cena must complete 12 perilous challenges in order to save her life</k>  </p>
</a>
