<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2019-08-15 22:51:23"><p id_tv="1042" o="2019-08-22 07:00:00" d="2019-08-22 08:45:00" c="1"><n>Star Wars: The Clone Wars</n><t>F</t>    <k>59% The Clone Wars begin as Anakin Skywalker and Obi-Wan battle to rescue Jabba The Hutt's son. Space animation featuring the voices of Christopher Lee and Samuel L Jackson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2019-08-22 08:45:00" d="2019-08-22 11:15:00" c="1"><n>Star Wars: Revenge Of The Sith</n><t>F</t>    <k>Anakin Skywalker becomes closer with Chancellor Palpatine and begins to succumb to the temptations of the dark side. Epic sci-fi adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2019-08-22 11:15:00" d="2019-08-22 13:30:00" c="1"><n>Star Wars: A New Hope</n><t>F</t>    <k>Luke Skywalker joins forces with Jedi Knight Obi-Wan Kenobi and cocky pilot Han Solo to rescue Princess Leia (the late Carrie Fisher). Iconic sci-fi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2019-08-22 13:30:00" d="2019-08-22 15:45:00" c="1"><n>Star Wars: The Empire Strikes Back</n><t>F</t>    <k>Luke Skywalker travels to a distant planet to train with Jedi master Yoda while Han and Leia (the late Carrie Fisher) are pursued by the Empire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2019-08-22 15:45:00" d="2019-08-22 18:15:00" c="1"><n>Star Wars: Return Of The Jedi</n><t>F</t>    <k>The Empire and the Rebellion prepare for a final stand-off as Luke confronts Darth Vader. With Mark Hamill, Harrison Ford and the late Carrie Fisher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2019-08-22 18:15:00" d="2019-08-22 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Star Wars: The Last Jedi</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% With the Resistance cornered, aspiring Jedi Rey must persuade the great Luke Skywalker to save the galaxy once more. Epic eighth instalment in the blockbuster sci-fi saga</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2019-08-22 21:00:00" d="2019-08-22 23:30:00" c="1"><n>Star Wars: The Phantom Menace</n><t>F</t>    <k>Two Jedi Knights (Ewan McGregor and Liam Neeson) discover a boy who may bring balance to the Force just as the evil Sith resurface. Sci-fi prequel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2019-08-22 23:30:00" d="2019-08-23 02:05:00" c="1"><n>Star Wars: Attack Of The Clones</n><t>F</t>    <k>A Jedi Knight (Ewan McGregor) and his young apprentice (Hayden Christensen) battle to protect the Republic from separatist leader Count Dooku</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2019-08-23 02:05:00" d="2019-08-23 04:40:00" c="1"><n>Star Wars: Revenge Of The Sith</n><t>F</t>    <k>Anakin Skywalker becomes closer with Chancellor Palpatine and begins to succumb to the temptations of the dark side. Epic sci-fi adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1042" o="2019-08-23 04:40:00" d="2019-08-23 07:00:00" c="1"><n>Speed 2: Cruise Control</n><t>F</t>    <k>41% Sandra Bullock returns in this high-octane sequel as a clumsy hero whose romantic cruise with lover Jason Patric is hijacked by terrorist Willem Dafoe</k>  </p>
</a>
