<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="13" t="2019-08-10 01:39:29"><p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-16 06:10:00" d="2019-08-16 06:30:00"><n>The 2019 Top Ten Show</n>    <k>Which movies are doing the best business at home and across the pond? Clips from the UK and US Top Ten show you the best of what's on offer on the big screen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-16 06:30:00" d="2019-08-16 08:10:00" c="1"><n>Blue Streak</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% Rollicking action comedy starring Martin Lawrence as a jewel thief forced to pose as a cop in order to recover a stashed diamond. With Luke Wilson and Dave Chappelle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-16 08:10:00" d="2019-08-16 09:50:00" c="1"><n>In &amp; Out</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Teacher Kevin Kline becomes the talk of the town after being pronounced gay by a famous ex-pupil. With an Oscar-nominated Joan Cusack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-16 09:50:00" d="2019-08-16 11:35:00" c="1"><n>The Nutty Professor</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% Overweight professor Eddie Murphy embarks on a wacky adventure when he invents a potion which can make him slim</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-16 11:35:00" d="2019-08-16 13:30:00" c="1"><n>Think Like A Man Too</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% Kevin Hart, Regina Hall and friends run riot when they hit Las Vegas for a wedding. Comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-16 13:30:00" d="2019-08-16 15:30:00" c="1"><n>Mamma Mia!</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Meryl Streep belts out the ABBA tunes in this adaptation of the musical, which sees a bride-to-be try to learn the identity of her dad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-16 15:30:00" d="2019-08-16 17:30:00" c="1"><n>Mamma Mia! Here We Go Again</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% The record-breaking jukebox musical returns for the grand opening of Hotel Bella Donna. With Meryl Streep, Lily James and Amanda Seyfried</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-16 17:30:00" d="2019-08-16 19:25:00" c="1"><n>Step Brothers</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% When their parents get married, step brothers Will Ferrell and John C Reilly are forced to grow up and move out. Extended version</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-16 19:25:00" d="2019-08-16 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Action Point</n><t>F</t>    <k>50% A failing amusement park owner takes drastic - and dangerous - action to save his debt-ridden business when a corporate mega-park opens nearby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-16 21:00:00" d="2019-08-16 23:00:00" c="1"><n>Mamma Mia!</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Meryl Streep belts out the ABBA tunes in this adaptation of the musical, which sees a bride-to-be try to learn the identity of her dad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-16 23:00:00" d="2019-08-17 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Mamma Mia! Here We Go Again</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% The record-breaking jukebox musical returns for the grand opening of Hotel Bella Donna. With Meryl Streep, Lily James and Amanda Seyfried</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-17 01:00:00" d="2019-08-17 03:05:00" c="1"><n>Talladega Nights: The Ballad Of Ricky Bobby</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% NASCAR superstar Will Ferrell is blessed with success. until French F1 show-off Sacha Baron Cohen shows up. Comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-17 03:05:00" d="2019-08-17 05:00:00" c="1"><n>Eurotrip</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Filthy fun ensues when a teen takes his mates on a trip across Europe to track down a German stunner. With a cameo from Matt Damon</k>  </p>
</a>
