<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-04-10 04:36:59"><p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-17 05:10:00" d="2020-04-17 07:10:00" c="1"><n>Roxanne</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Long-nosed fire chief Steve Martin falls for astronomer Daryl Hannah, but his eccentric looks make him too shy to make a move. Comedy retelling of Cyrano de Bergerac</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-17 07:10:00" d="2020-04-17 08:50:00" c="1"><n>Dusty And Me</n><t>F</t>    <k>49% Feel-good comedy starring BAFTA nominee Luke Newberry as a misfit teen who forms a special bond with a runaway greyhound. With Games of Thrones star Iain Glen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-17 08:50:00" d="2020-04-17 10:55:00" c="1"><n>The Favourite</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% Emma Stone and Rachel Weisz compete for the favour of Queen Anne, portrayed by an Oscar-winning Olivia Colman. Black comedy from Yorgos Lanthimos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-17 10:55:00" d="2020-04-17 12:55:00" c="1"><n>Tootsie</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% Dustin Hoffman plays an out of work actor who, out of desperation, pretends to be a woman to get a part on a soap opera. Classic comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-17 12:55:00" d="2020-04-17 14:55:00" c="1"><n>Instant Family</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% A couple decide to adopt, but get more than they bargained for when they take in a rebellious teen and her two siblings. Comedy-drama with Mark Wahlberg and Rose Byrne</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-17 14:55:00" d="2020-04-17 17:00:00" c="1"><n>Notting Hill</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Bookshop owner Hugh Grant forms an unlikely romance with superstar actress Julia Roberts in this hit Richard Curtis romcom. Co-stars Rhys Ifans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-17 17:00:00" d="2020-04-17 18:50:00" c="1"><n>The Addams Family</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% When a stranger claims to be their long lost uncle, the Addams Family attempt to uncover the truth. Comedy with Christina Ricci</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-17 18:50:00" d="2020-04-17 21:00:00" c="1"><n>The Favourite</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% Emma Stone and Rachel Weisz compete for the favour of Queen Anne, portrayed by an Oscar-winning Olivia Colman. Black comedy from Yorgos Lanthimos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-17 21:00:00" d="2020-04-18 00:00:00" c="1"><n>Instant Family</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% A couple decide to adopt, but get more than they bargained for when they take in a rebellious teen and her two siblings. Comedy-drama with Mark Wahlberg and Rose Byrne</k>  </p>
</a>
