<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="13" t="2019-08-15 22:51:29"><p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-22 06:15:00" d="2019-08-22 08:05:00" c="1"><n>Did You Hear About The Morgans?</n><t>F</t>    <k>49% Hugh Grant and Sarah Jessica Parker star as an estranged New York couple who lie low in rural Wyoming after witnessing a murder. Entertaining rom-com</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-22 08:05:00" d="2019-08-22 09:35:00" c="1"><n u="Airplane">Airplane II</n><t>F</t>    <k>The cast of Airplane! return for more chaotic fun in this delirious disaster movie spoof set aboard a doomed space shuttle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-22 09:35:00" d="2019-08-22 11:10:00" c="1"><n>Extracurricular Activities</n><t>F</t>    <k>A savvy student makes a killing from arranging 'accidents' for the overbearing parents of his peers. But is he smart enough to ward off a suspicious cop? Comedy thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-22 11:10:00" d="2019-08-22 13:10:00" c="1"><n>Father Figures</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% Road-trip comedy starring Owen Wilson and Ed Helms as bickering twin brothers who embark on a cross-country quest to find their real dad. With JK Simmons and Glenn Close</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-22 13:10:00" d="2019-08-22 15:10:00" c="1"><n>Friends With Benefits</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Headhunter Mila Kunis starts a no-strings relationship with client Justin Timberlake, but can the pair really keep romance out of the picture? Romcom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-22 15:10:00" d="2019-08-22 17:10:00" c="1"><n>That's My Boy</n><t>F</t>    <k>54% Feckless 40-something Adam Sandler tries to worm his way back into the life of estranged son Andy Samberg. Cheeky comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-22 17:10:00" d="2019-08-22 19:10:00" c="1"><n>We're The Millers</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% When he's asked to move a drug shipment across the border, Jason Sudeikis hires a fake family to avoid suspicion. Comedy with Jennifer Aniston</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-22 19:10:00" d="2019-08-22 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Made Of Honour</n><t>F</t>    <k>59% Love is in the air when Patrick Dempsey realises he's smitten with his friend. Problem is, she's about to marry someone else. Romcom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-22 21:00:00" d="2019-08-22 23:00:00" c="1"><n>Friends With Benefits</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Headhunter Mila Kunis starts a no-strings relationship with client Justin Timberlake, but can the pair really keep romance out of the picture? Romcom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-22 23:00:00" d="2019-08-23 01:00:00" c="1"><n>That's My Boy</n><t>F</t>    <k>54% Feckless 40-something Adam Sandler tries to worm his way back into the life of estranged son Andy Samberg. Cheeky comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-23 01:00:00" d="2019-08-23 02:55:00" c="1"><n>We're The Millers</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% When he's asked to move a drug shipment across the border, Jason Sudeikis hires a fake family to avoid suspicion. Comedy with Jennifer Aniston</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-23 02:55:00" d="2019-08-23 04:55:00" c="1"><n>You Don't Mess With The Zohan</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% Israeli commando Adam Sandler fakes his own death so he can become a New York hairdresser. Comedy with John Turturro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-23 04:55:00" d="2019-08-23 07:00:00" c="1"><n>You've Got Mail</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Romcom royalty Tom Hanks and Meg Ryan are rival booksellers unaware that they are also anonymous e-mail amours. Novel romance from the director of Sleepless In Seattle</k>  </p>
</a>
