<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="13" t="2019-08-09 01:41:41"><p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-15 05:45:00" d="2019-08-15 07:35:00" c="1"><n>The Odd Couple</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Irresistible comedy pairing poker-playing slob Walter Matthau with neurotic Jack Lemmon. One crackling, Oscar-nominated script, two perfect performances</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-15 07:35:00" d="2019-08-15 09:30:00" c="1"><n>I Do... Until I Don't</n><t>F</t>    <k>45% Comedy about a filmmaker hoping to show that marriage is an archaic idea that needs a rethink. Lake Bell writes, directs and stars alongside Ed Helms and Amber Heard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-15 09:30:00" d="2019-08-15 11:30:00" c="1"><n>Kingpin</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Woody Harrelson thinks Randy Quaid could be a tenpin king, but Bill Murray isn't champ for nothing. Classic comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-15 11:30:00" d="2019-08-15 13:40:00" c="1"><n>Think Like A Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Four relationships are thrown into chaos by the release of a book offering relationship advice. Rom-com starring Kevin Hart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-15 13:40:00" d="2019-08-15 15:45:00" c="1"><n>Night School</n><t>F</t>    <k>56% Comedy about a group of troublesome adults who are forced to attend night classes in a bid to finish high school. Starring Kevin Hart and Tiffany Haddish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-15 15:45:00" d="2019-08-15 17:30:00" c="1"><n>Juliet, Naked</n><t>F</t>    <k>A relationship is turned upside down by a woman's chance encounter with an obscure rocker who has an obsessive fan - her boyfriend. Charming rom-com with Ethan Hawke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-15 17:30:00" d="2019-08-15 19:15:00" c="1"><n>The Ugly Truth</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% TV producer Katherine Heigl gets candid relationship advice from dating guru Gerard Butler. Rom-com</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-15 19:15:00" d="2019-08-15 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Blades Of Glory</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% Will Ferrell and Jon Heder star as figure skaters who are fierce ice rivals. until they're forced to team up. Comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-15 21:00:00" d="2019-08-15 23:00:00" c="1"><n>Night School</n><t>F</t>    <k>56% Comedy about a group of troublesome adults who are forced to attend night classes in a bid to finish high school. Starring Kevin Hart and Tiffany Haddish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-15 23:00:00" d="2019-08-16 00:45:00" c="1"><n>Juliet, Naked</n><t>F</t>    <k>A relationship is turned upside down by a woman's chance encounter with an obscure rocker who has an obsessive fan - her boyfriend. Charming rom-com with Ethan Hawke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-16 00:45:00" d="2019-08-16 02:35:00" c="1"><n>She's Out Of My League</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% Geeky Jay Baruchel tries his best to keep it together when stunning Alice Eve falls for him. Comedy with Krysten Ritter and TJ Miller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-16 02:35:00" d="2019-08-16 04:05:00" c="1"><n>The Dictator</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% Fish-out-of-water spoof starring Sacha Baron Cohen as an African dictator who gets into all kinds of scrapes when he travels to New York to meet the UN</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-16 04:05:00" d="2019-08-16 06:10:00" c="1"><n>My Cousin Vinny</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% Brooklyn lawyer Joe Pesci is out of his depth trying to save his cousin from a murder rap. Hit comedy with Oscar winner Marisa Tomei</k>  </p>
</a>
