<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-04-09 04:35:58"><p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-16 05:20:00" d="2020-04-16 07:10:00" c="1"><n>Gideon</n><t>F</t>    <k>Touching tale starring Christopher Lambert as Gideon, a man with the mind of a child, who enlivens dull days for the inhabitants of an old people's home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-16 07:10:00" d="2020-04-16 08:55:00" c="1"><n>I Want Candy</n><t>F</t>    <k>54% Two students convince a Soho sleazebag to fund their film. There's a catch: it must star porn queen Candy Fiveways. Cheeky Brit romp with Carmen Electra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-16 08:55:00" d="2020-04-16 10:55:00" c="1"><n>Roxanne</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Long-nosed fire chief Steve Martin falls for astronomer Daryl Hannah, but his eccentric looks make him too shy to make a move. Comedy retelling of Cyrano de Bergerac</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-16 10:55:00" d="2020-04-16 12:50:00" c="1"><n>Father Of The Bride</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Doting father Steve Martin struggles to let his little girl go when she announces that she is engaged to be married. Comedy remake starring Diane Keaton and Martin Short</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-16 12:50:00" d="2020-04-16 14:40:00" c="1"><n>Tag</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Comedy following a group of super-competitive friends who every year play a marathon, month-long game of tag. Starring Ed Helms, Jon Hamm and Jeremy Renner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-16 14:40:00" d="2020-04-16 16:40:00" c="1"><n>Little</n><t>F</t>    <k>Regina Hall stars as a mean tech mogul who wakes up one morning to find herself back in her 13-year-old body after crossing the wrong magician. Comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-16 16:40:00" d="2020-04-16 18:20:00" c="1"><n>Family</n><t>F</t>    <k>A socially awkward woman is tasked with babysitting her equally awkward niece - and everything quickly goes awry. Comedy with Taylor Schilling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-16 18:20:00" d="2020-04-16 20:10:00" c="1"><n>Father Of The Bride</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Doting father Steve Martin struggles to let his little girl go when she announces that she is engaged to be married. Comedy remake starring Diane Keaton and Martin Short</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-16 20:10:00" d="2020-04-16 23:10:00" c="1"><n>Tag</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Comedy following a group of super-competitive friends who every year play a marathon, month-long game of tag. Starring Ed Helms, Jon Hamm and Jeremy Renner</k>  </p>
</a>
