<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2019-08-13 02:26:25"><p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-20 05:50:00" d="2019-08-20 08:00:00" c="1"><n>The Apartment</n><t>F</t>    <k>83% Ambitious insurance clerk Jack Lemmon lets his sleazy boss use his flat to philander with Shirley MacLaine. Cracking Oscar-winning comedy from director Billy Wilder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-20 08:00:00" d="2019-08-20 09:35:00" c="1"><n>Psych: The Movie</n><t>F</t>    <k>Fake psychic detective Shawn Spencer and best friend Gus Guster must reunite when a mystery assailant targets one of their own. Comedy based on the hit TV series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-20 09:35:00" d="2019-08-20 11:20:00" c="1"><n u="Wayne's World">Wayne's World 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% Hollywood's favourite metalheads make a riotous return to stage a rock concert. While Wayne's booking Aerosmith, Garth's scoring with Kim Basinger. Head-banging comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-20 11:20:00" d="2019-08-20 13:25:00" c="1"><n>Pretty Woman</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% The box office smash that made a star of Julia Roberts sees ruthless businessman Richard Gere falling for a call girl he has hired for the week</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-20 13:25:00" d="2019-08-20 15:30:00" c="1"><n>Hot Fuzz</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% Cops Simon Pegg and Nick Frost investigate a series of deaths in a quiet English village. Action comedy directed by Edgar Wright</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-20 15:30:00" d="2019-08-20 17:20:00" c="1"><n>Life Of The Party</n><t>F</t>    <k>57% Back-to-school comedy starring Melissa McCarthy as a down-on-her-luck fortysomething who decides to finally finish her degree - at the same college as her daughter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-20 17:20:00" d="2019-08-20 19:20:00" c="1"><n>Miss Congeniality 2 Armed And Fabulous</n><t>F</t>    <k>FBI agent Sandra Bullock might be too famous for undercover duty, but when bad guys kidnap Miss USA, she jumps back into action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-20 19:20:00" d="2019-08-20 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Bean</n><t>F</t>    <k>Rowan Atkinson reprises his hugely successful TV role as the hopelessly inept Mr Bean, who somehow finds himself travelling to America as an art expert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-20 21:00:00" d="2019-08-21 00:00:00" c="1"><n>Hot Fuzz</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% Cops Simon Pegg and Nick Frost investigate a series of deaths in a quiet English village. Action comedy directed by Edgar Wright</k>  </p>
</a>
