<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="14" t="2019-07-11 00:20:58"><p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-17 06:30:00" d="2019-07-17 07:00:00"><n>Yesterday: Special</n>    <k>A sneak peek at Danny Boyle's witty British comedy Yesterday, starring Lily James, Himesh Patel and Ed Sheeran</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-17 07:00:00" d="2019-07-17 08:30:00" c="1"><n>Naked Gun: From The Files of Police Squad!</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Leslie Nielsen stars as incompetent cop Frank Drebin, who is out to stop a plot to assassinate the Queen. Top slapstick comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-17 08:30:00" d="2019-07-17 10:00:00" c="1"><n>The Naked Gun 2 1/2: The Smell Of Fear</n><t>F</t>    <k>Slapstick fun as detective Leslie Nielsen stumbles upon an evil plan to destroy America</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-17 10:00:00" d="2019-07-17 11:30:00" c="1"><n>Naked Gun 33 1/3: The Final Insult</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Clueless cop Leslie Nielsen is hauled out of retirement to save the Academy Awards from bombers. Anna Nicole Smith co-stars in this comic sequel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-17 11:30:00" d="2019-07-17 13:30:00" c="1"><n>Miss Congeniality</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% Breezy comedy starring Sandra Bullock as a tomboy FBI agent tasked with going undercover as a beauty queen to foil a terrorist plot. With Michael Caine and Benjamin Bratt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-17 13:30:00" d="2019-07-17 15:20:00" c="1"><n>Blockers</n><t>F</t>    <k>A trio of concerned parents launch into a calamitous quest to stop their BFF high-school daughters from making good on a prom-night sex pact. Comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-17 15:20:00" d="2019-07-17 17:20:00"><n>Superbad</n>    <k>A pair of high-school seniors plan an ill-fated night of debauchery before heading off to college. Riotous comedy starring Michael Cera and Jonah Hill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-17 17:20:00" d="2019-07-17 19:10:00" c="1"><n>Think Like A Man Too</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% Kevin Hart, Regina Hall and friends run riot when they hit Las Vegas for a wedding. Comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-17 19:10:00" d="2019-07-17 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Bruce Almighty</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Cranky reporter Jim Carrey is mad at God, until the big man hands over his powers to show him how tough it is at the top. Comedy with Morgan Freeman and Jennifer Aniston</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-17 21:00:00" d="2019-07-17 22:45:00" c="1"><n>Blockers</n><t>F</t>    <k>A trio of concerned parents launch into a calamitous quest to stop their BFF high-school daughters from making good on a prom-night sex pact. Comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-17 22:45:00" d="2019-07-18 00:45:00"><n>Superbad</n>    <k>A pair of high-school seniors plan an ill-fated night of debauchery before heading off to college. Riotous comedy starring Michael Cera and Jonah Hill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-18 00:45:00" d="2019-07-18 02:15:00" c="1"><n>The Dictator</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% Fish-out-of-water spoof starring Sacha Baron Cohen as an African dictator who gets into all kinds of scrapes when he travels to New York to meet the UN</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-18 02:15:00" d="2019-07-18 04:05:00" c="1"><n>Beverly Hills Cop</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Streetwise Detroit detective Eddie Murphy pursues a colleague's killer to LA, causing mayhem for local cop Judge Reinhold. Action comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-18 04:05:00" d="2019-07-18 06:00:00" c="1"><n>Lost In London</n><t>F</t>    <k>Filmed in one take, follow Woody Harrelson on a wild night out in London - bumping into pals like Owen Wilson and Daniel Radcliffe before ending the night in the slammer</k>  </p>
</a>
