<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-05-29 04:36:20"><p id_tv="1043" o="2020-06-05 06:30:00" d="2020-06-05 08:20:00" c="1"><n>Gideon</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Touching tale starring Christopher Lambert as Gideon, a man with the mind of a child, who enlivens dull days for the inhabitants of an old people's home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-06-05 08:20:00" d="2020-06-05 10:00:00" c="1"><n>Little Monsters</n><t>F</t>    <k>Horror-comedy starring Lupita Nyong'o. A teacher teams up with a washed-up musician and a kids' TV personality to protect children from zombies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-06-05 10:00:00" d="2020-06-05 11:55:00" c="1"><n>Class Rank</n><t>F</t>    <k>Feeling they're being held back by the system, two teens attempt to take over their high school's board and change things for the better. Family comedy-drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-06-05 11:55:00" d="2020-06-05 13:55:00" c="1"><n>The Bromley Boys</n><t>F</t>    <k>Set in the early 1970s, Brenock O'Connor stars as a football-mad teenager on a hilarious mission to save his poorly-performing favourite football team. British comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-06-05 13:55:00" d="2020-06-05 16:05:00" c="1"><n>Instant Family</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% A couple decide to adopt, but get more than they bargained for when they take in a rebellious teen and her two siblings. Comedy-drama with Mark Wahlberg and Rose Byrne</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-06-05 16:05:00" d="2020-06-05 18:05:00" c="1"><n>The Other Guys</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Calamitous cops Will Ferrell and Mark Wahlberg stumble on a case which could repair their terrible reputations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-06-05 18:05:00" d="2020-06-05 20:10:00" c="1"><n>Just Go With It</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% When Adam Sandler's dream date mistakenly thinks he's married, assistant Jennifer Aniston steps in to play the wife he's pretending to divorce. Romcom with Nicole Kidman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-06-05 20:10:00" d="2020-06-05 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Adam</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Comedy following the journey of an awkward teenager named Adam, who is thrust into New York's lesbian and trans activist scene when he travels there to visit his sister</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-06-05 22:00:00" d="2020-06-06 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Instant Family</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% A couple decide to adopt, but get more than they bargained for when they take in a rebellious teen and her two siblings. Comedy-drama with Mark Wahlberg and Rose Byrne</k>  </p>
</a>
