<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-04-15 04:36:12"><p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-22 06:15:00" d="2020-04-22 08:15:00" c="1"><n>Gideon</n><t>F</t>    <k>Touching tale starring Christopher Lambert as Gideon, a man with the mind of a child, who enlivens dull days for the inhabitants of an old people's home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-22 08:15:00" d="2020-04-22 10:00:00" c="1"><n>Trouble</n><t>F</t>    <k>A sibling rivalry explodes when the brother tries to buy his father's old property - now owned by his angry sister. With Anjelica Huston, David Morse and Julia Stiles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-22 10:00:00" d="2020-04-22 11:45:00" c="1"><n>Eaten By Lions</n><t>F</t>    <k>Half-brothers Omar and Pete embark on a search for Omar's real dad, leading to a heart-warming journey of self-discovery. in Blackpool. Comedy starring Antonio Aakeel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-22 11:45:00" d="2020-04-22 13:30:00" c="1"><n>Better Start Running</n><t>F</t>    <k>A shop clerk goes on the run with his dream girl when a warped chain of events leaves a relentless FBI duo hot on their tails. With Alex Sharp and Oscar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-22 13:30:00" d="2020-04-22 15:20:00" c="1"><n>All Square</n><t>F</t>    <k>A bookie with money woes strikes up an unlikely friendship with his ex's 12-year-old son, which leads him to scheme up a hilarious, yet perfect plan to bring in the bacon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-22 15:20:00" d="2020-04-22 16:55:00" c="1"><n>Summer Rental</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% John Candy takes his first lead role as the stressed air traffic controller whose Florida family holiday turns into a nightmare. Bright and breezy comedy with Rip Torn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-22 16:55:00" d="2020-04-22 18:35:00" c="1"><n>Drunk On Love</n><t>F</t>    <k>Troublesome exes and nosy relatives cause problems for a lovestruck man who joins an Alcoholics Anonymous group to be closer to his stripper crush. Nick Robinson stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-22 18:35:00" d="2020-04-22 20:20:00" c="1"><n>Juliet, Naked</n><t>F</t>    <k>A relationship is turned upside down by a woman's chance encounter with an obscure rocker who has an obsessive fan - her boyfriend. Charming rom-com with Ethan Hawke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-22 20:20:00" d="2020-04-22 23:20:00" c="1"><n>Better Start Running</n><t>F</t>    <k>A shop clerk goes on the run with his dream girl when a warped chain of events leaves a relentless FBI duo hot on their tails. With Alex Sharp and Oscar</k>  </p>
</a>
