<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="13" t="2019-08-13 02:26:18"><p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-18 06:30:00" d="2019-08-18 08:15:00" c="1"><n>The Female Brain</n><t>F</t>    <k>Rom-com conventions get a brain scan as neuroscientist Whitney Cummings looks into the biochemistry of the female brain. With Sofia Vergara and Westworld's James Marsden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-18 08:15:00" d="2019-08-18 10:00:00" c="1"><n>Mean Machine</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Tough-tackling jail comedy with Vinnie Jones as the disgraced footballer blackmailed into leading a team of cons against the guards. With Jason Statham and Danny Dyer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-18 10:00:00" d="2019-08-18 11:45:00" c="1"><n>Weird Science</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Cult John Hughes comedy. Two teens build the perfect woman on their PC. Anthony Michael Hall, Kelly LeBrock, Bill Paxton and Robert Downey Jr star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-18 11:45:00" d="2019-08-18 13:25:00" c="1"><n>Paul Blart: Mall Cop</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% An out-of-shape security guard with delusions of grandeur is left to save the day when criminals hold up the mall. Family comedy with Kevin James</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-18 13:25:00" d="2019-08-18 15:30:00" c="1"><n>Crazy Rich Asians</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% When an NYU professor heads to Singapore with her boyfriend, she's surprised to learn he's from an extremely wealthy family. who aren't so approving of her. Hit romcom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-18 15:30:00" d="2019-08-18 17:20:00" c="1"><n>Blockers</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% A trio of concerned parents launch into a calamitous quest to stop their BFF high-school daughters from making good on a prom-night sex pact. Comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-18 17:20:00" d="2019-08-18 19:20:00" c="1"><n>Pitch Perfect</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% Aspiring music producer Anna Kendrick tries to add a touch of cool to her college a cappella group in this gag-packed musical comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-18 19:20:00" d="2019-08-18 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Paul Blart: Mall Cop</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% An out-of-shape security guard with delusions of grandeur is left to save the day when criminals hold up the mall. Family comedy with Kevin James</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-18 21:00:00" d="2019-08-18 23:05:00" c="1"><n>Crazy Rich Asians</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% When an NYU professor heads to Singapore with her boyfriend, she's surprised to learn he's from an extremely wealthy family. who aren't so approving of her. Hit romcom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-18 23:05:00" d="2019-08-19 00:50:00" c="1"><n>Blockers</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% A trio of concerned parents launch into a calamitous quest to stop their BFF high-school daughters from making good on a prom-night sex pact. Comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-19 00:50:00" d="2019-08-19 02:40:00" c="1"><n u="Beverly Hills Cop">Beverly Hills Cop II</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Motor-mouthed cop Axel Foley (Eddie Murphy) returns to LA to solve the 'alphabet robberies' that have been baffling local police. Action comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-19 02:40:00" d="2019-08-19 04:40:00" c="1"><n>Boomerang</n><t>F</t>    <k>56% Romcom starring Eddie Murphy as a womanising marketing director who meets his match in new boss Robin Givens. Halle Berry co-stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-19 04:40:00" d="2019-08-19 06:30:00" c="1"><n>Joyride</n><t>F</t>    <k>A trio of accidental outlaws find themselves on a cross-country road trip, with the police in hot pursuit. Big-hearted Kiwi crime caper with The Hobbit's Dean O'Gorman</k>  </p>
</a>
