<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="13" t="2019-08-13 02:26:22"><p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-19 06:30:00" d="2019-08-19 08:10:00" c="1"><n>Gloves Off</n><t>F</t>    <k>A down on his luck boxer attempts to save his beloved gym by training a talented bare-knuckle fighter. British comedy-drama with Ricky Tomlinson and Denise Van Outen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-19 08:10:00" d="2019-08-19 09:45:00" c="1"><n>Social Animals</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% Romantic comedy starring Noël Wells as a loveable loser attempting to save her struggling business and salvage her love life. With How I Met Your Mother's Josh Radnor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-19 09:45:00" d="2019-08-19 11:30:00" c="1"><n>Wayne's World</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Long-haired layabouts Mike Myers and Dana Carvey try to rescue their TV show from unscrupulous exec Rob Lowe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-19 11:30:00" d="2019-08-19 13:30:00" c="1"><n>Nobody's Fool</n><t>F</t>    <k>47% Tiffany Haddish and Whoopi Goldberg star in Tyler Perry's rom-com about an ex-con who suspects her high-flying sister is being catfished</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-19 13:30:00" d="2019-08-19 15:15:00" c="1"><n>Shaun Of The Dead</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% Life's a yawn for Shaun, until zombies take over London. Then it's a no guts, no glory rescue mission: to the pub! Comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-19 15:15:00" d="2019-08-19 17:00:00" c="1"><n u="Daddy's Home">Daddy's Home 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% Tensions boil over when the dad-stepdad double team of Will Ferrell and Mark Wahlberg invite their fathers over for Christmas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-19 17:00:00" d="2019-08-19 19:00:00" c="1"><n>Miss Congeniality</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% Breezy comedy starring Sandra Bullock as a tomboy FBI agent tasked with going undercover as a beauty queen to foil a terrorist plot. With Michael Caine and Benjamin Bratt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-19 19:00:00" d="2019-08-19 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Nobody's Fool</n><t>F</t>    <k>47% Tiffany Haddish and Whoopi Goldberg star in Tyler Perry's rom-com about an ex-con who suspects her high-flying sister is being catfished</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-19 21:00:00" d="2019-08-19 22:45:00" c="1"><n>Shaun Of The Dead</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% Life's a yawn for Shaun, until zombies take over London. Then it's a no guts, no glory rescue mission: to the pub! Comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-19 22:45:00" d="2019-08-20 00:30:00" c="1"><n u="Daddy's Home">Daddy's Home 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% Tensions boil over when the dad-stepdad double team of Will Ferrell and Mark Wahlberg invite their fathers over for Christmas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-20 00:30:00" d="2019-08-20 02:20:00" c="1"><n u="Beverly Hills Cop">Beverly Hills Cop III</n><t>F</t>    <k>56% Eddie Murphy returns as streetsmart detective Axel Foley, tracking a cop killer to an LA amusement park. Action comedy sequel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-20 02:20:00" d="2019-08-20 04:05:00" c="1"><n>Little Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>45% Tiny jewel thief Marlon Wayans must pose as a baby to retrieve his diamond stash. Pocket-sized comedy that punches below the belt, from the Scary Movie gang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-20 04:05:00" d="2019-08-20 05:50:00" c="1"><n>FML</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% Raucous road-trip comedy following two unlikely friends - a middle-aged comedian and a teen social media star - as they embark on a quest to reach a million followers</k>  </p>
</a>
