<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-04-16 04:36:38"><p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-23 05:25:00" d="2020-04-23 07:05:00" c="1"><n>Summer Rental</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% John Candy takes his first lead role as the stressed air traffic controller whose Florida family holiday turns into a nightmare. Bright and breezy comedy with Rip Torn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-23 07:05:00" d="2020-04-23 08:50:00" c="1"><n>50 First Dates</n><t>F</t>    <k>Adam Sandler finds his perfect match in Drew Barrymore. Everything is wonderful until the next day, when he discovers she's forgotten everything about him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-23 08:50:00" d="2020-04-23 10:35:00" c="1"><n>Mr Deeds</n><t>F</t>    <k>Smalltown chump Adam Sandler inherits a fortune (plus sneaky butler John Turturro). But his wealth draws gold-diggers and tricky reporter Winona Ryder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-23 10:35:00" d="2020-04-23 12:15:00" c="1"><n>Jack And Jill</n><t>F</t>    <k>36% A top ad exec is driven round the bend when his infuriating twin sister comes to stay. Boisterous comedy fun with Adam Sandler in both roles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-23 12:15:00" d="2020-04-23 13:55:00" c="1"><n>Happy Gilmore</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Hot-headed ice hockey player Adam Sandler swaps his stick for a golf club, but still struggles to curb his uncouth ways. Sporting comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-23 13:55:00" d="2020-04-23 15:55:00" c="1"><n>You Don't Mess With The Zohan</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% Israeli commando Adam Sandler fakes his own death so he can become a New York hairdresser. Comedy with John Turturro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-23 15:55:00" d="2020-04-23 17:40:00" c="1"><n>50 First Dates</n><t>F</t>    <k>Adam Sandler finds his perfect match in Drew Barrymore. Everything is wonderful until the next day, when he discovers she's forgotten everything about him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-23 17:40:00" d="2020-04-23 19:30:00" c="1"><n>Grown Ups</n><t>F</t>    <k>60% Knockabout fun as best buddies, including Adam Sandler, Kevin James and Chris Rock, get together for a weekend away. Chaotic comedy with Rob Schneider and Salma Hayek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-23 19:30:00" d="2020-04-23 21:15:00" c="1"><n u="Grown Ups">Grown Ups 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>54% Big kids Adam Sandler, Kevin James, David Spade and Chris Rock are back to cause more chaos. Comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-04-23 21:15:00" d="2020-04-24 00:15:00" c="1"><n>Happy Gilmore</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Hot-headed ice hockey player Adam Sandler swaps his stick for a golf club, but still struggles to curb his uncouth ways. Sporting comedy</k>  </p>
</a>
