<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-05-27 04:36:00"><p id_tv="1043" o="2020-06-03 05:30:00" d="2020-06-03 07:15:00" c="1"><n>Napoleon Dynamite</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Can high school geek Napoleon help his pal Pedro become class president? Jon Heder stars in this winning cult comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-06-03 07:15:00" d="2020-06-03 09:05:00" c="1"><n>Last Vegas</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Old pals Robert De Niro, Kevin Kline and Morgan Freeman travel to Las Vegas for friend Michael Douglas's bachelor party. Fun comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-06-03 09:05:00" d="2020-06-03 11:05:00" c="1"><n>How To Lose A Guy In 10 Days</n><t>F</t>    <k>Matthew McConaughey bets he can make reporter Kate Hudson fall for him, while she does her womanly worst to turn him off. Comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-06-03 11:05:00" d="2020-06-03 12:45:00" c="1"><n>Fletch</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% When a dying millionaire asks ace reporter Fletch (Chevy Chase) to bump him off, the hotshot hack knows he's stumbled onto a sensational story</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-06-03 12:45:00" d="2020-06-03 14:45:00" c="1"><n>Sorry To Bother You</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Dark comedy starring Lakeith Stanfield as a broke telemarketer, whose career takes a sinister and bizarre turn after he finds huge success using his 'white voice'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-06-03 14:45:00" d="2020-06-03 16:45:00" c="1"><n>The 40 Year Old Virgin</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% When nerdy Steve Carell's pals find out he's still a virgin they vow to help him out. Hit Judd Apatow comedy with Paul Rudd and Catherine Keener</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-06-03 16:45:00" d="2020-06-03 18:25:00" c="1"><n>Sell By</n><t>F</t>    <k>Ensemble romcom following once-passionate couples as they muddle through life in the smartphone era</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-06-03 18:25:00" d="2020-06-03 20:25:00" c="1"><n>How To Lose A Guy In 10 Days</n><t>F</t>    <k>Matthew McConaughey bets he can make reporter Kate Hudson fall for him, while she does her womanly worst to turn him off. Comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-06-03 20:25:00" d="2020-06-03 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Family</n><t>F</t>    <k>A socially awkward woman is tasked with babysitting her equally awkward niece - and everything quickly goes awry. Comedy with Taylor Schilling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-06-03 22:00:00" d="2020-06-04 01:00:00" c="1"><n>The 40 Year Old Virgin</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% When nerdy Steve Carell's pals find out he's still a virgin they vow to help him out. Hit Judd Apatow comedy with Paul Rudd and Catherine Keener</k>  </p>
</a>
