<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="13" t="2019-08-15 22:51:26"><p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-21 06:30:00" d="2019-08-21 08:15:00" c="1"><n>Half Magic</n><t>F</t>    <k>Bawdy comedy about three new friends desperate for more from life and love. Heather Graham writes, directs and stars alongside Brooklyn Nine-Nine's Stephanie Beatriz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-21 08:15:00" d="2019-08-21 09:55:00" c="1"><n>The Brits Are Coming</n><t>F</t>    <k>Breezy crime caper starring Uma Thurman and Tim Roth as a con-artist couple out to settle a gambling debt by pulling off a jewel heist. With Stephen Fry and Sofia Vergara</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-21 09:55:00" d="2019-08-21 11:35:00" c="1"><n>Night Owls</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% A one-night stand takes a disastrous turn when nice guy Adam Pally (The Mindy Project) discovers that the girl he's gone home with is his boss's ex-mistress. Dark rom-com</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-21 11:35:00" d="2019-08-21 13:20:00" c="1"><n>Look Who's Talking</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% Smash-hit comedy following single mother Kirstie Alley on her search for the perfect husband and father to baby Mikey (voiced by Bruce Willis). With John Travolta</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-21 13:20:00" d="2019-08-21 15:15:00" c="1"><n>The World's End</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Five friends attempting an epic pub crawl end up with the fate of the world in their hands. Comedy starring Simon Pegg and Nick Frost</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-21 15:15:00" d="2019-08-21 17:05:00" c="1"><n>Slaughterhouse Rulez</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% Chaos descends on an esteemed British boarding school when a mysterious sinkhole appears and unleashes pure terror. Comedy horror with Simon Pegg and Asa Butterfield</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-21 17:05:00" d="2019-08-21 19:25:00" c="1"><n>Downsizing</n><t>F</t>    <k>57% Alexander Payne (Sideways) directs this intelligent sci-fi satire set in a world where people can be shrunk down to five inches tall. Matt Damon stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-21 19:25:00" d="2019-08-21 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Mr Bean's Holiday</n><t>F</t>    <k>Mr Bean wins a holiday to Cannes. The French don't stand a chance. Comedy sequel of prawns and pratfalls, starring Rowan Atkinson and Willem Dafoe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-21 21:00:00" d="2019-08-21 23:00:00" c="1"><n>The World's End</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Five friends attempting an epic pub crawl end up with the fate of the world in their hands. Comedy starring Simon Pegg and Nick Frost</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-21 23:00:00" d="2019-08-22 00:50:00" c="1"><n>Slaughterhouse Rulez</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% Chaos descends on an esteemed British boarding school when a mysterious sinkhole appears and unleashes pure terror. Comedy horror with Simon Pegg and Asa Butterfield</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-22 00:50:00" d="2019-08-22 02:45:00" c="1"><n>Step Brothers</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% When their parents get married, step brothers Will Ferrell and John C Reilly are forced to grow up and move out. Extended version</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-22 02:45:00" d="2019-08-22 04:20:00" c="1"><n>Zoolander</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Model Ben Stiller is suddenly yesterday's face when cool Owen Wilson becomes the toast of the fashion world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-08-22 04:20:00" d="2019-08-22 06:15:00" c="1"><n>O Brother, Where Art Thou?</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% George Clooney and two pals escape the chain gang and go on a quest for treasure in 1930s Mississippi. From the Coen brothers</k>  </p>
</a>
