<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-05-12 04:38:14"><p id_tv="1043" o="2020-05-19 06:05:00" d="2020-05-19 08:10:00" c="1"><n>Fighting Temptations</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% Cuba Gooding Jr will only get his inheritance if he leads his late aunt's dire gospel choir to glory. Can lounge singer Beyonce Knowles help him triumph? Musical comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-05-19 08:10:00" d="2020-05-19 09:55:00" c="1"><n>You, Me and Him</n><t>F</t>    <k>Chaos ensues in this comedy-drama, when a lesbian couple both become pregnant. David Tennant and Lucy Punch star. Contains potentially upsetting scenes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-05-19 09:55:00" d="2020-05-19 11:45:00" c="1"><n>Fletch</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% When a dying millionaire asks ace reporter Fletch (Chevy Chase) to bump him off, the hotshot hack knows he's stumbled onto a sensational story</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-05-19 11:45:00" d="2020-05-19 13:30:00" c="1"><n>Eighth Grade</n><t>F</t>    <k>Introverted 13-year-old Kayla tries to make it through the last week of a disastrous year in eighth grade before starting high school. Comedy from Bo Burnham</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-05-19 13:30:00" d="2020-05-19 15:45:00" c="1"><n>Fighting Temptations</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% Cuba Gooding Jr will only get his inheritance if he leads his late aunt's dire gospel choir to glory. Can lounge singer Beyonce Knowles help him triumph? Musical comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-05-19 15:45:00" d="2020-05-19 17:25:00" c="1"><n u="Undercover Brother">Undercover Brother 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>Sixteen years on, Undercover Brother's little brother decides to finish the job they began together. Comedy sequel with Michael Jai White</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-05-19 17:25:00" d="2020-05-19 19:00:00" c="1"><n>Zoolander</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Model Ben Stiller is suddenly yesterday's face when cool Owen Wilson becomes the toast of the fashion world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-05-19 19:00:00" d="2020-05-19 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Kingpin</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Woody Harrelson thinks Randy Quaid could be a tenpin king, but Bill Murray isn't champ for nothing. Classic comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-05-19 21:00:00" d="2020-05-19 23:05:00" c="1"><n>Crazy, Stupid, Love</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% A middle-aged man has a perfect life. ntil his wife divorces him and he's suddenly catapulted into the world of dating. Rom-com starring Steve Carell and Ryan Gosling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-05-19 23:05:00" d="2020-05-20 02:05:00" c="1"><n>Eighth Grade</n><t>F</t>    <k>Introverted 13-year-old Kayla tries to make it through the last week of a disastrous year in eighth grade before starting high school. Comedy from Bo Burnham</k>  </p>
</a>
