<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-05-16 04:56:40"><p id_tv="1043" o="2020-05-23 05:45:00" d="2020-05-23 07:45:00" c="1"><n>That Thing You Do!</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Tom Hanks makes his directing debut with an upbeat tale about a 60s boy band. Comedy featuring early roles for Liv Tyler and Charlize Theron</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-05-23 07:45:00" d="2020-05-23 09:45:00" c="1"><n>Night School</n><t>F</t>    <k>56% Comedy about a group of troublesome adults who are forced to attend night classes in a bid to finish high school. Starring Kevin Hart and Tiffany Haddish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-05-23 09:45:00" d="2020-05-23 11:35:00" c="1"><n>Hot Tub Time Machine</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% John Cusack and pals get sent back to 1986 by a sudsy time machine in this crazy quantum-leaping comedy. With Craig Robinson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-05-23 11:35:00" d="2020-05-23 13:15:00" c="1"><n>Better Start Running</n><t>F</t>    <k>A shop clerk goes on the run with his dream girl when a warped chain of events leaves a relentless FBI duo hot on their tails. With Alex Sharp and Oscar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-05-23 13:15:00" d="2020-05-23 15:20:00" c="1"><n>Instant Family</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% A couple decide to adopt, but get more than they bargained for when they take in a rebellious teen and her two siblings. Comedy-drama with Mark Wahlberg and Rose Byrne</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-05-23 15:20:00" d="2020-05-23 17:10:00" c="1"><n>Grand-Daddy Day Care</n><t>F</t>    <k>A writer is inspired to start a day care business when his father-in-law moves in. But looking after a group of seniors isn't as easy as he thinks. Slapstick comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-05-23 17:10:00" d="2020-05-23 19:15:00" c="1"><n>How To Lose A Guy In 10 Days</n><t>F</t>    <k>Matthew McConaughey bets he can make reporter Kate Hudson fall for him, while she does her womanly worst to turn him off. Comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-05-23 19:15:00" d="2020-05-23 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Tag</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Comedy following a group of super-competitive friends who every year play a marathon, month-long game of tag. Starring Ed Helms, Jon Hamm and Jeremy Renner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-05-23 21:00:00" d="2020-05-23 23:05:00" c="1"><n>Instant Family</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% A couple decide to adopt, but get more than they bargained for when they take in a rebellious teen and her two siblings. Comedy-drama with Mark Wahlberg and Rose Byrne</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2020-05-23 23:05:00" d="2020-05-24 02:05:00" c="1"><n>Hot Tub Time Machine</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% John Cusack and pals get sent back to 1986 by a sudsy time machine in this crazy quantum-leaping comedy. With Craig Robinson</k>  </p>
</a>
