<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="13" t="2019-07-11 00:20:58"><p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-16 05:40:00" d="2019-07-16 07:30:00" c="1"><n>Roxanne</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Long-nosed fire chief Steve Martin falls for astronomer Daryl Hannah, but his eccentric looks make him too shy to make a move. Comedy retelling of Cyrano de Bergerac</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-16 07:30:00" d="2019-07-16 09:05:00" c="1"><n>Extracurricular Activities</n><t>F</t>    <k>A savvy student makes a killing from arranging 'accidents' for the overbearing parents of his peers. But is he smart enough to ward off a suspicious cop? Comedy thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-16 09:05:00" d="2019-07-16 10:40:00" c="1"><n>My Blind Brother</n><t>F</t>    <k>60% Slacker Nick Kroll and brother Adam Scott, a blind, marathon-running local celebrity, find themselves falling for the same girl. Romantic comedy co-starring Jenny Slate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-16 10:40:00" d="2019-07-16 12:40:00" c="1"><n>Patch Adams</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Robin Williams is the medic who believes laughter is the best medicine, but struggles to convince the authorities of his methods</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-16 12:40:00" d="2019-07-16 14:45:00" c="1"><n>Crazy, Stupid, Love</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% A middle-aged man has a perfect life. ntil his wife divorces him and he's suddenly catapulted into the world of dating. Rom-com starring Steve Carell and Ryan Gosling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-16 14:45:00" d="2019-07-16 17:00:00" c="1"><n>The Terminal</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% Immigrant Tom Hanks lands in New York, but becomes confined to the airport when he is caught in political limbo. From Steven Spielberg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-16 17:00:00" d="2019-07-16 19:10:00" c="1"><n>Think Like A Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Four relationships are thrown into chaos by the release of a book offering relationship advice. Rom-com starring Kevin Hart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-16 19:10:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Ghostbusters</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% Classic 80s comedy starring Bill Murray and Dan Aykroyd as paranormal experts battling the supernatural</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 23:05:00" c="1"><n>Crazy, Stupid, Love</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% A middle-aged man has a perfect life. ntil his wife divorces him and he's suddenly catapulted into the world of dating. Rom-com starring Steve Carell and Ryan Gosling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-16 23:05:00" d="2019-07-17 00:50:00" c="1"><n u="Super Troopers">Super Troopers 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>60% An unexpected border dispute between the US and Canada gives a group of disgraced state troopers a second chance. Comedy sequel with Rob Lowe and Brian Cox</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-17 00:50:00" d="2019-07-17 02:50:00" c="1"><n>The Other Guys</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Calamitous cops Will Ferrell and Mark Wahlberg stumble on a case which could repair their terrible reputations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-17 02:50:00" d="2019-07-17 04:50:00" c="1"><n>American Pie: Reunion</n><t>F</t>    <k>The gang go to their school reunion in this hilarious fourth entry in the hit series. Jason Biggs and Seann William Scott star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1043" o="2019-07-17 04:50:00" d="2019-07-17 06:30:00" c="1"><n>How To Get Girls</n><t>F</t>    <k>39% A nerdy teen attempts to use his best friend's post-puberty good looks to climb the social ladder and meet girls. Coming-of-age comedy with Anchorman's David Koechner</k>  </p>
</a>
