<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-04-09 04:35:59"><p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-16 05:15:00" d="2020-04-16 07:00:00" c="1"><n>Angel Flight Down</n><t>F</t>    <k>51% A child's life is at stake when an emergency flight crashes in the snowy wilderness. Adventure based on a true story with former Baywatch star David Charvet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-16 07:00:00" d="2020-04-16 08:45:00" c="1"><n>Accident</n><t>F</t>    <k>A joyride takes a terrifying turn for a group of teenagers when they suffer a horrific car crash and find themselves trapped at the bottom of a ravine. Thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-16 08:45:00" d="2020-04-16 10:35:00" c="1"><n>Out Of Blue</n><t>F</t>    <k>49% A police officer stumbles upon a world of cosmic secrets when she is profoundly impacted by her investigation into the murder of an astrophysicist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-16 10:35:00" d="2020-04-16 12:15:00" c="1"><n>Monsters And Men</n><t>F</t>    <k>Drama following three interweaving tales, including that of a young Brooklyn father who witnesses a police shooting of an unarmed black man</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-16 12:15:00" d="2020-04-16 13:55:00" c="1"><n>Poseidon</n><t>F</t>    <k>57% Kurt Russell leads a motley band of survivors on a perilous quest for safety when their cruise ship is upended by a freak wave. Disaster thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-16 13:55:00" d="2020-04-16 15:25:00" c="1"><n>Knuckleball</n><t>F</t>    <k>A 12-year-old boy finds himself in the midst of a terrifying ordeal, targeted, alone, and on an isolated farm. Thriller with Michael Ironside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-16 15:25:00" d="2020-04-16 16:55:00" c="1"><n>November Criminals</n><t>F</t>    <k>54% A high-school student launches an investigation into the mysterious murder of his friend, but discovers that it's more twisted and dark than he ever could have imagined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-16 16:55:00" d="2020-04-16 18:30:00" c="1"><n>The Standoff At Sparrow Creek</n><t>F</t>    <k>Suspense-filled claustrophobic thriller in which Texan militia-men turn on each other after their group is linked to a mass shooting. With Brian Geraghty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-16 18:30:00" d="2020-04-16 20:20:00" c="1"><n>Strange But True</n><t>F</t>    <k>A woman shocks the family of her dead boyfriend when she contacts them five years after his death, claiming to be pregnant with his child. Suspense-filled noir-thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-16 20:20:00" d="2020-04-16 23:20:00" c="1"><n>Poseidon</n><t>F</t>    <k>57% Kurt Russell leads a motley band of survivors on a perilous quest for safety when their cruise ship is upended by a freak wave. Disaster thriller</k>  </p>
</a>
