<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-08-13 02:26:31"><p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-19 06:00:00" d="2019-08-19 07:45:00" c="1"><n>Angel Flight Down</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% A child's life is at stake when an emergency flight crashes in the snowy wilderness. Adventure based on a true story with former Baywatch star David Charvet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-19 07:45:00" d="2019-08-19 10:15:00" c="1"><n>Hoffa</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Jack Nicholson stars as a union leader whose underworld connections lead to his downfall. Danny DeVito directs. Drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-19 10:15:00" d="2019-08-19 12:00:00" c="1"><n>Monsters And Men</n><t>F</t>    <k>Drama following three interweaving tales, including that of a young Brooklyn father who witnesses a police shooting of an unarmed black man</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-19 12:00:00" d="2019-08-19 13:45:00" c="1"><n>In Darkness</n><t>F</t>    <k>Blind pianist Natalie Dormer (who also co-writes) is drawn into a brutal criminal underworld after she overhears an attack on her neighbour. Thriller with Ed Skrein</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-19 13:45:00" d="2019-08-19 15:50:00" c="1"><n u="The Equalizer">The Equalizer 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Denzel Washington reprises his role as retired CIA agent Robert McCall in this fast-paced thriller. The murder of an old friend triggers a relentless quest for revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-19 15:50:00" d="2019-08-19 18:00:00" c="1"><n>The Town</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% Bank robber Ben Affleck falls for Rebecca Hall after heisting her workplace. Crime thriller with Jeremy Renner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-19 18:00:00" d="2019-08-19 20:00:00" c="1"><n>Gone In 60 Seconds</n><t>F</t>    <k>To save his brother from gangsters, legendary auto thief Nicolas Cage must steal 50 classic cars in one night. Action co-starring Angelina Jolie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-19 20:00:00" d="2019-08-19 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Three Billboards Outside Ebbing Missouri</n><t>F</t>    <k>An Oscar-winning Frances McDormand stars as a grieving mother out to shame the police into doing their job. Blackly comic drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-19 22:00:00" d="2019-08-20 00:05:00" c="1"><n u="The Equalizer">The Equalizer 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Denzel Washington reprises his role as retired CIA agent Robert McCall in this fast-paced thriller. The murder of an old friend triggers a relentless quest for revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-20 00:05:00" d="2019-08-20 02:20:00" c="1"><n>Se7en</n><t>F</t>    <k>Dark thriller starring Brad Pitt and Morgan Freeman as homicide detectives on the trail of a sick and twisted psychopath with a unique way of choosing his victims</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-20 02:20:00" d="2019-08-20 04:00:00" c="1"><n>Backtrace</n><t>F</t>    <k>A criminal with amnesia is forced to take a dangerous memory enhancing drug when he can't recall where the cash from a $20m bank raid is located. With Sylvester Stallone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-20 04:00:00" d="2019-08-20 05:55:00" c="1"><n>The Hurricane Heist</n><t>F</t>    <k>51% Full-throttle thriller about a team of hackers using a devastating hurricane as cover to steal millions. Sky Cinema Original Film from Rob Cohen</k>  </p>
</a>
