<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-05-29 04:36:20"><p id_tv="1044" o="2020-06-05 06:10:00" d="2020-06-05 07:55:00" c="1"><n>Sam Churchill: Search For A Homeless Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>Thriller about an ex-surfer turned detective (The Dukes Of Hazzard's John Schneider) who tracks a hostage held by a dangerous gang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-06-05 07:55:00" d="2020-06-05 09:40:00" c="1"><n>Jacob's Ladder</n><t>F</t>    <k>A surgeon's life unravels when he finds out his brother has died in Afghanistan and begins to experience mind-bending paranoia. Psychological thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-06-05 09:40:00" d="2020-06-05 12:00:00" c="1"><n>Papillon</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% Drama following the incredible story of Henri Charriere, and his fight to escape the brutal penal colony on Devil's Island when he is framed for murder. With Rami Malek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-06-05 12:00:00" d="2020-06-05 14:00:00" c="1"><n>SuperFly</n><t>F</t>    <k>51% A drug lord decides it's time to bow out of the game - but not before one last deal. Unfortunately for him, it looks like it's going to be the toughest one yet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-06-05 14:00:00" d="2020-06-05 15:55:00" c="1"><n>Miss Bala</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% A woman gets drawn into the murky world of cross-border crime as she battles to save her friend, who's been kidnapped in Mexico. Action thriller with Gina Rodriguez</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-06-05 15:55:00" d="2020-06-05 17:55:00" c="1"><n>The Italian Job</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% A gang of double-crossed thieves plan to cause a monumental traffic jam in a bid to reclaim their loot. Starring Mark Wahlberg and Ed Norton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-06-05 17:55:00" d="2020-06-05 19:45:00" c="1"><n>Poseidon</n><t>F</t>    <k>57% Kurt Russell leads a motley band of survivors on a perilous quest for safety when their cruise ship is upended by a freak wave. Disaster thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-06-05 19:45:00" d="2020-06-05 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Papillon</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% Drama following the incredible story of Henri Charriere, and his fight to escape the brutal penal colony on Devil's Island when he is framed for murder. With Rami Malek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-06-05 22:00:00" d="2020-06-06 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Cape Fear</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Robert De Niro stars as a convicted rapist who sets out to exact revenge on his lawyer. Taut thriller from Martin Scorsese</k>  </p>
</a>
