<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2019-08-11 01:39:31"><p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-17 06:20:00" d="2019-08-17 08:05:00" c="1"><n>Sam Churchill: Search For A Homeless Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>Thriller about an ex-surfer turned detective (The Dukes Of Hazzard's John Schneider) who tracks a hostage held by a dangerous gang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-17 08:05:00" d="2019-08-17 10:00:00" c="1"><n>Anon</n><t>F</t>    <k>60% Stylish sci-fi thriller starring Clive Owen as a troubled near-future detective investigating a series of mysterious murders. Sky Cinema Original Film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-17 10:00:00" d="2019-08-17 12:00:00" c="1"><n>John Q</n><t>F</t>    <k>Unable to afford the medical bills, desperate dad Denzel Washington holds the emergency room hostage until his young son gets a life-saving operation. Powerful drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-17 12:00:00" d="2019-08-17 14:40:00" c="1"><n>Zodiac</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% David Fincher's gripping crime thriller stars Jake Gyllenhaal as a newspaper cartoonist obsessed with tracking down the Zodiac killer. With Mark Ruffalo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-17 14:40:00" d="2019-08-17 16:45:00" c="1"><n>The Snowman</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% Adaptation of the bestselling Jo Nesbo thriller starring Michael Fassbender as a hard-drinking Oslo detective on the trail of a serial killer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-17 16:45:00" d="2019-08-17 18:25:00" c="1"><n>The Transporter</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Ice cool Jason Statham transports anything, no questions asked. However, one package could be his undoing in this crime thriller from writer Luc Besson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-17 18:25:00" d="2019-08-17 20:00:00" c="1"><n u="Transporter">Transporter 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>Driver Jason Statham burns rubber in a race to clear his name, save a kidnapped boy and take down a Colombian coke baron. Action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-17 20:00:00" d="2019-08-17 22:00:00" c="1"><n>The Untouchables</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% Robert De Niro stars as mob boss Al Capone, with Kevin Costner as the Treasury agent determined to take him down. Gangland thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-17 22:00:00" d="2019-08-18 01:00:00" c="1"><n u="The Godfather Part">The Godfather Part II</n><t>F</t>    <k>Robert De Niro won his first Oscar as a young Don Corleone, with Al Pacino as his ruthless successor, in this mighty Mob epic</k>  </p>
</a>
