<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-04-15 04:36:14"><p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-22 06:25:00" d="2020-04-22 08:10:00" c="1"><n>Sam Churchill: Search For A Homeless Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>Thriller about an ex-surfer turned detective (The Dukes Of Hazzard's John Schneider) who tracks a hostage held by a dangerous gang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-22 08:10:00" d="2020-04-22 10:25:00" c="1"><n>Marnie</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% Tippi Hedren lies, steals and hates men. But Sean Connery only finds out why after blackmailing her into marriage. From Alfred Hitchcock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-22 10:25:00" d="2020-04-22 12:25:00" c="1"><n>The Birds</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Unflappable socialite Tippi Hedren follows a handsome lawyer back to his coastal home, but becomes terrorized by flocks of angry birds. Legendary Hitchcock horror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-22 12:25:00" d="2020-04-22 14:40:00" c="1"><n>Vertigo</n><t>F</t>    <k>83% James Stewart is the detective with a fear of heights driven over the edge by icy blonde Kim Novak. Alfred Hitchcock's dizzying tale of obsession and intrigue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-22 14:40:00" d="2020-04-22 16:35:00" c="1"><n>Rear Window</n><t>F</t>    <k>84% Alfred Hitchcock's masterpiece sees a housebound James Stewart convinced his neighbour has murdered someone, recruiting Grace Kelly to investigate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-22 16:35:00" d="2020-04-22 18:25:00" c="1"><n>Psycho</n><t>F</t>    <k>85% Thief Janet Leigh makes a terrible mistake when she checks into a secluded motel run by Anthony Perkins. Alfred Hitchcock directs this groundbreaking thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-22 18:25:00" d="2020-04-22 20:00:00" c="1"><n>Jacob's Ladder</n><t>F</t>    <k>A surgeon's life unravels when he finds out his brother has died in Afghanistan and begins to experience mind-bending paranoia. Psychological thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-22 20:00:00" d="2020-04-22 23:00:00" c="1"><n>Gran Torino</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% Drama starring Clint Eastwood as a cantankerous Korean War veteran who reluctantly becomes a hero to his immigrant neighbours</k>  </p>
</a>
