<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-07-11 00:20:59"><p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-15 06:10:00" d="2019-07-15 07:55:00" c="1"><n>Point Last Seen</n><t>F</t>    <k>60% As tracker Linda Hamilton searches the desert for a missing girl, she's haunted by the disappearance of her own children, snatched by their violent dad. Drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-15 07:55:00" d="2019-07-15 09:30:00" c="1"><n>30 Minutes Or Less</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% When pizza boy Jesse Eisenberg is bound to a bomb and blackmailed, he needs to make a fast delivery of $100,000 or he'll be pepperoni. Comedy with Danny McBride</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-15 09:30:00" d="2019-07-15 11:20:00" c="1"><n>Affairs Of State</n><t>F</t>    <k>A young campaign aide proves he's willing to do almost anything to get ahead, but his schemes soon catch up with him. Political drama with Entourage's Adrian Grenier</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-15 11:20:00" d="2019-07-15 12:50:00" c="1"><n>B&amp;B</n><t>F</t>    <k>A gay couple refused a double bed at a remote Christian guest house decide to return after a court win. Then a Russian neo-Nazi checks in. Dark British thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-15 12:50:00" d="2019-07-15 15:20:00" c="1"><n>Mission: Impossible - Fallout</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% It's a race against time for Ethan Hunt and the team when a mission goes seriously wrong and a nuclear attack is on the horizon. Tom Cruise and Henry Cavill star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-15 15:20:00" d="2019-07-15 17:25:00" c="1"><n>The Mexican</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Brad Pitt and Julia Roberts star in a wild road caper involving a cursed antique gun, kidnapping and a sensitive Mob hitman. Co-starring the late James Gandolfini</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-15 17:25:00" d="2019-07-15 19:25:00" c="1"><n>The Snowman</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% Adaptation of the bestselling Jo Nesbo thriller starring Michael Fassbender as a hard-drinking Oslo detective on the trail of a serial killer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-15 19:25:00" d="2019-07-15 22:00:00" c="1"><n>The Firm</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Young lawyer Tom Cruise becomes embroiled in his new firm's shady dealings. Sydney Pollack directs this gripping drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-15 22:00:00" d="2019-07-16 00:30:00" c="1"><n>Mission: Impossible - Fallout</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% It's a race against time for Ethan Hunt and the team when a mission goes seriously wrong and a nuclear attack is on the horizon. Tom Cruise and Henry Cavill star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-16 00:30:00" d="2019-07-16 02:25:00" c="1"><n>Extremely Wicked, Shockingly...</n><t>F</t>    <k>Sky Cinema original exploring the horrific crimes of Ted Bundy (Zac Efron) as told from the perspective of his girlfriend Elizabeth Kloepfer (Lily Collins)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-16 02:25:00" d="2019-07-16 04:25:00" c="1"><n>Fatal Attraction</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Married Michael Douglas has a one-night stand with Glenn Close, but the bunny-hating harpy isn't ready to say goodbye. Thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-16 04:25:00" d="2019-07-16 06:25:00" c="1"><n>Sudden Impact</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% In his fourth outing as 'Dirty' Harry Callahan, Clint Eastwood - who also directs - tracks down a rape victim who is killing off the men responsible. Gritty thriller</k>  </p>
</a>
