<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2019-08-13 02:26:34"><p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-20 05:55:00" d="2019-08-20 07:40:00" c="1"><n>Point Last Seen</n><t>F</t>    <k>59% As tracker Linda Hamilton searches the desert for a missing girl, she's haunted by the disappearance of her own children, snatched by their violent dad. Drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-20 07:40:00" d="2019-08-20 09:25:00" c="1"><n>Beast Of Burden</n><t>F</t>    <k>36% Daniel Radcliffe stars as a drug-running pilot facing a desperate choice when his final job turns into a nightmare. Thriller with Orange Is the New Black's Pablo Schreiber</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-20 09:25:00" d="2019-08-20 11:10:00" c="1"><n>Thoroughbreds</n><t>F</t>    <k>Blackly comic thriller starring Olivia Cooke and Anya Taylor-Joy as estranged childhood friends who begin to form an unsettling new bond</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-20 11:10:00" d="2019-08-20 12:50:00" c="1"><n>Knuckleball</n><t>F</t>    <k>A 12-year-old boy finds himself in the midst of a terrifying ordeal, targeted, alone, and on an isolated farm. Thriller with Michael Ironside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-20 12:50:00" d="2019-08-20 14:20:00" c="1"><n>B&amp;B</n><t>F</t>    <k>A gay couple refused a double bed at a remote Christian guest house decide to return after a court win. Then a Russian neo-Nazi checks in. Dark British thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-20 14:20:00" d="2019-08-20 16:20:00" c="1"><n>The Girl In The Spider's Web</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% Claire Foy plays a savvy hacker on a frantic hunt for a stolen computer programme that could spark a global disaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-20 16:20:00" d="2019-08-20 18:00:00" c="1"><n>Breaking In</n><t>F</t>    <k>Gabrielle Union stars as a mother forced to desperately protect her family from four home invaders. Thriller from V for Vendetta director James McTeigue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-20 18:00:00" d="2019-08-20 20:00:00" c="1"><n>Black Swan</n><t>F</t>    <k>An Oscar-winning Natalie Portman plays a ballerina who mentally unravels as she pursues her dream role. Psychological drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-20 20:00:00" d="2019-08-20 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Extremely Wicked, Shockingly...</n><t>F</t>    <k>Sky Cinema original exploring the horrific crimes of Ted Bundy (Zac Efron) as told from the perspective of his girlfriend Elizabeth Kloepfer (Lily Collins)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-20 22:00:00" d="2019-08-21 01:00:00" c="1"><n>The Girl In The Spider's Web</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% Claire Foy plays a savvy hacker on a frantic hunt for a stolen computer programme that could spark a global disaster</k>  </p>
</a>
