<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-08-15 22:51:33"><p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-21 06:25:00" d="2019-08-21 08:10:00" c="1"><n>Sam Churchill: Search For A Homeless Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>Thriller about an ex-surfer turned detective (The Dukes Of Hazzard's John Schneider) who tracks a hostage held by a dangerous gang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-21 08:10:00" d="2019-08-21 10:10:00" c="1"><n>Sweet Country</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% After he shoots a white man in self-defence, Aboriginal farmhand Sam is forced to flee through the unforgiving outback of 1920s Australia. Gritty western with Sam Neill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-21 10:10:00" d="2019-08-21 12:00:00" c="1"><n>Serenity</n><t>F</t>    <k>53% Steamy thriller starring Matthew McConaughey as a fishing boat captain whose tranquil life is shattered by the arrival of ex-wife Anne Hathaway. Sky Cinema Original Film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-21 12:00:00" d="2019-08-21 13:45:00" c="1"><n>The Ladykillers</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% The Coen brothers' stateside revamp of the classic Ealing comedy sees five bungling bank robbers falling foul of their elderly landlady. Starring Tom Hanks and JK Simmons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-21 13:45:00" d="2019-08-21 15:40:00" c="1"><n>John Q</n><t>F</t>    <k>Unable to afford the medical bills, desperate dad Denzel Washington holds the emergency room hostage until his young son gets a life-saving operation. Powerful drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-21 15:40:00" d="2019-08-21 17:30:00" c="1"><n>The Negotiator</n><t>F</t>    <k>Former US diplomat Jon Hamm is forced to return to the scene of a heartbreaking tragedy in order to negotiate the release of an old friend. Thriller with Rosamund Pike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-21 17:30:00" d="2019-08-21 19:05:00" c="1"><n>Proud Mary</n><t>F</t>    <k>Action thriller starring Taraji P Henson as a Boston hitwoman who develops a bond with a young boy orphaned by a job gone bad. With Danny Glover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-21 19:05:00" d="2019-08-21 22:00:00" c="1"><n>The Godfather</n><t>F</t>    <k>92% Marlon Brando won Best Actor as the ageing Mafia don replaced by steely son Al Pacino. Francis Ford Coppola's towering Mob epic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-21 22:00:00" d="2019-08-22 00:00:00" c="1"><n>Murder On The Orient Express</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Starry adaptation of Agatha Christie's classic murder mystery novel, with director Kenneth Branagh also playing Belgian sleuth Hercule Poirot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-22 00:00:00" d="2019-08-22 02:00:00" c="1"><n>SuperFly</n><t>F</t>    <k>51% A drug lord decides it's time to bow out of the game - but not before one last deal. Unfortunately for him, it looks like it's going to be the toughest one yet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-22 02:00:00" d="2019-08-22 03:45:00" c="1"><n>48 Hrs.</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Grizzled cop Nick Nolte and wiseass crook Eddie Murphy clash when they're thrown together to catch a killer. Action comedy hit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-22 03:45:00" d="2019-08-22 05:30:00" c="1"><n>Another 48 Hrs</n><t>F</t>    <k>Nick Nolte's no-nonsense cop reteams with Eddie Murphy's motor-mouthed crook to take down a ruthless San Francisco drug lord</k>  </p>
</a>
