<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-04-10 04:37:01"><p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-17 06:00:00" d="2020-04-17 07:45:00" c="1"><n>Point Last Seen</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% As tracker Linda Hamilton searches the desert for a missing girl, she's haunted by the disappearance of her own children, snatched by their violent dad. Drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-17 07:45:00" d="2020-04-17 09:35:00" c="1"><n>Reprisal</n><t>F</t>    <k>42% A bank manager teams up with his ex-cop neighbour to hunt down the thieves who killed his friend in a botched heist. Action thriller starring Frank Grillo and Bruce Willis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-17 09:35:00" d="2020-04-17 11:20:00" c="1"><n>Dogman</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% A gentle dog groomer finds himself pitted against a violent former boxer who's been terrorising his neighbourhood. Crime drama. In Italian with English subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-17 11:20:00" d="2020-04-17 13:00:00" c="1"><n>10 Minutes Gone</n><t>F</t>    <k>35% A man suffers amnesia during a bank heist gone wrong. Now he's being hunted, and must find a way to remember who sabotaged him. Bruce Willis and Michael Chiklis star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-17 13:00:00" d="2020-04-17 14:50:00" c="1"><n>Darkness Visible</n><t>F</t>    <k>Ronnie travels to India after his mother goes missing. He finds a strange Kolkata hospital, and makes a gruesome discovery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-17 14:50:00" d="2020-04-17 16:25:00" c="1"><n>Galveston</n><t>F</t>    <k>When a dying mob hitman is set up by his boss, he flees to his hometown of Galveston where he plots his revenge. But can he stay safe? Action starring Ben Foster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-17 16:25:00" d="2020-04-17 18:20:00" c="1"><n>The Hummingbird Project</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Jesse Eisenberg and Alexander Skarsgard play for big money in high-frequency trading. As they try to cash in from a fibre-optic cable line, problems arise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-17 18:20:00" d="2020-04-17 19:55:00" c="1"><n>Jacob's Ladder</n><t>F</t>    <k>A surgeon's life unravels when he finds out his brother has died in Afghanistan and begins to experience mind-bending paranoia. Psychological thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-04-17 19:55:00" d="2020-04-17 22:55:00" c="1"><n>Argo</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Ben Affleck's CIA agent is charged with bringing home six Americans stranded in revolutionary Iran. Oscar-winning thriller</k>  </p>
</a>
