<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-08-09 01:41:45"><p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-15 06:15:00" d="2019-08-15 08:00:00" c="1"><n>Angel Flight Down</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% A child's life is at stake when an emergency flight crashes in the snowy wilderness. Adventure based on a true story with former Baywatch star David Charvet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-15 08:00:00" d="2019-08-15 10:00:00" c="1"><n>Uncle John</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Dual-narrative drama that weaves together the tales of two courting co-workers and a small-town widower first seen disposing of a body. Midnight Run's John Ashton stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-15 10:00:00" d="2019-08-15 11:50:00" c="1"><n>Monsters And Men</n><t>F</t>    <k>Drama following three interweaving tales, including that of a young Brooklyn father who witnesses a police shooting of an unarmed black man</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-15 11:50:00" d="2019-08-15 13:45:00" c="1"><n u="Ocean's">Ocean's 8</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% After getting out of prison, Debbie Ocean plots to steal a priceless necklace from New York's Met Gala. Heist caper with Sandra Bullock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-15 13:45:00" d="2019-08-15 15:35:00" c="1"><n>The Ladykillers</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% The Coen brothers' stateside revamp of the classic Ealing comedy sees five bungling bank robbers falling foul of their elderly landlady. Starring Tom Hanks and JK Simmons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-15 15:35:00" d="2019-08-15 17:25:00" c="1"><n>Black Swan</n><t>F</t>    <k>An Oscar-winning Natalie Portman plays a ballerina who mentally unravels as she pursues her dream role. Psychological drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-15 17:25:00" d="2019-08-15 19:20:00" c="1"><n>Bad Samaritan</n><t>F</t>    <k>Horror thriller starring Robert Sheehan as a petty crook who stumbles upon the gruesome kidnap plot of wealthy sadist David Tennant. Geostorm's Dean Devlin directs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-15 19:20:00" d="2019-08-15 21:00:00" c="1"><n>The First Purge</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% The hit action-horror series gets an origins story as the government first trials a controversial experiment to legalise all crime for one night. With Marisa Tomei</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-15 21:00:00" d="2019-08-15 23:00:00" c="1"><n u="Ocean's">Ocean's 8</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% After getting out of prison, Debbie Ocean plots to steal a priceless necklace from New York's Met Gala. Heist caper with Sandra Bullock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-15 23:00:00" d="2019-08-16 01:20:00" c="1"><n>Se7en</n><t>F</t>    <k>Dark thriller starring Brad Pitt and Morgan Freeman as homicide detectives on the trail of a sick and twisted psychopath with a unique way of choosing his victims</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-16 01:20:00" d="2019-08-16 03:10:00" c="1"><n>Heartlock</n><t>F</t>    <k>Seasoned inmate Continental takes New York prison newcomer Lee under his wing, hoping to persuade him to manipulate a female guard into facilitating their escape. Drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-16 03:10:00" d="2019-08-16 05:20:00" c="1"><n>Con Air</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Paroled US Army ranger Nicolas Cage becomes trapped on a hijacked prison plane. OTT action with Steve Buscemi and John Malkovich among the cons</k>  </p>
</a>
