<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-05-28 04:41:25"><p id_tv="1044" o="2020-06-04 05:40:00" d="2020-06-04 07:25:00" c="1"><n>Point Last Seen</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% As tracker Linda Hamilton searches the desert for a missing girl, she's haunted by the disappearance of her own children, snatched by their violent dad. Drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-06-04 07:25:00" d="2020-06-04 09:30:00" c="1"><n>Charlie Says</n><t>F</t>    <k>A graduate student is tasked with teaching three young women who are serving life in prison for the infamous Manson murders. Biographical drama with Hannah Murray</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-06-04 09:30:00" d="2020-06-04 11:25:00" c="1"><n>Brothers In Arms</n><t>F</t>    <k>A by-the-book police officer is driven to take drastic measures when his brother is jailed unfairly. Tense thriller starring Jai Courtney and Leighton Meester</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-06-04 11:25:00" d="2020-06-04 13:15:00" c="1"><n>Greta</n><t>F</t>    <k>60% A young woman befriends a lonely widow, who hides a dark and sinister plan behind maternal charm. A Neil Jordan thriller with Chloe Grace Moretz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-06-04 13:15:00" d="2020-06-04 15:15:00" c="1"><n>The Mule</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% An elderly man winds up working as a drug courier for a Mexican cartel. Oscar winner Clint Eastwood directs and stars, alongside Bradley Cooper and Laurence Fishburne</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-06-04 15:15:00" d="2020-06-04 17:00:00" c="1"><n>Cold Blood Legacy</n><t>F</t>    <k>A legendary but retired hit man is lured back into his lethal ways when his life collides with that of a mysterious woman harbouring a secret. Jean Reno stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-06-04 17:00:00" d="2020-06-04 18:35:00" c="1"><n>The Bouncer</n><t>F</t>    <k>An imprisoned bodyguard is forced to work with the police and infiltrate a dangerous gang in order to secure his release. Jean-Claude Van Damme stars. English subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-06-04 18:35:00" d="2020-06-04 20:15:00" c="1"><n>We Die Young</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% When a 10-year-old and his brother flee the cruelty of gang life, a veteran with PTSD takes them under his wing. Jean-Claude Van Damme stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-06-04 20:15:00" d="2020-06-04 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Greta</n><t>F</t>    <k>60% A young woman befriends a lonely widow, who hides a dark and sinister plan behind maternal charm. A Neil Jordan thriller with Chloe Grace Moretz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-06-04 22:00:00" d="2020-06-05 01:00:00" c="1"><n>The Mule</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% An elderly man winds up working as a drug courier for a Mexican cartel. Oscar winner Clint Eastwood directs and stars, alongside Bradley Cooper and Laurence Fishburne</k>  </p>
</a>
