<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="11" t="2019-08-13 02:26:28"><p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-18 05:40:00" d="2019-08-18 07:25:00" c="1"><n>Deep Family Secrets</n><t>F</t>    <k>48% Thriller about a wealthy businessman who claims that his wife has been kidnapped. The couple's youngest daughter sets out to uncover the truth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-18 07:25:00" d="2019-08-18 09:25:00" c="1"><n>Bad Samaritan</n><t>F</t>    <k>Horror thriller starring Robert Sheehan as a petty crook who stumbles upon the gruesome kidnap plot of wealthy sadist David Tennant. Geostorm's Dean Devlin directs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-18 09:25:00" d="2019-08-18 11:55:00" c="1"><n>The Da Vinci Code</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Tom Hanks and Audrey Tautou race across Europe in a bid to uncover a secret protected for centuries. Mystery thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-18 11:55:00" d="2019-08-18 14:15:00" c="1"><n>Angels &amp; Demons</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Tom Hanks is called in to save Vatican City from being incinerated by an ancient sect. Sequel to The Da Vinci Code</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-18 14:15:00" d="2019-08-18 16:40:00" c="1"><n>Blood Diamond</n><t>F</t>    <k>80% Mercenary Leonardo DiCaprio helps Djimon Hounsou find his stolen son in exchange for a rare jewel, in war-torn Sierra Leone. Thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-18 16:40:00" d="2019-08-18 18:30:00" c="1"><n>Searching</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% When his daughter goes missing, a widowed dad trawls her social media in a desperate attempt to find her. But can he handle what he uncovers? Thriller starring Jon Cho</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-18 18:30:00" d="2019-08-18 21:00:00" c="1"><n>The Da Vinci Code</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Tom Hanks and Audrey Tautou race across Europe in a bid to uncover a secret protected for centuries. Mystery thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-18 21:00:00" d="2019-08-18 23:20:00" c="1"><n>Angels &amp; Demons</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Tom Hanks is called in to save Vatican City from being incinerated by an ancient sect. Sequel to The Da Vinci Code</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-18 23:20:00" d="2019-08-19 01:55:00" c="1"><n>The Firm</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Young lawyer Tom Cruise becomes embroiled in his new firm's shady dealings. Sydney Pollack directs this gripping drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-19 01:55:00" d="2019-08-19 03:55:00" c="1"><n>Three Days Of The Condor</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% When his colleagues are killed by a mysterious assassin, CIA employee Robert Redford races to identify the culprit. Sydney Pollack thriller co-starring Faye Dunaway</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-19 03:55:00" d="2019-08-19 06:00:00" c="1"><n>The Krays</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Gritty crime drama about gangsters Reggie and Ronnie Kray (Gary and Martin Kemp), who terrorised East London during the 1960s</k>  </p>
</a>
