<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="13" t="2019-08-10 01:39:29"><p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-16 05:20:00" d="2019-08-16 07:05:00" c="1"><n>Point Last Seen</n><t>F</t>    <k>59% As tracker Linda Hamilton searches the desert for a missing girl, she's haunted by the disappearance of her own children, snatched by their violent dad. Drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-16 07:05:00" d="2019-08-16 08:45:00" c="1"><n>Distorted</n><t>F</t>    <k>A woman becomes suspicious of the luxury 'smart apartment' she's just moved into as she begins to receive a series of disturbing subliminal messages. With John Cusack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-16 08:45:00" d="2019-08-16 10:45:00" c="1"><n>Collateral Damage</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% Fireman Arnold Schwarzenegger wants revenge when Colombian terrorists kill his family. Blockbusting jungle action from the director of The Fugitive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-16 10:45:00" d="2019-08-16 12:25:00" c="1"><n>Blood Brother</n><t>F</t>    <k>A bloodthirsty convict is released from jail after 15 years, and he's coming straight for the old pals he feels betrayed him, including one who is now a cop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-16 12:25:00" d="2019-08-16 14:25:00" c="1"><n>Paycheck</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% Ben Affleck sells three years of his memory, but on payday there's no cash and he's wanted for murder. Sci-fi based on a story by Philip K Dick. With Uma Thurman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-16 14:25:00" d="2019-08-16 16:05:00" c="1"><n>Breaking In</n><t>F</t>    <k>Gabrielle Union stars as a mother forced to desperately protect her family from four home invaders. Thriller from V for Vendetta director James McTeigue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-16 16:05:00" d="2019-08-16 18:00:00" c="1"><n>Serenity</n><t>F</t>    <k>53% Steamy thriller starring Matthew McConaughey as a fishing boat captain whose tranquil life is shattered by the arrival of ex-wife Anne Hathaway. Sky Cinema Original Film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-16 18:00:00" d="2019-08-16 20:00:00" c="1"><n>Gone In 60 Seconds</n><t>F</t>    <k>To save his brother from gangsters, legendary auto thief Nicolas Cage must steal 50 classic cars in one night. Action co-starring Angelina Jolie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-16 20:00:00" d="2019-08-16 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Gran Torino</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% Drama starring Clint Eastwood as a cantankerous Korean War veteran who reluctantly becomes a hero to his immigrant neighbours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-16 22:00:00" d="2019-08-17 00:15:00" c="1"><n>BlacKkKlansman</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% The incredible true story of an African-American cop who bravely infiltrated the Ku Klux Klan to take them down. Oscar winner from Spike Lee. Contains distressing scenes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-17 00:15:00" d="2019-08-17 02:40:00" c="1"><n>Strange Days</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% Ralph Fiennes stars as an ex-cop selling virtual reality sleaze in a lawless Los Angeles. Dark sci-fi thriller co-written by James Cameron and directed by Kathryn Bigelow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-17 02:40:00" d="2019-08-17 04:40:00" c="1"><n>Gone In 60 Seconds</n><t>F</t>    <k>To save his brother from gangsters, legendary auto thief Nicolas Cage must steal 50 classic cars in one night. Action co-starring Angelina Jolie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-08-17 04:40:00" d="2019-08-17 06:20:00" c="1"><n>Breaking In</n><t>F</t>    <k>Gabrielle Union stars as a mother forced to desperately protect her family from four home invaders. Thriller from V for Vendetta director James McTeigue</k>  </p>
</a>
