<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-05-15 04:58:15"><p id_tv="1044" o="2020-05-22 05:20:00" d="2020-05-22 07:05:00" c="1"><n>Angel Flight Down</n><t>F</t>    <k>51% A child's life is at stake when an emergency flight crashes in the snowy wilderness. Adventure based on a true story with former Baywatch star David Charvet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-05-22 07:05:00" d="2020-05-22 08:55:00" c="1"><n>Monsters And Men</n><t>F</t>    <k>Drama following three interweaving tales, including that of a young Brooklyn father who witnesses a police shooting of an unarmed black man</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-05-22 08:55:00" d="2020-05-22 10:50:00" c="1"><n>Searching</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% When his daughter goes missing, a widowed dad trawls her social media in a desperate attempt to find her. But can he handle what he uncovers? Thriller starring Jon Cho</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-05-22 10:50:00" d="2020-05-22 12:40:00" c="1"><n>Strange But True</n><t>F</t>    <k>A woman shocks the family of her dead boyfriend when she contacts them five years after his death, claiming to be pregnant with his child. Suspense-filled noir-thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-05-22 12:40:00" d="2020-05-22 14:40:00" c="1"><n>Cape Fear</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% Robert Mitchum is unforgettable as the psychotic ex-con out for revenge on Gregory Peck, the lawyer who put him away. Thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-05-22 14:40:00" d="2020-05-22 16:25:00" c="1"><n>Cold Blood Legacy</n><t>F</t>    <k>A legendary but retired hit man is lured back into his lethal ways when his life collides with that of a mysterious woman harbouring a secret. Jean Reno stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-05-22 16:25:00" d="2020-05-22 18:10:00" c="1"><n>Gemini</n><t>F</t>    <k>When a celebrity is shot dead, her assistant begins to unravel the mystery of the murder while confronting her own demons. Mystery thriller with Zoe Kravitz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-05-22 18:10:00" d="2020-05-22 20:00:00" c="1"><n>Searching</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% When his daughter goes missing, a widowed dad trawls her social media in a desperate attempt to find her. But can he handle what he uncovers? Thriller starring Jon Cho</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-05-22 20:00:00" d="2020-05-22 22:00:00" c="1"><n>The Operative</n><t>F</t>    <k>When a spy vanishes without a trace, her boss embarks on a panicked hunt to find her before she becomes a threat to their mission. Martin Freeman and Diane Kruger star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-05-22 22:00:00" d="2020-05-23 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Cape Fear</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Robert De Niro stars as a convicted rapist who sets out to exact revenge on his lawyer. Taut thriller from Martin Scorsese</k>  </p>
</a>
