<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-05-13 04:36:11"><p id_tv="1044" o="2020-05-20 06:30:00" d="2020-05-20 08:20:00" c="1"><n>Sam Churchill: Search For A Homeless Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>Thriller about an ex-surfer turned detective (The Dukes Of Hazzard's John Schneider) who tracks a hostage held by a dangerous gang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-05-20 08:20:00" d="2020-05-20 10:10:00" c="1"><n>Killers Anonymous</n><t>F</t>    <k>The members of a killers' support group begin to turn on each other as they try to determine which one of them is behind a high-profile attempted murder. Gary Oldman stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-05-20 10:10:00" d="2020-05-20 12:00:00" c="1"><n>Grand Isle</n><t>F</t>    <k>A chain of perplexing events unfolds when a couple lure a young stranger into their Victorian home to escape a hurricane. Thriller with Nicolas Cage and Kelsey Grammer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-05-20 12:00:00" d="2020-05-20 14:05:00" c="1"><n>White Boy Rick</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% Crime drama with Matthew McConaughey based on the true story of Rick Wershe, a teenage drug kingpin who became the youngest informant in the history of the FBI</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-05-20 14:05:00" d="2020-05-20 15:55:00" c="1"><n>Backtrace</n><t>F</t>    <k>A criminal with amnesia is forced to take a dangerous memory enhancing drug when he can't recall where the cash from a $20m bank raid is located. With Sylvester Stallone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-05-20 15:55:00" d="2020-05-20 18:00:00" c="1"><n>The Hummingbird Project</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Jesse Eisenberg and Alexander Skarsgard play for big money in high-frequency trading. As they try to cash in from a fibre-optic cable line, problems arise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-05-20 18:00:00" d="2020-05-20 19:50:00" c="1"><n>Killers Anonymous</n><t>F</t>    <k>The members of a killers' support group begin to turn on each other as they try to determine which one of them is behind a high-profile attempted murder. Gary Oldman stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-05-20 19:50:00" d="2020-05-20 22:00:00" c="1"><n>The Recruit</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Al Pacino recruits computer hotshot Colin Farrell for the CIA, then throws him into the hunt for a mole in the Agency. Smart double-cross thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2020-05-20 22:00:00" d="2020-05-21 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Extremely Wicked, Shockingly...</n><t>F</t>    <k>Sky Cinema original exploring the crimes of Ted Bundy (Zac Efron) from the perspective of his girlfriend Elizabeth Kloepfer</k>  </p>
</a>
