<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-07-11 00:20:59"><p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-16 06:25:00" d="2019-07-16 08:10:00" c="1"><n>Sam Churchill: Search For A Homeless Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>Thriller about an ex-surfer turned detective (The Dukes Of Hazzard's John Schneider) who tracks a hostage held by a dangerous gang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-16 08:10:00" d="2019-07-16 10:00:00" c="1"><n>Hitman</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Assassin Timothy Olyphant is caught up in a deadly conspiracy when a hit goes wrong and he's stuck with a Russian callgirl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-16 10:00:00" d="2019-07-16 12:05:00" c="1"><n>Shot Caller</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Gritty prison thriller starring Nikolaj Coster-Waldau (Game of Thrones) as a family man drawn into an unfamiliar criminal underworld following a fatal road accident</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-16 12:05:00" d="2019-07-16 14:05:00" c="1"><n>The Untouchables</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% Robert De Niro stars as mob boss Al Capone, with Kevin Costner as the Treasury agent determined to take him down. Gangland thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-16 14:05:00" d="2019-07-16 16:05:00" c="1"><n>American Made</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Tom Cruise stars as a frustrated airline pilot who gets mixed up with both the CIA and drug kingpin Pablo Escobar. From Edge of Tomorrow's Doug Liman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-16 16:05:00" d="2019-07-16 18:05:00" c="1"><n>Gone In 60 Seconds</n><t>F</t>    <k>To save his brother from gangsters, legendary auto thief Nicolas Cage must steal 50 classic cars in one night. Action co-starring Angelina Jolie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-16 18:05:00" d="2019-07-16 20:05:00" c="1"><n>Contraband</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Former smuggler Mark Wahlberg is forced back for one last run when his brother-in-law lets down unhinged crime boss Giovanni Ribisi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-16 20:05:00" d="2019-07-16 22:00:00" c="1"><n>In Darkness</n><t>F</t>    <k>Blind pianist Natalie Dormer (who also co-writes) is drawn into a brutal criminal underworld after she overhears an attack on her neighbour. Thriller with Ed Skrein</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-16 22:00:00" d="2019-07-16 23:45:00" c="1"><n>Hotel Artemis</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% Sci-fi thriller starring Jodie Foster as the operator of a secret, criminals-only safe house in a dystopian, near-future LA. With Jeff Goldblum and Dave Bautista</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-16 23:45:00" d="2019-07-17 01:50:00" c="1"><n>The Untouchables</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% Robert De Niro stars as mob boss Al Capone, with Kevin Costner as the Treasury agent determined to take him down. Gangland thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-17 01:50:00" d="2019-07-17 03:40:00" c="1"><n u="Rise Of The Footsoldier">Rise Of The Footsoldier 3</n><t>F</t>    <k>British crime thriller starring Craig Fairbrass as a ruthless Essex gangster plotting revenge on the drug baron who betrayed him and left him in prison. With Larry Lamb</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1044" o="2019-07-17 03:40:00" d="2019-07-17 05:30:00" c="1"><n>Trendy</n><t>F</t>    <k>When a teacher with a simple life moves to London, an exciting fresh start becomes a hellish, drug-fuelled nightmare when the city life awakens his dark impulses</k>  </p>
</a>
