<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="13" t="2019-07-11 00:21:02"><p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-15 05:45:00" d="2019-07-15 07:55:00" c="1"><n>The Odyssey</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Award-winning biopic of legendary oceanographer and filmmaker Jacques-Yves Cousteau, starring Lambert Wilson and Amelie's Audrey Tautou. In French with English subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-15 07:55:00" d="2019-07-15 09:40:00" c="1"><n>The Blind Spot</n><t>F</t>    <k>An uncompromising cop set to retire and make a controversial move into politics leads one last drug raid, but it doesn't go to plan. In Dutch and French with subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-15 09:40:00" d="2019-07-15 11:35:00" c="1"><n>The Ballad of Lefty Brown</n><t>F</t>    <k>Having witnessed the brutal murder of his partner, cowboy Bill Pullman tracks the killers through the desolate Montana plains. Western with Kathy Baker and Jim Caviezel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-15 11:35:00" d="2019-07-15 13:20:00" c="1"><n>Apostasy</n><t>F</t>    <k>A family of devout Jehovah's Witnesses - sisters Alex and Luisa and mother Ivanna - suffer a crisis of faith. BAFTA-nominated drama with Happy Valley's Siobhan Finneran</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-15 13:20:00" d="2019-07-15 14:55:00" c="1"><n>The Desert Rats</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Scottish commando Richard Burton leads a platoon of hardbitten Aussies in a war of attrition with James Mason's Rommel. WWII action sequel to The Desert Fox</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-15 14:55:00" d="2019-07-15 17:35:00" c="1"><n>Amistad</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% A shipload of slaves take on the US legal system in a battle to win their freedom. Powerful Spielberg drama with Morgan Freeman, Matthew McConaughey and Anthony Hopkins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-15 17:35:00" d="2019-07-15 19:15:00" c="1"><n>Kidulthood</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% In a tough London school, the suicide of a bullied girl gives her tormentors a free day to go on the rampage. Gritty British drama written by and starring Noel Clarke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-15 19:15:00" d="2019-07-15 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Iceman</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% Consumed by anger and pain, a Neolithic nomad sets out to avenge the brutal murder of his wife and son. Intense Stone Age thriller with unsubtitled Rhaetian dialogue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-15 21:00:00" d="2019-07-15 22:45:00" c="1"><n>Lady Bird</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% Greta Gerwig's Golden Globe winner stars Saoirse Ronan as a teen desperate to move on and start a new life elsewhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-15 22:45:00" d="2019-07-16 00:35:00" c="1"><n>Layer Cake</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% A drug dealer is trapped between vicious crime bosses and a mountain of stolen ecstasy. Slick gangland thriller starring Daniel Craig, from director Matthew Vaughn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-16 00:35:00" d="2019-07-16 02:30:00" c="1"><n>I'm A Killer</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Inspired by real events, a young police detective fights to bring down The Silesian Vampire - a vicious serial killer of women. Polish with English subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-16 02:30:00" d="2019-07-16 04:50:00" c="1"><n>Bugsy</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Oscar-winning biopic starring Warren Beatty as Bugsy Siegel, the mobster who put Vegas on the map. Gangland drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-16 04:50:00" d="2019-07-16 06:30:00" c="1"><n>Miss Hokusai</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Keiichi Hara's award-winning animation explores the relationship between famed 19th-century artist Katsushika Hokusai and daughter O-Ei. In Japanese</k>  </p>
</a>
