<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2021-07-13 05:04:12"><p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-20 06:30:00" d="2021-07-20 08:00:00" c="1"><n>Asterix: The Secret Of The Magic Potion</n><t>F</t>    <k>Asterix and Obelix search for Getafix's druid successor. But an evil wizard is out to steal his potion's secret recipe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-20 08:00:00" d="2021-07-20 09:40:00" c="1"><n>Howard Lovecraft &amp; The Frozen...</n><t>F</t>    <k>Animated adventure about a young boy who accidentally opens a portal to a strange frozen world filled with horrifying creatures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-20 09:40:00" d="2021-07-20 11:15:00" c="1"><n>Dragon Rider</n><t>F</t>    <k>53% An adventure ensues for a young silver dragon as he sets out to find a mysterious haven for his kind. With the voice of Sir Patrick Stewart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-20 11:15:00" d="2021-07-20 13:15:00" c="1"><n>Magical Adventures In The Forbidden City</n><t>F</t>    <k>A young girl uncovers a magical secret as she searches for her father in a city ravaged by an epidemic. Fantasy adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-20 13:15:00" d="2021-07-20 15:00:00" c="1"><n>The Secret Garden</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% Unlock your imagination as a young orphan discovers a magical garden when she's sent to live on her uncle's estate. Colin Firth stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-20 15:00:00" d="2021-07-20 16:40:00" c="1"><n>Howard Lovecraft &amp; The Frozen...</n><t>F</t>    <k>Animated adventure about a young boy who accidentally opens a portal to a strange frozen world filled with horrifying creatures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-20 16:40:00" d="2021-07-20 18:20:00" c="1"><n>The Wishmas Tree</n><t>F</t>    <k>45% A young possum must undo her damage and save her hometown when she freezes it after wishing for a white Wishmas. Family animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-20 18:20:00" d="2021-07-20 20:20:00" c="1"><n>Four Kids And It</n><t>F</t>    <k>50% Sky original based on Jacqueline Wilson's novel about four children who find a wish-granting sand creature. With Michael Caine, Russell Brand and Matthew Goode</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-20 20:20:00" d="2021-07-20 21:00:00" c="1"><n>How To Train Your Dragon: Homecoming</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% Hiccup and Toothless team up to remind everyone of the inseparable bond between vikings and dragons. Magical animated adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-20 21:00:00" d="2021-07-20 22:40:00" c="1"><n>Dragonheart: Vengeance</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% When his family is brutally slain, Lukas embarks on a quest for revenge with the help of an ice-breathing dragon. Fantasy with the voice of Helena Bonham Carter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-20 22:40:00" d="2021-07-21 00:10:00" c="1"><n>Adventures Of Rufus: The Fantastic Pet</n><t>F</t>    <k>41% When two friends discover a mysterious creature named Rufus, they embark on a magical mission with the help of an ancient spell book. Family adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-21 00:10:00" d="2021-07-21 03:10:00" c="1"><n>Asterix: The Secret Of The Magic Potion</n><t>F</t>    <k>Asterix and Obelix search for Getafix's druid successor. But an evil wizard is out to steal his potion's secret recipe</k>  </p>
</a>
