<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="11" t="2019-08-13 02:27:30"><p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-18 05:55:00" d="2019-08-18 07:50:00" c="1"><n>Batman</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Batman and Robin have a battle on their hands as Catwoman, The Joker, The Riddler and The Penguin join forces against them. Starring the late Adam West</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-18 07:50:00" d="2019-08-18 09:20:00" c="1"><n>Lego DC Comics Super Heroes. Justice League</n><t>F</t>    <k>Attack of the Legion of Doom: The Justice League jump into action when Lex Luthor assembles a team of super villains. Animated adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-18 09:20:00" d="2019-08-18 11:25:00" c="1"><n>Batman Forever</n><t>F</t>    <k>60% Villains Jim Carrey and Tommy Lee Jones pose a deadly riddle for caped crusader Val Kilmer. Superhero adventure with Nicole Kidman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-18 11:25:00" d="2019-08-18 13:50:00" c="1"><n>Man Of Steel</n><t>F</t>    <k>Henry Cavill dons the Superman suit, as a young Clark Kent embarks on a path to save the world from the villainous Zod</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-18 13:50:00" d="2019-08-18 16:25:00" c="1"><n>Batman V Superman: Dawn. Of Justice</n><t>F</t>    <k>Get ready for an earth-shattering battle of the egos as Ben Affleck's Batman picks a fight with Superman Henry Cavill. Spectacular superhero showdown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-18 16:25:00" d="2019-08-18 18:30:00" c="1"><n>Justice League</n><t>F</t>    <k>When a terrifying new villain emerges Batman and Wonder Woman must assemble a team capable of fighting back. DC action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-18 18:30:00" d="2019-08-18 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Batman Begins</n><t>F</t>    <k>A billionaire playboy begins a one-man crusade to clean up Gotham City's streets. Christian Bale stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-18 21:00:00" d="2019-08-18 23:30:00" c="1"><n>The Dark Knight</n><t>F</t>    <k>Christian Bale returns as the Caped Crusader, battling Heath Ledger's Joker on the streets of Gotham. From Christopher Nolan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-18 23:30:00" d="2019-08-19 02:15:00" c="1"><n>The Dark Knight Rises</n><t>F</t>    <k>84% Christian Bale's Batman battles Tom Hardy's unstoppable villain Bane in the epic conclusion to Christopher Nolan's trilogy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-19 02:15:00" d="2019-08-19 04:20:00" c="1"><n>Constantine</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Keanu Reeves stars as a doomed exorcist trying to earn his place in heaven by sending demons back to hell. Action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-19 04:20:00" d="2019-08-19 06:30:00" c="1"><n>Batman Forever</n><t>F</t>    <k>60% Villains Jim Carrey and Tommy Lee Jones pose a deadly riddle for caped crusader Val Kilmer. Superhero adventure with Nicole Kidman</k>  </p>
</a>
