<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-08-15 22:52:20"><p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-22 06:30:00" d="2019-08-22 08:20:00" c="1"><n>Batman</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Batman and Robin have a battle on their hands as Catwoman, The Joker, The Riddler and The Penguin join forces against them. Starring the late Adam West</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-22 08:20:00" d="2019-08-22 09:45:00" c="1"><n u="Batman: The Dark Knight Returns Part">Batman: The Dark Knight Returns Part 1</n><t>F</t>    <k>A decade after he retired the Batsuit, Bruce Wayne renews his war on Gotham's criminals. Peter Weller voices the Caped Crusader in this dark animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-22 09:45:00" d="2019-08-22 11:05:00" c="1"><n u="Batman: The Dark Knight. Returns Part">Batman: The Dark Knight. Returns Part 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>With Gotham in turmoil, a new commissioner orders Batman's arrest. Can the Caped Crusader evade the police and save the city when an old foe returns?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-22 11:05:00" d="2019-08-22 13:40:00" c="1"><n>The Dark Knight</n><t>F</t>    <k>Christian Bale returns as the Caped Crusader, battling Heath Ledger's Joker on the streets of Gotham. From Christopher Nolan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-22 13:40:00" d="2019-08-22 15:45:00" c="1"><n>Batman Forever</n><t>F</t>    <k>60% Villains Jim Carrey and Tommy Lee Jones pose a deadly riddle for caped crusader Val Kilmer. Superhero adventure with Nicole Kidman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-22 15:45:00" d="2019-08-22 17:55:00" c="1"><n u="Superman">Superman III</n><t>F</t>    <k>50% Tech whizz Richard Pryor helps develop a red kryptonite which splits Superman (Christopher Reeve) in two. Will his heroic or evil side win out?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-22 17:55:00" d="2019-08-22 18:25:00"><n>Aquaman: Special</n>    <k>Sky Cinema takes a special look at the DC superhero spectacular, directed by James Wan (Furious 7) and starring Jason Momoa as the Marine Marvel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-22 18:25:00" d="2019-08-22 21:00:00" c="1"><n>The Dark Knight</n><t>F</t>    <k>Christian Bale returns as the Caped Crusader, battling Heath Ledger's Joker on the streets of Gotham. From Christopher Nolan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-22 21:00:00" d="2019-08-22 23:00:00" c="1"><n>Justice League</n><t>F</t>    <k>When a terrifying new villain emerges Batman and Wonder Woman must assemble a team capable of fighting back. DC action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-22 23:00:00" d="2019-08-23 01:35:00"><n>Superman Returns</n>    <k>Superman blasts back to do battle with his nemesis, but can evil Lex Luthor temper the Man of Steel? Kryptonite-charged showdown with Kevin Spacey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-23 01:35:00" d="2019-08-23 03:40:00" c="1"><n>Constantine</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Keanu Reeves stars as a doomed exorcist trying to earn his place in heaven by sending demons back to hell. Action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-23 03:40:00" d="2019-08-23 05:05:00" c="1"><n>Superman Unbound</n><t>F</t>    <k>When Metropolis comes under attack from an alien android, only the Man of Steel can save humankind. Epic comic book animation with the voice of Matt Bomer</k>  </p>
</a>
