<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-05-29 04:36:23"><p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-05 06:25:00" d="2020-06-05 08:10:00" c="1"><n>Superman IV - The Quest For Peace</n><t>F</t>    <k>In a bid to save the world, Superman takes on Lex Luthor's latest creation - Nuclear Man. Action adventure with Christopher Reeve and Gene Hackman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-05 08:10:00" d="2020-06-05 10:20:00" c="1"><n>Iron Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>Robert Downey Jr has a blast as the cocky weapons designer turned peacemaker in this slick action adventure. With Jeff Bridges and Gwyneth Paltrow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-05 10:20:00" d="2020-06-05 12:30:00" c="1"><n u="Iron Man">Iron Man 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Robert Downey Jr steels the show as his metal-clad hero takes on Mickey Rourke's vengeful villain. Superb sequel with Don Cheadle, Scarlett Johansson and Sam Rockwell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-05 12:30:00" d="2020-06-05 14:30:00" c="1"><n>Venom</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% A journalist is left with superhuman strength and power when his body merges with the alien Venom. But how will he use his new-found abilities? Tom Hardy stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-05 14:30:00" d="2020-06-05 16:30:00" c="1"><n>The Incredible Hulk</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Ed Norton goes green as the superhero with anger issues. Muscular Marvel Comics action with Tim Roth as the Hulk's horribly mutated nemesis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-05 16:30:00" d="2020-06-05 18:45:00" c="1"><n>Captain Marvel</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Oscar winner Brie Larson is Captain Marvel, one of the great heroes of the universe, caught up in an intergalactic struggle between alien worlds. With Samuel L Jackson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-05 18:45:00" d="2020-06-05 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Spider-Man: Far From Home</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% Tom Holland stars as the web-slinging teenager, whose holiday is cut short when Europe comes under attack. Epic superhero sequel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-05 21:00:00" d="2020-06-05 23:00:00" c="1"><n>Venom</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% A journalist is left with superhuman strength and power when his body merges with the alien Venom. But how will he use his new-found abilities? Tom Hardy stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-05 23:00:00" d="2020-06-06 02:00:00" c="1"><n>Captain Marvel</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Oscar winner Brie Larson is Captain Marvel, one of the great heroes of the universe, caught up in an intergalactic struggle between alien worlds. With Samuel L Jackson</k>  </p>
</a>
