<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-05-30 04:39:57"><p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-06 05:25:00" d="2020-06-06 06:40:00" c="1"><n>Lego Batman The Movie DC Super Heroes Unite</n><t>F</t>    <k>Batman and Superman join forces with the rest of the Justice League to stop Lex Luthor and the Joker from bringing down Gotham. Animated action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-06 06:40:00" d="2020-06-06 08:05:00" c="1"><n>Superman Vs. The Elite</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% A new band of crime-fighting superheroes have jumped to the Man of Steel's aid, but are their methods for combatting evil causing more harm than good? DC animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-06 08:05:00" d="2020-06-06 10:20:00" c="1"><n>Glass</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% David Dunn hunts a dangerous superhuman with 24 personalities in M Night Shyamalan's final instalment of the Unbreakable trilogy. With Bruce Willis and James McAvoy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-06 10:20:00" d="2020-06-06 12:25:00" c="1"><n u="Deadpool">Deadpool 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Action comedy sequel with Ryan Reynolds suiting up once more, this time to do battle with Josh Brolin's time-travelling super-soldier. Atomic Blonde's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-06 12:25:00" d="2020-06-06 14:25:00" c="1"><n>Thor</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Exiled to Earth, Norse god Chris Hemsworth seeks the help of scientist Natalie Portman to get back home. Action-packed Marvel Comics adventure with Anthony Hopkins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-06 14:25:00" d="2020-06-06 16:35:00" c="1"><n>Captain America: The First Avenger</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% When a secret experiment turns frail kid Chris Evans into a rippling, spandex-clad superhero, the fate of WWII rests in his all-American hands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-06 16:35:00" d="2020-06-06 18:35:00" c="1"><n>Thor: The Dark World</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Chris Hemsworth returns as the Mighty Avenger, who must battle a race of Dark Elves to save the world. Marvel action with Tom Hiddleston</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-06 18:35:00" d="2020-06-06 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Avengers: Age Of Ultron</n><t>F</t>    <k>The Avengers reassemble in order to take down terrifying new enemy Ultron. Spectacular superhero fun with Robert Downey Jr, Chris Hemsworth and Scarlett Johansson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-06 21:00:00" d="2020-06-07 00:00:00" c="1"><n>Batman V Superman: Dawn. Of Justice</n><t>F</t>    <k>Get ready for an earth-shattering battle of the egos as Ben Affleck's Batman picks a fight with Superman Henry Cavill. Spectacular superhero showdown</k>  </p>
</a>
