<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-07-11 00:21:02"><p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-16 06:30:00" d="2019-07-16 08:50:00" c="1"><n>Brothers In Arms</n><t>F</t>    <k>A group of Turkish special forces soldiers set out on a dangerous mission to rescue a journalist from Islamic State militants. In Turkish with English subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-16 08:50:00" d="2019-07-16 10:20:00" c="1"><n>Two Lottery Tickets</n><t>F</t>    <k>A trio of down-on-their-luck pals embark on a madcap quest when a bag containing their winning lottery ticket is stolen. Award-winning Romanian comedy with subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-16 10:20:00" d="2019-07-16 12:10:00" c="1"><n>Modern Life Is Rubbish</n><t>F</t>    <k>This sweet-hearted British rom-com, which takes its title from the classic Blur album, charts the romance between a wannabe rock star and his graphic designer girlfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-16 12:10:00" d="2019-07-16 14:05:00" c="1"><n>Fashionista</n><t>F</t>    <k>With her personal life falling apart a young woman begins to develop an unsettling obsession with the clothes from her vintage fashion store. Genre-bending thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-16 14:05:00" d="2019-07-16 16:05:00" c="1"><n>Blade Runner</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% Theatrical version of Ridley Scott's classic sci-fi thriller, with Harrison Ford as a troubled cop on the trail of fugitive androids. Based on a novel by Philip K. Dick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-16 16:05:00" d="2019-07-16 18:50:00" c="1"><n u="Blade Runner">Blade Runner 2049</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% Dazzling sequel to Ridley Scott's sci-fi noir masterpiece, starring Ryan Gosling as an LAPD officer who unearths a long-buried secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-16 18:50:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Out Of Sight</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Bank robber George Clooney charms the pants off cop Jennifer Lopez, but will it stop her putting him away? Sizzling crime caper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 23:00:00" c="1"><n>First Reformed</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Oscar-nominated drama starring Ethan Hawke as a tormented New York pastor suffering a crisis of faith. Taxi Driver's Paul Schrader writes and directs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-16 23:00:00" d="2019-07-17 00:50:00" c="1"><n>The Truman Show</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% Jim Carrey is an ordinary guy in an ordinary town. He's also the unsuspecting star of the world's longest-running reality TV show. Intelligent drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-17 00:50:00" d="2019-07-17 03:10:00" c="1"><n>A Clockwork Orange</n><t>F</t>    <k>83% Stanley Kubrick's controversial classic about an off-the-wall gang who embark on a violent crime spree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-17 03:10:00" d="2019-07-17 04:55:00" c="1"><n>Godless</n><t>F</t>    <k>Award-winning drama about a morphine-addicted dementia nurse stirred from her joyless routine when she befriends a new patient. In Bulgarian with English subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-17 04:55:00" d="2019-07-17 06:30:00" c="1"><n>I Got Life!</n><t>F</t>    <k>Uplifting comedy-drama starring Agnes Jaoui as a fiftysomething divorcee who has a chance encounter with a former flame. In French with English subtitles</k>  </p>
</a>
