<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-05-26 04:34:31"><p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-02 05:30:00" d="2020-06-02 07:00:00" c="1"><n>Lego DC Comics Super Heroes. Justice League</n><t>F</t>    <k>Attack of the Legion of Doom: The Justice League jump into action when Lex Luthor assembles a team of super villains. Animated adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-02 07:00:00" d="2020-06-02 08:55:00" c="1"><n>Batman</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Batman and Robin have a battle on their hands as Catwoman, The Joker, The Riddler and The Penguin join forces against them. Starring the late Adam West</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-02 08:55:00" d="2020-06-02 11:00:00" c="1"><n>Batman Forever</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% Villains Jim Carrey and Tommy Lee Jones pose a deadly riddle for caped crusader Val Kilmer. Superhero adventure with Nicole Kidman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-02 11:00:00" d="2020-06-02 13:10:00" c="1"><n>Batman &amp; Robin</n><t>F</t>    <k>39% George Clooney and Chris O'Donnell star in this rollicking adventure which pits them against Mr Freeze (Arnold Schwarzenegger) and Poison Ivy (Uma Thurman)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-02 13:10:00" d="2020-06-02 14:50:00" c="1"><n>Hancock</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Alcoholic superhero Will Smith hires a PR officer to help improve his image. With Charlize Theron</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-02 14:50:00" d="2020-06-02 17:00:00" c="1"><n u="Superman">Superman II</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Man of Steel Christopher Reeve sacrifices his powers to be with Lois Lane, but needs them back to defeat Terence Stamp's evil General Zod</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-02 17:00:00" d="2020-06-02 19:00:00" c="1"><n>Ant-Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>Paul Rudd stars as a cat burglar given the ability to shrink to the size of an ant. Subatomic superhero fun with Michael Douglas and Evangeline Lilly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-02 19:00:00" d="2020-06-02 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Thor</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Exiled to Earth, Norse god Chris Hemsworth seeks the help of scientist Natalie Portman to get back home. Action-packed Marvel Comics adventure with Anthony Hopkins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-02 21:00:00" d="2020-06-02 23:00:00" c="1"><n>Thor: The Dark World</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Chris Hemsworth returns as the Mighty Avenger, who must battle a race of Dark Elves to save the world. Marvel action with Tom Hiddleston</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-02 23:00:00" d="2020-06-03 02:00:00" c="1"><n>Captain America: The First Avenger</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% When a secret experiment turns frail kid Chris Evans into a rippling, spandex-clad superhero, the fate of WWII rests in his all-American hands</k>  </p>
</a>
