<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-08-10 01:39:29"><p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-16 05:15:00" d="2019-08-16 07:00:00" c="1"><n>Apostasy</n><t>F</t>    <k>A family of devout Jehovah's Witnesses - sisters Alex and Luisa and mother Ivanna - suffer a crisis of faith. BAFTA-nominated drama with Happy Valley's Siobhan Finneran</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-16 07:00:00" d="2019-08-16 08:30:00" c="1"><n>The Elephant and the Butterfly</n><t>F</t>    <k>A father gets the chance to connect with the daughter he left behind after turning up unannounced on his ex-partner's doorstep. In French with English subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-16 08:30:00" d="2019-08-16 10:20:00" c="1"><n>Casablanca</n><t>F</t>    <k>85% Oscar-winning wartime romance starring Humphrey Bogart as an ex-pat bar owner torn between love and virtue. Ingrid Bergman co-stars as his former flame</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-16 10:20:00" d="2019-08-16 12:20:00" c="1"><n>Patti Cake$</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Feelgood underdog tale following an unlikely New Jersey rapper desperate to escape her humdrum life and make it big. Danielle Macdonald stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-16 12:20:00" d="2019-08-16 14:05:00" c="1"><n>Wonder Wheel</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Woody Allen's 1950s-set drama stars Kate Winslet as a former actress whose life is upturned by the appearance of her husband's estranged daughter. With Juno Temple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-16 14:05:00" d="2019-08-16 17:00:00" c="1"><n>The Great Escape</n><t>F</t>    <k>82% Steve McQueen is the POW determined to give his Nazi captors the slip in this iconic WWII classic. Bronson, Garner and Attenborough form the all-star escape committee</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-16 17:00:00" d="2019-08-16 19:20:00" c="1"><n>Downsizing</n><t>F</t>    <k>57% Alexander Payne (Sideways) directs this intelligent sci-fi satire set in a world where people can be shrunk down to five inches tall. Matt Damon stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-16 19:20:00" d="2019-08-16 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Thoroughbreds</n><t>F</t>    <k>Blackly comic thriller starring Olivia Cooke and Anya Taylor-Joy as estranged childhood friends who begin to form an unsettling new bond</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-16 21:00:00" d="2019-08-16 22:45:00" c="1"><n>Gravity</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% When disaster hits, astronauts Sandra Bullock and George Clooney are left fighting for survival in space. Stunning winner of seven Oscars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-16 22:45:00" d="2019-08-17 00:50:00" c="1"><n>The Social Network</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Jesse Eisenberg plays Facebook founder Mark Zuckerberg in David Fincher's Oscar-winning drama. With Andrew Garfield and Justin Timberlake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-17 00:50:00" d="2019-08-17 02:40:00" c="1"><n>Snatch</n><t>F</t>    <k>83% Brad Pitt stars in Guy Ritchie's sizzling East End thriller with bare-knuckle boxing, wheeler-dealers and conmen in pursuit of a stolen jewel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-17 02:40:00" d="2019-08-17 05:00:00" c="1"><n>A Clockwork Orange</n><t>F</t>    <k>83% Stanley Kubrick's controversial classic about an off-the-wall gang who embark on a violent crime spree</k>  </p>
</a>
