<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="11" t="2019-08-13 02:27:33"><p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-19 06:30:00" d="2019-08-19 08:00:00" c="1"><n>Batman: Mystery Of The Batwoman</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% The Dark Knight has a female rival to unmask as well as old enemies The Penguin and Bane to battle. Gotham's not big enough for all of them. Animated adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-19 08:00:00" d="2019-08-19 09:30:00" c="1"><n>Batman: Gotham Knight</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Action-packed animated adventure pitting the avenger of Gotham City against dangerous villains Scarecrow, Killer Croc and Deadshot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-19 09:30:00" d="2019-08-19 11:30:00" c="1"><n>Catwoman</n><t>F</t>    <k>36% Halle Berry plays the shy woman bestowed with the qualities of a feline, turning her into a slinky criminal vigilante. Action thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-19 11:30:00" d="2019-08-19 13:45:00" c="1"><n>Batman &amp; Robin</n><t>F</t>    <k>39% George Clooney and Chris O'Donnell star in this rollicking adventure which pits them against Mr Freeze (Arnold Schwarzenegger) and Poison Ivy (Uma Thurman)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-19 13:45:00" d="2019-08-19 15:55:00" c="1"><n>Constantine</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Keanu Reeves stars as a doomed exorcist trying to earn his place in heaven by sending demons back to hell. Action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-19 15:55:00" d="2019-08-19 18:20:00" c="1"><n>Batman Begins</n><t>F</t>    <k>A billionaire playboy begins a one-man crusade to clean up Gotham City's streets. Christian Bale stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-19 18:20:00" d="2019-08-19 21:00:00" c="1"><n>The Dark Knight</n><t>F</t>    <k>Christian Bale returns as the Caped Crusader, battling Heath Ledger's Joker on the streets of Gotham. From Christopher Nolan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-19 21:00:00" d="2019-08-19 23:45:00" c="1"><n>The Dark Knight Rises</n><t>F</t>    <k>84% Christian Bale's Batman battles Tom Hardy's unstoppable villain Bane in the epic conclusion to Christopher Nolan's trilogy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-19 23:45:00" d="2019-08-20 02:10:00" c="1"><n>Man Of Steel</n><t>F</t>    <k>Henry Cavill dons the Superman suit, as a young Clark Kent embarks on a path to save the world from the villainous Zod</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-20 02:10:00" d="2019-08-20 04:30:00" c="1"><n>V For Vendetta</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% In a Britain crushed by dictator John Hurt, a masked avenger enlists Natalie Portman in a fight for freedom. Dystopian thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-20 04:30:00" d="2019-08-20 06:30:00" c="1"><n>Catwoman</n><t>F</t>    <k>36% Halle Berry plays the shy woman bestowed with the qualities of a feline, turning her into a slinky criminal vigilante. Action thriller</k>  </p>
</a>
