<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2019-08-09 01:42:07"><p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-15 06:10:00" d="2019-08-15 08:25:00" c="1"><n>The Odyssey</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Award-winning biopic of legendary oceanographer and filmmaker Jacques-Yves Cousteau, starring Lambert Wilson and Amelie's Audrey Tautou. In French with English subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-15 08:25:00" d="2019-08-15 10:45:00" c="1"><n>The Battleship Island</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Hundreds of Korean prisoners forced to work in a brutal Japanese labour camp attempt a daring escape. Award-winning WWII action. In Korean with English subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-15 10:45:00" d="2019-08-15 13:40:00" c="1"><n>The Thin Red Line</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% Terrence Malick directs an epic war drama, set during the battle for Guadalcanal. Sean Penn, James Caviezel and Adrien Brody star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-15 13:40:00" d="2019-08-15 15:40:00" c="1"><n>Sands Of Iwo Jima</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% Bruising WWII drama starring John Wayne in one of the roles which made him a star. He was Oscar nominated as the hard-nosed marine knocking recruits into shape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-15 15:40:00" d="2019-08-15 18:25:00" c="1"><n>The Bridge On The River Kwai</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% William Holden and Alec Guinness star as British POWs charged with building a bridge that their own side want to obliterate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-15 18:25:00" d="2019-08-15 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Empire Of The Sun</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% Spoilt youngster Christian Bale fights to survive a Japanese POW camp alongside American scrounger John Malkovich. Epic WWII drama from Steven Spielberg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-15 21:00:00" d="2019-08-15 23:00:00" c="1"><n>Leave No Trace</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% A father and daughter living in idyllic seclusion in the Oregon woods are forced to re-enter society. Drama from Winter's Bone director Debra Granik, starring Ben Foster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-15 23:00:00" d="2019-08-16 00:45:00" c="1"><n>Unsane</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% A troubled young woman (Claire Foy) convinced that someone is stalking her is involuntarily committed to a mental institution. Psychological thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-16 00:45:00" d="2019-08-16 03:30:00" c="1"><n>Munich</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% After 11 Israeli athletes are kidnapped and killed at the 1972 Olympics, Mossad assassin Eric Bana is sent out for retribution</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-16 03:30:00" d="2019-08-16 05:15:00" c="1"><n>The Warriors</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% Wrongly accused of murder, a New York gang must fight its way back to Coney Island. Cult thriller from 48 Hrs director Walter Hill</k>  </p>
</a>
