<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2019-08-13 02:27:36"><p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-20 06:30:00" d="2019-08-20 07:50:00" c="1"><n>Wonder Woman</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% A headstrong Amazonian princess must come to the rescue when the god of war attempts to start a devastating conflict. Animated adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-20 07:50:00" d="2019-08-20 09:05:00" c="1"><n>Superman/Batman: Public Enemies</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% When Lex Luthor is elected President, Batman and Superman suddenly find themselves on the wrong side of the law. Action-packed animated adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-20 09:05:00" d="2019-08-20 10:30:00" c="1"><n>Superman/Batman: Apocalypse</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Superman and Batman join forces to protect a Kryptonian girl from the villainous Darkseid. Action-packed animated adventure with the voices of Kevin Conroy and Summer Glau</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-20 10:30:00" d="2019-08-20 12:00:00" c="1"><n>Teen Titans Go! To The Movies</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Join the Teen Titans on a Hollywood adventure as they fulfil their dream of starring in their very own superhero movie. With Kristen Bell and Will Arnett</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-20 12:00:00" d="2019-08-20 14:15:00" c="1"><n>V For Vendetta</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% In a Britain crushed by dictator John Hurt, a masked avenger enlists Natalie Portman in a fight for freedom. Dystopian thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-20 14:15:00" d="2019-08-20 16:30:00" c="1"><n>Batman</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% Michael Keaton's Bruce Wayne takes on Jack Nicholson's villainous Joker. Gothic Gotham fantasy directed by Tim Burton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-20 16:30:00" d="2019-08-20 19:00:00" c="1"><n>Superman</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Superman fights to thwart criminal Lex Luthor's (Gene Hackman) plans for world domination. Christopher Reeve stars as the Man of Steel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-20 19:00:00" d="2019-08-20 20:30:00" c="1"><n>Teen Titans Go! To The Movies</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Join the Teen Titans on a Hollywood adventure as they fulfil their dream of starring in their very own superhero movie. With Kristen Bell and Will Arnett</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-08-20 20:30:00" d="2019-08-20 23:30:00" c="1"><n>Man Of Steel</n><t>F</t>    <k>Henry Cavill dons the Superman suit, as a young Clark Kent embarks on a path to save the world from the villainous Zod</k>  </p>
</a>
