<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-04-16 04:36:57"><p id_tv="1045" o="2020-04-23 06:30:00" d="2020-04-23 07:50:00" c="1"><n>Superman Vs. The Elite</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% A new band of crime-fighting superheroes have jumped to the Man of Steel's aid, but are their methods for combatting evil causing more harm than good? DC animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-04-23 07:50:00" d="2020-04-23 09:40:00" c="1"><n u="Kick-Ass">Kick-Ass 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Chris D'Amico sets out to get revenge on Kick-Ass and Hit-Girl in this brutal comic book comedy. Aaron Taylor-Johnson stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-04-23 09:40:00" d="2020-04-23 12:00:00" c="1"><n>Spider-Man: Far From Home</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% Tom Holland stars as the web-slinging teenager, whose holiday is cut short when Europe comes under attack. Epic superhero sequel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-04-23 12:00:00" d="2020-04-23 14:35:00" c="1"><n>Batman V Superman: Dawn. Of Justice</n><t>F</t>    <k>Get ready for an earth-shattering battle of the egos as Ben Affleck's Batman picks a fight with Superman Henry Cavill. Spectacular superhero showdown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-04-23 14:35:00" d="2020-04-23 17:00:00" c="1"><n>Avengers: Age Of Ultron</n><t>F</t>    <k>The Avengers reassemble in order to take down terrifying new enemy Ultron. Spectacular superhero fun with Robert Downey Jr, Chris Hemsworth and Scarlett Johansson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-04-23 17:00:00" d="2020-04-23 19:00:00" c="1"><n>Thor</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Exiled to Earth, Norse god Chris Hemsworth seeks the help of scientist Natalie Portman to get back home. Action-packed Marvel Comics adventure with Anthony Hopkins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-04-23 19:00:00" d="2020-04-23 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Thor: The Dark World</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Chris Hemsworth returns as the Mighty Avenger, who must battle a race of Dark Elves to save the world. Marvel action with Tom Hiddleston</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-04-23 21:00:00" d="2020-04-24 00:00:00" c="1"><n>Spider-Man: Far From Home</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% Tom Holland stars as the web-slinging teenager, whose holiday is cut short when Europe comes under attack. Epic superhero sequel</k>  </p>
</a>
