<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-05-27 04:36:03"><p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-03 05:00:00" d="2020-06-03 07:10:00" c="1"><n>Batman &amp; Robin</n><t>F</t>    <k>39% George Clooney and Chris O'Donnell star in this rollicking adventure which pits them against Mr Freeze (Arnold Schwarzenegger) and Poison Ivy (Uma Thurman)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-03 07:10:00" d="2020-06-03 08:10:00" c="1"><n>Lego DC Comics Super Heroes. Justice League vs Bizarro League</n><t>F</t>    <k>The Justice League team up with their bizarre counterparts when the galaxy comes under threat from villain Darkseid. Animated adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-03 08:10:00" d="2020-06-03 10:20:00" c="1"><n u="Superman">Superman III</n><t>F</t>    <k>51% Tech whizz Richard Pryor helps develop a red kryptonite which splits Superman (Christopher Reeve) in two. Will his heroic or evil side win out?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-03 10:20:00" d="2020-06-03 13:25:00" c="1"><n>Avengers: Endgame</n><t>F</t>    <k>83% In the dramatic, concluding film in the Infinity saga, the remaining Avengers reassemble to try and undo the deadly actions of Thanos. Robert Downey Jr stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-03 13:25:00" d="2020-06-03 15:55:00" c="1"><n>Man Of Steel</n><t>F</t>    <k>Henry Cavill dons the Superman suit, as a young Clark Kent embarks on a path to save the world from the villainous Zod</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-03 15:55:00" d="2020-06-03 18:30:00" c="1"><n>Batman V Superman: Dawn. Of Justice</n><t>F</t>    <k>Get ready for an earth-shattering battle of the egos as Ben Affleck's Batman picks a fight with Superman Henry Cavill. Spectacular superhero showdown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-03 18:30:00" d="2020-06-03 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Avengers: Age Of Ultron</n><t>F</t>    <k>The Avengers reassemble in order to take down terrifying new enemy Ultron. Spectacular superhero fun with Robert Downey Jr, Chris Hemsworth and Scarlett Johansson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2020-06-03 21:00:00" d="2020-06-04 00:00:00" c="1"><n>Avengers: Endgame</n><t>F</t>    <k>83% In the dramatic, concluding film in the Infinity saga, the remaining Avengers reassemble to try and undo the deadly actions of Thanos. Robert Downey Jr stars</k>  </p>
</a>
