<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="11" t="2019-07-11 00:21:02"><p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-17 06:30:00" d="2019-07-17 08:10:00" c="1"><n>Permanent</n><t>F</t>    <k>Teen Kira McLean is desperate to fit in at school, but a disastrous new haircut doesn't much help matters. Comedy with Patricia Arquette and The Office's Rainn Wilson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-17 08:10:00" d="2019-07-17 10:10:00" c="1"><n>Zama</n><t>F</t>    <k>Award-winning drama about an officer of the Spanish crown desperately hoping for a transfer away from a remote South American colony. In Spanish with subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-17 10:10:00" d="2019-07-17 12:10:00" c="1"><n>A Fantastic Woman</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% Oscar-winning drama about a transgender singer whose life is thrown into turmoil following the sudden death of her partner. In Spanish with subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-17 12:10:00" d="2019-07-17 13:55:00" c="1"><n>Who We Are Now</n><t>F</t>    <k>Drama starring Julianne Nicholson as a mother trying to regain custody of her young son after being released from prison. With Emma Roberts and Zachary Quinto</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-17 13:55:00" d="2019-07-17 16:00:00" c="1"><n>A Place In The Sun</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% Oscar-winning drama starring Montgomery Clift as a doomed young man who finds himself trapped between his true love and a wealthier woman. With Elizabeth Taylor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-17 16:00:00" d="2019-07-17 18:20:00" c="1"><n>He Got Game</n><t>F</t>    <k>Denzel Washington stars as the jailbird dad paroled from prison to convince his basketball prodigy son to join a college team. Intelligent drama from director Spike Lee</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-17 18:20:00" d="2019-07-17 20:00:00" c="1"><n>Daphne</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% A hedonistic London thirtysomething has her life thrown off balance when she witnesses a violent crime. Soulful British drama starring a BIFA-nominated Emily Beecham</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-17 20:00:00" d="2019-07-17 22:30:00" c="1"><n>Catch Me If You Can</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% Leo DiCaprio stars as the teen conman who led the FBI on a paper chase, with Tom Hanks as the agent on his trail. Real-life caper from Steven Spielberg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-17 22:30:00" d="2019-07-18 01:45:00" c="1"><n>Schindler's List</n><t>F</t>    <k>89% Businessman Liam Neeson attempts to save his Jewish workers from the Nazis. Oscar-winning drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-18 01:45:00" d="2019-07-18 04:30:00" c="1"><n>Django Unchained</n><t>F</t>    <k>84% Quentin Tarantino's Oscar-winning western stars Jamie Foxx as a freed slave on a quest to find his wife</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2019-07-18 04:30:00" d="2019-07-18 06:30:00" c="1"><n>The Thing</n><t>F</t>    <k>84% A mutating alien life-force causes terror among Kurt Russell's Antarctic research crew. Horror classic from Halloween director John Carpenter</k>  </p>
</a>
