<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="13" t="2021-07-09 07:10:31"><p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-16 05:40:00" d="2021-07-16 07:50:00" c="1"><n u="Spider-Man">Spider-Man 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Tobey Maguire returns as the Webbed Wonder, battling evil in New York with Kirsten Dunst at his side. Action-packed superhero sequel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-16 07:50:00" d="2021-07-16 09:25:00" c="1"><n>Archenemy</n><t>F</t>    <k>A teenager and a superhero from another dimension join forces to take on the city's vicious organised crime gangs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-16 09:25:00" d="2021-07-16 10:45:00" c="1"><n>Batman Unlimited: Mechs. Vs Mutants</n><t>F</t>    <k>A super suit turns Batman into a giant fighting machine just in time to save Gotham from a villain with a freeze-powered mutant. Souped-up animated action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-16 10:45:00" d="2021-07-16 12:05:00" c="1"><n>Justice League: Gods And Monsters</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% In an alternate universe, the members of the Justice League are framed for an embassy bombing. DC animation with the voices of Michael C Hall and Benjamin Bratt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-16 12:05:00" d="2021-07-16 14:40:00"><n>Superman Returns</n>    <k>Superman blasts back to do battle with his nemesis, but can evil Lex Luthor temper the Man of Steel? Kryptonite-charged showdown with Kevin Spacey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-16 14:40:00" d="2021-07-16 16:15:00" c="1"><n>Archenemy</n><t>F</t>    <k>A teenager and a superhero from another dimension join forces to take on the city's vicious organised crime gangs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-16 16:15:00" d="2021-07-16 18:05:00" c="1"><n>Elektra</n><t>F</t>    <k>49% Jennifer Garner sizzles as the sultry assassin who battles against supernatural ninjas. Daredevil spin-off with Goran Visnjic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-16 18:05:00" d="2021-07-16 20:35:00" c="1"><n u="Spider-Man">Spider-Man 3</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Super-powered action as Spidey (Tobey Maguire) battles his inner demons while Sandman and Venom plot to take him down</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-16 20:35:00" d="2021-07-16 23:00:00" c="1"><n>Hulk</n><t>F</t>    <k>56% Following a lab accident, scientist Bruce Banner finds he becomes a destructive green monster whenever he gets angry. Eric Bana stars in Ang Lee's comic book actioner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-16 23:00:00" d="2021-07-17 01:05:00" c="1"><n>The Punisher</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% When his family is murdered by mobster John Travolta, scarred FBI man Tom Jane lives only for revenge. Dark crime-fighting action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-17 01:05:00" d="2021-07-17 02:45:00" c="1"><n>Elektra</n><t>F</t>    <k>49% Jennifer Garner sizzles as the sultry assassin who battles against supernatural ninjas. Daredevil spin-off with Goran Visnjic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-17 02:45:00" d="2021-07-17 04:05:00" c="1"><n>Batman Unlimited: Mechs. Vs Mutants</n><t>F</t>    <k>A super suit turns Batman into a giant fighting machine just in time to save Gotham from a villain with a freeze-powered mutant. Souped-up animated action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1045" o="2021-07-17 04:05:00" d="2021-07-17 05:30:00" c="1"><n>Henchmen</n><t>F</t>    <k>A teenager and his mentor team up to stop an evil supervillain and save the world. Animation with James Marsden and Rosario Dawson</k>  </p>
</a>
