<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-05-26 04:34:31"><p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-02 06:30:00" d="2020-06-02 08:10:00" c="1"><n>Asterix: The Secret Of The Magic Potion</n><t>F</t>    <k>Asterix and Obelix search for Getafix's druid successor. But an evil wizard is out to steal his potion's secret recipe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-02 08:10:00" d="2020-06-02 10:10:00" c="1"><n>Herbie Goes To Monte Carlo</n><t>F</t>    <k>57% Racing champ Jim Douglas revs up the lovable VW for the Monte Carlo Rally. Little does he know thieves have stowed a priceless diamond in the gas tank! Four-wheeled fun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-02 10:10:00" d="2020-06-02 12:00:00" c="1"><n>King Ralph</n><t>F</t>    <k>54% Las Vegas showman John Goodman is launched into high society when he is found to be the only living heir to the British throne. Royally funny comedy with Peter O'Toole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-02 12:00:00" d="2020-06-02 13:50:00" c="1"><n>An Elephant's Journey</n><t>F</t>    <k>Ageing and ailing, elephant Flora is due to be put down, but the circus owner's 14-year-old daughter Dawn has other ideas. Drama with David Arquette</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-02 13:50:00" d="2020-06-02 15:35:00" c="1"><n>Confessions Of A Teenage Drama Queen</n><t>F</t>    <k>46% When her parents move house, city teen Lindsay Lohan tries to adjust to life in the suburbs. Family comedy with Megan Fox, Adam Garcia and Alison Pill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-02 15:35:00" d="2020-06-02 17:25:00" c="1"><n>A Boy Called Sailboat</n><t>F</t>    <k>A family's extraordinary son, named Sailboat, leads this tale about a boy who brings magic to the world with the music of his guitar. With JK Simmons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-02 17:25:00" d="2020-06-02 19:00:00" c="1"><n u="Beverly Hills Chihuahua">Beverly Hills Chihuahua 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>43% With their owner's house under threat, chihuahua Chloe and her pups enter a dog show to raise the money to save it. Fun family sequel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-02 19:00:00" d="2020-06-02 20:40:00" c="1"><n>Confessions Of A Teenage Drama Queen</n><t>F</t>    <k>46% When her parents move house, city teen Lindsay Lohan tries to adjust to life in the suburbs. Family comedy with Megan Fox, Adam Garcia and Alison Pill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-02 20:40:00" d="2020-06-02 22:30:00" c="1"><n>King Ralph</n><t>F</t>    <k>54% Las Vegas showman John Goodman is launched into high society when he is found to be the only living heir to the British throne. Royally funny comedy with Peter O'Toole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-02 22:30:00" d="2020-06-03 01:30:00" c="1"><n>Bedtime Stories</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% From the Old West to ancient Greece, hotel handyman Adam Sandler finds his bedtime stories become reality after lights out. Vibrant fantasy adventure</k>  </p>
</a>
