<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="14" t="2019-08-15 22:51:58"><p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-22 06:10:00" d="2019-08-22 07:45:00" c="1"><n>Cats &amp; Dogs: The Revenge Of Kitty Galore</n><t>F</t>    <k>46% With a feline superspy plotting world domination, cats and dogs must put their rivalries aside to defeat her. Family. Slapstick violence/flashing images</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-22 07:45:00" d="2019-08-22 09:15:00" c="1"><n>Cleo</n><t>F</t>    <k>The long-awaited arrival of winter break only means one thing to this group of fun-loving kids. a huge snowball fight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-22 09:15:00" d="2019-08-22 10:50:00" c="1"><n>Cloudy With A Chance Of Meatballs</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% An inventor builds a machine that turns rain showers into food showers, but greed soon sends it spinning out of control. Delectable animation with the voice of Anna Faris</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-22 10:50:00" d="2019-08-22 12:40:00" c="1"><n>Cats</n><t>F</t>    <k>An adventure ensues when Blanket the cat decides to face his fears and leave home to find his son, who's ventured out in search of a legendary feline paradise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-22 12:40:00" d="2019-08-22 14:40:00" c="1"><n>The Chronicles Of Narnia: The Voyage of the Dawn Treader</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% The Pevensie kids take to the high seas for their most thrilling Narnian adventure yet. Featuring Ben Barnes and the voice of Simon Pegg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-22 14:40:00" d="2019-08-22 16:15:00" c="1"><n>Johnny English Strikes Again</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Rowan Atkinson returns for a third time as secret service agent Johnny English. This time, a sinister cyber attack sees him sent on an adventure in the South of France</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-22 16:15:00" d="2019-08-22 17:55:00" c="1"><n>Diary Of A Wimpy Kid</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% Greg starts at a new school, but finds his quest for coolness thwarted by his dorky best friend. Fun family comedy featuring Chloë Grace Moretz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-22 17:55:00" d="2019-08-22 19:25:00" c="1"><n>Dr. Seuss' Horton Hears A Who!</n><t>F</t>    <k>Can Horton the elephant save tiny Whoville from an evil vulture? Candy striped Dr Seuss adventure voiced by Jim Carrey and Steve Carell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-22 19:25:00" d="2019-08-22 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Cloudy With A Chance Of Meatballs</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% An inventor builds a machine that turns rain showers into food showers, but greed soon sends it spinning out of control. Delectable animation with the voice of Anna Faris</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-22 21:00:00" d="2019-08-22 22:35:00" c="1"><n>Johnny English Strikes Again</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Rowan Atkinson returns for a third time as secret service agent Johnny English. This time, a sinister cyber attack sees him sent on an adventure in the South of France</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-22 22:35:00" d="2019-08-23 00:30:00" c="1"><n>Lu Over The Wall</n><t>F</t>    <k>Talented but troubled teen Kai forms an unlikely friendship when his band's music attracts the attention of a singing mermaid named Lu. Eye-catching Japanese animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-23 00:30:00" d="2019-08-23 02:50:00" c="1"><n>The Legend Of Zorro</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% Antonio Banderas returns as the masked Mexican daredevil, battling slippery Rufus Sewell and saving Catherine Zeta-Jones. Gunpowder action comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-23 02:50:00" d="2019-08-23 04:50:00" c="1"><n>The Chronicles Of Narnia: The Voyage of the Dawn Treader</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% The Pevensie kids take to the high seas for their most thrilling Narnian adventure yet. Featuring Ben Barnes and the voice of Simon Pegg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-23 04:50:00" d="2019-08-23 06:25:00" c="1"><n>Flying The Nest</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% Having failed to learn to fly, a plover chick is left to fend for himself during the harsh winter after his family migrate south. Family animation</k>  </p>
</a>
