<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-05-16 04:56:55"><p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-23 06:35:00" d="2020-05-23 08:35:00" c="1"><n>Sister Act 2: Back In The Habit</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% With a local school under threat of closure, undercover nun Whoopi Goldberg returns to answer Mother Superior Maggie Smith's prayers. Fun comedy sequel with Lauryn Hill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-23 08:35:00" d="2020-05-23 10:15:00" c="1"><n u="George Of The Jungle">George Of The Jungle 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>33% The lord of the japes swings into action to keep his family together - but there are no vines in Vegas! More monkey business among the treetops with John Cleese</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-23 10:15:00" d="2020-05-23 11:55:00" c="1"><n>Bernie The Dolphin</n><t>F</t>    <k>51% After befriending a dolphin, two kids uncover a plot that could destroy the beach and their new pal's home, and make a plan to stop the bad guys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-23 11:55:00" d="2020-05-23 13:40:00" c="1"><n>Bean</n><t>F</t>    <k>Rowan Atkinson reprises his hugely successful TV role as the hopelessly inept Mr Bean, who somehow finds himself travelling to America as an art expert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-23 13:40:00" d="2020-05-23 15:20:00" c="1"><n u="The Secret Life Of Pets">The Secret Life Of Pets 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Sequel to the hit film about the adventures of our pets that we don't see when we leave home. With the voices of Kevin Hart and Harrison Ford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-23 15:20:00" d="2020-05-23 17:00:00" c="1"><n>Confessions Of A Teenage Drama Queen</n><t>F</t>    <k>46% When her parents move house, city teen Lindsay Lohan tries to adjust to life in the suburbs. Family comedy with Megan Fox, Adam Garcia and Alison Pill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-23 17:00:00" d="2020-05-23 18:35:00" c="1"><n>Gulliver's Travels</n><t>F</t>    <k>50% Slacker Jack Black is shipwrecked on the fantastical isle of Liliput where he towers over the tiny population. Light-hearted adventure with Jason Segel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-23 18:35:00" d="2020-05-23 20:20:00" c="1"><n>Beethoven</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% When a stray St Bernard becomes the newest member of the Newton family, his owners have to ward off a pair of dastardly dog-nappers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-23 20:20:00" d="2020-05-23 22:00:00" c="1"><n u="The Secret Life Of Pets">The Secret Life Of Pets 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Sequel to the hit film about the adventures of our pets that we don't see when we leave home. With the voices of Kevin Hart and Harrison Ford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-23 22:00:00" d="2020-05-24 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Bean</n><t>F</t>    <k>Rowan Atkinson reprises his hugely successful TV role as the hopelessly inept Mr Bean, who somehow finds himself travelling to America as an art expert</k>  </p>
</a>
