<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-05-14 04:53:53"><p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-21 06:25:00" d="2020-05-21 08:00:00" c="1"><n>Up And Away</n><t>F</t>    <k>Young Hodja gets to go on the adventure he's been longing for when he is given a flying carpet by a man who wants him to find his lost grandchild. Fun animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-21 08:00:00" d="2020-05-21 09:50:00" c="1"><n>Labyrinth</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% A teenage girl embarks on a mind-bending adventure when her wish for her baby brother's disappearance comes true. Musical fantasy with Jennifer Connelly and David Bowie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-21 09:50:00" d="2020-05-21 11:40:00" c="1"><n>Bedtime Stories</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% From the Old West to ancient Greece, hotel handyman Adam Sandler finds his bedtime stories become reality after lights out. Vibrant fantasy adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-21 11:40:00" d="2020-05-21 13:30:00" c="1"><n>Evolution</n><t>F</t>    <k>Scientists David Duchovny, Orlando Jones and Julianne Moore try to stop mutating aliens from taking over Earth. Sci-fi comedy from Ivan 'Ghostbusters' Reitman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-21 13:30:00" d="2020-05-21 15:30:00" c="1"><n>Step Up</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Rough street dancer Channing Tatum learns to tell his pirouette from his body-popping as he dances for the heart of ballet student Jenna Dewan. With Rachel Griffiths</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-21 15:30:00" d="2020-05-21 17:40:00" c="1"><n u="The Karate Kid Part">The Karate Kid Part III</n><t>F</t>    <k>Hothead Daniel dumps Mr Miyagi for a new coach. But without his ally, can the youngster defeat the toxic waste baron who is training an old enemy?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-21 17:40:00" d="2020-05-21 20:00:00" c="1"><n>The Legend Of Zorro</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% Antonio Banderas returns as the masked Mexican daredevil, battling slippery Rufus Sewell and saving Catherine Zeta-Jones. Gunpowder action comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-21 20:00:00" d="2020-05-21 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Step Up</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Rough street dancer Channing Tatum learns to tell his pirouette from his body-popping as he dances for the heart of ballet student Jenna Dewan. With Rachel Griffiths</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-21 22:00:00" d="2020-05-22 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Labyrinth</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% A teenage girl embarks on a mind-bending adventure when her wish for her baby brother's disappearance comes true. Musical fantasy with Jennifer Connelly and David Bowie</k>  </p>
</a>
