<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="11" t="2020-05-13 04:36:12"><p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-20 05:00:00" d="2020-05-20 06:40:00" c="1"><n>Minuscule</n><t>F</t>    <k>When a plucky young ladybug gets trapped in a box, he suddenly finds himself being shipped to the Caribbean, so his insect friends assemble a team to rescue him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-20 06:40:00" d="2020-05-20 08:15:00" c="1"><n>Wheely</n><t>F</t>    <k>In a world of cars, one cab tries to become king of the road. When he goes on a journey of personal discovery, he finds out that being true to himself is more important</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-20 08:15:00" d="2020-05-20 09:55:00" c="1"><n>An Elephant's Journey</n><t>F</t>    <k>Ageing and ailing, elephant Flora is due to be put down, but the circus owner's 14-year-old daughter Dawn has other ideas. Drama with David Arquette</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-20 09:55:00" d="2020-05-20 11:30:00" c="1"><n>Racetime</n><t>F</t>    <k>Frankie Four-Eyes and his team return for a spectacular sled race through the city, taking on a sneaky opponent with a few tricks up his sleeve</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-20 11:30:00" d="2020-05-20 13:30:00" c="1"><n>Spider-Man: Into The Spider-Verse</n><t>F</t>    <k>83% Academy Award-winning animated film exploring the weaves, webs and alternate realities of the incredible Spider-Man universe. With Shameik Moore and Nicolas Cage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-20 13:30:00" d="2020-05-20 15:30:00" c="1"><n u="The Karate Kid Part">The Karate Kid Part II</n><t>F</t>    <k>High-kicking karate student Daniel and his mentor Mr Miyagi travel to Japan to settle an old score. Family action sequel with Pat Morita and Ralph Macchio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-20 15:30:00" d="2020-05-20 16:50:00" c="1"><n u="Open Season">Open Season 3</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% A topsy-turvy adventure begins when Boog finds himself on the way to Russia with a circus. Elliot and the gang race to rescue him, but will they make it in time?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-20 16:50:00" d="2020-05-20 18:30:00" c="1"><n>An Elephant's Journey</n><t>F</t>    <k>Ageing and ailing, elephant Flora is due to be put down, but the circus owner's 14-year-old daughter Dawn has other ideas. Drama with David Arquette</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-20 18:30:00" d="2020-05-20 20:00:00" c="1"><n>Stuart Little</n><t>F</t>    <k>Charming tale following the adventures of a spirited young mouse adopted by humans Geena Davis and Hugh Laurie. Fun family adventure featuring the voice of Michael J Fox</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-20 20:00:00" d="2020-05-20 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Spider-Man: Into The Spider-Verse</n><t>F</t>    <k>83% Academy Award-winning animated film exploring the weaves, webs and alternate realities of the incredible Spider-Man universe. With Shameik Moore and Nicolas Cage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-20 22:00:00" d="2020-05-21 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Up And Away</n><t>F</t>    <k>Young Hodja gets to go on the adventure he's been longing for when he is given a flying carpet by a man who wants him to find his lost grandchild. Fun animation</k>  </p>
</a>
