<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="14" t="2019-07-11 00:21:00"><p id_tv="1046" o="2019-07-16 06:25:00" d="2019-07-16 08:10:00" c="1"><n>My Pet Dinosaur</n><t>F</t>    <k>When a young boy accidentally discovers a strange and mischievous little creature his already troubled town is plunged into chaos. Especially as it won't stop growing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-07-16 08:10:00" d="2019-07-16 09:50:00" c="1"><n>Mr. Popper's Penguins</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Ruthless businessman Jim Carrey inherits six penguins, and they soon turn his apartment, and his life, upside down. Heart-warming family comedy with Angela Lansbury</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-07-16 09:50:00" d="2019-07-16 11:30:00" c="1"><n>Monster Family</n><t>F</t>    <k>The first Sky Cinema Original Film sees a young family cursed by a witch and transformed into monsters. Animated comedy with the voices of Emily Watson and Jason Isaacs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-07-16 11:30:00" d="2019-07-16 13:05:00" c="1"><n>The Flintstones</n><t>F</t>    <k>50% Jurassic jollies with Fred, Barney, Dino and the gang in their first live-action adventure. John Goodman, Rick Moranis and Halle Berry star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-07-16 13:05:00" d="2019-07-16 14:35:00" c="1"><n>Maya The Bee: The Honey Games</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% Headstrong young worker bee Maya assembles a team of underachieving misfits to compete in the Honey Games and save her hive's supply of honey. Charming family animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-07-16 14:35:00" d="2019-07-16 16:05:00" c="1"><n>Adventures In Zambezia</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% A young falcon embarks on an exciting adventure to a fabulous bird city where he learns the truth about his origins. Animated family film with the voice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-07-16 16:05:00" d="2019-07-16 17:45:00" c="1"><n>Monster Family</n><t>F</t>    <k>The first Sky Cinema Original Film sees a young family cursed by a witch and transformed into monsters. Animated comedy with the voices of Emily Watson and Jason Isaacs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-07-16 17:45:00" d="2019-07-16 19:25:00" c="1"><n>Mr. Popper's Penguins</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Ruthless businessman Jim Carrey inherits six penguins, and they soon turn his apartment, and his life, upside down. Heart-warming family comedy with Angela Lansbury</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-07-16 19:25:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Cloudy With A Chance Of Meatballs</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% An inventor builds a machine that turns rain showers into food showers, but greed soon sends it spinning out of control. Delectable animation with the voice of Anna Faris</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 22:40:00" c="1"><n u="Cloudy With A Chance Of Meatballs">Cloudy With A Chance Of Meatballs 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Chaos ensues when a scientist discovers his invention, which turns water into meals, is creating animals made of food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-07-16 22:40:00" d="2019-07-17 00:15:00" c="1"><n>The Flintstones</n><t>F</t>    <k>50% Jurassic jollies with Fred, Barney, Dino and the gang in their first live-action adventure. John Goodman, Rick Moranis and Halle Berry star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-07-17 00:15:00" d="2019-07-17 01:55:00" c="1"><n>The Flintstones In Viva Rock Vegas</n><t>F</t>    <k>39% Cave men capers as bedrock bachelors Fred and Barney head to a glitzy quarry casino to win the hearts of Wilma and Betty. Energetic prequel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-07-17 01:55:00" d="2019-07-17 03:50:00" c="1"><n>#Roxy</n><t>F</t>    <k>54% The Cyrano de Bergerac story gets a high-school spin as self-conscious teen Cyrus reluctantly helps a classmate woo the girl he's secretly in love with. Romantic comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-07-17 03:50:00" d="2019-07-17 05:30:00" c="1"><n>The Oddsockeaters</n><t>F</t>    <k>57% Two rival gangs of Oddsockeaters - secretive creatures who eat socks, but only one from each pair - come into conflict. Animated fun based on the bestselling book series</k>  </p>
</a>
