<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="14" t="2019-08-10 01:39:29"><p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-16 06:00:00" d="2019-08-16 07:35:00" c="1"><n>Flying The Nest</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% Having failed to learn to fly, a plover chick is left to fend for himself during the harsh winter after his family migrate south. Family animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-16 07:35:00" d="2019-08-16 09:25:00" c="1"><n u="The Smurfs">The Smurfs 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% Evil wizard Gargamel kidnaps Smurfette so she can turn his mischievous Smurf-like creatures into real Smurfs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-16 09:25:00" d="2019-08-16 11:10:00" c="1"><n>Smallfoot</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% An epic journey ensues when a Yeti named Migo stumbles across a real human being - but is banished from his snowy home when no-one believes him. With Channing Tatum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-16 11:10:00" d="2019-08-16 12:30:00" c="1"><n>Lego Scooby Doo!: Haunted Hollywood</n><t>F</t>    <k>Scooby and the gang have another mystery to solve when classic movie monsters pitch up during a Hollywood studio tour. With the voice of Matthew Lillard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-16 12:30:00" d="2019-08-16 14:00:00" c="1"><n>Teen Titans Go! To The Movies</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Join the Teen Titans on a Hollywood adventure as they fulfil their dream of starring in their very own superhero movie. With Kristen Bell and Will Arnett</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-16 14:00:00" d="2019-08-16 15:50:00" c="1"><n u="The Smurfs">The Smurfs 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% Evil wizard Gargamel kidnaps Smurfette so she can turn his mischievous Smurf-like creatures into real Smurfs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-16 15:50:00" d="2019-08-16 17:45:00" c="1"><n>The Chronicles Of Narnia: The Voyage of the Dawn Treader</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% The Pevensie kids take to the high seas for their most thrilling Narnian adventure yet. Featuring Ben Barnes and the voice of Simon Pegg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-16 17:45:00" d="2019-08-16 19:30:00" c="1"><n>Smallfoot</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% An epic journey ensues when a Yeti named Migo stumbles across a real human being - but is banished from his snowy home when no-one believes him. With Channing Tatum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-16 19:30:00" d="2019-08-16 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Teen Titans Go! To The Movies</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Join the Teen Titans on a Hollywood adventure as they fulfil their dream of starring in their very own superhero movie. With Kristen Bell and Will Arnett</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-16 21:00:00" d="2019-08-16 22:40:00" c="1"><n>Charlotte's Web</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Starry remake of EB White's classic tale. Dakota Fanning is the farmer's daughter who, with the help of smart spider Charlotte, tries to save pig Wilbur from the butcher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-16 22:40:00" d="2019-08-17 00:35:00" c="1"><n>The Chronicles Of Narnia: The Voyage of the Dawn Treader</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% The Pevensie kids take to the high seas for their most thrilling Narnian adventure yet. Featuring Ben Barnes and the voice of Simon Pegg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-17 00:35:00" d="2019-08-17 02:25:00" c="1"><n>The Sandlot</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% Charming coming-of-age caper about a young boy who finds new friends on a baseball team and takes on a snarling hound known as The Beast. With Karen Allen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-17 02:25:00" d="2019-08-17 04:10:00" c="1"><n>A Wizard's Tale</n><t>F</t>    <k>Family animation about a normal kid whisked away to a magical kingdom robbed of laughter and happiness by a grumpy wizard. With the voices of Lily Collins and Toby Kebbell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-17 04:10:00" d="2019-08-17 05:55:00" c="1"><n>My Pet Dinosaur</n><t>F</t>    <k>When a young boy accidentally discovers a strange and mischievous little creature his already troubled town is plunged into chaos. Especially as it won't stop growing</k>  </p>
</a>
