<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-05-29 04:36:21"><p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-05 06:25:00" d="2020-06-05 08:10:00" c="1"><n>Jack And Jill</n><t>F</t>    <k>36% A top ad exec is driven round the bend when his infuriating twin sister comes to stay. Boisterous comedy fun with Adam Sandler in both roles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-05 08:10:00" d="2020-06-05 10:00:00" c="1"><n>Ghostbusters</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% Classic 80s comedy starring Bill Murray and Dan Aykroyd as paranormal experts battling the supernatural</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-05 10:00:00" d="2020-06-05 11:50:00" c="1"><n u="Ghostbusters">Ghostbusters 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% When a ghostly painting wreaks havoc in New York, who you gonna call? Comedy sequel starring Bill Murray and Dan Aykroyd</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-05 11:50:00" d="2020-06-05 14:00:00" c="1"><n>Aladdin</n><t>F</t>    <k>Live-action re-imagining of the Disney classic about a street urchin who unleashes the power of a genie sparking a magical adventure. With Will Smith</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-05 14:00:00" d="2020-06-05 15:35:00" c="1"><n>The Emperor's New Groove</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% A cocky young emperor is magically transformed into a llama in this hilarious animation. Can he learn some tough lessons and regain his throne?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-05 15:35:00" d="2020-06-05 17:15:00" c="1"><n>Nanny McPhee</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Emma Thompson plays a snaggletoothed nanny who brings a touch of magic into the house of widowed Colin Firth and his seven kids. Family drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-05 17:15:00" d="2020-06-05 19:15:00" c="1"><n>Nanny McPhee &amp; The Big Bang</n><t>F</t>    <k>Snaggle-toothed kiddie whizz, Nanny McPhee (Emma Thompson) is called to the Green family when mum Isabel loses control of her boisterous brood. Fun family sequel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-05 19:15:00" d="2020-06-05 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Hotel Transylvania 3: A Monster Vacation</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% A stressed-out Dracula is whisked away on a luxury summer cruise that winds up being far from smooth sailing. Animated fun with the voice of Adam Sandler</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-05 21:00:00" d="2020-06-05 23:10:00" c="1"><n>Aladdin</n><t>F</t>    <k>Live-action re-imagining of the Disney classic about a street urchin who unleashes the power of a genie sparking a magical adventure. With Will Smith</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-05 23:10:00" d="2020-06-06 02:10:00" c="1"><n>The Emperor's New Groove</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% A cocky young emperor is magically transformed into a llama in this hilarious animation. Can he learn some tough lessons and regain his throne?</k>  </p>
</a>
