<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-04-15 04:36:21"><p id_tv="1046" o="2020-04-22 06:20:00" d="2020-04-22 08:00:00" c="1"><n>The Witches</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Orphan Luke stumbles onto a witch's plot to rid the world of children. Can he stop their evil scheme? Splendidly scary adaptation of Roald Dahl's novel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-04-22 08:00:00" d="2020-04-22 09:40:00" c="1"><n>Racetime</n><t>F</t>    <k>Frankie Four-Eyes and his team return for a spectacular sled race through the city, taking on a sneaky opponent with a few tricks up his sleeve</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-04-22 09:40:00" d="2020-04-22 11:30:00" c="1"><n>Father Of The Bride</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Doting father Steve Martin struggles to let his little girl go when she announces that she is engaged to be married. Comedy remake starring Diane Keaton and Martin Short</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-04-22 11:30:00" d="2020-04-22 12:50:00" c="1"><n>Anchors Up</n><t>F</t>    <k>Norway's favourite rescue boat returns as Elias is recruited by a bigger harbour. But he soon discovers that bigger doesn't always mean better! Family animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-04-22 12:50:00" d="2020-04-22 14:25:00" c="1"><n>Teen Titans Go! To The Movies</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Join the Teen Titans on a Hollywood adventure as they fulfil their dream of starring in their very own superhero movie. With Kristen Bell and Will Arnett</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-04-22 14:25:00" d="2020-04-22 16:20:00" c="1"><n>How To Train Your Dragon: The Hidden World</n><t>F</t>    <k>82% Hiccup and Toothless venture out into a hidden world to protect their village from the darkest threat yet. With America Ferrera and Cate Blanchett</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-04-22 16:20:00" d="2020-04-22 18:10:00" c="1"><n>Tooth Fairy</n><t>F</t>    <k>Arrogant ice hockey player Dwayne Johnson is turned into the tooth fairy for two weeks. Sweet family comedy with Billy Crystal and Stephen Merchant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-04-22 18:10:00" d="2020-04-22 20:00:00" c="1"><n>Father Of The Bride</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Doting father Steve Martin struggles to let his little girl go when she announces that she is engaged to be married. Comedy remake starring Diane Keaton and Martin Short</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-04-22 20:00:00" d="2020-04-22 23:00:00" c="1"><n>How To Train Your Dragon: The Hidden World</n><t>F</t>    <k>82% Hiccup and Toothless venture out into a hidden world to protect their village from the darkest threat yet. With America Ferrera and Cate Blanchett</k>  </p>
</a>
