<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-05-27 04:36:01"><p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-03 05:35:00" d="2020-06-03 07:35:00" c="1"><n>Herbie Goes To Monte Carlo</n><t>F</t>    <k>57% Racing champ Jim Douglas revs up the lovable VW for the Monte Carlo Rally. Little does he know thieves have stowed a priceless diamond in the gas tank! Four-wheeled fun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-03 07:35:00" d="2020-06-03 09:25:00" c="1"><n>Bedtime Stories</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% From the Old West to ancient Greece, hotel handyman Adam Sandler finds his bedtime stories become reality after lights out. Vibrant fantasy adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-03 09:25:00" d="2020-06-03 11:15:00" c="1"><n>Mousehunt</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Lee Evans and Nathan Lane are the bumbling brothers whose plans to renovate a valuable building are thwarted by a super smart rodent. Comedy with Christopher Walken</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-03 11:15:00" d="2020-06-03 13:00:00" c="1"><n>Babe</n><t>F</t>    <k>Plucky piglet Babe discovers an unexpected talent for herding sheep which may just save him from becoming the Christmas dinner. Family favourite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-03 13:00:00" d="2020-06-03 14:50:00" c="1"><n>Babe: Pig In The City</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% Sheepherding pig Babe goes to the city to show off his talents in a state fair, but finds himself in trouble when he gets separated from his owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-03 14:50:00" d="2020-06-03 16:45:00" c="1"><n>Muppet Treasure Island</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Kermit and pals give this classic pirate yarn a Muppet-style makeover. Swashbuckling family adventure starring Tim Curry, Billy Connolly and Jennifer Saunders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-03 16:45:00" d="2020-06-03 18:20:00" c="1"><n>Leo Da Vinci: Mission Mona Lisa</n><t>F</t>    <k>49% A young Leonardo Da Vinci embarks on an epic adventure with his friends after meeting a mysterious storyteller who tells him about hidden treasures. Animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-03 18:20:00" d="2020-06-03 20:00:00" c="1"><n>Beverly Hills Chihuahua 3 Viva La Fiesta!</n><t>F</t>    <k>When they move into a new home, pooch Papi has to help unhappy runt of the litter Rosa feel special. Cute canine caper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-03 20:00:00" d="2020-06-03 21:50:00" c="1"><n>Mousehunt</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Lee Evans and Nathan Lane are the bumbling brothers whose plans to renovate a valuable building are thwarted by a super smart rodent. Comedy with Christopher Walken</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-06-03 21:50:00" d="2020-06-04 00:50:00" c="1"><n>Babe</n><t>F</t>    <k>Plucky piglet Babe discovers an unexpected talent for herding sheep which may just save him from becoming the Christmas dinner. Family favourite</k>  </p>
</a>
