<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-05-12 04:38:23"><p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-19 05:40:00" d="2020-05-19 07:30:00" c="1"><n>The Nutcracker And The Four Realms</n><t>F</t>    <k>56% Disney twist on a classic tale, as heroine Clara (Mackenzie Foy) discovers a magical land beset by conflict. Fantasy with Keira Knightley and Helen Mirren</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-19 07:30:00" d="2020-05-19 09:15:00" c="1"><n>Smallfoot</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% An epic journey ensues when a Yeti named Migo stumbles across a real human being - but is banished from his snowy home when no-one believes him. With Channing Tatum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-19 09:15:00" d="2020-05-19 11:20:00" c="1"><n>Annie</n><t>F</t>    <k>Quvenzhane Wallis, Jamie Foxx and Cameron Diaz star in this adaptation of the classic musical about a foster kid taken in by a wealthy businessman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-19 11:20:00" d="2020-05-19 13:00:00" c="1"><n>Cinderella</n><t>F</t>    <k>Cinderella is shocked to discover an evil witch has turned the prince into a mouse. Now, it's up to her to save him - can she do it in time? Enchanting animated fun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-19 13:00:00" d="2020-05-19 14:30:00" c="1"><n u="Open Season">Open Season 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% Elliot the mule deer and Boog the bear set out to free their friend from a gang of preening pets. Animated sequel with the voice of Billy Connolly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-19 14:30:00" d="2020-05-19 16:40:00" c="1"><n>The Karate Kid</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% New kid Daniel stands up to his bullies with the help of karate master Mr Miyagi in this family favourite. Starring Ralph Macchio and Pat Morita</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-19 16:40:00" d="2020-05-19 18:25:00" c="1"><n>Minuscule</n><t>F</t>    <k>When a plucky young ladybug gets trapped in a box, he suddenly finds himself being shipped to the Caribbean, so his insect friends assemble a team to rescue him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-19 18:25:00" d="2020-05-19 20:00:00" c="1"><n>Wheely</n><t>F</t>    <k>In a world of cars, one cab tries to become king of the road. When he goes on a journey of personal discovery, he finds out that being true to himself is more important</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-19 20:00:00" d="2020-05-19 21:45:00" c="1"><n>Smallfoot</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% An epic journey ensues when a Yeti named Migo stumbles across a real human being - but is banished from his snowy home when no-one believes him. With Channing Tatum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2020-05-19 21:45:00" d="2020-05-20 00:45:00" c="1"><n>Annie</n><t>F</t>    <k>Quvenzhane Wallis, Jamie Foxx and Cameron Diaz star in this adaptation of the classic musical about a foster kid taken in by a wealthy businessman</k>  </p>
</a>
