<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="14" t="2019-08-09 01:41:56"><p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-15 05:50:00" d="2019-08-15 07:25:00" c="1"><n>The Time Team</n><t>F</t>    <k>When a time-travelling mishap scatters his friends across the ages, Krash the rabbit must race to rescue them before it's too late. Frenetic animated adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-15 07:25:00" d="2019-08-15 08:50:00" c="1"><n u="Open Season">Open Season 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% Elliot the mule deer and Boog the bear set out to free their friend from a gang of preening pets. Animated sequel with the voice of Billy Connolly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-15 08:50:00" d="2019-08-15 10:10:00" c="1"><n u="Open Season">Open Season 3</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% A topsy-turvy adventure begins when Boog finds himself on the way to Russia with a circus. Elliot and the gang race to rescue him, but will they make it in time?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-15 10:10:00" d="2019-08-15 11:55:00" c="1"><n>The Lego Movie</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% An ordinary Lego construction worker becomes responsible for stopping a dastardly tyrant. Animated hit with an all-star voice cast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-15 11:55:00" d="2019-08-15 13:25:00" c="1"><n>The Cat In The Hat</n><t>F</t>    <k>39% Dr Seuss's mischievous moggy (Mike Myers) guarantees fun for the kids, but causes total chaos in their home. Cheerful fantasy featuring Alec Baldwin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-15 13:25:00" d="2019-08-15 15:25:00" c="1"><n>Lu Over The Wall</n><t>F</t>    <k>Talented but troubled teen Kai forms an unlikely friendship when his band's music attracts the attention of a singing mermaid named Lu. Eye-catching Japanese animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-15 15:25:00" d="2019-08-15 17:15:00" c="1"><n>Nanny McPhee</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Emma Thompson is a snaggletoothed Mary Poppins, bringing a touch of magic into the house of widowed Colin Firth and his seven rowdy kids. Charming family drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-15 17:15:00" d="2019-08-15 19:15:00" c="1"><n>Nanny McPhee &amp; The Big Bang</n><t>F</t>    <k>Snaggle-toothed kiddie whizz, Nanny McPhee (Emma Thompson) is called to the Green family when mum Isabel loses control of her boisterous brood. Fun family sequel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-15 19:15:00" d="2019-08-15 21:00:00" c="1"><n>The Lego Movie</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% An ordinary Lego construction worker becomes responsible for stopping a dastardly tyrant. Animated hit with an all-star voice cast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-15 21:00:00" d="2019-08-15 22:40:00" c="1"><n>Patrick</n><t>F</t>    <k>Teacher Sarah finds her life uprooted when she inherits her grandmother's prize possession - a spoilt pug named Patrick. From the director of Absolutely</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-15 22:40:00" d="2019-08-16 00:55:00" c="1"><n>The Legend Of Zorro</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% Antonio Banderas returns as the masked Mexican daredevil, battling slippery Rufus Sewell and saving Catherine Zeta-Jones. Gunpowder action comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-16 00:55:00" d="2019-08-16 02:35:00" c="1"><n>School Spirits</n><t>F</t>    <k>A teen relocates to a creepy small town filled with secrets and spooky activity. When she discovers it's haunted by ghosts, she takes on a dangerous battle to expel them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-16 02:35:00" d="2019-08-16 04:25:00" c="1"><n>Nanny McPhee</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Emma Thompson is a snaggletoothed Mary Poppins, bringing a touch of magic into the house of widowed Colin Firth and his seven rowdy kids. Charming family drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1046" o="2019-08-16 04:25:00" d="2019-08-16 06:00:00" c="1"><n>The Cat In The Hat</n><t>F</t>    <k>39% Dr Seuss's mischievous moggy (Mike Myers) guarantees fun for the kids, but causes total chaos in their home. Cheerful fantasy featuring Alec Baldwin</k>  </p>
</a>
