<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-05-13 04:36:13"><p id_tv="1047" o="2020-05-20 06:20:00" d="2020-05-20 08:00:00" c="1"><n>The Desert Rats</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Scottish commando Richard Burton leads a platoon of hardbitten Aussies in a war of attrition with James Mason's Rommel. WWII action sequel to The Desert Fox</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-05-20 08:00:00" d="2020-05-20 10:20:00" c="1"><n>The Rock</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% It's up to FBI scientist Nicolas Cage and federal prisoner Sean Connery to stop a turncoat general from destroying San Francisco</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-05-20 10:20:00" d="2020-05-20 12:00:00" c="1"><n u="Winchester">Winchester 73</n><t>F</t>    <k>Classic Western adventure following cowboy James Stewart as he battles to track down his prized Winchester rifle. Co-starring Shelley Winters and Dan Duryea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-05-20 12:00:00" d="2020-05-20 14:00:00" c="1"><n>Rear Window</n><t>F</t>    <k>84% Alfred Hitchcock's masterpiece sees a housebound James Stewart convinced his neighbour has murdered someone, recruiting Grace Kelly to investigate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-05-20 14:00:00" d="2020-05-20 16:15:00" c="1"><n>Vertigo</n><t>F</t>    <k>83% James Stewart is the detective with a fear of heights driven over the edge by icy blonde Kim Novak. Alfred Hitchcock's dizzying tale of obsession and intrigue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-05-20 16:15:00" d="2020-05-20 18:20:00" c="1"><n>The Man Who Shot Liberty Valance</n><t>F</t>    <k>80% Monumental John Ford western with Jimmy Stewart as the straight arrow lawyer who enlists hard-hitting cowboy John Wayne to tame vicious gunslinger Lee Marvin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-05-20 18:20:00" d="2020-05-20 20:10:00" c="1"><n>Shenandoah</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Pacifist farmer James Stewart strives to keep his family out of the American Civil War, but the capture of his youngest son forces him into action. Moving classic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-05-20 20:10:00" d="2020-05-20 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Three Men And A Baby</n><t>F</t>    <k>Tom Selleck, Ted Danson and Steve Guttenberg must adapt to life as parents after one of their ex-girlfriends lumbers them with a new-born. Fatherly fun with Nancy Travis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-05-20 22:00:00" d="2020-05-21 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Saving Private Ryan</n><t>F</t>    <k>85% Steven Spielberg's Oscar-winner stars Tom Hanks as the hardened veteran leading a platoon on a WWII rescue mission</k>  </p>
</a>
