<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-07-11 00:21:01"><p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-17 05:15:00" d="2019-07-17 07:00:00" c="1"><n>Casablanca</n><t>F</t>    <k>85% Oscar-winning wartime romance starring Humphrey Bogart as an ex-pat bar owner torn between love and virtue. Ingrid Bergman co-stars as his former flame</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-17 07:00:00" d="2019-07-17 09:00:00" c="1"><n>The Sugarland Express</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Goldie Hawn busts her husband out of jail, kidnaps a cop and goes on the run in Texas. Crime drama from Steven Spielberg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-17 09:00:00" d="2019-07-17 11:00:00" c="1"><n>To Sir With Love</n><t>F</t>    <k>New teacher Sidney Poitier tries to inspire the students of a rough east London school using his own unorthodox methods. Touching drama co-starring Lulu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-17 11:00:00" d="2019-07-17 12:50:00" c="1"><n>Cool Runnings</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Disgraced ex-bobsledder John Candy attempts to coach Jamaica's first ever bobsleigh team to an unlikely Olympic victory. Feelgood family favourite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-17 12:50:00" d="2019-07-17 14:50:00" c="1"><n>Trading Places</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% A bet between two rich old brokers puts skint hustler Eddie Murphy on Wall St and snob Dan Aykroyd in the gutter. Classic John Landis comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-17 14:50:00" d="2019-07-17 16:50:00" c="1"><n>Kramer Vs Kramer</n><t>F</t>    <k>Dustin Hoffman and Meryl Streep won Oscars for their roles in this landmark drama about two parents fighting for custody of their son. Poignant Best Picture winner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-17 16:50:00" d="2019-07-17 19:10:00" c="1"><n>The Sting</n><t>F</t>    <k>83% Grifters Robert Redford and Paul Newman try their hand at conning a fortune out of a murderous banker. Top crime caper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-17 19:10:00" d="2019-07-17 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Cool Runnings</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Disgraced ex-bobsledder John Candy attempts to coach Jamaica's first ever bobsleigh team to an unlikely Olympic victory. Feelgood family favourite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-17 21:00:00" d="2019-07-17 23:00:00" c="1"><n>Trading Places</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% A bet between two rich old brokers puts skint hustler Eddie Murphy on Wall St and snob Dan Aykroyd in the gutter. Classic John Landis comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-17 23:00:00" d="2019-07-18 01:25:00" c="1"><n>Face/Off</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Nicolas Cage and John Travolta tear it up as a crook and a cop who swap faces in John Woo's superslick action extravaganza. With Joan Allen and Gina Gershon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-18 01:25:00" d="2019-07-18 03:45:00" c="1"><n>Primal Fear</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Altar boy Edward Norton convinces hotshot lawyer Richard Gere to defend him in a murder case. Psychological thriller with strong language</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-18 03:45:00" d="2019-07-18 05:25:00" c="1"><n>Alien Nation</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% In a world where aliens live among the human population, cop James Caan works with ET police detective Mandy Patinkin to track down his partner's killer. Sci-fi thriller</k>  </p>
</a>
