<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2021-07-09 07:10:28"><p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-14 05:10:00" d="2021-07-14 07:35:00" c="1"><n>The Quiet Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Ex-boxer John Wayne returns to his rural Irish hometown to settle down and tame feisty Maureen O'Hara. Hugely enjoyable slice of Oscar-winning blarney from John Ford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-14 07:35:00" d="2021-07-14 10:05:00" c="1"><n>Walk The Line</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% Joaquin Phoenix stars as country music legend Johnny Cash. Cracking biopic of the Man in Black with Oscar-winning backing from Reese Witherspoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-14 10:05:00" d="2021-07-14 11:50:00" c="1"><n>The Browning Version</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% Literary drama with the late Albert Finney excellent as the disliked classics teacher pushed into retirement by headmaster Michael Gambon. Directed by Mike Figgis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-14 11:50:00" d="2021-07-14 13:50:00" c="1"><n>Breakfast At Tiffany's</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% This film has outdated attitudes, language and cultural depictions which may cause offence today. Iconic romance based on Truman Capote's novella with Audrey Hepburn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-14 13:50:00" d="2021-07-14 15:20:00" c="1"><n>Locke</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Construction manager Tom Hardy has a great job and a wonderful family, until one phone call threatens to bring everything crashing down. Real-time drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-14 15:20:00" d="2021-07-14 17:40:00" c="1"><n>Walk The Line</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% Joaquin Phoenix stars as country music legend Johnny Cash. Cracking biopic of the Man in Black with Oscar-winning backing from Reese Witherspoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-14 17:40:00" d="2021-07-14 20:00:00" c="1"><n>Love Actually</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Richard Curtis's romantic comedy follows the intertwining lives of a group of loved-up Londoners. Starring Hugh Grant, Colin Firth and Liam Neeson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-14 20:00:00" d="2021-07-14 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Breakfast At Tiffany's</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% This film has outdated attitudes, language and cultural depictions which may cause offence today. Iconic romance based on Truman Capote's novella with Audrey Hepburn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-14 22:00:00" d="2021-07-15 00:20:00" c="1"><n>Jerry Maguire</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% Tom Cruise stars as a struggling sports agent who falls for single mum Renee Zellweger. Top romantic comedy with Cuba Gooding Jr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-15 00:20:00" d="2021-07-15 02:10:00" c="1"><n>First Blood</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% When Vietnam vet John Rambo (Sylvester Stallone) is arrested and humiliated by an over-zealous sheriff, he escapes, drawing the police into a violent pursuit. Iconic action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-15 02:10:00" d="2021-07-15 04:00:00" c="1"><n u="Rambo: First Blood Part">Rambo: First Blood Part II</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Sylvester Stallone returns as aggressive army veteran John Rambo, sent back to Vietnam on a top secret assignment. Oscar-nominated action sequel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-15 04:00:00" d="2021-07-15 06:00:00" c="1"><n>Guess Who's Coming To Dinner</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% A young woman throws her parents into a moral turmoil when she brings her black fiancé home to dinner. Starring Katharine Hepburn, Spencer Tracy and Sidney Poitier</k>  </p>
</a>
