<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-04-09 04:36:01"><p id_tv="1047" o="2020-04-16 06:30:00" d="2020-04-16 08:10:00" c="1"><n>Raising Arizona</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Nicolas Cage is the ex-con who swipes one of Arizona's famous quintuplets for childless wife Holly Hunter. Crime comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-04-16 08:10:00" d="2020-04-16 10:00:00" c="1"><n>Monty Python's Meaning Of Life</n><t>F</t>    <k>The Pythons' final film features bedroom tips from headmaster John Cleese, reasonably violent accountants and the lardy Mr Creosote</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-04-16 10:00:00" d="2020-04-16 11:40:00" c="1"><n>King Ralph</n><t>F</t>    <k>54% Las Vegas showman John Goodman is launched into high society when he is found to be the only living heir to the British throne. Royally funny comedy with Peter O'Toole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-04-16 11:40:00" d="2020-04-16 13:40:00" c="1"><n>The Bourne Supremacy</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Matt Damon returns as the amnesiac assassin, forced to abandon his quiet new life when he's framed for murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-04-16 13:40:00" d="2020-04-16 15:55:00" c="1"><n>The Bodyguard</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Megastar singer Whitney Houston hires bodyguard Kevin Costner to protect her from a stalker. Oscar-nominated romantic drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-04-16 15:55:00" d="2020-04-16 18:00:00" c="1"><n>The Social Network</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Jesse Eisenberg plays Facebook founder Mark Zuckerberg in David Fincher's Oscar-winning drama. With Andrew Garfield and Justin Timberlake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-04-16 18:00:00" d="2020-04-16 20:00:00" c="1"><n>Gran Torino</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% Drama starring Clint Eastwood as a cantankerous Korean War veteran who reluctantly becomes a hero to his immigrant neighbours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-04-16 20:00:00" d="2020-04-16 23:00:00"><n>Elizabeth: The Golden Age</n>    <k>In an England overshadowed by mighty Spain, queen Cate Blanchett courts Clive Owen and competes with rival Samantha Morton. Lavish drama nominated for two Oscars. Violence.(2007)</k>  </p>
</a>
