<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2019-08-13 02:27:17"><p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-20 05:00:00" d="2019-08-20 07:00:00" c="1"><n>Rio Grande</n><t>F</t>    <k>Besieged colonel John Wayne battles Apache raiders, but his hardest fight is with his own son. Strong western; a fitting finale to John Ford's legendary Cavalry trilogy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-20 07:00:00" d="2019-08-20 09:10:00" c="1"><n>Taps</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Army cadets Tom Cruise and Sean Penn go to extreme lengths to protect their academy when it is threatened by local developers. Gripping drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-20 09:10:00" d="2019-08-20 10:55:00" c="1"><n>Dr. Seuss' The Lorax</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% In the synthetic town of Thneedville, a besotted boy takes up a quest to find the last real tree on earth. Animation with the voice of Danny DeVito</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-20 10:55:00" d="2019-08-20 12:55:00" c="1"><n>Gran Torino</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% Drama starring Clint Eastwood as a cantankerous Korean War veteran who reluctantly becomes a hero to his immigrant neighbours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-20 12:55:00" d="2019-08-20 15:20:00" c="1"><n>Catch Me If You Can</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% Leo DiCaprio stars as the teen conman who led the FBI on a paper chase, with Tom Hanks as the agent on his trail. Real-life caper from Steven Spielberg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-20 15:20:00" d="2019-08-20 17:00:00" c="1"><n>Honey, I Shrunk The Kids</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% Eccentric scientist Rick Moranis has some explaining to do after he reduces four children to the size of insects. Can the tiny tots survive long enough</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-20 17:00:00" d="2019-08-20 19:00:00" c="1"><n>Tootsie</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% Dustin Hoffman plays an out of work actor who, out of desperation, pretends to be a woman to get a part on a soap opera. Classic comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-20 19:00:00" d="2019-08-20 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Gran Torino</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% Drama starring Clint Eastwood as a cantankerous Korean War veteran who reluctantly becomes a hero to his immigrant neighbours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-20 21:00:00" d="2019-08-21 00:00:00" c="1"><n>Catch Me If You Can</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% Leo DiCaprio stars as the teen conman who led the FBI on a paper chase, with Tom Hanks as the agent on his trail. Real-life caper from Steven Spielberg</k>  </p>
</a>
