<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-05-27 04:36:02"><p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-03 06:30:00" d="2020-06-03 09:00:00" c="1"><n>Blood Diamond</n><t>F</t>    <k>80% Mercenary Leonardo DiCaprio helps Djimon Hounsou find his stolen son in exchange for a rare jewel, in war-torn Sierra Leone. Thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-03 09:00:00" d="2020-06-03 10:50:00" c="1"><n>Father Of The Bride</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Doting father Steve Martin struggles to let his little girl go when she announces that she is engaged to be married. Comedy remake starring Diane Keaton and Martin Short</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-03 10:50:00" d="2020-06-03 14:05:00" c="1"><n>Spartacus</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% Stanley Kubrick's Oscar-winning epic stars the late Kirk Douglas as the heroic slave who leads a rebellion against the Romans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-03 14:05:00" d="2020-06-03 16:25:00" c="1"><n>Evita</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% Madonna gives a career-best performance as Argentina's controversial Eva Peron. Antonio Banderas co-stars in an Oscar-winning adaptation of Andrew Lloyd Webber's musical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-03 16:25:00" d="2020-06-03 18:25:00" c="1"><n>Twister</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Helen Hunt and the late Bill Paxton star in this FX-filled action movie about rival teams of scientists competing to investigate a series of destructive tornadoes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-03 18:25:00" d="2020-06-03 20:15:00" c="1"><n>Twins</n><t>F</t>    <k>60% Two unlikely brothers reunite after years apart to seek out their long-lost mother. Comedy with Danny DeVito</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-03 20:15:00" d="2020-06-03 22:00:00" c="1"><n>The Truman Show</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% Jim Carrey is an ordinary guy in an ordinary town. He's also the unsuspecting star of the world's longest-running reality TV show. Intelligent drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-03 22:00:00" d="2020-06-04 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Carlito's Way</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% Al Pacino stars as the ex-con trying to go straight but unable to escape his violent past. Thriller with Sean Penn</k>  </p>
</a>
