<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2021-07-08 05:05:12"><p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-13 05:05:00" d="2021-07-13 07:00:00" c="1"><n>Holiday Inn</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% This film has outdated attitudes, language and cultural depictions which may cause offence today. Musical romance starring Fred Astaire and Bing Crosby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-13 07:00:00" d="2021-07-13 08:55:00" c="1"><n>That Touch Of Mink</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Smooth talking banker Cary Grant tries to woo the late Doris Day into a no-strings attached weekend away to Bermuda, but she's holding out for a wedding ring. Fun comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-13 08:55:00" d="2021-07-13 11:15:00" c="1"><n>The Quiet Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Ex-boxer John Wayne returns to his rural Irish hometown to settle down and tame feisty Maureen O'Hara. Hugely enjoyable slice of Oscar-winning blarney from John Ford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-13 11:15:00" d="2021-07-13 13:00:00" c="1"><n u="Jurassic Park">Jurassic Park III</n><t>F</t>    <k>60% Dino expert Sam Neill is hired by warring couple William H Macy and Tea Leoni to rescue their son from raptors. Steven Spielberg produces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-13 13:00:00" d="2021-07-13 15:25:00" c="1"><n>Vanilla Sky</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Playboy Tom Cruise's new romance with dancer Penelope Cruz is ruined by crazed lover Cameron Diaz in this mindbending mystery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-13 15:25:00" d="2021-07-13 17:05:00" c="1"><n>The Browning Version</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% Literary drama with the late Albert Finney excellent as the disliked classics teacher pushed into retirement by headmaster Michael Gambon. Directed by Mike Figgis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-13 17:05:00" d="2021-07-13 19:20:00" c="1"><n>Glory</n><t>F</t>    <k>Oscar-winning drama chronicling the story of the first all-black regiment to fight in the US Civil war. Starring Matthew Broderick, Morgan Freeman and Denzel Washington</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-13 19:20:00" d="2021-07-13 21:00:00" c="1"><n u="Jurassic Park">Jurassic Park III</n><t>F</t>    <k>60% Dino expert Sam Neill is hired by warring couple William H Macy and Tea Leoni to rescue their son from raptors. Steven Spielberg produces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-13 21:00:00" d="2021-07-13 23:30:00" c="1"><n>Vanilla Sky</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Playboy Tom Cruise's new romance with dancer Penelope Cruz is ruined by crazed lover Cameron Diaz in this mindbending mystery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-13 23:30:00" d="2021-07-14 01:30:00" c="1"><n>American Psycho</n><t>F</t>    <k>Slick banker Christian Bale lets his murderous alter-ego out to play in this wickedly sharp drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-14 01:30:00" d="2021-07-14 03:15:00" c="1"><n>Another 48 Hrs</n><t>F</t>    <k>Nick Nolte's no-nonsense cop reteams with Eddie Murphy's motor-mouthed crook to take down a ruthless San Francisco drug lord</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-14 03:15:00" d="2021-07-14 05:10:00" c="1"><n>That Touch Of Mink</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Smooth talking banker Cary Grant tries to woo the late Doris Day into a no-strings attached weekend away to Bermuda, but she's holding out for a wedding ring. Fun comedy</k>  </p>
</a>
