<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-05-29 04:36:22"><p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-05 07:25:00" d="2020-06-05 09:45:00" c="1"><n>Master And Commander: The Far Side Of The World</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% Outgunned but defiant, captain Russell Crowe and his fearless crew hunt a French warship. Rip-roaring epic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-05 09:45:00" d="2020-06-05 12:00:00" c="1"><n>The Karate Kid</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% New kid Daniel stands up to his bullies with the help of karate master Mr Miyagi in this family favourite. Starring Ralph Macchio and Pat Morita</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-05 12:00:00" d="2020-06-05 14:00:00" c="1"><n u="The Karate Kid Part">The Karate Kid Part II</n><t>F</t>    <k>High-kicking karate student Daniel and his mentor Mr Miyagi travel to Japan to settle an old score. Family action sequel with Pat Morita and Ralph Macchio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-05 14:00:00" d="2020-06-05 16:00:00" c="1"><n u="The Karate Kid Part">The Karate Kid Part III</n><t>F</t>    <k>Hothead Daniel dumps Mr Miyagi for a new coach. But without his ally, can the youngster defeat the toxic waste baron who is training an old enemy?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-05 16:00:00" d="2020-06-05 18:00:00" c="1"><n>Argo</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Ben Affleck's CIA agent is charged with bringing home six Americans stranded in revolutionary Iran. Oscar-winning thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-05 18:00:00" d="2020-06-05 20:00:00" c="1"><n>The Goonies</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% Sean Astin, Corey Feldman and Josh Brolin star in this comedy adventure following a group of kids on their perilous search for pirate treasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-05 20:00:00" d="2020-06-05 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Lethal Weapon</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Veteran cop Danny Glover and suicidal young maverick Mel Gibson team up in the quest to thwart a drug-smuggling operation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-05 22:00:00" d="2020-06-06 01:00:00" c="1"><n u="Lethal Weapon">Lethal Weapon 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Rapid-fire action sequel with Mel Gibson and Danny Glover as the bickering cops closing the net on a mob of South African drug smugglers</k>  </p>
</a>
