<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-07-11 00:21:01"><p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-16 05:15:00" d="2019-07-16 07:30:00" c="1"><n>Chariots Of Fire</n><t>F</t>    <k>Oscar-winning drama following the fortunes of two very different athletes battling to compete in the 1924 Olympics. Starring Ben Cross and Ian Charleson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-16 07:30:00" d="2019-07-16 09:25:00" c="1"><n>Closer</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Julia Roberts, Clive Owen, Natalie Portman and Jude Law: two boys, two girls, two couples. But who ends up with whom? Crackling drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-16 09:25:00" d="2019-07-16 11:00:00" c="1"><n>Little Nicky</n><t>F</t>    <k>53% It's hell on earth for Satan's useless son, who can't quite get to grips with his dad's evil ways. Imaginative comedy with Adam Sandler, Harvey Keitel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-16 11:00:00" d="2019-07-16 13:00:00" c="1"><n>Tropic Thunder</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Ben Stiller plays a Hollywood star who unwittingly leads a group of actors into a real war zone. Comedy with Robert Downey Jr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-16 13:00:00" d="2019-07-16 15:15:00" c="1"><n>U.S. Marshals</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% In this sequel to The Fugitive, Tommy Lee Jones's dogged lawman is on the trail of rogue government hitman Wesley Snipes. Action thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-16 15:15:00" d="2019-07-16 17:15:00" c="1"><n>Casablanca</n><t>F</t>    <k>85% Oscar-winning wartime romance starring Humphrey Bogart as an ex-pat bar owner torn between love and virtue. Ingrid Bergman co-stars as his former flame</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-16 17:15:00" d="2019-07-16 19:25:00" c="1"><n>The Magnificent Seven</n><t>F</t>    <k>80% Yul Brynner is the enigmatic gunslinger who rounds up a posse of roguish mercenaries to help rid a poor Mexican farming village of bandit Eli Wallach. Classic Western</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-16 19:25:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Little Nicky</n><t>F</t>    <k>53% It's hell on earth for Satan's useless son, who can't quite get to grips with his dad's evil ways. Imaginative comedy with Adam Sandler, Harvey Keitel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 23:00:00" c="1"><n>Tropic Thunder</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Ben Stiller plays a Hollywood star who unwittingly leads a group of actors into a real war zone. Comedy with Robert Downey Jr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-16 23:00:00" d="2019-07-17 01:15:00" c="1"><n>U.S. Marshals</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% In this sequel to The Fugitive, Tommy Lee Jones's dogged lawman is on the trail of rogue government hitman Wesley Snipes. Action thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-17 01:15:00" d="2019-07-17 02:50:00" c="1"><n>The Wicker Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% Policeman Edward Woodward travels to a remote island to investigate a disappearance, but slowly discovers there is something more sinister afoot. Classic Brit horror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-07-17 02:50:00" d="2019-07-17 05:15:00" c="1"><n>The Doors</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Val Kilmer triumphs as Lizard King Jim Morrison in director Oliver Stone's freewheeling adaptation of the magnetic music legend's life. With Meg Ryan and Kyle MacLachlan</k>  </p>
</a>
