<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2021-07-10 05:03:15"><p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-17 07:00:00" d="2021-07-17 09:00:00" c="1"><n>Annie</n><t>F</t>    <k>Quvenzhane Wallis, Jamie Foxx and Cameron Diaz star in this adaptation of the classic musical about a foster kid taken in by a wealthy businessman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-17 09:00:00" d="2021-07-17 11:10:00" c="1"><n>Annie</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Classic musical about a scrappy young orphan whose life changes overnight when she is taken in by a billionaire. Starring Carol Burnett and the late Albert Finney</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-17 11:10:00" d="2021-07-17 13:20:00" c="1"><n>Batman</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% Michael Keaton's Bruce Wayne takes on Jack Nicholson's villainous Joker. Gothic Gotham fantasy directed by Tim Burton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-17 13:20:00" d="2021-07-17 15:45:00" c="1"><n>Batman Begins</n><t>F</t>    <k>A billionaire playboy begins a one-man crusade to clean up Gotham City's streets. Christian Bale stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-17 15:45:00" d="2021-07-17 17:30:00" c="1"><n>Italian Job, The</n><t>F</t>    <k>Ex-convict Michael Caine hatches an audacious plan to steal $4 million, involving a bus, two Jaguars and, of course, three Mini Coopers. Comic adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-17 17:30:00" d="2021-07-17 19:30:00" c="1"><n>The Italian Job</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% A gang of double-crossed thieves plan to cause a monumental traffic jam in a bid to reclaim their loot. Starring Mark Wahlberg and Ed Norton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-17 19:30:00" d="2021-07-17 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Superman</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Superman fights to thwart criminal Lex Luthor's (Gene Hackman) plans for world domination. Christopher Reeve stars as the Man of Steel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2021-07-17 22:00:00" d="2021-07-18 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Man Of Steel</n><t>F</t>    <k>Henry Cavill dons the Superman suit, as a young Clark Kent embarks on a path to save the world from the villainous Zod</k>  </p>
</a>
