<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-08-15 22:52:02"><p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-21 05:45:00" d="2019-08-21 07:30:00" c="1"><n>Honey, I Shrunk The Kids</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% Eccentric scientist Rick Moranis has some explaining to do after he reduces four children to the size of insects. Can the tiny tots survive long enough</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-21 07:30:00" d="2019-08-21 09:25:00" c="1"><n>Charlie's Angels</n><t>F</t>    <k>57% Cameron Diaz, Lucy Liu and Drew Barrymore star as the sexy crime-fighting trio in this frenetic action comedy based on the hit 70s TV series. With Bill Murray</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-21 09:25:00" d="2019-08-21 11:30:00" c="1"><n>Boomerang</n><t>F</t>    <k>56% Romcom starring Eddie Murphy as a womanising marketing director who meets his match in new boss Robin Givens. Halle Berry co-stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-21 11:30:00" d="2019-08-21 13:30:00" c="1"><n>Safe House</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Sparks fly when CIA man Ryan Reynolds is tasked with keeping watch over murderous rogue agent Denzel Washington. Action thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-21 13:30:00" d="2019-08-21 15:35:00" c="1"><n>The Untouchables</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% Robert De Niro stars as mob boss Al Capone, with Kevin Costner as the Treasury agent determined to take him down. Gangland thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-21 15:35:00" d="2019-08-21 17:10:00" c="1"><n>Weird Science</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Cult John Hughes comedy. Two teens build the perfect woman on their PC. Anthony Michael Hall, Kelly LeBrock, Bill Paxton and Robert Downey Jr star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-21 17:10:00" d="2019-08-21 19:00:00" c="1"><n>Jason And The Argonauts</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% An enthralling story following the famous Greek hero, Jason, as he embarks on a treacherous journey in the hope of finding the legendary Golden Fleece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-21 19:00:00" d="2019-08-21 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Safe House</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Sparks fly when CIA man Ryan Reynolds is tasked with keeping watch over murderous rogue agent Denzel Washington. Action thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-21 21:00:00" d="2019-08-21 23:00:00" c="1"><n>The Untouchables</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% Robert De Niro stars as mob boss Al Capone, with Kevin Costner as the Treasury agent determined to take him down. Gangland thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-21 23:00:00" d="2019-08-22 00:40:00" c="1"><n>The Transporter</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Ice cool Jason Statham transports anything, no questions asked. However, one package could be his undoing in this crime thriller from writer Luc Besson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-22 00:40:00" d="2019-08-22 02:20:00" c="1"><n u="Transporter">Transporter 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>Driver Jason Statham burns rubber in a race to clear his name, save a kidnapped boy and take down a Colombian coke baron. Action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-22 02:20:00" d="2019-08-22 05:00:00" c="1"><n>The Hurricane</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% Powerful drama with Denzel Washington as Rubin 'Hurricane' Carter, a boxer wrongfully imprisoned who fights to prove his innocence</k>  </p>
</a>
