<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-08-09 01:41:59"><p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-15 05:30:00" d="2019-08-15 07:15:00" c="1"><n>Singin' In The Rain</n><t>F</t>    <k>84% In one of the most acclaimed musicals of all time, silent movie actors Gene Kelly and Lina Lamont make a toe-tapping transition into the new-fangled era of the talkies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-15 07:15:00" d="2019-08-15 09:15:00" c="1"><n>To Sir With Love</n><t>F</t>    <k>New teacher Sidney Poitier tries to inspire the students of a rough east London school using his own unorthodox methods. Touching drama co-starring Lulu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-15 09:15:00" d="2019-08-15 11:15:00" c="1"><n>Roman Holiday</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% Timeless romance that gave us an Oscar-winning Audrey Hepburn as the Italian princess who falls for hardbitten Yankee reporter Gregory Peck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-15 11:15:00" d="2019-08-15 13:20:00" c="1"><n>Frost/Nixon</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% TV presenter David Frost (Michael Sheen) tries to prise a confession out of disgraced ex-president Richard Nixon (Frank Langella). Drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-15 13:20:00" d="2019-08-15 15:25:00" c="1"><n>Hot Fuzz</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% Cops Simon Pegg and Nick Frost investigate a series of deaths in a quiet English village. Action comedy directed by Edgar Wright</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-15 15:25:00" d="2019-08-15 17:25:00" c="1"><n>Nine To Five</n><t>F</t>    <k>Harassed secretaries Dolly Parton, Jane Fonda and Lily Tomlin decide to get even with their chauvinist pig of a boss. Comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-15 17:25:00" d="2019-08-15 19:00:00" c="1"><n>All The Right Moves</n><t>F</t>    <k>59% Young football player Tom Cruise hopes a college scholarship will help him escape small-town life, but clashes with his coach threaten to derail his dreams. Sports drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-15 19:00:00" d="2019-08-15 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Shanghai Knights</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% When Chinese sheriff Jackie Chan's father is murdered, he teams up with Owen Wilson and heads to London to gain revenge. Action comedy sequel with Aidan Gillen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-15 21:00:00" d="2019-08-15 23:00:00" c="1"><n>Hot Fuzz</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% Cops Simon Pegg and Nick Frost investigate a series of deaths in a quiet English village. Action comedy directed by Edgar Wright</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-15 23:00:00" d="2019-08-16 01:05:00" c="1"><n>American Pie: Reunion</n><t>F</t>    <k>The gang go to their school reunion in this hilarious fourth entry in the hit series. Jason Biggs and Seann William Scott star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-16 01:05:00" d="2019-08-16 03:00:00" c="1"><n>The Accused</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Jodie Foster is exceptional as the rape victim who struggles to prosecute her attackers. Harrowing drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-16 03:00:00" d="2019-08-16 05:00:00" c="1"><n>Hollow Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% Unhinged scientist Kevin Bacon steals a new invisibility serum and stalks his colleagues to conceal his crime. Dark sci-fi from the director of Robocop</k>  </p>
</a>
