<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-08-13 02:27:14"><p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-19 05:35:00" d="2019-08-19 07:10:00" c="1"><n>The Swan Princess</n><t>F</t>    <k>After being turned into a swan by a greedy magician, Princess Odette looks to her new animal chums for help. Animated fairytale with John Cleese among the voice cast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-19 07:10:00" d="2019-08-19 08:55:00" c="1"><n>All The Right Moves</n><t>F</t>    <k>59% Young football player Tom Cruise hopes a college scholarship will help him escape small-town life, but clashes with his coach threaten to derail his dreams. Sports drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-19 08:55:00" d="2019-08-19 10:45:00" c="1"><n>We're No Angels</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Escaped convicts Robert De Niro and Sean Penn are mistaken for priests. Demi Moore co-stars in a small-town comedy scripted by David Mamet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-19 10:45:00" d="2019-08-19 13:15:00" c="1"><n>A.I. Artificial Intelligence</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% Haley Joel Osment is the robot boy who wants only to be human, Jude Law the mechanical gigolo helping him find his future. Steven Spielberg sci-fi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-19 13:15:00" d="2019-08-19 15:00:00" c="1"><n>Gravity</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% When disaster hits, astronauts Sandra Bullock and George Clooney are left fighting for survival in space. Stunning winner of seven Oscars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-19 15:00:00" d="2019-08-19 16:45:00" c="1"><n>Say Anything...</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% Classic teen romance from Jerry Maguire director Cameron Crowe. A beautiful and brilliant high school student finds herself pursued by charming underachiever John Cusack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-19 16:45:00" d="2019-08-19 18:30:00" c="1"><n>Napoleon Dynamite</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Can high school geek Napoleon help his pal Pedro become class president? Jon Heder stars in this winning cult comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-19 18:30:00" d="2019-08-19 21:00:00" c="1"><n>A.I. Artificial Intelligence</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% Haley Joel Osment is the robot boy who wants only to be human, Jude Law the mechanical gigolo helping him find his future. Steven Spielberg sci-fi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-19 21:00:00" d="2019-08-19 22:45:00" c="1"><n>Gravity</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% When disaster hits, astronauts Sandra Bullock and George Clooney are left fighting for survival in space. Stunning winner of seven Oscars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-19 22:45:00" d="2019-08-20 00:40:00" c="1"><n u="District">District 9</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% A government official gets a shock when he evicts an alien race from their Johannesburg town. Sci-fi action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-20 00:40:00" d="2019-08-20 02:50:00" c="1"><n>Deep Impact</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% With an unstoppable asteroid headed for earth, could this be the end for humankind? Sci-fi disaster epic with Morgan Freeman and Tea Leoni</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-20 02:50:00" d="2019-08-20 05:00:00" c="1"><n>American Beauty</n><t>F</t>    <k>84% Stifled suburbanite Kevin Spacey impulsively overhauls his life, creating friction with wife Annette Bening. Oscar-winning drama from Sam Mendes</k>  </p>
</a>
