<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-04-15 04:36:23"><p id_tv="1047" o="2020-04-22 05:30:00" d="2020-04-22 07:25:00" c="1"><n>Shenandoah</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Pacifist farmer James Stewart strives to keep his family out of the American Civil War, but the capture of his youngest son forces him into action. Moving classic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-04-22 07:25:00" d="2020-04-22 09:40:00" c="1"><n>The Verdict</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Oscar nominated Paul Newman is the washed-up lawyer who swaps the bottle for a malpractice suit against slick James Mason. Riveting courtroom drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-04-22 09:40:00" d="2020-04-22 12:15:00" c="1"><n>Armageddon</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Ben Affleck and Bruce Willis star as expert drillers who are sent into space to plant explosives inside an asteroid headed for Earth. Blockbusting action from Michael Bay</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-04-22 12:15:00" d="2020-04-22 13:55:00" c="1"><n>Gravity</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% When disaster hits, astronauts Sandra Bullock and George Clooney are left fighting for survival in space. Stunning winner of seven Oscars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-04-22 13:55:00" d="2020-04-22 16:05:00" c="1"><n>Notting Hill</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Bookshop owner Hugh Grant forms an unlikely romance with superstar actress Julia Roberts in this hit Richard Curtis romcom. Co-stars Rhys Ifans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-04-22 16:05:00" d="2020-04-22 17:55:00" c="1"><n>Shaun Of The Dead</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% Life's a yawn for Shaun, until zombies take over London. Then it's a no guts, no glory rescue mission: to the pub! Comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-04-22 17:55:00" d="2020-04-22 19:55:00" c="1"><n>Blade Runner: The Final Cut</n><t>F</t>    <k>The ultimate version of Ridley Scott's classic. Harrison Ford stars as a bounty hunter who must hunt dangerous 'Replicants'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-04-22 19:55:00" d="2020-04-22 22:55:00" c="1"><n>Argo</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Ben Affleck's CIA agent is charged with bringing home six Americans stranded in revolutionary Iran. Oscar-winning thriller</k>  </p>
</a>
