<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-05-26 04:34:31"><p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-02 05:50:00" d="2020-06-02 07:30:00" c="1"><n u="Winchester">Winchester 73</n><t>F</t>    <k>Classic Western adventure following cowboy James Stewart as he battles to track down his prized Winchester rifle. Co-starring Shelley Winters and Dan Duryea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-02 07:30:00" d="2020-06-02 09:10:00" c="1"><n>Weird Science</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Cult John Hughes comedy. Two teens build the perfect woman on their PC. Anthony Michael Hall, Kelly LeBrock, Bill Paxton and Robert Downey Jr star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-02 09:10:00" d="2020-06-02 11:05:00" c="1"><n>The Royal Tenenbaums</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% Wily dad Gene Hackman tries to reunite his family of oddball geniuses in Wes Anderson's quirky black comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-02 11:05:00" d="2020-06-02 12:35:00" c="1"><n u="Evil Dead">Evil Dead II</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Savage sequel to Sam Raimi's 1981 hit horror. A weekend break at an isolated cabin turns nasty when Bruce Campbell unwittingly unleashes an evil spirit on the guests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-02 12:35:00" d="2020-06-02 15:20:00" c="1"><n>Once Upon A Time In The West</n><t>F</t>    <k>Hired gun Henry Fonda and mysterious stranger Charles Bronson square off in this landmark Western. Magnificent classic from the legendary Sergio Leone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-02 15:20:00" d="2020-06-02 17:40:00" c="1"><n>Terminator 2: Judgement Day</n><t>F</t>    <k>Classic sci-fi action sequel starring Arnold Schwarzenegger as a cyborg sent back in time to protect humanity's hope for the future. James Cameron directs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-02 17:40:00" d="2020-06-02 20:00:00" c="1"><n u="Zulu">Zulu (1963)</n><t>F</t>    <k>A handful of British troops face Zulu attack at Rorke's Drift in 1879. Stirring war classic featuring Michael Caine in his breakthrough role</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-02 20:00:00" d="2020-06-02 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Road To Perdition</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Gangster Tom Hanks goes on the run to save his son from mob boss Paul Newman and killer Jude Law. Oscar-winning Sam Mendes drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2020-06-02 22:00:00" d="2020-06-03 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Notting Hill</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Bookshop owner Hugh Grant forms an unlikely romance with superstar actress Julia Roberts in this hit Richard Curtis romcom. Co-stars Rhys Ifans</k>  </p>
</a>
