<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-08-15 22:52:05"><p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-22 05:00:00" d="2019-08-22 07:00:00" c="1"><n>Jason And The Argonauts</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% An enthralling story following the famous Greek hero, Jason, as he embarks on a treacherous journey in the hope of finding the legendary Golden Fleece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-22 07:00:00" d="2019-08-22 09:00:00" c="1"><n>Steel Magnolias</n><t>F</t>    <k>Julia Roberts and a stellar cast of southern belles ride out emotional storms with tears, laughter and good manicures. Comedy drama with Sally Field and Shirley MacLaine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-22 09:00:00" d="2019-08-22 10:50:00" c="1"><n>Signs</n><t>F</t>    <k>When crop circles herald the arrival of alien invaders, ex-preacher Mel Gibson must fight to save his family. Sci-fi suspense with Joaquin Phoenix</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-22 10:50:00" d="2019-08-22 12:50:00" c="1"><n>I, Robot</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% In 2035, robots are built to help humans. But when there's a murder, cop Will Smith is convinced that the machines have gone bad. Sci-fi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-22 12:50:00" d="2019-08-22 14:50:00" c="1"><n>Poltergeist</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% A young suburban family are targeted by sinister supernatural forces in this haunted-house horror from The Texas Chain Saw Massacre director Tobe Hooper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-22 14:50:00" d="2019-08-22 17:00:00" c="1"><n>The Sting</n><t>F</t>    <k>83% Grifters Robert Redford and Paul Newman try their hand at conning a fortune out of a murderous banker. Top crime caper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-22 17:00:00" d="2019-08-22 19:00:00" c="1"><n>The Truman Show</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% Jim Carrey is an ordinary guy in an ordinary town. He's also the unsuspecting star of the world's longest-running reality TV show. Intelligent drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-22 19:00:00" d="2019-08-22 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Signs</n><t>F</t>    <k>When crop circles herald the arrival of alien invaders, ex-preacher Mel Gibson must fight to save his family. Sci-fi suspense with Joaquin Phoenix</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-22 21:00:00" d="2019-08-22 23:00:00" c="1"><n>I, Robot</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% In 2035, robots are built to help humans. But when there's a murder, cop Will Smith is convinced that the machines have gone bad. Sci-fi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-22 23:00:00" d="2019-08-23 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Poltergeist</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% A young suburban family are targeted by sinister supernatural forces in this haunted-house horror from The Texas Chain Saw Massacre director Tobe Hooper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-23 01:00:00" d="2019-08-23 03:20:00" c="1"><n>Rising Sun</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Cops Sean Connery and Wesley Snipes battle to get to the truth when a Japanese call-girl's murder is caught on videotape. Thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1047" o="2019-08-23 03:20:00" d="2019-08-23 05:15:00" c="1"><n>28 Days</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Drama starring Sandra Bullock as a party girl forced to reconsider her lifestyle when she stumbles into rehab. Steve Buscemi co-stars</k>  </p>
</a>
