<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="13" t="2020-04-15 04:36:25"><p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-22 06:30:00" d="2020-04-22 07:00:00"><n>Jacqueline Wilson: Four Kids Kids, It and Me</n>    <k>New. The award-winning author speaks from her home in East Sussex, about her love of E Nesbit and how she created her own adaptation of Five Children and It</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-22 07:00:00" d="2020-04-22 08:45:00" c="1"><n>Battle Of Leningrad</n><t>F</t>    <k>September, 1941. Amid the Battle of Leningrad, two young lovers look to flee, but their evacuation runs into trouble. Russian with subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-22 08:45:00" d="2020-04-22 10:35:00" c="1"><n>Extra Time</n><t>F</t>    <k>A former football star comes out of retirement with an unusual and controversial plan to rescue his local team when they are confronted with the threat of closure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-22 10:35:00" d="2020-04-22 10:50:00"><n>Top Ten: James Bond</n>    <k>Enjoy a host of clips from the Oscar-winning film franchise as Sky Cinema counts down the top 10 moments of all things James Bond</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-22 10:50:00" d="2020-04-22 12:35:00" c="1"><n>Into The Ashes</n><t>F</t>    <k>When his criminal past catches up with him, a reformed man faces the tough choice of whether to stay on his new path or take revenge. Thriller with Frank Grillo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-22 12:35:00" d="2020-04-22 13:05:00"><n>Jacqueline Wilson: Four Kids Kids, It and Me</n>    <k>New. The award-winning author speaks from her home in East Sussex, about her love of E Nesbit and how she created her own adaptation of Five Children and It</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-22 13:05:00" d="2020-04-22 15:05:00" c="1"><n>Tolkien</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Drama set in the early years of iconic author JRR Tolkien's life, as he discovers friendship, love and inspiration among fellow outcasts at school. Nicholas Hoult stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-22 15:05:00" d="2020-04-22 15:20:00"><n>The 2020 Top Ten Show</n>    <k>Which movies are doing the best business at home and across the pond? Clips from the UK and US Top Ten show you the best of what's on offer on the big screen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-22 15:20:00" d="2020-04-22 16:55:00" c="1"><n>The Wave</n><t>F</t>    <k>A lawyer's celebratory night on the town with a colleague takes a bizarre turn when he's dosed with a hallucinogen that completely alters his perception of the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-22 16:55:00" d="2020-04-22 17:10:00"><n>Top Ten: Movie Musicals</n>    <k>Enjoy a countdown of the top 10 movie musical moments as chosen by Alex Zane</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-22 17:10:00" d="2020-04-22 19:00:00" c="1"><n>MA</n><t>F</t>    <k>57% A fun night for a group of teens descends into a hellish nightmare when they befriend a lonely woman. Psychological horror starring Octavia Spencer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-22 19:00:00" d="2020-04-22 21:00:00" c="1"><n>The Operative</n><t>F</t>    <k>When a spy vanishes without a trace, her boss embarks on a panicked hunt to find her before she becomes a threat to their mission. Martin Freeman and Diane Kruger star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-22 21:00:00" d="2020-04-23 00:00:00" c="1"><n>Tolkien</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Drama set in the early years of iconic author JRR Tolkien's life, as he discovers friendship, love and inspiration among fellow outcasts at school. Nicholas Hoult stars</k>  </p>
</a>
