<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="13" t="2020-05-13 04:36:13"><p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-20 05:15:00" d="2020-05-20 07:00:00" c="1"><n>Leo Da Vinci: Mission Mona Lisa</n><t>F</t>    <k>49% A young Leonardo Da Vinci embarks on an epic adventure with his friends after meeting a mysterious storyteller who tells him about hidden treasures. Animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-20 07:00:00" d="2020-05-20 08:45:00" c="1"><n>Adam</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Comedy following the journey of an awkward teenager named Adam, who is thrust into New York's lesbian and trans activist scene when he travels there to visit his sister</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-20 08:45:00" d="2020-05-20 10:30:00" c="1"><n>Curious George: Royal Monkey</n><t>F</t>    <k>Animated adventure in which George trades places with the king's monkey, Philippe. While Philippe's flawless manners impress, George's fun-loving antics raise eyebrows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-20 10:30:00" d="2020-05-20 10:45:00"><n>Free Preview Bad Boys For Life</n>    <k>A free preview of Bad Boys For Life as Will Smith and Martin Lawrence return to uphold the law and stop a criminal gang hellbent on revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-20 10:45:00" d="2020-05-20 13:00:00" c="1"><n>Corpus Christi</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% When a criminal experiences a spiritual transformation after his release from prison, he decides to minister a small-town parish. In Polish with English subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-20 13:00:00" d="2020-05-20 15:15:00" c="1"><n>Alita: Battle Angel</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% A battle cyborg awakens in a post-apocalyptic world with no memory and embarks on a search to find out who she really is. Epic sci-fi adventure co-written by James Cameron</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-20 15:15:00" d="2020-05-20 15:30:00"><n>The 2020 Top Ten Show</n>    <k>Which movies are doing the best business at home and across the pond? Clips from the UK and US Top Ten show you the best of what's on offer on the big screen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-20 15:30:00" d="2020-05-20 17:15:00" c="1"><n>The Bouncer</n><t>F</t>    <k>An imprisoned bodyguard is forced to work with the police and infiltrate a dangerous gang in order to secure his release. Jean-Claude Van Damme stars. English subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-20 17:15:00" d="2020-05-20 18:45:00" c="1"><n>CRSHD</n><t>F</t>    <k>A college student attends an exclusive 'Crush Party' in a last-ditch attempt to lose her virginity before the freshman year ends, but things don't go to plan. Comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-20 18:45:00" d="2020-05-20 19:00:00"><n>Free Preview Little Women</n>    <k>A sneak peek of Greta Gerwig's brand-new adaptation of Louisa May Alcott's classic drama starring Emma Watson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-20 19:00:00" d="2020-05-20 21:00:00" c="1"><n>State Like Sleep</n><t>F</t>    <k>The secrets of a man's double life come to light when his widow receives a mysterious phone call one year after his untimely death. Drama with Katherine Waterston</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-20 21:00:00" d="2020-05-20 23:10:00" c="1"><n>Alita: Battle Angel</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% A battle cyborg awakens in a post-apocalyptic world with no memory and embarks on a search to find out who she really is. Epic sci-fi adventure co-written by James Cameron</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-20 23:10:00" d="2020-05-21 02:10:00" c="1"><n>The Bouncer</n><t>F</t>    <k>An imprisoned bodyguard is forced to work with the police and infiltrate a dangerous gang in order to secure his release. Jean-Claude Van Damme stars. English subtitles</k>  </p>
</a>
