<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="11" t="2020-04-09 04:36:01"><p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-16 06:30:00" d="2020-04-16 07:00:00"><n>Final Score: Special</n>    <k>A special look at the latest Sky Cinema Original Film, an explosive action thriller featuring Guardians of the Galaxy and Avengers star Dave Bautista</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-16 07:00:00" d="2020-04-16 08:35:00" c="1"><n u="Undercover Brother">Undercover Brother 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>Sixteen years on, Undercover Brother's little brother decides to finish the job they began together. Comedy sequel with Michael Jai White</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-16 08:35:00" d="2020-04-16 10:25:00" c="1"><n>Extra Time</n><t>F</t>    <k>A former football star comes out of retirement with an unusual and controversial plan to rescue his local team when they are confronted with the threat of closure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-16 10:25:00" d="2020-04-16 12:40:00" c="1"><n>Spider-Man: Far From Home</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% Tom Holland stars as the web-slinging teenager, whose holiday is cut short when Europe comes under attack. Epic superhero sequel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-16 12:40:00" d="2020-04-16 12:55:00"><n>Free Preview Jumanji: The....</n>    <k>A sneak peek at the next instalment in the Jumanji franchise, starring Dwayne Johnson, Kevin Hart and Jack Black</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-16 12:55:00" d="2020-04-16 14:45:00" c="1"><n>Pokemon Detective Pikachu</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Ryan Reynolds voices the famous Pokémon hero as he puts his sleuthing skills to work to help a 21-year-old find his missing detective father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-16 14:45:00" d="2020-04-16 15:00:00"><n>Top Ten: Movie Musicals</n>    <k>Enjoy a countdown of the top 10 movie musical moments as chosen by Alex Zane</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-16 15:00:00" d="2020-04-16 17:00:00" c="1"><n>Yesterday</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% A struggling singer is the only person who remembers The Beatles after waking up from a freak accident. Comedy from Richard Curtis and Danny Boyle. With Ed Sheeran</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-16 17:00:00" d="2020-04-16 18:45:00" c="1"><n>Into The Ashes</n><t>F</t>    <k>When his criminal past catches up with him, a reformed man faces the tough choice of whether to stay on his new path or take revenge. Thriller with Frank Grillo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-16 18:45:00" d="2020-04-16 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Spider-Man: Far From Home</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% Tom Holland stars as the web-slinging teenager, whose holiday is cut short when Europe comes under attack. Epic superhero sequel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-04-16 21:00:00" d="2020-04-17 00:00:00" c="1"><n>Pokemon Detective Pikachu</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Ryan Reynolds voices the famous Pokémon hero as he puts his sleuthing skills to work to help a 21-year-old find his missing detective father</k>  </p>
</a>
