<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-05-15 04:58:35"><p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-22 05:30:00" d="2020-05-22 07:00:00" c="1"><n>Curious George: Royal Monkey</n><t>F</t>    <k>Animated adventure in which George trades places with the king's monkey, Philippe. While Philippe's flawless manners impress, George's fun-loving antics raise eyebrows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-22 07:00:00" d="2020-05-22 09:00:00" c="1"><n>Corpus Christi</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% When a criminal experiences a spiritual transformation after his release from prison, he decides to minister a small-town parish. In Polish with English subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-22 09:00:00" d="2020-05-22 11:00:00" c="1"><n>State Like Sleep</n><t>F</t>    <k>The secrets of a man's double life come to light when his widow receives a mysterious phone call one year after his untimely death. Drama with Katherine Waterston</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-22 11:00:00" d="2020-05-22 13:00:00" c="1"><n>Killerman</n><t>F</t>    <k>When a money launderer wakes up with millions in stolen cash and drugs, and no memory of how he got it, he sets out to find answers. But a crew of dirty cops are after him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-22 13:00:00" d="2020-05-22 15:20:00" c="1"><n>Fast &amp; Furious Presents: Hobbs...</n><t>F</t>    <k>Spin-off from the iconic franchise. Luke Hobbs (Dwayne Johnson) and Deckard Shaw (Jason Statham) must put their differences aside and team up to stop a huge terror threat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-22 15:20:00" d="2020-05-22 17:30:00" c="1"><n>Alita: Battle Angel</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% A battle cyborg in a post-apocalyptic world with no memory embarks on a search to find out who she really is. Co-written by James Cameron</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-22 17:30:00" d="2020-05-22 19:00:00" c="1"><n>CRSHD</n><t>F</t>    <k>A college student attends an exclusive 'Crush Party' in a last-ditch attempt to lose her virginity before the freshman year ends, but things don't go to plan. Comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-22 19:00:00" d="2020-05-22 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Killerman</n><t>F</t>    <k>When a money launderer wakes up with millions in stolen cash and drugs, and no memory of how he got it, he sets out to find answers. But a crew of dirty cops are after him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-22 21:00:00" d="2020-05-23 00:00:00" c="1"><n>Fast &amp; Furious Presents: Hobbs...</n><t>F</t>    <k>Spin-off from the iconic franchise. Luke Hobbs (Dwayne Johnson) and Deckard Shaw (Jason Statham) must put their differences aside and team up to stop a huge terror threat</k>  </p>
</a>
