<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2020-05-12 04:38:28"><p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-19 05:30:00" d="2020-05-19 07:00:00" c="1"><n>Leo Da Vinci: Mission Mona Lisa</n><t>F</t>    <k>49% A young Leonardo Da Vinci embarks on an epic adventure with his friends after meeting a mysterious storyteller who tells him about hidden treasures. Animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-19 07:00:00" d="2020-05-19 08:45:00" c="1"><n>Curious George: Royal Monkey</n><t>F</t>    <k>Animated adventure in which George trades places with the king's monkey, Philippe. While Philippe's flawless manners impress, George's fun-loving antics raise eyebrows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-19 08:45:00" d="2020-05-19 10:30:00" c="1"><n>Adam</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Comedy following the journey of an awkward teenager named Adam, who is thrust into New York's lesbian and trans activist scene when he travels there to visit his sister</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-19 10:30:00" d="2020-05-19 12:00:00" c="1"><n>Leo Da Vinci: Mission Mona Lisa</n><t>F</t>    <k>49% A young Leonardo Da Vinci embarks on an epic adventure with his friends after meeting a mysterious storyteller who tells him about hidden treasures. Animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-19 12:00:00" d="2020-05-19 14:15:00" c="1"><n>Alita: Battle Angel</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% A battle cyborg awakens in a post-apocalyptic world with no memory and embarks on a search to find out who she really is. Epic sci-fi adventure co-written by James Cameron</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-19 14:15:00" d="2020-05-19 14:30:00"><n>Free Preview Little Women</n>    <k>A sneak peek of Greta Gerwig's brand-new adaptation of Louisa May Alcott's classic drama starring Emma Watson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-19 14:30:00" d="2020-05-19 16:00:00" c="1"><n>The Head Hunter</n><t>F</t>    <k>A medieval warrior who keeps a gory assortment of severed heads sets out to complete his collection by hunting down the monster that killed his daughter. Fantasy horror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-19 16:00:00" d="2020-05-19 17:45:00" c="1"><n>Curious George: Royal Monkey</n><t>F</t>    <k>Animated adventure in which George trades places with the king's monkey, Philippe. While Philippe's flawless manners impress, George's fun-loving antics raise eyebrows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-19 17:45:00" d="2020-05-19 19:30:00" c="1"><n>Brothers In Arms</n><t>F</t>    <k>A by-the-book police officer is driven to take drastic measures when his brother is jailed unfairly. Tense thriller starring Jai Courtney and Leighton Meester</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-19 19:30:00" d="2020-05-19 21:00:00" c="1"><n>CRSHD</n><t>F</t>    <k>A college student attends an exclusive 'Crush Party' in a last-ditch attempt to lose her virginity before the freshman year ends, but things don't go to plan. Comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-19 21:00:00" d="2020-05-19 23:15:00" c="1"><n>Alita: Battle Angel</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% A battle cyborg awakens in a post-apocalyptic world with no memory and embarks on a search to find out who she really is. Epic sci-fi adventure co-written by James Cameron</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1048" o="2020-05-19 23:15:00" d="2020-05-20 02:15:00" c="1"><n>Satanic Panic</n><t>F</t>    <k>Chaos ensues for a pizza delivery girl when she realises her last customers of the night are a group of satanists. Horror-comedy with Rebecca Romijn</k>  </p>
</a>
