<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-08-13 02:26:37"><p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-18 06:15:00" d="2019-08-18 08:25:00" c="1"><n>Sabrina</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% Romantic drama about a woman who captures the heart of a handsome, wealthy man whom she secretly loved as a girl. Starring Julia Ormond and Harrison Ford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-18 08:25:00" d="2019-08-18 10:30:00" c="1"><n>Antwone Fisher</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% Denzel Washington directs and stars in this moving true-life drama about a US Navy psychiatrist who helps a troubled young recruit with a short fuse. With Derek Luke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-18 10:30:00" d="2019-08-18 10:50:00"><n>The 2019 Top Ten Show</n>    <k>Which movies are doing the best business at home and across the pond? Clips from the UK and US Top Ten show you the best of what's on offer on the big screen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-18 10:50:00" d="2019-08-18 13:15:00" c="1"><n>Mary Poppins</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% Timeless musical starring Julie Andrews as the nanny who uses her magic touch to bring a troubled family together. Supercalifragilistic fun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-18 13:15:00" d="2019-08-18 15:15:00" c="1"><n>The Leisure Seeker</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Warm comedy-drama starring Donald Sutherland and Helen Mirren as a long-married couple who embark on a golden-years road trip in their family's old camper-van</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-18 15:15:00" d="2019-08-18 17:00:00" c="1"><n>Euphoria</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% Alicia Vikander and Eva Green star as two estranged sisters who reunite for a tense trip to the Swiss mountains, where a dark secret is revealed. Distressing themes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-18 17:00:00" d="2019-08-18 19:00:00" c="1"><n>8 Mile</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Eminem plays an aspiring rapper who must battle poverty, prejudice and his own insecurities to become a respected MC. Hip-hop drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-18 19:00:00" d="2019-08-18 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Professor Marston And The Wonder Women</n><t>F</t>    <k>The story of psychology professor William Moulton Marston and the three-way romance that inspired the creation of DC's Wonder Woman. Luke Evans stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-18 21:00:00" d="2019-08-18 23:15:00" c="1"><n>Call Me By Your Name</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% Oscar-winning drama charting the summer romance between precocious teen Timothee Chalamet and grad student Armie Hammer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-18 23:15:00" d="2019-08-19 01:10:00" c="1"><n>Serenity</n><t>F</t>    <k>53% Steamy thriller starring Matthew McConaughey as a fishing boat captain whose tranquil life is shattered by the arrival of ex-wife Anne Hathaway. Sky Cinema Original Film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-19 01:10:00" d="2019-08-19 03:40:00" c="1"><n>The Doors</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Val Kilmer triumphs as Lizard King Jim Morrison in director Oliver Stone's freewheeling adaptation of the magnetic music legend's life. With Meg Ryan and Kyle MacLachlan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-19 03:40:00" d="2019-08-19 05:20:00" c="1"><n>An Ordinary Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>A Bosnian Serb army general accused of war crimes and forced to go into hiding develops a relationship with his young maid. Thoughtful drama starring Ben Kingsley</k>  </p>
</a>
