<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-05-16 04:56:47"><p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-23 05:30:00" d="2020-05-23 07:00:00" c="1"><n>Memories Of Christmas</n><t>F</t>    <k>Christina Milian and Mark Taylor star in this charming Christmas film about a woman whose late mother's Christmas decorating secret leads her to unexpected love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-23 07:00:00" d="2020-05-23 09:05:00" c="1"><n>Sabrina</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Audrey Hepburn falls for handsome, wealthy William Holden, to the consternation of his elder brother Humphrey Bogart. Could he want her for himself? Classic romance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-23 09:05:00" d="2020-05-23 11:25:00" c="1"><n>Bohemian Rhapsody</n><t>F</t>    <k>80% Smash hit biopic following the highs and lows of the legendary rock band Queen, and their late famed frontman Freddie Mercury, played by Academy Award-winner Rami Malek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-23 11:25:00" d="2020-05-23 13:15:00" c="1"><n>The Nutcracker And The Four Realms</n><t>F</t>    <k>56% Disney twist on a classic tale, as heroine Clara (Mackenzie Foy) discovers a magical land beset by conflict. Fantasy with Keira Knightley and Helen Mirren</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-23 13:15:00" d="2020-05-23 16:00:00" c="1"><n>The Firm</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Young lawyer Tom Cruise becomes embroiled in his new firm's shady dealings. Sydney Pollack directs this gripping drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-23 16:00:00" d="2020-05-23 18:30:00" c="1"><n>First Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% Damien Chazelle's biographical drama stars Ryan Gosling as American astronaut Neil Armstrong in the years leading up to the Apollo 11 mission to the moon. With Claire Foy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-23 18:30:00" d="2020-05-23 21:00:00" c="1"><n>The Shawshank Redemption</n><t>F</t>    <k>93% A man is thrown into the brutality of prison life when he gets two life sentences for a crime he claims he didn't commit. Drama starring Tim Robbins and Morgan Freeman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-23 21:00:00" d="2020-05-23 23:15:00" c="1"><n>Bohemian Rhapsody</n><t>F</t>    <k>80% Smash hit biopic following the highs and lows of the legendary rock band Queen, and their late famed frontman Freddie Mercury, played by Academy Award-winner Rami Malek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-23 23:15:00" d="2020-05-24 02:15:00" c="1"><n>Mapplethorpe</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% Matt Smith plays the controversial photographer Robert Mapplethorpe in a compelling biopic tracing his life from his rise to fame to his death. Contains graphic nudity</k>  </p>
</a>
