<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-04-10 04:37:03"><p id_tv="1049" o="2020-04-17 05:00:00" d="2020-04-17 07:00:00" c="1"><n>Kramer Vs Kramer</n><t>F</t>    <k>Dustin Hoffman and Meryl Streep won Oscars for their roles in this landmark drama about two parents fighting for custody of their son. Poignant Best Picture winner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-04-17 07:00:00" d="2020-04-17 08:50:00" c="1"><n>Puzzle</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Drama with Kelly Macdonald as Agnes, a stay-at-home mother whose talent for solving puzzles leads her to New York and a new life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-04-17 08:50:00" d="2020-04-17 10:50:00" c="1"><n>The Music Of Silence</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% Inspiring musical biopic detailing the life of blind opera star Andrea Bocelli who against all odds rose to become a huge international success. Antonio Banderas stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-04-17 10:50:00" d="2020-04-17 13:00:00" c="1"><n>Robert The Bruce</n><t>F</t>    <k>Angus Macfadyen plays 14th-century King of Scots Robert the Bruce in the drama following the Scottish legend as he rebuilds his life after a series of military defeats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-04-17 13:00:00" d="2020-04-17 15:10:00" c="1"><n>Philadelphia</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% An Oscar-winning Tom Hanks stars as a gay lawyer fighting against wrongful dismissal with the help of attorney Denzel Washington</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-04-17 15:10:00" d="2020-04-17 16:50:00" c="1"><n>Changeland</n><t>F</t>    <k>Following a devastating personal crisis, a man jets off on a Thailand adventure with a childhood friend in a bid to cure his blues. Comedy-drama with Macaulay Culkin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-04-17 16:50:00" d="2020-04-17 18:50:00" c="1"><n>Boy Erased</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% A Baptist pastor's son is sent to conversion therapy when he's outed as gay to his parents. Powerful biographical drama with Russell Crowe and Nicole Kidman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-04-17 18:50:00" d="2020-04-17 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Robert The Bruce</n><t>F</t>    <k>Angus Macfadyen plays 14th-century King of Scots Robert the Bruce in the drama following the Scottish legend as he rebuilds his life after a series of military defeats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-04-17 21:00:00" d="2020-04-18 00:00:00" c="1"><n>Philadelphia</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% An Oscar-winning Tom Hanks stars as a gay lawyer fighting against wrongful dismissal with the help of attorney Denzel Washington</k>  </p>
</a>
