<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2019-08-11 01:39:33"><p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-17 05:00:00" d="2019-08-17 07:05:00" c="1"><n>White Christmas</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Bing Crosby and Danny Kaye star as the song and dance duo out to save a snowless ski resort. Show-stopping musical with a terrific soundtrack from Irving Berlin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-17 07:05:00" d="2019-08-17 09:20:00" c="1"><n>Carousel</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Troubled soul Billy Bigelow (Gordon MacRae) is given the chance to leave heaven for one day to help his family back on Earth. Glorious Rodgers and Hammerstein musical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-17 09:20:00" d="2019-08-17 11:35:00" c="1"><n>The Evening Star</n><t>F</t>    <k>59% The emotional sequel to Terms of Endearment, in which Aurora Greenway (Shirley MacLaine) must raise her late daughter's three children. With Jack Nicholson and Marion Ross</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-17 11:35:00" d="2019-08-17 14:05:00" c="1"><n>First Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Damien Chazelle's biographical drama stars Ryan Gosling as American astronaut Neil Armstrong in the years leading up to the Apollo 11 mission to the moon. With Claire Foy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-17 14:05:00" d="2019-08-17 17:25:00" c="1"><n>Titanic</n><t>F</t>    <k>Leonardo DiCaprio and Kate Winslet are the lovers aboard the doomed ocean liner in James Cameron's Oscar-winning romantic blockbuster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-17 17:25:00" d="2019-08-17 19:05:00" c="1"><n>The Boy Downstairs</n><t>F</t>    <k>57% Rom-com with Girls star Zosia Mamet as a struggling writer who moves into a new apartment, unaware that her ex lives downstairs. Matthew Shear (Mistress America) co-stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-17 19:05:00" d="2019-08-17 21:00:00" c="1"><n>The Senator</n><t>F</t>    <k>Senator Ted Kennedy (Jason Clarke) struggles to save his political career and maintain his family's legacy after a tragic accident. Historical drama with Kate Mara</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-17 21:00:00" d="2019-08-18 00:00:00" c="1"><n>First Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Damien Chazelle's biographical drama stars Ryan Gosling as American astronaut Neil Armstrong in the years leading up to the Apollo 11 mission to the moon. With Claire Foy</k>  </p>
</a>
