<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-05-15 04:58:19"><p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-22 05:10:00" d="2020-05-22 07:00:00" c="1"><n>Kramer Vs Kramer</n><t>F</t>    <k>Dustin Hoffman and Meryl Streep won Oscars for their roles in this landmark drama about two parents fighting for custody of their son. Poignant Best Picture winner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-22 07:00:00" d="2020-05-22 08:55:00" c="1"><n>What They Had</n><t>F</t>    <k>Tensions boil over when a woman suffering from Alzheimer's wanders into a blizzard and her family must decide how to help her. Drama starring Oscar winner Hilary Swank</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-22 08:55:00" d="2020-05-22 10:55:00" c="1"><n>Save The Last Dance</n><t>F</t>    <k>Promising ballerina Julia Stiles moves to a tough high school where she and hip-hopping Sean Patrick Thomas click on and off the dance floor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-22 10:55:00" d="2020-05-22 12:50:00" c="1"><n>Say Anything...</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Classic teen romance from Jerry Maguire director Cameron Crowe. A beautiful and brilliant high school student finds herself pursued by charming underachiever John Cusack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-22 12:50:00" d="2020-05-22 15:05:00" c="1"><n>The Bodyguard</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Megastar singer Whitney Houston hires bodyguard Kevin Costner to protect her from a stalker. Oscar-nominated romantic drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-22 15:05:00" d="2020-05-22 17:00:00" c="1"><n>Bel Canto</n><t>F</t>    <k>54% Oscar winner Julianne Moore stars as a famous singer who finds herself embroiled in a hostage situation when she travels to South America to perform for a wealthy man</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-22 17:00:00" d="2020-05-22 18:55:00" c="1"><n>What They Had</n><t>F</t>    <k>Tensions boil over when a woman suffering from Alzheimer's wanders into a blizzard and her family must decide how to help her. Drama starring Oscar winner Hilary Swank</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-22 18:55:00" d="2020-05-22 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Good Morning Vietnam</n><t>F</t>    <k>As the Vietnam War rages, hell-raising radio DJ Robin Williams brings his unique brand of entertainment to the troops. Comedy-drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-22 21:00:00" d="2020-05-22 23:10:00" c="1"><n>The Bodyguard</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Megastar singer Whitney Houston hires bodyguard Kevin Costner to protect her from a stalker. Oscar-nominated romantic drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-22 23:10:00" d="2020-05-23 02:10:00" c="1"><n>The Wolf Of Wall Street</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% Leonardo DiCaprio depicts the excessive life of a shady stockbroker in Martin Scorsese's crime comedy</k>  </p>
</a>
