<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-05-26 04:34:31"><p id_tv="1049" o="2020-06-02 05:00:00" d="2020-06-02 07:20:00" c="1"><n>Always</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% Firefighting pilot Richard Dreyfuss dies but returns to watch over Holly Hunter. Steven Spielberg's fantasy romance features Audrey Hepburn's last role</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-06-02 07:20:00" d="2020-06-02 08:55:00" c="1"><n>Age Of Summer</n><t>F</t>    <k>After relocating with his family, a teenage boy navigates challenges and new relationships as he tries to fit in with the cool kids in the summer of '86. Charming drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-06-02 08:55:00" d="2020-06-02 10:45:00" c="1"><n>Becks</n><t>F</t>    <k>A heartbroken singer discovers her musical voice through a new friendship when she moves home after a breakup. Lena Hall and American Beauty's Mena Suvari star. LGBT Drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-06-02 10:45:00" d="2020-06-02 12:30:00" c="1"><n>3 Generations</n><t>F</t>    <k>When a teen begins his transition from female to male, family secrets are revealed as everyone tries to come to terms with the decision. With Naomi Watts and Susan Sarandon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-06-02 12:30:00" d="2020-06-02 15:05:00" c="1"><n>The Shawshank Redemption</n><t>F</t>    <k>93% A man is thrown into the brutality of prison life when he gets two life sentences for a crime he claims he didn't commit. Drama starring Tim Robbins and Morgan Freeman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-06-02 15:05:00" d="2020-06-02 17:10:00" c="1"><n>Hands Of Stone</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Boxing biopic charting the life and career of former world champion Roberto Duran, and the lead-up to his history-making fight with Sugar Ray Leonard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-06-02 17:10:00" d="2020-06-02 19:10:00" c="1"><n>Breakthrough</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% When her adopted son falls through the ice on a frozen lake, Joyce refuses to give up as she stays by his bedside and prays for a miracle. Based on an true story</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-06-02 19:10:00" d="2020-06-02 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Euphoria</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% Alicia Vikander and Eva Green star as two estranged sisters who reunite for a tense trip to the Swiss mountains, where a dark secret is revealed. Distressing themes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-06-02 21:00:00" d="2020-06-02 23:25:00" c="1"><n>The Shawshank Redemption</n><t>F</t>    <k>93% A man is thrown into the brutality of prison life when he gets two life sentences for a crime he claims he didn't commit. Drama starring Tim Robbins and Morgan Freeman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-06-02 23:25:00" d="2020-06-03 02:25:00" c="1"><n>The People Vs. Larry Flynt</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% Woody Harrelson stars as the pornographer who outraged America and pushed the law to the limit. Oscar-nominated drama with Courtney Love</k>  </p>
</a>
