<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-05-12 04:38:19"><p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-19 07:00:00" d="2020-05-19 09:05:00" c="1"><n>The Sisters Brothers</n><t>F</t>    <k>Dark western starring Jake Gyllenhaal and Riz Ahmed as two men who embark on a powerful journey while on the run from assassin brothers John C Reilly and Joaquin Phoenix</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-19 09:05:00" d="2020-05-19 11:05:00" c="1"><n>Escape From Sobibor</n><t>F</t>    <k>Thought-provoking war drama following Soviet prisoner Alexander Pechersky as he organises a rebellion and escape from a Nazi death camp in Poland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-19 11:05:00" d="2020-05-19 12:50:00" c="1"><n>Genius</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Colin Firth stars as world-renowned book editor Maxwell Perkins, who strikes up a complex friendship with author Thomas Wolfe. With Jude Law and Nicole Kidman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-19 12:50:00" d="2020-05-19 14:55:00" c="1"><n>Hotel Mumbai</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% The true story of the Taj Hotel terror attacks, and the heroic hotel staff. With Dev Patel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-19 14:55:00" d="2020-05-19 16:55:00" c="1"><n>The Music Of Silence</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% Inspiring musical biopic detailing the life of blind opera star Andrea Bocelli who against all odds rose to become a huge international success. Antonio Banderas stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-19 16:55:00" d="2020-05-19 18:55:00" c="1"><n>Life Itself</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% A multi-generational tale of life, loss and love starring Oscar Isaac and Olivia Wilde. Sky Cinema Original Film from the creator of This Is Us</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-19 18:55:00" d="2020-05-19 21:00:00" c="1"><n>The Sisters Brothers</n><t>F</t>    <k>Dark western starring Jake Gyllenhaal and Riz Ahmed as two men who embark on a powerful journey while on the run from assassin brothers John C Reilly and Joaquin Phoenix</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-19 21:00:00" d="2020-05-19 23:05:00" c="1"><n>Hotel Mumbai</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% The true story of the Taj Hotel terror attacks, and the heroic hotel staff. With Dev Patel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2020-05-19 23:05:00" d="2020-05-20 02:05:00" c="1"><n>Blue My Mind</n><t>F</t>    <k>Seemingly normal teenager Mia begins to face an overwhelming bodily transformation that calls her existence into question. In German with subtitles</k>  </p>
</a>
