<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="11" t="2019-08-10 01:39:29"><p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-16 05:00:00" d="2019-08-16 08:00:00" c="1"><n>The Bible</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% Epic Hollywood retelling of Genesis, from Adam to Abraham. John Huston directs and stars as Noah, with Richard Harris, Ava Gardner and Peter O'Toole co-starring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-16 08:00:00" d="2019-08-16 10:00:00" c="1"><n>The Music Of Silence</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% Inspiring musical biopic detailing the life of blind opera star Andrea Bocelli who against all odds rose to become a huge international success. Antonio Banderas stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-16 10:00:00" d="2019-08-16 12:15:00" c="1"><n>Philadelphia</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% An Oscar-winning Tom Hanks stars as a gay lawyer fighting against wrongful dismissal with the help of attorney Denzel Washington</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-16 12:15:00" d="2019-08-16 14:25:00" c="1"><n>Notorious</n><t>F</t>    <k>Candid biopic about rapper Biggie Smalls, from his days as a drug dealer to the bitter rivalries that led to his murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-16 14:25:00" d="2019-08-16 16:20:00" c="1"><n>Cocktail</n><t>F</t>    <k>59% Tom Cruise stars as an ambitious barman who falls for a wealthy beauty, but risks everything to win a bet. Romantic drama with Elisabeth Shue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-16 16:20:00" d="2019-08-16 18:10:00" c="1"><n>28 Days</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Drama starring Sandra Bullock as a party girl forced to reconsider her lifestyle when she stumbles into rehab. Steve Buscemi co-stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-16 18:10:00" d="2019-08-16 21:00:00" c="1"><n>The Curious Case Of Benjamin Button</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% Brad Pitt is the boy who ages backwards in this sumptuous epic of life, death and love from director David Fincher. Cate Blanchett co-stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-16 21:00:00" d="2019-08-16 23:00:00" c="1"><n>The Mountain Between Us</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Stranded on a mountain after a plane crash, strangers Kate Winslet and Idris Elba face a perilous journey through hundreds of miles of frozen wilderness. Tense two-hander</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-16 23:00:00" d="2019-08-17 00:50:00" c="1"><n>Fifty Shades Freed</n><t>F</t>    <k>46% Strap in for the final chapter of the steamy trilogy, as Jamie Dornan and Dakota Johnson return as kinky business mogul Christian Grey and paramour Ana</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-17 00:50:00" d="2019-08-17 03:20:00" c="1"><n>The Hurricane</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% Powerful drama with Denzel Washington as Rubin 'Hurricane' Carter, a boxer wrongfully imprisoned who fights to prove his innocence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-17 03:20:00" d="2019-08-17 05:00:00" c="1"><n>Lucky</n><t>F</t>    <k>The late Harry Dean Stanton stars as Lucky, a 90-year-old atheist who embarks on a spiritual journey in a bid to find enlightenment as he faces his own mortality</k>  </p>
</a>
