<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-07-11 00:20:59"><p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-17 05:00:00" d="2019-07-17 07:10:00" c="1"><n>Sabrina</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% Romantic drama about a woman who captures the heart of a handsome, wealthy man whom she secretly loved as a girl. Starring Julia Ormond and Harrison Ford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-17 07:10:00" d="2019-07-17 08:55:00" c="1"><n>The Bachelors</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Widowed teacher JK Simmons and teenage son Josh Wiggins pack up and head to LA in search of a fresh start. Moving comedy-drama with Julie Delpy and Lady Bird's Odeya Rush</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-17 08:55:00" d="2019-07-17 10:50:00" c="1"><n>8 Mile</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Eminem plays an aspiring rapper who must battle poverty, prejudice and his own insecurities to become a respected MC. Hip-hop drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-17 10:50:00" d="2019-07-17 13:10:00" c="1"><n>A Star Is Born</n><t>F</t>    <k>87% A complex love story unfolds when a musician battling his inner demons helps a struggling singer find fame. Starring Bradley Cooper and Lady Gaga</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-17 13:10:00" d="2019-07-17 15:10:00" c="1"><n>Marshall</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% Thurgood Marshall, the first African-American justice in the US Supreme Court, takes on a case that may define his career. Biopic with Black Panther's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-17 15:10:00" d="2019-07-17 17:00:00" c="1"><n>The Escape</n><t>F</t>    <k>Overworked and emotionally numb, housewife and mother Gemma Arterton makes a drastic decision in an effort to reclaim her life. British drama with Dominic Cooper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-17 17:00:00" d="2019-07-17 19:00:00" c="1"><n>Crazy Heart</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% An Oscar-winning Jeff Bridges stars as an alcoholic country singer getting one last shot at the big time. Maggie Gyllenhaal and Colin Farrell co-star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-17 19:00:00" d="2019-07-17 21:00:00" c="1"><n>The Mountain Between Us</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Stranded on a mountain after a plane crash, strangers Kate Winslet and Idris Elba face a perilous journey through hundreds of miles of frozen wilderness. Tense two-hander</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-17 21:00:00" d="2019-07-17 23:20:00" c="1"><n>Phantom Thread</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% Daniel Day-Lewis stars as a celebrated British dressmaker who falls in love with shy but strong-willed waitress Vicky Krieps. Oscar-winning drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-17 23:20:00" d="2019-07-18 01:45:00" c="1"><n>A Star Is Born</n><t>F</t>    <k>87% A complex love story unfolds when a musician battling his inner demons helps a struggling singer find fame. Starring Bradley Cooper and Lady Gaga</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-18 01:45:00" d="2019-07-18 04:05:00" c="1"><n>All The Money In The World</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Ageing oil tycoon J Paul Getty refuses to play ball when his teenage grandson is kidnapped and held for ransom. Crime thriller with Christopher Plummer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-18 04:05:00" d="2019-07-18 05:45:00" c="1"><n>Freak Show</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Feel-good comedy-drama starring Alex Lawther as a flamboyant, out-and-proud teen challenging the status quo at an ultra-conservative high school. With Abigail Breslin</k>  </p>
</a>
