<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="14" t="2019-07-11 00:20:59"><p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-15 05:15:00" d="2019-07-15 07:25:00" c="1"><n>Taps</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Army cadets Tom Cruise and Sean Penn go to extreme lengths to protect their academy when it is threatened by local developers. Gripping drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-15 07:25:00" d="2019-07-15 09:10:00" c="1"><n>The Butterfly Tree</n><t>F</t>    <k>Father and son Al and Fin find themselves entranced by a mysterious florist as they attempt to deal with the death of Fin's mother. Drama with Wildlife's Ed Oxenbould</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-15 09:10:00" d="2019-07-15 10:50:00" c="1"><n>All The Right Moves</n><t>F</t>    <k>59% Young football player Tom Cruise hopes a college scholarship will help him escape small-town life, but clashes with his coach threaten to derail his dreams. Sports drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-15 10:50:00" d="2019-07-15 13:20:00" c="1"><n>Babel</n><t>F</t>    <k>83% The accidental shooting of tourist Cate Blanchett in Morocco has a world-wide ripple effect. Drama with Brad Pitt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-15 13:20:00" d="2019-07-15 15:30:00" c="1"><n>Tristan + Isolde</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% A chance meeting between English knight James Franco and Irish princess Sophia Myles leads to a passionate yet perilous affair. With Rufus Sewell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-15 15:30:00" d="2019-07-15 17:25:00" c="1"><n>I Can Only Imagine</n><t>F</t>    <k>The inspiring story of singer Bart Millard, who escaped an abusive childhood and went on to write the biggest selling Christian pop song of all time. With Dennis Quaid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-15 17:25:00" d="2019-07-15 17:40:00"><n>The 2019 Top Ten Show</n>    <k>Which movies are doing the best business at home and across the pond? Clips from the UK and US Top Ten show you the best of what's on offer on the big screen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-15 17:40:00" d="2019-07-15 19:20:00" c="1"><n>Anything</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% After attempting to take his own life, small-town widower John Carroll Lynch moves to Los Angeles where he begins to bond with his eccentric Hollywood neighbours. Drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-15 19:20:00" d="2019-07-15 21:00:00" c="1"><n>The 15:17 To Paris</n><t>F</t>    <k>53% True-life drama focusing on the lives of three US backpackers who thwarted a terrorist attack on a high-speed train. Clint Eastwood directs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-15 21:00:00" d="2019-07-15 22:45:00" c="1"><n>Say Anything...</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% Classic teen romance from Jerry Maguire director Cameron Crowe. A beautiful and brilliant high school student finds herself pursued by charming underachiever John Cusack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-15 22:45:00" d="2019-07-16 00:45:00" c="1"><n>The Leisure Seeker</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Warm comedy-drama starring Donald Sutherland and Helen Mirren as a long-married couple who embark on a golden-years road trip in their family's old camper-van</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-16 00:45:00" d="2019-07-16 02:40:00" c="1"><n>My Cousin Rachel</n><t>F</t>    <k>60% Young heir Sam Claflin vows revenge against his late cousin's wife, but soon finds himself falling under her spell. Dark romance with Rachel Weisz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-16 02:40:00" d="2019-07-16 04:50:00" c="1"><n>An Officer And A Gentleman</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Classic romantic drama starring Richard Gere as a troubled trainee naval officer who falls for Debra Winger's sassy factory girl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-16 04:50:00" d="2019-07-16 06:45:00" c="1"><n>To Sir With Love</n><t>F</t>    <k>New teacher Sidney Poitier tries to inspire the students of a rough east London school using his own unorthodox methods. Touching drama co-starring Lulu</k>  </p>
</a>
