<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="11" t="2019-08-13 02:26:40"><p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-19 05:20:00" d="2019-08-19 07:25:00" c="1"><n>Steel Magnolias</n><t>F</t>    <k>Julia Roberts and a stellar cast of southern belles ride out emotional storms with tears, laughter and good manicures. Comedy drama with Sally Field and Shirley MacLaine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-19 07:25:00" d="2019-08-19 09:40:00" c="1"><n>The Prince Of Tides</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Barbra Streisand directs and stars as a psychiatrist drawn to the troubled brother of one of her patients. Oscar-nominated romantic drama co-starring Nick Nolte</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-19 09:40:00" d="2019-08-19 12:10:00" c="1"><n>Hello, Dolly!</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% In her second film, Barbra Streisand is the matchmaker determined to woo millionaire grouch Walter Matthau. Oscar-winning musical with Michael Crawford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-19 12:10:00" d="2019-08-19 14:20:00" c="1"><n>Roman J. Israel, Esq</n><t>F</t>    <k>An Oscar-nominated Denzel Washington stars as a brilliant but reclusive LA civil rights lawyer whose moral compass takes a hit. With Colin Farrell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-19 14:20:00" d="2019-08-19 16:55:00" c="1"><n>South Pacific</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Spectacular big-screen version of the classic Rodgers and Hammerstein musical set on a South Pacific Island during World War Two. Starring Mitzi Gaynor and Rossano Brazzi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-19 16:55:00" d="2019-08-19 18:55:00" c="1"><n>Hope Floats</n><t>F</t>    <k>60% Former beauty queen Sandra Bullock returns to her sleepy Texan hometown after she is humiliated and dumped on a talk show. Romance with Harry Connick Jr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-19 18:55:00" d="2019-08-19 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Mary Magdalene</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% Biblical drama with Rooney Mara as Mary Magdalene, a young woman who leaves her small fishing village to follow Jesus of Nazareth (Joaquin Phoenix). Garth Davis directs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-19 21:00:00" d="2019-08-19 23:05:00" c="1"><n>Battle Of The Sexes</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Charming comedy-drama about the famed match between women's tennis star Billie Jean King (Emma Stone) and former male champ Bobby Riggs (Steve Carell)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-19 23:05:00" d="2019-08-20 01:45:00" c="1"><n>Amistad</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% A shipload of slaves take on the US legal system in a battle to win their freedom. Powerful Spielberg drama with Morgan Freeman, Matthew McConaughey and Anthony Hopkins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-20 01:45:00" d="2019-08-20 03:30:00" c="1"><n>Ingrid Goes West</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% It's Single White Female for the smartphone era as troubled Aubrey Plaza latches onto LA influencer Elizabeth Olsen. and won't let go. Dark comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-20 03:30:00" d="2019-08-20 05:35:00" c="1"><n>Frost/Nixon</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% TV presenter David Frost (Michael Sheen) tries to prise a confession out of disgraced ex-president Richard Nixon (Frank Langella). Drama</k>  </p>
</a>
