<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="13" t="2019-08-15 22:51:43"><p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-22 05:15:00" d="2019-08-22 07:05:00" c="1"><n>Field Of Dreams</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% Moving fantasy starring Kevin Costner as a Iowa farmer who, in answer to a mystical voice, turns his cornfield into a baseball pitch, with miraculous results</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-22 07:05:00" d="2019-08-22 08:45:00" c="1"><n>Freak Show</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Feel-good comedy-drama starring Alex Lawther as a flamboyant, out-and-proud teen challenging the status quo at an ultra-conservative high school. With Abigail Breslin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-22 08:45:00" d="2019-08-22 10:30:00" c="1"><n>Say Anything...</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% Classic teen romance from Jerry Maguire director Cameron Crowe. A beautiful and brilliant high school student finds herself pursued by charming underachiever John Cusack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-22 10:30:00" d="2019-08-22 12:40:00" c="1"><n>An Officer And A Gentleman</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Classic romantic drama starring Richard Gere as a troubled trainee naval officer who falls for Debra Winger's sassy factory girl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-22 12:40:00" d="2019-08-22 14:40:00" c="1"><n>Love, Simon</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% Coming-of-age comedy starring Nick Robinson (Everything, Everything) as a closeted high-schooler who begins to fall for an anonymous classmate online. But who is he?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-22 14:40:00" d="2019-08-22 16:30:00" c="1"><n>The Tribes Of Palos Verdes</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% After her family moves to the picturesque Palos Verdes, teen outcast Maika Monroe battles to prove herself among the surfers on the California shore. With Jennifer Garner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-22 16:30:00" d="2019-08-22 19:10:00" c="1"><n>The Insider</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% Russell Crowe is the tobacco industry exec turned whistleblower, Al Pacino the newsman who persuades him to talk. Hard-hitting, heavyweight drama directed by Michael Mann</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-22 19:10:00" d="2019-08-22 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Wonder Wheel</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Woody Allen's 1950s-set drama stars Kate Winslet as a former actress whose life is upturned by the appearance of her husband's estranged daughter. With Juno Temple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-22 21:00:00" d="2019-08-22 23:00:00" c="1"><n>Love, Simon</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% Coming-of-age comedy starring Nick Robinson (Everything, Everything) as a closeted high-schooler who begins to fall for an anonymous classmate online. But who is he?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-22 23:00:00" d="2019-08-23 00:50:00" c="1"><n>Cocktail</n><t>F</t>    <k>59% Tom Cruise stars as an ambitious barman who falls for a wealthy beauty, but risks everything to win a bet. Romantic drama with Elisabeth Shue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-23 00:50:00" d="2019-08-23 02:55:00" c="1"><n>American Beauty</n><t>F</t>    <k>84% Stifled suburbanite Kevin Spacey impulsively overhauls his life, creating friction with wife Annette Bening. Oscar-winning drama from Sam Mendes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-23 02:55:00" d="2019-08-23 04:50:00" c="1"><n>My Friend Dahmer</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Chilling biopic exploring the troubled high-school years of notorious cannibalistic serial killer Jeffrey Dahmer. With Anne Heche and Hereditary star Alex Wolff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-23 04:50:00" d="2019-08-23 07:10:00" c="1"><n>It's A Wonderful Life</n><t>F</t>    <k>86% Businessman James Stewart is on the brink of suicide when an angel gives him a glimpse of what the world would've been like without him. Much-loved drama from Frank Capra</k>  </p>
</a>
