<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-07-11 00:20:59"><p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-16 06:45:00" d="2019-07-16 07:00:00"><n>The 2019 Top Ten Show</n>    <k>Which movies are doing the best business at home and across the pond? Clips from the UK and US Top Ten show you the best of what's on offer on the big screen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-16 07:00:00" d="2019-07-16 09:05:00" c="1"><n>The Forgiven</n><t>F</t>    <k>Roland Joffe's drama stars Forest Whitaker as Archbishop Desmond Tutu, summoned to a maximum-security prison by a notorious murderer seeking clemency. With Eric Bana</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-16 09:05:00" d="2019-07-16 11:10:00" c="1"><n>Antwone Fisher</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% Denzel Washington directs and stars in this moving true-life drama about a US Navy psychiatrist who helps a troubled young recruit with a short fuse. With Derek Luke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-16 11:10:00" d="2019-07-16 13:05:00" c="1"><n>Goodbye Christopher Robin</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% British drama charting the fraught relationship between Winnie-the-Pooh creator AA Milne and the son who inspired his writing. Domhnall Gleeson stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-16 13:05:00" d="2019-07-16 15:25:00" c="1"><n>Wall Street: Money Never Sleeps</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% Shia LaBeouf is a young trader embroiled in the dodgy dealings of Michael Douglas's Gordon Gekko in this slick sequel to the 80s' classic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-16 15:25:00" d="2019-07-16 17:10:00" c="1"><n>The Browning Version</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% Literary drama with the late Albert Finney excellent as the disliked classics teacher pushed into retirement by headmaster Michael Gambon. Directed by Mike Figgis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-16 17:10:00" d="2019-07-16 19:10:00" c="1"><n>Footloose</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% Kenny Wormald and Julianne Hough bring dance back to the masses, much to the horror of preacher dad Dennis Quaid. Fun reboot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-16 19:10:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00" c="1"><n>The Disaster Artist</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Behind-the-scenes farce charting the chaotic production of cult film The Room, starring a Golden Globe-winning James Franco as Tommy Wiseau</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 23:00:00" c="1"><n>Genius</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Colin Firth stars as world-renowned book editor Maxwell Perkins, who strikes up a complex friendship with author Thomas Wolfe. With Jude Law and Nicole Kidman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-16 23:00:00" d="2019-07-17 00:50:00" c="1"><n>The Senator</n><t>F</t>    <k>Senator Ted Kennedy (Jason Clarke) struggles to save his political career and maintain his family's legacy after a tragic accident. Historical drama with Kate Mara</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-17 00:50:00" d="2019-07-17 02:55:00" c="1"><n>Boys Don't Cry</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% Moving to a new town, an Oscar-winning Hilary Swank hides a secret that could rip her life apart. True-life drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-07-17 02:55:00" d="2019-07-17 05:00:00" c="1"><n>Pirates Of Somalia</n><t>F</t>    <k>A rookie journalist finds himself in way over his head as he searches for a career-defining story in Somalia. True-life drama with Al Pacino and X-Men star Evan Peters</k>  </p>
</a>
