<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-08-15 22:51:40"><p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-21 05:35:00" d="2019-08-21 07:25:00" c="1"><n>Casablanca</n><t>F</t>    <k>85% Oscar-winning wartime romance starring Humphrey Bogart as an ex-pat bar owner torn between love and virtue. Ingrid Bergman co-stars as his former flame</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-21 07:25:00" d="2019-08-21 09:10:00" c="1"><n>So B. It</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Coming-of-age drama starring Talitha Bateman (Love, Simon) as a spirited youngster who embarks on a cross-country trip to unravel the truth about her family history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-21 09:10:00" d="2019-08-21 11:00:00" c="1"><n>Honey: Rise Up And Dance</n><t>F</t>    <k>Against the wishes of her mum, aspiring street dancer Skyler enters Atlanta's underground dance scene in order to hone her moves for a life-changing scholarship. Drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-21 11:00:00" d="2019-08-21 12:50:00" c="1"><n>Blame</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% Modern take on The Crucible starring Chris Messina as a substitute drama teacher whose taboo relationship with an unstable student strikes a nerve</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-21 12:50:00" d="2019-08-21 15:00:00" c="1"><n>Seven Pounds</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Will Smith is the good Samaritan driven to acts of incredible kindness by a dark secret in this powerful, life-affirming drama. With Woody Harrelson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-21 15:00:00" d="2019-08-21 17:00:00" c="1"><n>Crazy Heart</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% An Oscar-winning Jeff Bridges stars as an alcoholic country singer getting one last shot at the big time. Maggie Gyllenhaal and Colin Farrell co-star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-21 17:00:00" d="2019-08-21 19:00:00" c="1"><n>The Pursuit Of Happyness</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% Will Smith inspires as the down on his luck dad chasing the American Dream in 80s San Francisco. Heart-warming drama co-starring Jaden Smith</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-21 19:00:00" d="2019-08-21 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Victoria &amp; Abdul</n><t>F</t>    <k>An ageing and isolated Queen Victoria (Judi Dench) begins an unlikely friendship with a young Indian clerk. Period drama from Stephen Frears</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-21 21:00:00" d="2019-08-21 23:05:00" c="1"><n>The Social Network</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Jesse Eisenberg plays Facebook founder Mark Zuckerberg in David Fincher's Oscar-winning drama. With Andrew Garfield and Justin Timberlake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-21 23:05:00" d="2019-08-22 01:20:00" c="1"><n>Phantom Thread</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% Daniel Day-Lewis stars as a celebrated British dressmaker who falls in love with shy but strong-willed waitress Vicky Krieps. Oscar-winning drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-22 01:20:00" d="2019-08-22 03:15:00" c="1"><n>Closer</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% Julia Roberts, Clive Owen, Natalie Portman and Jude Law: two boys, two girls, two couples. But who ends up with whom? Crackling drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-22 03:15:00" d="2019-08-22 05:15:00" c="1"><n u="United">United 93</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% Two planes hit the World Trade Center on 9/11, one hit the Pentagon; this is the story of the fourth aircraft. Unflinching drama</k>  </p>
</a>
