<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2019-08-13 02:26:44"><p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-20 05:35:00" d="2019-08-20 07:45:00" c="1"><n>Million Dollar Arm</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Struggling sports agent Jon Hamm holds a contest to find future baseball stars in India. Uplifting drama based on a true story</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-20 07:45:00" d="2019-08-20 10:00:00" c="1"><n>Wall Street: Money Never Sleeps</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% Shia LaBeouf is a young trader embroiled in the dodgy dealings of Michael Douglas's Gordon Gekko in this slick sequel to the 80s' classic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-20 10:00:00" d="2019-08-20 10:15:00"><n>The 2019 Top Ten Show</n>    <k>Which movies are doing the best business at home and across the pond? Clips from the UK and US Top Ten show you the best of what's on offer on the big screen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-20 10:15:00" d="2019-08-20 12:35:00" c="1"><n>Walk The Line</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% Joaquin Phoenix stars as country music legend Johnny Cash. Cracking biopic of the Man in Black with Oscar-winning backing from Reese Witherspoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-20 12:35:00" d="2019-08-20 14:50:00" c="1"><n>Erin Brockovich</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% Julia Roberts plays the gutsy mum who takes on a corporation polluting local water. Oscar winner from Steven Soderbergh, with the late Albert Finney</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-20 14:50:00" d="2019-08-20 18:40:00" c="1"><n>Gone With The Wind</n><t>F</t>    <k>82% Epic Oscar-winning romance starring Vivien Leigh and Clark Gable as tempestuous lovers driven apart by the Civil War and their own explosive passions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-20 18:40:00" d="2019-08-20 21:00:00" c="1"><n>All The Money In The World</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Ageing oil tycoon J Paul Getty refuses to play ball when his teenage grandson is kidnapped and held for ransom. Crime thriller with Christopher Plummer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1049" o="2019-08-20 21:00:00" d="2019-08-21 00:00:00" c="1"><n>Life Itself</n><t>F</t>    <k>A multi-generational tale of life, loss and love starring Oscar Isaac and Olivia Wilde. Sky Cinema Original Film from the creator of This Is Us</k>  </p>
</a>
