<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2019-07-11 00:20:56"><p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-15 05:00:00" d="2019-07-15 06:00:00"><n u="Trailblazers: Pub Rock">Trailblazers: Pub Rock I (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A fascinating musical journey examining the back-to-basics pub rock movement that emerged in the south of England in the 1970s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-15 06:00:00" d="2019-07-15 07:00:00"><n u="Trailblazers: Dance">Trailblazers: Dance I (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An eye-opening look at the most memorable dance videos ever made, from Madonna's Vogue to Psy's Gangnam Style</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-15 07:00:00" d="2019-07-15 08:00:00"><n u="Eras Of Music History">Eras Of Music History I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>From Baroque and Viennese Classicism to Romantic and the modern era, this series vividly brings to life the evolution of classical music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-15 08:00:00" d="2019-07-15 08:30:00"><n>Auction</n>    <k>Series exploring some of the most intriguing and pricey pieces to pass through the world's greatest auction houses. A 1933 vintage car and Turner's Modern</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-15 08:30:00" d="2019-07-15 09:00:00"><n u="Watercolour Challenge">Watercolour Challenge I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Competition in which budding artists are challenged to paint a scene in four hours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-15 09:00:00" d="2019-07-15 10:00:00"><n u="Master Of Photography">Master Of Photography I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Beauty of Rome
Actress Isabella Rossellini hosts as Sky Arts launches a life-changing competition to find Europe's best photographer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-15 10:00:00" d="2019-07-15 10:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Who's Got The Lady?
When a piece of art is stolen, the gallery owner gets his girlfriend to make copies of it to sell. But did the work ever really leave the building?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-15 10:30:00" d="2019-07-15 11:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Skeleton Key
A woman discovers a nasty side to her husband's personality when he goes into hospital before a holiday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-15 11:00:00" d="2019-07-15 11:30:00"><n u="The British">The British I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% Values
Fascinating art pieces explore what it means to be British today, including a filmed poem from Simon Armitage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-15 11:30:00" d="2019-07-15 12:00:00"><n u="Billy Connolly: The South Bank Show Originals">Billy Connolly: The South Bank Show Originals V (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Melvyn Bragg looks back to his previous South Bank Show meeting with Billy Connolly and reflects on the Glaswegian's remarkable career in comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-15 12:00:00" d="2019-07-15 13:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Peter Lorre">Discovering: Peter Lorre VIII (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Film experts look back at the prolific career of Hungarian actor Peter Lorre, who gained international stardom for his portrayal of a psychotic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-15 13:00:00" d="2019-07-15 14:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Maximilian Schell">Discovering: Maximilian Schell VIII (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A fascinating look back at the life and career of actor Maximilian Schell, best remembered for his Oscar-winning performance in Stanley Kramer's Judgment at Nuremberg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-15 14:00:00" d="2019-07-15 14:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected VI (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Passing Opportunity
Frank is struggling financially and will do anything for money. When he meets a rich and successful schoolmate, he realises</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-15 14:30:00" d="2019-07-15 15:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected VI (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Memory Man
Down on his luck, 'Memory Man' Colin agrees to help a shady character remember the number of a station locker. But then Colin becomes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-15 15:00:00" d="2019-07-15 16:15:00"><n>Bee Gees: In Our Own Time</n>    <k>The late Robin Gibb and his brother Barry tell the extraordinary story of their family act, speaking candidly about their rise to fame and the tragedies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-15 16:15:00" d="2019-07-15 18:00:00"><n>Laurel &amp; Hardy: Their Lives and Magic</n>    <k>Behind-the-scenes documentary shedding new light on the exciting and turbulent private lives of Stan Laurel and Oliver Hardy and the genuine friendship between them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-15 18:00:00" d="2019-07-15 19:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Robert Taylor">Discovering: Robert Taylor VIII (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An intimate portrait of American actor Robert Taylor. One of the most popular leading men of the 30s and 40s, he starred in films such as Magnificent Obsession and Bataan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-15 19:00:00" d="2019-07-15 20:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Montgomery Clift">Discovering: Montgomery Clift VIII (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life and career of American actor Montgomery Clift, who starred in films such as Red River, A Place in the Sun and From Here to Eternity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-15 20:00:00" d="2019-07-15 21:00:00"><n u="Luciano Pavarotti: Legends of Opera">Luciano Pavarotti: Legends of Opera I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Critics, directors and singers celebrate the world's greatest opera stars, past and present, starting with the late great Italian tenor Luciano Pavarotti</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-15 21:00:00" d="2019-07-15 22:40:00"><n>Pavarotti - Live In Barcelona</n>    <k>Legendary operatic master Pavarotti performs songs including Un Aura Amorosa, La Danza and O Sole Mio in a spectacular solo concert from Barcelona's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-15 22:40:00" d="2019-07-15 23:40:00"><n>Pavarotti: Birth Of A Pop Star</n>    <k>New. The fascinating story of Luciano Pavarotti's journey from concert performer to international superstar as he helped expand the popularity of opera worldwide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-15 23:40:00" d="2019-07-16 01:10:00"><n>Royal Air Force In Concert</n>    <k>Filmed at Birmingham Symphony Hall, this special concert captures the illustrious Band of the Royal Air Force College on their annual tour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 01:10:00" d="2019-07-16 02:10:00"><n>Paris: The Golden Twenties</n>    <k>New. A magical in-depth exploration of the city of Paris, from the rich culture to the hidden rivalry between two districts - the rebellious Montmartre</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 02:10:00" d="2019-07-16 03:10:00"><n>Josephine Baker: The Story of an Awakening</n>    <k>New. A look into the fascinating fifty-year career of Josephine Baker, who rose to become an icon and a humanist fighter from a journey plagued by racism and tragedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 03:10:00" d="2019-07-16 05:10:00"><n>Moulin Rouge: The Ballet</n>    <k>New. Nineteenth-century Paris roars back to life in this stunning ballet based on the award-winning film Moulin Rouge. Choreographed by Jorden Morris</k>  </p>
</a>
