<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="20" t="2020-05-14 04:57:57"><p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-21 05:05:00" d="2020-05-21 06:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Jane Fonda">Discovering: Jane Fonda IX (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Movie experts look back at the life and career of Jane Fonda, who won Oscars for her performances in both neo-noir crime-thriller Klute and wartime drama Coming Home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-21 06:00:00" d="2020-05-21 07:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Peter Finch">Discovering: Peter Finch IX (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. An intimate portrait of Peter Finch, the actor known for his portrayal of anchorman Howard Beale in Network, for which he received the first ever posthumous Oscar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-21 07:00:00" d="2020-05-21 08:00:00"><n>Music For Mercy</n>    <k>Andrea Bocelli, Carly Paoli, David Foster and Elaine Paige are among the performers lighting up the Roman Forum in this 2016 concert marking the Pope's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-21 08:00:00" d="2020-05-21 10:00:00"><n>Hollywood In Vienna: The Sound Of Space &amp; Alexandre Desplat</n>    <k>A musical journey from Star Trek to Star Wars to ET, plus a tribute to The Shape of Water composer Alexandre Desplat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-21 10:00:00" d="2020-05-21 10:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bosom Friends
Nell and Emma are old friends who are reunited after years apart. However, things turn sour when the penniless Emma looks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-21 10:30:00" d="2020-05-21 11:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Glowing Future
Jack and Betsy are lovers. That is until Jack decides to go halfway across the world to be with his new Australian lover. But Betsy isn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-21 11:00:00" d="2020-05-21 12:00:00"><n u="The Art Of Architecture">The Art Of Architecture I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>With his work loved by the Prince of Wales, John Simpson is the modern architect who creates breathtaking classical buildings - including his own Hampshire house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-21 12:00:00" d="2020-05-21 13:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Jane Fonda">Discovering: Jane Fonda IX (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Movie experts look back at the life and career of Jane Fonda, who won Oscars for her performances in both neo-noir crime-thriller Klute and wartime drama Coming Home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-21 13:00:00" d="2020-05-21 14:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Peter Finch">Discovering: Peter Finch IX (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. An intimate portrait of Peter Finch, the actor known for his portrayal of anchorman Howard Beale in Network, for which he received the first ever posthumous Oscar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-21 14:00:00" d="2020-05-21 14:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Way To Do It
The casino offers Roger an escape from his domineering aunt. He has a love for both gambling and a pretty hostess. But the casino boss has a score to settle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-21 14:30:00" d="2020-05-21 15:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Hijack
A hijacker on an aeroplane takes a stewardess hostage before demanding a million dollars and a parachute. Will Captain Waterhouse give in to his demands?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-21 15:00:00" d="2020-05-21 16:00:00"><n u="Landscape Artist Of The Year">Landscape Artist Of The Year 2019 V (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Final
The artists must impress the judges in their toughest challenge yet - a night-painting of the iconic Battersea Power Station for the contest's grand final</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-21 16:00:00" d="2020-05-21 17:00:00"><n u="Portrait Artist Of The Year">Portrait Artist Of The Year 2019 (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Nine more hopefuls get just four hours to make their mark on the judges as they paint Nitin Sawhney, Sophie Ellis-Bextor and Adrian Lester</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-21 17:00:00" d="2020-05-21 18:00:00"><n u="Master Of Photography">Master Of Photography II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Travel
The photography competition returns and the contestants are sent to Sicily in a travel-themed challenge. Oliviero Toscani, Caroline Hunter and Darcy Padilla judge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-21 18:00:00" d="2020-05-21 19:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Gene Wilder">Discovering: Gene Wilder IX (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life and career of Gene Wilder, the charismatic star of Willy Wonka &amp; the Chocolate Factory, Blazing Saddles and Young Frankenstein</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-21 19:00:00" d="2020-05-21 20:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Laurence Harvey">Discovering: Laurence Harvey IX (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life and career of Laurence Harvey, the Oscar-nominated star of the 1959 drama Room at the Top. Contains archive footage which may be considered offensive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-21 20:00:00" d="2020-05-21 21:00:00"><n u="Landscape Artist Of The Year">Landscape Artist Of The Year 2019 V (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Winners Film
Join this year's winner on an exciting trip to Venice, as they set out to complete a ?10,000 commission for the Royal Institute of British Architects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-21 21:00:00" d="2020-05-21 22:00:00"><n u="Portrait Artist Of The Year">Portrait Artist Of The Year 2019 (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Nine more artists fight for a spot in the semi-final, getting just four hours to wow the judges with paintings of Angela Griffin, Gina McKee and Jamael Westman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-21 22:00:00" d="2020-05-21 23:00:00"><n u="Brian Johnson &amp; Roger Daltrey">Brian Johnson &amp; Roger Daltrey I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>AC/DC frontman Brian Johnson meets some of rock'n'roll's biggest names to share stories about what life is really like on the road. First up is The Who's Roger Daltrey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-21 23:00:00" d="2020-05-22 02:00:00"><n u="The Who: Live At Kilburn">The Who: Live At Kilburn 1977</n>    <k>New. Join legendary rock band The Who for an electrifying live performance of their most loved hits, including My Generation and Pinball Wizard</k>  </p>
</a>
