<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2020-05-13 04:36:09"><p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-20 06:00:00" d="2020-05-20 07:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Jack Nicholson">Discovering: Jack Nicholson IX (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A fascinating look at the life and career of Jack Nicholson, the Oscar-winning actor whose film credits include Easy Rider, The Shining, A Few Good Men and The Departed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-20 07:00:00" d="2020-05-20 08:45:00"><n>Mario Lanza: The Best Of Everything</n>    <k>A biographical portrait of Mario Lanza, the tenor and movie star who rose to fame in the 50s and paved the way for the likes of José Carreras and Plácido Domingo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-20 08:45:00" d="2020-05-20 10:00:00"><n>Pavarotti: 10th Anniversary Gala</n>    <k>Enjoy a star-studded event at the Verona Arena honouring the life of tenor Luciano Pavarotti. With touching performances from Placido Domingo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-20 10:00:00" d="2020-05-20 10:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Completely Foolproof
Wealthy New Yorker Joe Brisson is a self-made man with a plan to kill his disgruntled wife. Unfortunately for</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-20 10:30:00" d="2020-05-20 11:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>There's One Born Every Minute
Arthur and Margaret are a quiet couple. When Margaret inherits ?50,000, Arthur reluctantly agrees to gamble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-20 11:00:00" d="2020-05-20 12:00:00"><n u="The Art Of Architecture">The Art Of Architecture I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An inside look at the architecture behind London's new Design Museum in Kensington, a result of minimalist John Pawson's exquisite vision</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-20 12:00:00" d="2020-05-20 13:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Robert Duvall">Discovering: Robert Duvall VIII (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A portrait of actor Robert Duvall, who has starred in an array of iconic films and TV projects, including To Kill a Mockingbird, Apocalypse Now and The Godfather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-20 13:00:00" d="2020-05-20 14:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Jack Nicholson">Discovering: Jack Nicholson IX (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A fascinating look at the life and career of Jack Nicholson, the Oscar-winning actor whose film credits include Easy Rider, The Shining, A Few Good Men and The Departed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-20 14:00:00" d="2020-05-20 14:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bosom Friends
Nell and Emma are old friends who are reunited after years apart. However, things turn sour when the penniless Emma looks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-20 14:30:00" d="2020-05-20 15:30:00"><n u="Landscape Artist Of The Year">Landscape Artist Of The Year 2019 V (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Semi Final Cromarty
The judges have chosen the semi-finalists. Joined by the Wildcard Winner, they're at the banks of the Firth of Cromarty for another challenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-20 15:30:00" d="2020-05-20 16:30:00"><n u="Portrait Artist Of The Year">Portrait Artist Of The Year 2019 (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A new bunch of hopefuls pitch their easels as they bid to paint their way to the semi-finals. Mark Gatiss, Georgina Campbell and Tanni Grey-Thompson strike a pose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-20 16:30:00" d="2020-05-20 18:00:00"><n u="Master Of Photography">Master Of Photography I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Places and Faces
The photographers travel to four different European capitals to capture the diverse aspects of the continent. David LaChapelle then critiques their work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-20 18:00:00" d="2020-05-20 19:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Jane Fonda">Discovering: Jane Fonda IX (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Movie experts look back at the life and career of Jane Fonda, who won Oscars for her performances in both neo-noir crime-thriller Klute and wartime drama Coming Home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-20 19:00:00" d="2020-05-20 20:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Peter Finch">Discovering: Peter Finch IX (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. An intimate portrait of Peter Finch, the actor known for his portrayal of anchorman Howard Beale in Network, for which he received the first ever posthumous Oscar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-20 20:00:00" d="2020-05-20 21:00:00"><n u="Landscape Artist Of The Year">Landscape Artist Of The Year 2019 V (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Final
The artists must impress the judges in their toughest challenge yet - a night-painting of the iconic Battersea Power Station for the contest's grand final</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-20 21:00:00" d="2020-05-20 22:00:00"><n u="Portrait Artist Of The Year">Portrait Artist Of The Year 2019 (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Nine more hopefuls get just four hours to make their mark on the judges as they paint Nitin Sawhney, Sophie Ellis-Bextor and Adrian Lester</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-20 22:00:00" d="2020-05-20 23:00:00"><n u="The History Of Comedy">The History Of Comedy I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Parody and Satire
From Mel Brooks and 'Weird Al' Yankovic to Spinal Tap and The Simpsons, this episode examines parody and the great humour found in serious subjects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-20 23:00:00" d="2020-05-21 02:00:00"><n u="Comedy Legends: Tommy Cooper">Comedy Legends: Tommy Cooper I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Barry Cryer pays tribute to the heroes of comedy who he has worked with over his many years in the business, starting with Tommy Cooper</k>  </p>
</a>
