<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2021-07-09 07:14:48"><p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 05:00:00" d="2021-07-15 05:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Stinker
When millionaire Jack runs into Harold, a boy he bullied at school, he gives him a job. But Harold soon suspects his wife of having an affair with his new boss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 05:30:00" d="2021-07-15 06:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>I'll Be Seeing You
When Roland leaves his cruel, millionairess wife Vivien for a fresh start with his mistress Anna, the snubbed spouse plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 06:00:00" d="2021-07-15 07:00:00"><n u="Tate Britain's Great Art Walks">Tate Britain's Great Art Walks II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Actress Harriet Walter travels from London's seedy underworld to the picturesque English seaside to shed light on the work of Victorian painter Walter Sickert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 07:00:00" d="2021-07-15 08:00:00"><n u="Darbar Festival">Darbar Festival 2018 (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sky Arts presents a selection of the finest performances from the 2018 Darbar festival in London, celebrating the very best in Indian classical music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 08:00:00" d="2021-07-15 10:00:00"><n>Song For Nature: London Climate Change Festival</n>    <k>The arts meets activism in this unique concert. Featuring Nathan Evans, Brian May, Kerry Ellis, Rob Brydon, David Suchet and Danielle de Niese</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 10:00:00" d="2021-07-15 10:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Girl Can't Always Have Everything
Struggling actresses Suzy and Pat meet Herbert, a wealthy widower. Seductive Suzy enjoys his money, but things</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 10:30:00" d="2021-07-15 11:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Parson's Pleasure
Cyril Boggis makes a profitable living as a rogue antiques dealer. But when he buys Farmer Rummins' valuable furniture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 11:00:00" d="2021-07-15 12:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Anthony Hopkins">Discovering: Anthony Hopkins IX (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the career of Anthony Hopkins, the Oscar-winning actor known for roles in films such as The Silence of the Lambs, The Remains of the Day and Amistad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 12:00:00" d="2021-07-15 13:00:00"><n u="The Art Of Architecture">The Art Of Architecture I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>How did Santiago Calatrava's World Trade Center Transportation Hub come to be? This intriguing new series explores the inspirations behind the world's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 13:00:00" d="2021-07-15 14:00:00"><n>Paris: The Golden Twenties</n>    <k>A magical in-depth exploration of the city of Paris, from the rich culture to the hidden rivalry between two districts - the rebellious Montmartre</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 14:00:00" d="2021-07-15 14:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Stinker
When millionaire Jack runs into Harold, a boy he bullied at school, he gives him a job. But Harold soon suspects his wife of having an affair with his new boss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 14:30:00" d="2021-07-15 15:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>I'll Be Seeing You
When Roland leaves his cruel, millionairess wife Vivien for a fresh start with his mistress Anna, the snubbed spouse plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 15:00:00" d="2021-07-15 16:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Faye Dunaway">Discovering: Faye Dunaway IX (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A closer look at the life and career of Faye Dunaway, the Oscar-winning actress known for her roles in Bonnie and Clyde, The Thomas Crown Affair, Chinatown and Network</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 16:00:00" d="2021-07-15 17:00:00"><n>The Grapes Of Wrath: The Ghost of Modern America</n>    <k>Eye-opening film examining the scandalous, cult book by John Steinbeck. 80 years later, the themes in the novel are more current than ever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 17:00:00" d="2021-07-15 17:30:00"><n u="Simple Minds: Music Icons">Simple Minds: Music Icons III (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The story of the chart-topping rock band who have spent over two decades delighting fans with tracks like Don't You (Forget About Me) and Alive and Kicking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 17:30:00" d="2021-07-15 18:00:00"><n u="Frankie Goes To Hollywood: Video Killed The Radio Star">Frankie Goes To Hollywood: Video Killed The Radio Star V (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Director Kevin Godley reflects on the success and controversies of the videos for Relax, Two Tribes and Christmas hit The Power of Love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 18:00:00" d="2021-07-15 18:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Party
When disgruntled factory manager Harry is left feeling undervalued by his colleagues, he decides to take revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 18:30:00" d="2021-07-15 19:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Would You Believe It
Two archaeologists working in Jordan get more than they bargain for when they decide to smuggle the statue of a mysterious woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 19:00:00" d="2021-07-15 20:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Vincent Price">Discovering: Vincent Price IX (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life and career of Vincent Price, the suavely menacing star of numerous horror films including House of Wax and The Abominable Dr Phibes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 20:00:00" d="2021-07-15 21:00:00"><n>Warren Beatty: A Hollywood Obsession</n>    <k>A colourful portrait of Warren Beatty, the flamboyant yet private Oscar-winning director and actor known for films such as Bonnie and Clyde, Reds and Heaven Can Wait</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 21:00:00" d="2021-07-15 22:00:00"><n u="Sharon Tate: Too Young To Die">Sharon Tate: Too Young To Die I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life of Sharon Tate, the actress and model who suffered a tragic and untimely death at the hands of followers of murderous cult leader Charles Manson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 22:00:00" d="2021-07-15 23:00:00"><n u="New: The South Bank Show">New: The South Bank Show 2021 (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Arielle Smith &amp; Alberta Whittle
Meet more young and talented creatives nominated for the 2021 Sky Arts South Bank Times Breakthrough Awards</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 23:00:00" d="2021-07-16 01:00:00"><n>I Am Bruce Lee</n>    <k>An insightful film documenting the life of actor and martial artist Bruce Lee, with insight from his family shedding light on who he really was</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 01:00:00" d="2021-07-16 02:00:00"><n u="Guy Garvey: From The Vaults">Guy Garvey: From The Vaults (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. 1983
Tina Turner's career reaches new heights thanks to The Tube. American stars like Shalamar and ZZ Top also appear. Political affairs influence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 02:00:00" d="2021-07-16 03:40:00"><n>Lauryn Hill: Live At Baloise Session</n>    <k>New. The multi-Grammy Award winner performs her biggest hits, including Doo Wop, Ex-Factor and Everything is Everything from her album The Miseducation of Lauryn Hill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 03:40:00" d="2021-07-16 04:00:00"><n>Arts Uncovered</n>    <k>New. Gary James McQueen: A series of fascinating shorts taking you deeper into the world of art and the people behind it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 04:00:00" d="2021-07-16 05:00:00"><n u="World War II &amp; Cinema">World War II &amp; Cinema (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The World Is Now At War
It's the 1940s, and with the whole world at war, the USA and the UK join forces both in action and on the big screen</k>  </p>
</a>
