<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2021-07-08 04:55:20"><p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 05:00:00" d="2021-07-13 05:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Proof Of Guilt
George is denying murder, even though he was in a locked room with the victim when he was shot. Inspector Walters just can't find any evidence against him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 05:30:00" d="2021-07-13 06:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Vengeance Is Mine Inc
Mrs Wilbur gets more than she bargained for when she calls upon the services of Tom and George, two actors from</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 06:00:00" d="2021-07-13 07:00:00"><n u="Tate Britain's Great Art Walks">Tate Britain's Great Art Walks II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Travelling from Blenheim Palace and Ightham Mote all the way to Paris, photographer David Bailey and Gus Casely-Hayford explore the world of John Singer Sargent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 07:00:00" d="2021-07-13 07:30:00"><n>Gilbert &amp; Sullivan: A Motley Pair</n>    <k>As tensions between the pair threatened to tear Gilbert and Sullivan apart, impresario Richard D'Oyly Carte makes the decision to move the company</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 07:30:00" d="2021-07-13 08:45:00"><n>Ludovico Einaudi: Elements Live</n>    <k>Italian composer Ludovico Einaudi takes inspiration from the elements of nature in this stunning work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 08:45:00" d="2021-07-13 09:45:00"><n>Pavarotti: Birth Of A Pop Star</n>    <k>The fascinating story of Luciano Pavarotti's journey from concert performer to international superstar as he helped expand the popularity of opera worldwide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 09:45:00" d="2021-07-13 10:00:00"><n>Arts Uncovered</n>    <k>Arts Uncovered joins the stage managers at the Royal Opera House as they prepare for a new production at the iconic Covent Garden venue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 10:00:00" d="2021-07-13 10:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Back For Christmas
A philandering physician with an obsession for orchids cultivates a deadly plot to see off his wife. Siân Phillips and Richard Johnson star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 10:30:00" d="2021-07-13 11:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Picture Of A Place
Hazel is an elderly widow who lives in a farmhouse full of antiques. When a conman arrives he dupes her into selling him a picture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 11:00:00" d="2021-07-13 12:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Charles Laughton">Discovering: Charles Laughton IX (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life and career of Charles Laughton, the Yorkshire-born stage and film actor who starred in The Old Dark House and Mutiny on the Bounty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 12:00:00" d="2021-07-13 13:00:00"><n u="Tate Britain's Great Art Walks">Tate Britain's Great Art Walks II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Actor Robert Lindsay travels from the Sussex coast to the back streets of Chelsea to explore the landscapes that inspired Victorian painter William Holman Hunt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 13:00:00" d="2021-07-13 14:00:00"><n u="The Art Show">The Art Show I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Dr James Fox explores the art of Jodhpur, while Will Best and Kate Bryan take an artistic tour of Venice. Meanwhile, Carrie Scott talks to British</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 14:00:00" d="2021-07-13 14:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Proof Of Guilt
George is denying murder, even though he was in a locked room with the victim when he was shot. Inspector Walters just can't find any evidence against him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 14:30:00" d="2021-07-13 15:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Vengeance Is Mine Inc
Mrs Wilbur gets more than she bargained for when she calls upon the services of Tom and George, two actors from</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 15:00:00" d="2021-07-13 16:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Karl Malden">Discovering: Karl Malden IX (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An intimate profile of Karl Malden, the actor who won an Oscar for his role as Mitch in A Streetcar Named Desire and was nominated for another for On the Waterfront</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 16:00:00" d="2021-07-13 17:00:00"><n>1968: A Year Of War Turmoil and Beyond</n>    <k>A look at the importance of 1968 in American history, from Apollo 8 and Vietnam, to the race riots and assassinations of Martin Luther King and Robert F Kennedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 17:00:00" d="2021-07-13 17:30:00"><n u="Foreigner: Music Icons">Foreigner: Music Icons III (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A glimpse into the career of one of the world's best-selling bands of all time, and the hitmakers of the anthem I Want To Know What Love Is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 17:30:00" d="2021-07-13 18:00:00"><n u="Oasis: Video Killed The Radio Star">Oasis: Video Killed The Radio Star V (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Director Nigel Dick discusses the iconic music videos he has made with Oasis and reflects on his fractious relationship with the Gallagher brothers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 18:00:00" d="2021-07-13 18:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Girl Can't Always Have Everything
Struggling actresses Suzy and Pat meet Herbert, a wealthy widower. Seductive Suzy enjoys his money, but things</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 18:30:00" d="2021-07-13 19:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Parson's Pleasure
Cyril Boggis makes a profitable living as a rogue antiques dealer. But when he buys Farmer Rummins' valuable furniture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 19:00:00" d="2021-07-13 20:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Anthony Hopkins">Discovering: Anthony Hopkins IX (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the career of Anthony Hopkins, the Oscar-winning actor known for roles in films such as The Silence of the Lambs, The Remains of the Day and Amistad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 20:00:00" d="2021-07-13 21:00:00"><n u="Leonardo: The Works">Leonardo: The Works (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A film marking the 500th anniversary of the world-famous artist's death, with a look at his vast collection of work including The Mona Lisa and The Last Supper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 21:00:00" d="2021-07-13 22:00:00"><n u="Master Of Photography">Master Of Photography III (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Home Sweet Home
The photographers head home where they must take pictures depicting their life and the places that are familiar to them, as well as a self-portrait</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 22:00:00" d="2021-07-13 23:30:00"><n>Art And Mind</n>    <k>An exploration of visionary artists and the creative impulse, from the Flemish Masters of the Renaissance to the avant-garde movement of Surrealism</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-13 23:30:00" d="2021-07-14 01:30:00"><n>My Rembrandt</n>    <k>Thrilling film offering a glimpse into the exclusive world of the Old Masters collectors, through a mosaic of gripping stories, each fuelled by a passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 01:30:00" d="2021-07-14 02:45:00"><n>League Of Exotique Dancers</n>    <k>Eye-opening documentary revealing the sexism and discrimination hidden behind the glitz and glamour of the golden age of Burlesque. From award-winning director Rama Rau</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 02:45:00" d="2021-07-14 03:15:00"><n u="Unmuted">Unmuted (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Nayha Ahmad meets real-life superhero Jess Thom AKA Touretteshero. Nicole Holliday checks out the UK Vogue scene. Plus, there's a performance from Emeli Sande</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 03:15:00" d="2021-07-14 04:10:00"><n u="Mystery Of The Lost Monet">Mystery Of The Lost Monet I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Art experts attempt to digitally reconstruct Monet's Water Lilies, a much beloved painting that was destroyed in a fire at New York's Museum of Modern Art in 1958</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 04:10:00" d="2021-07-14 05:05:00"><n u="Design Dealers">Design Dealers I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Paul and Sarah visit Ireland's Huntington Castle on a mission to buy antiques. They also reclaim lost treasures from local junkyards and unveil a fabulous new shop display</k>  </p>
</a>
