<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2021-07-09 07:14:58"><p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 05:00:00" d="2021-07-16 05:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Party
When disgruntled factory manager Harry is left feeling undervalued by his colleagues, he decides to take revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 05:30:00" d="2021-07-16 06:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Would You Believe It
Two archaeologists working in Jordan get more than they bargain for when they decide to smuggle the statue of a mysterious woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 06:00:00" d="2021-07-16 07:00:00"><n u="The Art Of Architecture">The Art Of Architecture I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>How did Santiago Calatrava's World Trade Center Transportation Hub come to be? This intriguing new series explores the inspirations behind the world's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 07:00:00" d="2021-07-16 07:55:00"><n>Force Of Nature Natalia</n>    <k>BAFTA Award-winning filmmaker Gerry Fox provides an unprecedented look into the life of ballerina superstar Natalia Osipova as she prepares for her Royal Ballet season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 07:55:00" d="2021-07-16 10:05:00"><n>Matthew Bourne's Swan Lake 2019</n>    <k>Olivier Award-winning interpretation of Tchaikovsky's beloved tale, retaining all the iconic elements with a spellbinding originality. With Will Bozier and Liam Mower</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 10:05:00" d="2021-07-16 10:35:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Stinker
When millionaire Jack runs into Harold, a boy he bullied at school, he gives him a job. But Harold soon suspects his wife of having an affair with his new boss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 10:35:00" d="2021-07-16 11:05:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>I'll Be Seeing You
When Roland leaves his cruel, millionairess wife Vivien for a fresh start with his mistress Anna, the snubbed spouse plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 11:05:00" d="2021-07-16 12:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Faye Dunaway">Discovering: Faye Dunaway IX (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A closer look at the life and career of Faye Dunaway, the Oscar-winning actress known for her roles in Bonnie and Clyde, The Thomas Crown Affair, Chinatown and Network</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 12:00:00" d="2021-07-16 13:00:00"><n u="The Art Of Architecture">The Art Of Architecture I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at London's mammoth Battersea Power Station, brought back to life after 30 years of dereliction with designs from architect Jim Eyre</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 13:00:00" d="2021-07-16 14:00:00"><n u="Leonardo: The Works">Leonardo: The Works (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A film marking the 500th anniversary of the world-famous artist's death, with a look at his vast collection of work including The Mona Lisa and The Last Supper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 14:00:00" d="2021-07-16 14:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Party
When disgruntled factory manager Harry is left feeling undervalued by his colleagues, he decides to take revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 14:30:00" d="2021-07-16 15:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Would You Believe It
Two archaeologists working in Jordan get more than they bargain for when they decide to smuggle the statue of a mysterious woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 15:00:00" d="2021-07-16 16:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Vincent Price">Discovering: Vincent Price IX (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life and career of Vincent Price, the suavely menacing star of numerous horror films including House of Wax and The Abominable Dr Phibes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 16:00:00" d="2021-07-16 17:00:00"><n u="Mystery Of The Lost Monet">Mystery Of The Lost Monet I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Art experts attempt to digitally reconstruct Monet's Water Lilies, a much beloved painting that was destroyed in a fire at New York's Museum of Modern Art in 1958</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 17:00:00" d="2021-07-16 17:30:00"><n u="Red Hot Chilli Peppers: Music Icons">Red Hot Chilli Peppers: Music Icons III (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look into the career of one of the best-selling rock bands in the world. The six-time Grammy Award winners' hits include Scar Tissue and Dani California</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 17:30:00" d="2021-07-16 18:00:00"><n u="Joe Strummer: Video Killed the Radio Star">Joe Strummer: Video Killed the Radio Star V (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Pogues' Shane MacGowan is among those examining Joe Strummer's exit from The Clash, his part in The Pogues and his spaghetti western Straight to Hell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 18:00:00" d="2021-07-16 18:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Vicious Circle
When an elderly lady catches a burglar trying to rob her, she decides to help him go straight. But she has to take a different approach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 18:30:00" d="2021-07-16 19:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Boy Who Talked With Animals
When David rescues a giant turtle, it looks as though he's found a new friend. But there could be more to his pet than meets the eye</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 19:00:00" d="2021-07-16 20:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Judi Dench">Discovering: Judi Dench IX (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look back at the career of Judi Dench, who won an Oscar for her role as Queen Elizabeth in Shakespeare in Love before going on to star as M in eight James Bond movies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 20:00:00" d="2021-07-16 21:00:00"><n>The British Invasion: Small Faces</n>    <k>A look at the short but brilliant career of The Small Faces, featuring interviews with original members and performances of classic hits, including</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 21:00:00" d="2021-07-16 22:00:00"><n u="New: Guy Garvey: From The Vaults">New: Guy Garvey: From The Vaults (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. 1985
Chaka Khan and Tom Waits perform live on The Tube. Also, new series Bliss brings live sets from the likes of The Cult and Propaganda</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-16 22:00:00" d="2021-07-17 00:00:00"><n>New: Michael Kiwanuka: Live At Baloise Session</n>    <k>New. The Mercury Prize-winning singer-songwriter performs tracks from his hit albums Home Again and Love &amp; Hate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-17 00:00:00" d="2021-07-17 01:30:00"><n>The Kinks: Echoes Of A World</n>    <k>The story of the 1968 album The Kinks Are the Village Green Preservation Society. After failing to chart upon release it went on to become</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-17 01:30:00" d="2021-07-17 01:55:00"><n u="The Kinks: Music Icons">The Kinks: Music Icons II (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The spotlight falls on British Invasion band The Kinks, whose 60s hits You Really Got Me and All Day and All of the Night paved the way for the next decade's hard rock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-17 01:55:00" d="2021-07-17 04:05:00"><n>Manson: Music From An Unsound Mind</n>    <k>Filmmaker Tom O'Dell explores how Charles Manson's obsession with becoming a rock star and his time in the LA music scene led to his descent into violence and murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-17 04:05:00" d="2021-07-17 05:00:00"><n>Hip Hop And Me By Nihal</n>    <k>DJ Nihal Arthanayake explores his love of hip hop, meeting some of the genre's biggest names and mentoring an aspiring young rapper all</k>  </p>
</a>
