<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2019-07-11 00:20:57"><p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 05:10:00" d="2019-07-16 06:05:00"><n u="Discovering: Robert Taylor">Discovering: Robert Taylor VIII (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An intimate portrait of American actor Robert Taylor. One of the most popular leading men of the 30s and 40s, he starred in films such as Magnificent Obsession and Bataan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 06:05:00" d="2019-07-16 07:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Montgomery Clift">Discovering: Montgomery Clift VIII (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life and career of American actor Montgomery Clift, who starred in films such as Red River, A Place in the Sun and From Here to Eternity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 07:00:00" d="2019-07-16 08:00:00"><n u="Eras Of Music History">Eras Of Music History I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Travelling through Florence, Venice, Leipzig, Paris and London, this episode explores the music of the Baroque era. Featuring Anna Netrebko and Rolando Villazon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 08:00:00" d="2019-07-16 08:30:00"><n>Auction</n>    <k>The sculptures of Modigliani set a new record in Paris, the Spencers auction off the contents of their aristocratic attic, and art from the golden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 08:30:00" d="2019-07-16 09:00:00"><n u="Watercolour Challenge">Watercolour Challenge I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Competition in which budding artists are challenged to paint a scene in four hours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 09:00:00" d="2019-07-16 10:00:00"><n u="Master Of Photography">Master Of Photography I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Berlin Nightlife
The contestants are flown into Berlin, where they are challenged to tell a story with three nighttime photos. Acclaimed photographer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 10:00:00" d="2019-07-16 10:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected VI (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Passing Opportunity
Frank is struggling financially and will do anything for money. When he meets a rich and successful schoolmate, he realises</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 10:30:00" d="2019-07-16 11:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected VI (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Memory Man
Down on his luck, 'Memory Man' Colin agrees to help a shady character remember the number of a station locker. But then Colin becomes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 11:00:00" d="2019-07-16 11:30:00"><n u="The British">The British I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% Youth
Intriguing works explore the challenges facing young people in Britain today, featuring a powerful dance film from hip-hop dance troupe Boy Blue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 11:30:00" d="2019-07-16 12:00:00"><n u="Joan Rivers: The South Bank Show Originals">Joan Rivers: The South Bank Show Originals V (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Melvyn Bragg looks back on his entertaining 2002 meeting with Joan Rivers in a warm-hearted tribute to the late New York comedian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 12:00:00" d="2019-07-16 13:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Robert Taylor">Discovering: Robert Taylor VIII (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An intimate portrait of American actor Robert Taylor. One of the most popular leading men of the 30s and 40s, he starred in films such as Magnificent Obsession and Bataan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 13:00:00" d="2019-07-16 14:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Montgomery Clift">Discovering: Montgomery Clift VIII (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life and career of American actor Montgomery Clift, who starred in films such as Red River, A Place in the Sun and From Here to Eternity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 14:00:00" d="2019-07-16 14:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected VI (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Sad Loss
Claire and her boyfriend have always counted on inheriting Claire's wealthy aunt's fortune. But when they hear she has a new heir lined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 14:30:00" d="2019-07-16 15:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected VI (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Clerical Error
While winding up his late father's affairs, Paul finds a bill demanding over ?1,000 for pornography. He's suspicious of the claim. for a very good reason</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 15:00:00" d="2019-07-16 17:00:00"><n>Moulin Rouge: The Ballet</n>    <k>New. Nineteenth-century Paris roars back to life in this stunning ballet based on the award-winning film Moulin Rouge. Choreographed by Jorden Morris</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 17:00:00" d="2019-07-16 18:00:00"><n>Josephine Baker: The Story of an Awakening</n>    <k>New. A look into the fascinating fifty-year career of Josephine Baker, who rose to become an icon and a humanist fighter from a journey plagued by racism and tragedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 18:00:00" d="2019-07-16 19:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Warren Beatty">Discovering: Warren Beatty VIII (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An intimate portrait of Warren Beatty, the Oscar-winning director and actor known for such films as Bonnie and Clyde, Reds and Heaven Can Wait</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 19:00:00" d="2019-07-16 20:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Jack Palance">Discovering: Jack Palance VIII (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A fascinating look at the life and career of actor Jack Palance, best known for playing villainous roles in the 60s and for his award-winning appearance in City Slickers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 20:00:00" d="2019-07-16 20:30:00"><n u="Neil Young: Video Killed The Radio Star">Neil Young: Video Killed The Radio Star VII (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at some of the most iconic music videos of Neil Young, known for recording hits such as Old Man, Harvest Moon and Heart of Gold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 20:30:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00"><n u="Earth, Wind And Fire: Music Icons">Earth, Wind And Fire: Music Icons I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The fascinating story of the genre-spanning Earth, Wind and Fire, one of the most popular funk bands of the 70s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 22:00:00"><n>Passions: William Blake by Alison Lapper</n>    <k>Artist Alison Lapper shares her love of poet William Blake, whose radical politics and progressive attitudes towards art and sexual freedom influenced generations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 22:00:00" d="2019-07-16 23:00:00"><n u="The 2000s">The 2000s I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>79% A compelling look back to 2009 when Barack Obama became the 44th President of the United States after one of the most fascinating elections in American history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-16 23:00:00" d="2019-07-17 00:00:00"><n u="Jed Mercurio: The South Bank Show">Jed Mercurio: The South Bank Show IX (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Jed Mercurio
Melvyn Bragg sits down for an exclusive interview with the writer and creator of Bodyguard and Line of Duty, Jed Mercurio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 00:00:00" d="2019-07-17 01:00:00"><n u="John Sturges: The Directors">John Sturges: The Directors III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. A fascinating look at the life and career of Oscar-nominated director John Sturges, the mind behind classic films such as The Great Escape and The Magnificent Seven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 01:00:00" d="2019-07-17 02:20:00"><n>Queen: The Magic Years</n>    <k>They came, they rocked and they influenced. See how the music of Queen's Brian May, Freddie Mercury, Roger Taylor and John Deacon earned them respect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 02:20:00" d="2019-07-17 04:00:00"><n>Pulp: A Film About Life Death &amp; Supermarkets</n>    <k>New. Twenty-five years and 10 million album sales since the Britpop band found fame, they return to their hometown for their last ever UK concert. Documentary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 04:00:00" d="2019-07-17 05:00:00"><n u="Jed Mercurio: The South Bank Show">Jed Mercurio: The South Bank Show IX (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Jed Mercurio
Melvyn Bragg sits down for an exclusive interview with the writer and creator of Bodyguard and Line of Duty, Jed Mercurio</k>  </p>
</a>
