<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2019-08-13 02:25:08"><p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-18 06:30:00" d="2019-08-18 07:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Janis Joplin">Discovering: Janis Joplin V (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life and music of Janis Joplin. Known for her powerful, blues-inspired vocals, she rose to fame in the late 1960s before dying of a drug overdose in 1970</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-18 07:00:00" d="2019-08-18 07:35:00"><n u="Classical Destinations">Classical Destinations III (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In Melbourne, Aled Jones uncovers the eccentric world of Percy Grainger, whose work was often experimental and unusual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-18 07:35:00" d="2019-08-18 08:00:00"><n u="Sons Of Vienna">Sons Of Vienna I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Series exploring the vibrant musical journeys of history's great composers, including Beethoven, Mozart, Haydn and Schubert, who, at one time or another</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-18 08:00:00" d="2019-08-18 08:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Landlady
When a young man arrives in Bath, he is shocked to find his seemingly charming landlady has a dark side</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-18 08:30:00" d="2019-08-18 09:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Neck
A young lady is cut down to size by her husband's loyal butler when it is discovered she is having an affair</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-18 09:00:00" d="2019-08-18 09:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Edward the Conqueror
When Edward grows tired of his wife Louisa's obsession with a stray cat and decides to get rid of it, Louisa exacts her revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-18 09:30:00" d="2019-08-18 10:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Dip in the Pool
An American gambler must come up with a cunning plan to slow down a ship at sea in order to win a bet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-18 10:00:00" d="2019-08-18 10:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Way Up To Heaven
Mrs Foster exacts an intriguing revenge on her husband after his dawdling causes her to miss a flight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-18 10:30:00" d="2019-08-18 11:00:00"><n u="Frank Auerbach: The South Bank Show Originals">Frank Auerbach: The South Bank Show Originals VI (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. A look back at Melvyn Bragg's insightful interview with the celebrated German-British artist in a classic episode of The South Bank Show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-18 11:00:00" d="2019-08-18 12:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Bing Crosby">Discovering: Bing Crosby II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Leading film critics discuss the life and career of Bing Crosby, who became an Oscar-winning movie star and best-selling singer despite a number of personal troubles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-18 12:00:00" d="2019-08-18 13:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Vivien Leigh">Discovering: Vivien Leigh II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the career of Vivien Leigh, who scooped an Oscar as Scarlett O'Hara, famously married star Laurence Olivier and died of tuberculosis aged 53</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-18 13:00:00" d="2019-08-18 14:00:00"><n u="Discovering: James Cagney">Discovering: James Cagney II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The story of the actor renowned for his roles in gangster films The Public Enemy and White Heat, whose battles with the Hollywood studios changed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-18 14:00:00" d="2019-08-18 15:00:00"><n u="Discovering: John Wayne">Discovering: John Wayne II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An intimate look at the life and career of John Wayne. Born Marion Morrison, the former football player would become one of the most iconic actors of the 20th century</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-18 15:00:00" d="2019-08-18 16:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Charlton Heston">Discovering: Charlton Heston II (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Leading film critics discuss the career of Charlton Heston. After humble beginnings on stage, he took Hollywood by storm with starring in Ben-Hur and Planet of the Apes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-18 16:00:00" d="2019-08-18 17:00:00"><n>Passions: Bernstein By Dame Kiri Te Kanawa</n>    <k>New. Opera star Dame Kiri Te Kanawa explores the genius of Leonard Bernstein, with whom she worked on the landmark 1984 recording of West Side Story</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-18 17:00:00" d="2019-08-18 17:55:00"><n u="The Art Of Architecture">The Art Of Architecture I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. A look at how Thomas Heatherwick's unusual and stunning design of many staircases became a mind-blowing tourist attraction in Manhattan, known as the Vessel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-18 17:55:00" d="2019-08-18 18:50:00"><n>Elvis Presley: A Legend in Concert</n>    <k>Sensational collection of TV performances from The King. Featuring the notorious screen debut of his famous pelvic gyrations and the time Steve Allen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-18 18:50:00" d="2019-08-18 20:30:00"><n>Festival Express</n>    <k>Documentary chronicling the extraordinary five-day train ride and series of concerts across Canada in 1970 that featured Janis Joplin, The Grateful Dead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-18 20:30:00" d="2019-08-18 22:00:00"><n>Come Together: The Rise Of The Festival</n>    <k>Documentary examining the evolution of the music festival, from Newport, Monterey Pop, Woodstock and the Isle of Wight in the 60s to modern events such as Glastonbury</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-18 22:00:00" d="2019-08-18 23:45:00"><n>Joe Cocker: Mad Dog With Soul</n>    <k>Documentary charting the rise of Joe Cocker, a gas fitter who played in Sheffield pubs and was catapulted to stardom following a spectacular appearance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-18 23:45:00" d="2019-08-19 01:15:00"><n>The Festival That Rocked The...</n>    <k>New. Exclusive interviews and astonishing footage tell the epic story of the 1969 Woodstock festival. In a time of civil unrest, half a million people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-19 01:15:00" d="2019-08-19 02:50:00"><n>Santana: Greatest Hits Live at Montreux</n>    <k>Carlos Santana and his band plays their greatest hits, including Black Magic Woman and Oye Coma Va, at the 2011 Montreux Jazz Festival in Switzerland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-19 02:50:00" d="2019-08-19 04:45:00"><n>Classic Artists: Jimi Hendrix</n>    <k>Friends and fans of Jimi Hendrix tell the story of one of rock's great icons, who dazzled crowds in the 60s with his outrageous electric guitar playing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-19 04:45:00" d="2019-08-19 05:15:00"><n u="Discovering: The Who">Discovering: The Who V (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the rise of rock opera pioneers The Who, from their formation at school in Acton, London, to their award-winning albums and sell out tours around the world</k>  </p>
</a>
