<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2019-07-11 00:20:57"><p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 05:00:00" d="2019-07-17 06:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Warren Beatty">Discovering: Warren Beatty VIII (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An intimate portrait of Warren Beatty, the Oscar-winning director and actor known for such films as Bonnie and Clyde, Reds and Heaven Can Wait</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 06:00:00" d="2019-07-17 07:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Jack Palance">Discovering: Jack Palance VIII (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A fascinating look at the life and career of actor Jack Palance, best known for playing villainous roles in the 60s and for his award-winning appearance in City Slickers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 07:00:00" d="2019-07-17 08:00:00"><n u="Eras Of Music History">Eras Of Music History I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>From Mozart to Beethoven, this episode explores the people who shaped the sound of the Viennese classical scene. Featuring Diana Damrau and Lang Lang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 08:00:00" d="2019-07-17 08:30:00"><n>Auction</n>    <k>Found in a bin bag, Princess Diana's black Emmanuel gown goes on sale. Plus late dealer Ambroise Vollard's collection finally comes up for auction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 08:30:00" d="2019-07-17 09:00:00"><n u="Watercolour Challenge">Watercolour Challenge I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Competition in which budding artists are challenged to paint a scene in four hours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 09:00:00" d="2019-07-17 10:00:00"><n u="Master Of Photography">Master Of Photography I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Body
The contestants arrive in Rome, where they are challenged to take pictures of the human body. Finnish photographer Elina Brotherus mentors</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 10:00:00" d="2019-07-17 10:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected VI (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Sad Loss
Claire and her boyfriend have always counted on inheriting Claire's wealthy aunt's fortune. But when they hear she has a new heir lined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 10:30:00" d="2019-07-17 11:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected VI (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Clerical Error
While winding up his late father's affairs, Paul finds a bill demanding over ?1,000 for pornography. He's suspicious of the claim. for a very good reason</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 11:00:00" d="2019-07-17 11:30:00"><n u="The British">The British I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% Race
Talented artists explore multiculturalism and race relations in the UK with thought-provoking short films, and a new national anthem by Nitin Sawhney</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 11:30:00" d="2019-07-17 12:00:00"><n u="Ian McKellen: The South Bank Show Originals">Ian McKellen: The South Bank Show Originals V (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Melvyn Bragg looks back at Sir Ian McKellen's appearances on The South Bank Show, tracing his rise from the National Theatre to Hollywood stardom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 12:00:00" d="2019-07-17 13:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Warren Beatty">Discovering: Warren Beatty VIII (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An intimate portrait of Warren Beatty, the Oscar-winning director and actor known for such films as Bonnie and Clyde, Reds and Heaven Can Wait</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 13:00:00" d="2019-07-17 14:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Jack Palance">Discovering: Jack Palance VIII (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A fascinating look at the life and career of actor Jack Palance, best known for playing villainous roles in the 60s and for his award-winning appearance in City Slickers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 14:00:00" d="2019-07-17 14:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected VI (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Heir Presumptuous
George is murdered, and one of his nephews is seen fleeing the scene. The problem is his nephews are identical twins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 14:30:00" d="2019-07-17 15:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected VI (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Down Along And Sheltering Palms
An ex-soldier meets a beautiful woman on a nostalgic trip back to his old base. But she isn't all she seems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 15:00:00" d="2019-07-17 16:00:00"><n>Paris: The Golden Twenties</n>    <k>New. A magical in-depth exploration of the city of Paris, from the rich culture to the hidden rivalry between two districts - the rebellious Montmartre</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 16:00:00" d="2019-07-17 17:00:00"><n>Pavarotti: Birth Of A Pop Star</n>    <k>New. The fascinating story of Luciano Pavarotti's journey from concert performer to international superstar as he helped expand the popularity of opera worldwide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 17:00:00" d="2019-07-17 18:00:00"><n u="Luciano Pavarotti: Legends of Opera">Luciano Pavarotti: Legends of Opera I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Critics, directors and singers celebrate the world's greatest opera stars, past and present, starting with the late great Italian tenor Luciano Pavarotti</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 18:00:00" d="2019-07-17 19:00:00"><n u="Discovering: George C Scott">Discovering: George C Scott VIII (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life and career of American actor George C Scott. Despite winning an Oscar for his portrayal of George S Patton in 1970, he refused to accept the award</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 19:00:00" d="2019-07-17 20:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Julie Christie">Discovering: Julie Christie VIII (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An intimate profile of Julie Christie, the acclaimed British actress who has won the Academy, Golden Globe, BAFTA and Screen Actors Guild awards</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 20:00:00" d="2019-07-17 21:00:00"><n>The Drawings Of Yves Saint Laurent</n>    <k>An incredible collection of Yves Saint Laurent's sketches are brought to life in a special look at the iconic designer's legacy. With YSL fashion tycoon Pierre Berge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 21:00:00" d="2019-07-17 23:00:00"><n>The First Film</n>    <k>Intriguing documentary exploring the mysterious 1890 disappearance of Leeds-based film pioneer Louis Le Prince, a man some believe was the true inventor of moving pictures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-17 23:00:00" d="2019-07-18 00:00:00"><n u="The History Of Comedy">The History Of Comedy II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. No Offense
A look at how comedians and sitcom writers have found creative ways through euphemisms and innuendo to just about abide by the rules</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-18 00:00:00" d="2019-07-18 01:15:00"><n>California Dreamin' : The Songs Of The Mamas &amp; The Papas</n>    <k>Interviews and performance footage tells the remarkable story of 1960s Californian pop group The Mamas and the Papas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-18 01:15:00" d="2019-07-18 02:30:00"><n>Fairport Convention: Folk Heroes</n>    <k>The original members of Fairport Convention look back on the band's 50-year history and reflect on how they pioneered the British folk rock movement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-18 02:30:00" d="2019-07-18 04:10:00"><n>Manic Street Preachers: Escape From History</n>    <k>Documentary by BAFTA-winning director Kieran Evans telling the story of how The Manic Street Preachers' acclaimed 1996 album Everything Must Go was created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-07-18 04:10:00" d="2019-07-18 05:10:00"><n>John Lennon: Classic Albums</n>    <k>A fascinating look at the making of John Lennon's debut solo album, Plastic Ono Band, which saw the former Beatle dealing with issues such as abandonment</k>  </p>
</a>
