<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2020-04-10 04:36:43"><p id_tv="1050" o="2020-04-17 05:00:00" d="2020-04-17 06:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Olivia De Havilland">Discovering: Olivia De Havilland V (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An intimate profile of Olivia de Havilland. Best known as Melanie in Gone with the Wind, she won Academy Awards for her roles in To Each His Own and The Heiress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-04-17 06:00:00" d="2020-04-17 07:00:00"><n u="Discovering: William Holden">Discovering: William Holden V (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A fascinating look at the life and career of William Holden, an actor who became one of Hollywood's biggest box office draws from the 1950s through to the 1970s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-04-17 07:00:00" d="2020-04-17 07:55:00"><n u="Darbar Festival">Darbar Festival 2018 (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Sky Arts presents a selection of the finest performances from the 2018 Darbar festival in London, celebrating the very best in Indian classical music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-04-17 07:55:00" d="2020-04-17 09:30:00"><n>The Metamorphosis</n>    <k>Edward Watson gives an Olivier Award-winning performance in the Royal Opera House's sell-out 2013 show. He stars as salesman Gregor, who wakes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-04-17 09:30:00" d="2020-04-17 10:00:00"><n u="Watercolour Challenge">Watercolour Challenge I (35)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Competition in which budding artists are challenged to paint a scene in four hours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-04-17 10:00:00" d="2020-04-17 10:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IX (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Time To Die
Yves's marriage has gone stale and his young mistress has announced that she is pregnant. But he then makes a decision which changes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-04-17 10:30:00" d="2020-04-17 11:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IX (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mr Know-All
When pretty hotel worker Elly is charmed by a guest, archaeologist Max Kelada, it seems that the Mr Know-All professor might not be the man he claims to be</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-04-17 11:00:00" d="2020-04-17 12:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Olivia De Havilland">Discovering: Olivia De Havilland V (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An intimate profile of Olivia de Havilland. Best known as Melanie in Gone with the Wind, she won Academy Awards for her roles in To Each His Own and The Heiress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-04-17 12:00:00" d="2020-04-17 13:00:00"><n u="Discovering: William Holden">Discovering: William Holden V (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A fascinating look at the life and career of William Holden, an actor who became one of Hollywood's biggest box office draws from the 1950s through to the 1970s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-04-17 13:00:00" d="2020-04-17 14:00:00"><n u="The Seventies">The Seventies I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Television Gets Real
Emmy-nominated documentary series examining the politics, culture and historic events of the 1970s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-04-17 14:00:00" d="2020-04-17 14:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Man From The South
A young American couple on holiday meet a mysterious old gentleman who makes them a macabre wager</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-04-17 14:30:00" d="2020-04-17 15:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mrs Bixby and the Colonel's Coat
Unable to show her dentist husband Cyril the fur coat her lover has given her, Mrs Bixby proceeds to hatch a clever plan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-04-17 15:00:00" d="2020-04-17 16:00:00"><n u="Landscape Artist Of The Year">Landscape Artist Of The Year 2017 (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The remaining artists compete for a place in next week's final as they aim to impress the judges with their landscapes of the Hop Shop lavender farm in Kent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-04-17 16:00:00" d="2020-04-17 17:00:00"><n u="Portrait Artist Of The Year">Portrait Artist Of The Year 2017 III (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The six heat winners arrive for the semi-final where celebrity sitter Imelda Staunton awaits. The pressure is on as only three artists will be chosen for the final</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-04-17 17:00:00" d="2020-04-17 18:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Barbara Stanwyck">Discovering: Barbara Stanwyck V (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A profile of Barbara Stanwyck, an actress who enjoyed a 60-year career in film and television, best known for her strong female roles in films, such as Double Indemnity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-04-17 18:00:00" d="2020-04-17 19:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Gregory Peck">Discovering: Gregory Peck V (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An eye-opening look at the life and films of American film legend Gregory Peck, the Academy Award-winning star of the 1962 drama To Kill a Mockingbird</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-04-17 19:00:00" d="2020-04-17 20:00:00"><n u="The Seventies">The Seventies I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The United States Vs Nixon
A look at how the Watergate scandal led to Richard Nixon being the only president in United States history to resign from office</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-04-17 20:00:00" d="2020-04-17 23:00:00"><n>Pink Floyd: Delicate Sound Of Thunder</n>    <k>Spectacular concert film from Pink Floyd's 1988 A Momentary Lapse of Reason tour, featuring hits Learning to Fly, Comfortably Numb and Wish You Were Here</k>  </p>
</a>
