<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-05-26 04:39:09"><p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-02 05:00:00" d="2020-06-02 06:00:00"><n u="Fritz Lang: The Directors">Fritz Lang: The Directors I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An intimate portrait of Austrian-born filmmaker Fritz Lang, one of the most accomplished and enduring directors of the 20th century</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-02 06:00:00" d="2020-06-02 06:30:00"><n u="Auction">Auction IV (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>EH Shepard's first depiction of Winnie-The-Pooh with Christopher Robin goes on sale. Blueprints for The Beetle and works by Van Dyck and Joseph Wright</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-02 06:30:00" d="2020-06-02 07:00:00"><n u="Auction">Auction IV (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Works by Belgian artist Rene Magritte go to the highest bidder in a surrealist art sale in London. Meanwhile, a one-million-dollar desk goes under the hammer in Manhattan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-02 07:00:00" d="2020-06-02 07:55:00"><n u="Jose Carreras: Legends Of Opera">Jose Carreras: Legends Of Opera I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An intimate profile of José Carreras, the Spanish tenor who achieved worldwide fame with his performances as one of the Three Tenors</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-02 07:55:00" d="2020-06-02 10:00:00"><n>Sir Simon Rattle Conducts An Imaginary Orchestral Journey</n>    <k>Sir Simon Rattle presents the Prelude and Liebestod from Wagner's ground-breaking opera Tristan and Isolde, followed by work by Joseph Haydn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-02 10:00:00" d="2020-06-02 10:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>What Have You Been Up To Lately?
Richard and Fergus meet after 25 years. Pondering a girl they both loved, they discover that their marriages failed along with their careers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-02 10:30:00" d="2020-06-02 11:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Absence Of Emily
Norma owns a big house and lets her sister Emily and her husband live there. But when Emily disappears, Norma makes too much fuss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-02 11:00:00" d="2020-06-02 12:00:00"><n u="The Adventurers Of Modern Art">The Adventurers Of Modern Art I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Libertad!
In 1936, war erupts in Spain. While Malraux and Hemingway cover the Republicans' struggle as journalists, Picasso creates a monumental canvas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-02 12:00:00" d="2020-06-02 13:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Sean Connery">Discovering: Sean Connery X (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life and legendary career of the original James Bond - Academy Award-winning Sean Connery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-02 13:00:00" d="2020-06-02 14:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Robin Williams">Discovering: Robin Williams X (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life of the late Robin Williams, the Academy Award-winning star of much-loved films such as Good Will Hunting, Jumanji and Mrs Doubtfire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-02 14:00:00" d="2020-06-02 14:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In The Bag
Cara hires safecracker Sam to get back her confiscated jewels. But when she insists on joining him on the job, Sam could be making the biggest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-02 14:30:00" d="2020-06-02 15:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Man With A Fortune
A rich and lonely American ventures to England in search of his long-lost family. But when he meets Jane and her flatmate Eva, things begin to go wrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-02 15:00:00" d="2020-06-02 16:00:00"><n u="Trailblazers: Glam Rock">Trailblazers: Glam Rock I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>From the flamboyant clothes to the extravagant make up, Noddy Holder narrates this fascinating look at the evolution of glam rock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-02 16:00:00" d="2020-06-02 17:00:00"><n>Michelangelo's Pietas</n>    <k>A fascinating look at why Michelangelo became obsessed with the Pieta - the powerful scene of the Virgin Mary holding the dying body of Jesus in her arms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-02 17:00:00" d="2020-06-02 18:00:00"><n u="Master Of Photography">Master Of Photography III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Dancing Naples
The competition returns as 10 photographers compete to impress the judges in a series of creative challenges around Europe, starting in Naples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-02 18:00:00" d="2020-06-02 19:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Robert De Niro">Discovering: Robert De Niro X (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life of legendary two-time Academy Award winner Robert De Niro, star of The Godfather Part II, Taxi Driver and Goodfellas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-02 19:00:00" d="2020-06-02 20:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Alain Delon">Discovering: Alain Delon X (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Alain Delon
A glimpse into the life of French star and winner of the 2019 Honorary Palme d'Or, Alain Delon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-02 20:00:00" d="2020-06-02 21:00:00"><n u="The Adventurers Of Modern Art">The Adventurers Of Modern Art I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Libertad!
In 1936, war erupts in Spain. While Malraux and Hemingway cover the Republicans' struggle as journalists, Picasso creates a monumental canvas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-02 21:00:00" d="2020-06-02 22:00:00"><n u="Battle Of The Brass Bands">Battle Of The Brass Bands (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Britain's most famous brass bands are battling it out for top spot in national competitions and you've got a front-row ticket! Join them on the ultimate quest for victory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-02 22:00:00" d="2020-06-02 23:00:00"><n u="Portrait Artist Of The Year">Portrait Artist Of The Year 2020 VI (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Asa Butterfield, Micky Flanagan, Anjli Mohindra
This year's hopefuls prepare to paint their way to success as the competition begins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-02 23:00:00" d="2020-06-03 02:00:00"><n u="The Nineties">The Nineties I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% Can We All Get Along?
A look at the 90s' social issues, from the LA riots to the OJ Simpson murder case</k>  </p>
</a>
