<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-05-30 04:39:20"><p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-06 05:00:00" d="2020-06-06 06:00:00"><n u="Frank Capra: The Directors">Frank Capra: The Directors I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An intimate portrait of Frank Capra, the celebrated Italian-American director known for films such as It's a Wonderful Life and Mr Smith Goes to Washington</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-06 06:00:00" d="2020-06-06 06:30:00"><n u="Auction">Auction V (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at some of the most valuable and iconic pieces to recently be sold at the world's greatest auction houses. A painting by Francesco Guardi goes under the hammer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-06 06:30:00" d="2020-06-06 07:00:00"><n u="Auction">Auction V (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A painting from Monet's watercolour series fetches an impressive price at Sotheby's. Elsewhere in London, rare pieces by French glassmaker Rene Lalique</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-06 07:00:00" d="2020-06-06 08:35:00"><n>Elizabeth</n>    <k>Carlos Acosta and Zenaida Yanowsky take centre stage at the Royal Opera House in Will Tuckett's thrilling work of dance, music and theatre that explores</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-06 08:35:00" d="2020-06-06 09:05:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>What Have You Been Up To Lately?
Richard and Fergus meet after 25 years. Pondering a girl they both loved, they discover that their marriages failed along with their careers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-06 09:05:00" d="2020-06-06 09:35:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Absence Of Emily
Norma owns a big house and lets her sister Emily and her husband live there. But when Emily disappears, Norma makes too much fuss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-06 09:35:00" d="2020-06-06 10:05:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In The Bag
Cara hires safecracker Sam to get back her confiscated jewels. But when she insists on joining him on the job, Sam could be making the biggest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-06 10:05:00" d="2020-06-06 10:35:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Man With A Fortune
A rich and lonely American ventures to England in search of his long-lost family. But when he meets Jane and her flatmate Eva, things begin to go wrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-06 10:35:00" d="2020-06-06 11:05:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Who's Got The Lady?
When a piece of art is stolen, the gallery owner gets his girlfriend to make copies of it to sell. But did the work ever really leave the building?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-06 11:05:00" d="2020-06-06 12:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Sean Connery">Discovering: Sean Connery X (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life and legendary career of the original James Bond - Academy Award-winning Sean Connery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-06 12:00:00" d="2020-06-06 13:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Robin Williams">Discovering: Robin Williams X (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life of the late Robin Williams, the Academy Award-winning star of much-loved films such as Good Will Hunting, Jumanji and Mrs Doubtfire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-06 13:00:00" d="2020-06-06 14:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Robert De Niro">Discovering: Robert De Niro X (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life of legendary two-time Academy Award winner Robert De Niro, star of The Godfather Part II, Taxi Driver and Goodfellas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-06 14:00:00" d="2020-06-06 15:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Alain Delon">Discovering: Alain Delon X (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Alain Delon
A glimpse into the life of French star and winner of the 2019 Honorary Palme d'Or, Alain Delon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-06 15:00:00" d="2020-06-06 16:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Maggie Smith">Discovering: Maggie Smith X (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life of Academy Award-winning Maggie Smith. From Harry Potter to Downton Abbey, her huge portfolio makes her one of the UK's most recognisable actresses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-06 16:00:00" d="2020-06-06 17:00:00"><n u="The Sixties">The Sixties I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% The Space Race
A look at the beginning of space exploration and the competition between the United States and the Soviet Union to be the first to land on the moon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-06 17:00:00" d="2020-06-06 18:00:00"><n u="The Sixties">The Sixties I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% 1968
A look at the year which saw the assassinations of Robert F Kennedy and Martin Luther King Jr, as well as the escalation of the Vietnam War and civil rights protests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-06 18:00:00" d="2020-06-06 19:00:00"><n u="The Sixties">The Sixties I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% The British Invasion
A look at how American culture was forever altered by The Beatles and the new wave of British bands and artists that followed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-06 19:00:00" d="2020-06-06 20:45:00"><n>Beatles Stories</n>    <k>Fans and friends of The Beatles discuss their experiences of the Fab Four, from eating beans on toast with Ringo Starr to playing Scrabble with George Harrison. Warm documentary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-06 20:45:00" d="2020-06-06 22:00:00"><n>The Rolling Stones: Sweet Summer Sun - Hyde Park Live</n>    <k>The Rolling Stones make an unforgettable and historic return to Hyde Park, London, during their 2013 50 and Counting Tour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-06 22:00:00" d="2020-06-06 23:20:00"><n>New: Ronnie Wood: Somebody Up There Likes Me</n>    <k>New. Film exploring the turbulent life of legendary rock guitarist and The Rolling Stones member Ronnie Wood. With insight from Keith Richards, Mick Jagger and more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-06 23:20:00" d="2020-06-07 02:20:00"><n>The Rolling Stones: Sticky Fingers Live at the Fonda Theatre</n>    <k>Recorded on 20 May 2015 at the Fonda Theatre in Hollywood, California, The Rolling Stones perform their entire Sticky Fingers album</k>  </p>
</a>
