<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2019-08-09 01:41:17"><p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 05:00:00" d="2019-08-15 06:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Greta Garbo">Discovering: Greta Garbo II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the extraordinary career of the Ninotchka and Grand Hotel star. An incredibly private actress, Greta Garbo never married and retired when she was just 35</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 06:00:00" d="2019-08-15 07:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Bing Crosby">Discovering: Bing Crosby II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Leading film critics discuss the life and career of Bing Crosby, who became an Oscar-winning movie star and best-selling singer despite a number of personal troubles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 07:00:00" d="2019-08-15 08:00:00"><n u="Jose Carreras: Legends Of Opera">Jose Carreras: Legends Of Opera I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. An intimate profile of José Carreras, the Spanish tenor who achieved worldwide fame with his performances as one of the Three Tenors</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 08:00:00" d="2019-08-15 08:30:00"><n u="Auction">Auction III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A hundred years after the sinking of the Titanic, a crew member's suitcase appears at auction. At Christie's, a larger-than-life baby sculpture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 08:30:00" d="2019-08-15 09:00:00"><n u="Watercolour Challenge">Watercolour Challenge I (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Competition in which budding artists are challenged to paint a scene in four hours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 09:00:00" d="2019-08-15 10:00:00"><n u="Master Of Photography">Master Of Photography IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Archeological Landscape
In a single picture, the contestants must capture the spirit and historical significance of one of Italy's most famous sites: Ostia Antica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 10:00:00" d="2019-08-15 10:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lamb to the Slaughter
When Mary kills her husband with a frozen leg of lamb, she must think quickly to hide the evidence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 10:30:00" d="2019-08-15 11:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Landlady
When a young man arrives in Bath, he is shocked to find his seemingly charming landlady has a dark side</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 11:00:00" d="2019-08-15 12:00:00"><n u="Gail Rebuck: The South Bank Show">Gail Rebuck: The South Bank Show (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Melvyn Bragg talks to Gail Rebuck. As one of the most influential figures in British publishing she was awarded a CBE in 2000 and made a Dame in 2009</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 12:00:00" d="2019-08-15 13:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Greta Garbo">Discovering: Greta Garbo II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the extraordinary career of the Ninotchka and Grand Hotel star. An incredibly private actress, Greta Garbo never married and retired when she was just 35</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 13:00:00" d="2019-08-15 14:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Bing Crosby">Discovering: Bing Crosby II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Leading film critics discuss the life and career of Bing Crosby, who became an Oscar-winning movie star and best-selling singer despite a number of personal troubles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 14:00:00" d="2019-08-15 14:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Neck
A young lady is cut down to size by her husband's loyal butler when it is discovered she is having an affair</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 14:30:00" d="2019-08-15 15:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Edward the Conqueror
When Edward grows tired of his wife Louisa's obsession with a stray cat and decides to get rid of it, Louisa exacts her revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 15:00:00" d="2019-08-15 16:00:00"><n>Andre Rieu: Wedding Special</n>    <k>Violin maestro Andre Rieu hosts a very special wedding party, thrilling the crowd with a host of celebratory songs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 16:00:00" d="2019-08-15 17:00:00"><n>Beach Boys: Good Vibrations Tour</n>    <k>This biographical musical film directed by Gary Weis intertwines 1976 concert footage with interviews with the band, along with Blues Brothers Dan Aykroyd and John Belushi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 17:00:00" d="2019-08-15 17:30:00"><n u="Discovering: The Eagles">Discovering: The Eagles V (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the legacy of LA rock band The Eagles. Among the most successful recording artists of the 1970s, their hits include Hotel California and Take it Easy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 17:30:00" d="2019-08-15 18:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Fleetwood Mac">Discovering: Fleetwood Mac I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the tumultuous history of Fleetwood Mac. Their story of break-ups, drugs and broken hearts inspired their bestselling music, including their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 18:00:00" d="2019-08-15 19:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Vivien Leigh">Discovering: Vivien Leigh II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the career of Vivien Leigh, who scooped an Oscar as Scarlett O'Hara, famously married star Laurence Olivier and died of tuberculosis aged 53</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 19:00:00" d="2019-08-15 20:00:00"><n u="Discovering: James Cagney">Discovering: James Cagney II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The story of the actor renowned for his roles in gangster films The Public Enemy and White Heat, whose battles with the Hollywood studios changed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 20:00:00" d="2019-08-15 21:00:00"><n u="The Seventies">The Seventies I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>What's Goin' On
American popular music explodes into new formats, while established artists, including Blondie, Billy Joel and KISS find new ways to express themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 21:00:00" d="2019-08-15 22:00:00"><n u="New: John Frankenheimer: The Directors">New: John Frankenheimer: The Directors III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. A look at the life and career of the award-winning director behind movies such as The Manchurian Candidate, Birdman of Alcatraz, The Train and Ronin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 22:00:00" d="2019-08-15 23:15:00"><n>Chaplin: The Birth Of The Tramp</n>    <k>A fascinating look beyond the toothbrush moustache, derby hat, walking cane and splayed feet to uncover the remarkable rise of Charlie Chaplin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-15 23:15:00" d="2019-08-16 01:00:00"><n>Mario Lanza: The Best Of Everything</n>    <k>A biographical portrait of Mario Lanza, the tenor and movie star who rose to fame in the 50s and paved the way for the likes of José Carreras and Plácido Domingo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 01:00:00" d="2019-08-16 02:10:00"><n u="Punk">Punk (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. The series concludes with a look at punk's journey into the mainstream, with the success of artists like Nirvana and Green Day, and the emergence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 02:10:00" d="2019-08-16 03:10:00"><n>The Making Of Marc Bolan</n>    <k>This moving documentary, featuring friends, family and well-known fans, tells the story of how East End boy Mark Feld became T. Rex frontman and glam-rock icon Marc Bolan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 03:10:00" d="2019-08-16 05:10:00"><n>Joan Jett: Bad Reputation</n>    <k>New. Film chronicling the life of rock star Joan Jett, from founding The Runaways as an ambitious teenager to her evolution into the icon and activist she is today</k>  </p>
</a>
