<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="17" t="2020-05-16 04:56:13"><p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-23 05:00:00" d="2020-05-23 06:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Donald Sutherland">Discovering: Donald Sutherland IX (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life and career of Donald Sutherland, the Canadian actor whose credits include The Dirty Dozen, M_A_S_H, Pride &amp; Prejudice and The Hunger Games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-23 06:00:00" d="2020-05-23 07:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Dirk Bogarde">Discovering: Dirk Bogarde IX (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Movie experts reflect on the career of Dirk Bogarde, the great English actor known for his complex roles in the dark films Victim, Death in Venice and The Night Porter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-23 07:00:00" d="2020-05-23 09:30:00"><n>Daniel Harding - The Inaugural Concert</n>    <k>Schumann Scenes From Faust. New. For his first concert as music director of the Orchestre de Paris, Daniel Harding explores Schumann's work Scenes from Goethe's Faust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-23 09:30:00" d="2020-05-23 10:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Last Bottle In The World
Kyros plans on giving his wife a priceless bottle of wine for their anniversary. But he has no intention of drinking to her health</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-23 10:00:00" d="2020-05-23 10:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Kindly Dig Your Grave
The unscrupulous Madame La Grue runs an art gallery, exploiting young artists. But she finally gets her comeuppance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-23 10:30:00" d="2020-05-23 11:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Completely Foolproof
Wealthy New Yorker Joe Brisson is a self-made man with a plan to kill his disgruntled wife. Unfortunately for</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-23 11:00:00" d="2020-05-23 11:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>There's One Born Every Minute
Arthur and Margaret are a quiet couple. When Margaret inherits ?50,000, Arthur reluctantly agrees to gamble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-23 11:30:00" d="2020-05-23 12:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bosom Friends
Nell and Emma are old friends who are reunited after years apart. However, things turn sour when the penniless Emma looks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-23 12:00:00" d="2020-05-23 14:00:00"><n>Cats: The Musical</n>    <k>Elaine Paige stars in Andrew Lloyd Webber's world-famous musical. A group of cats gather to choose one lucky feline, who will go to a magical place to be reborn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-23 14:00:00" d="2020-05-23 15:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Julie Christie">Discovering: Julie Christie VIII (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An intimate profile of Julie Christie, the acclaimed British actress who has won the Academy, Golden Globe, BAFTA and Screen Actors Guild awards</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-23 15:00:00" d="2020-05-23 16:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Carole Lombard">Discovering: Carole Lombard VIII (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A fascinating look at the life and career of actress Carole Lombard, who starred in a host of comedic films during the 1930s but died in a tragic plane accident in 1942</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-23 16:00:00" d="2020-05-23 17:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Robert Duvall">Discovering: Robert Duvall VIII (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A portrait of actor Robert Duvall, who has starred in an array of iconic films and TV projects, including To Kill a Mockingbird, Apocalypse Now and The Godfather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-23 17:00:00" d="2020-05-23 18:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Jack Nicholson">Discovering: Jack Nicholson IX (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A fascinating look at the life and career of Jack Nicholson, the Oscar-winning actor whose film credits include Easy Rider, The Shining, A Few Good Men and The Departed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-23 18:00:00" d="2020-05-23 19:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Jane Fonda">Discovering: Jane Fonda IX (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Movie experts look back at the life and career of Jane Fonda, who won Oscars for her performances in both neo-noir crime-thriller Klute and wartime drama Coming Home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-23 19:00:00" d="2020-05-23 20:30:00"><n>Bob Marley Live At The Rainbow</n>    <k>Shortly after Bob Marley released his 1977 album Exodus, he performed at London's famous Rainbow Theatre. Set highlights include I Shot The Sheriff, Lively</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-23 20:30:00" d="2020-05-23 22:15:00"><n>Queen: Live At The Rainbow</n>    <k>A treat for all Queen fans as Freddie, Brian, John and Roger perform early hits such as Killer Queen and Seven Seas of Rhye at the Rainbow Theatre in London in 1974</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-05-23 22:15:00" d="2020-05-24 01:15:00"><n>Freddie Mercury: The Great Pretender</n>    <k>With archive footage of interviews, concerts and personal material, this award-winning documentary offers a compelling insight into the solo work of Freddie Mercury</k>  </p>
</a>
