<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2021-07-09 07:14:38"><p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 05:05:00" d="2021-07-14 05:35:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Girl Can't Always Have Everything
Struggling actresses Suzy and Pat meet Herbert, a wealthy widower. Seductive Suzy enjoys his money, but things</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 05:35:00" d="2021-07-14 06:05:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Parson's Pleasure
Cyril Boggis makes a profitable living as a rogue antiques dealer. But when he buys Farmer Rummins' valuable furniture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 06:05:00" d="2021-07-14 07:00:00"><n u="Tate Britain's Great Art Walks">Tate Britain's Great Art Walks II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Actor Robert Lindsay travels from the Sussex coast to the back streets of Chelsea to explore the landscapes that inspired Victorian painter William Holman Hunt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 07:00:00" d="2021-07-14 08:20:00"><n u="Hollywood Singing &amp; Dancing">Hollywood Singing &amp; Dancing (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at how Hollywood used the musical to provide much-needed escapism during the Great Depression of the early 1930s, and introduced stars such as Shirley Temple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 08:20:00" d="2021-07-14 10:00:00"><n>Lang Lang: New York Rhapsody</n>    <k>From the Lincoln Center in New York, acclaimed pianist Lang Lang performs a love letter to the Big Apple with help from friends including Rufus Wainwright and Regina Spektor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 10:00:00" d="2021-07-14 10:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Proof Of Guilt
George is denying murder, even though he was in a locked room with the victim when he was shot. Inspector Walters just can't find any evidence against him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 10:30:00" d="2021-07-14 11:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Vengeance Is Mine Inc
Mrs Wilbur gets more than she bargained for when she calls upon the services of Tom and George, two actors from</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 11:00:00" d="2021-07-14 12:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Karl Malden">Discovering: Karl Malden IX (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An intimate profile of Karl Malden, the actor who won an Oscar for his role as Mitch in A Streetcar Named Desire and was nominated for another for On the Waterfront</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 12:00:00" d="2021-07-14 13:00:00"><n u="Tate Britain's Great Art Walks">Tate Britain's Great Art Walks II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Actress Harriet Walter travels from London's seedy underworld to the picturesque English seaside to shed light on the work of Victorian painter Walter Sickert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 13:00:00" d="2021-07-14 14:00:00"><n>E.M. Forster: His Longest Journey</n>    <k>Special film about the life of A Passage to India author EM Forster, following his huge growth as a writer and the twists and turns of his personal life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 14:00:00" d="2021-07-14 14:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Girl Can't Always Have Everything
Struggling actresses Suzy and Pat meet Herbert, a wealthy widower. Seductive Suzy enjoys his money, but things</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 14:30:00" d="2021-07-14 15:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Parson's Pleasure
Cyril Boggis makes a profitable living as a rogue antiques dealer. But when he buys Farmer Rummins' valuable furniture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 15:00:00" d="2021-07-14 16:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Anthony Hopkins">Discovering: Anthony Hopkins IX (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the career of Anthony Hopkins, the Oscar-winning actor known for roles in films such as The Silence of the Lambs, The Remains of the Day and Amistad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 16:00:00" d="2021-07-14 17:00:00"><n u="Brunelleschi's Impossible Dome">Brunelleschi's Impossible Dome (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Part two looks at British artist Luke Jerram's contemporary dome, a public artwork in Coal Drops Yard, near King's Cross, and how it has developed over time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 17:00:00" d="2021-07-14 17:30:00"><n u="Patti Smith: Music Icons">Patti Smith: Music Icons III (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A glimpse into the life of the 'Because the Night' hitmaker who has inspired the likes of Madonna and R.E.M's Michael Stipe throughout her long and fruitful career</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 17:30:00" d="2021-07-14 18:00:00"><n u="Michael Jackson: Video Killed The Radio Star">Michael Jackson: Video Killed The Radio Star V (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Directors behind some of Michael Jackson's iconic music videos, including Thriller and Smooth Criminal, discuss their collaborations with the King of Pop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 18:00:00" d="2021-07-14 18:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Stinker
When millionaire Jack runs into Harold, a boy he bullied at school, he gives him a job. But Harold soon suspects his wife of having an affair with his new boss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 18:30:00" d="2021-07-14 19:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected III (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>I'll Be Seeing You
When Roland leaves his cruel, millionairess wife Vivien for a fresh start with his mistress Anna, the snubbed spouse plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 19:00:00" d="2021-07-14 20:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Faye Dunaway">Discovering: Faye Dunaway IX (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A closer look at the life and career of Faye Dunaway, the Oscar-winning actress known for her roles in Bonnie and Clyde, The Thomas Crown Affair, Chinatown and Network</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 20:00:00" d="2021-07-14 21:00:00"><n u="Portrait Artist Of The Year">Portrait Artist Of The Year 2020 VI (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Deborah Findlay, Wunmi Mosaku, Omid Djalili
Nine more artists look to impress the judges in the last heat before the semi-final</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 21:00:00" d="2021-07-14 22:00:00"><n u="Landscape Artist Of The Year">Landscape Artist Of The Year 2019 V (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Gateshead Millennium Bridge
The artists head to the banks of the River Tyne, with four hours to create an artwork of the engineering marvel and impress the judges</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 22:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:00:00"><n u="The 2000s">The 2000s I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>79% Quagmire
Bush's Second Term: A reflective look at George W Bush's second term as president, which encompassed Hurricane Katrina and the global financial crisis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 23:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:30:00"><n u="New: Unmuted">New: Unmuted (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Remel London meets three ballet stars and talks diversity in the industry, before chatting with UK champion B-boy Karam Singh. Jords performs his hit single, Enemies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-14 23:30:00" d="2021-07-15 00:00:00"><n u="Princess Diana, Freddie Mercury and Kenny Everett">Princess Diana, Freddie Mercury and Kenny Everett III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Urban Myths. Freddie Mercury and Kenny Everett disguise Princess Diana and take her on a night out in this Sky original</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 00:00:00" d="2021-07-15 01:00:00"><n>Dr. Jack And Mr. Nicholson</n>    <k>Film exploring Jack Nicholson's dazzling five-decade long career, in which he has worked on more than 60 films and with many top directors including Roman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 01:00:00" d="2021-07-15 02:00:00"><n u="The South Bank Show">The South Bank Show 2021 (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Noah Jupe, Mishka Rushdie Momen &amp; Alex Woolf
Meet more young and talented creatives nominated for the 2021 Sky Arts South Bank Times Breakthrough Awards</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 02:00:00" d="2021-07-15 03:00:00"><n>Hollywood Censored</n>    <k>This documentary by Clara and Julia Kuperberg examines how a set of moral guidelines known as the Hays Code influenced movie-making in Hollywood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 03:00:00" d="2021-07-15 04:00:00"><n u="BAFTA: Nicole Kidman Life in Pictures">BAFTA: Nicole Kidman Life in Pictures I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Nicole Kidman chats about her childhood love of the limelight, the highs and lows of her career and her memorable stint on London's West End</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-15 04:00:00" d="2021-07-15 05:00:00"><n>Philip Larkin By Andrew Motion</n>    <k>Former poet laureate Sir Andrew Motion heads to Hull to explore Philip Larkin's extraordinary - and sometimes controversial - legacy</k>  </p>
</a>
