<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2019-08-15 22:50:38"><p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-21 05:00:00" d="2019-08-21 06:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Gary Cooper">Discovering: Gary Cooper II (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A portrait of Hollywood icon Gary Cooper, whose films include High Noon, Sergeant York and Mr Deeds Goes to Town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-21 06:00:00" d="2019-08-21 07:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Natalie Wood">Discovering: Natalie Wood II (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Portrait of icon Natalie Wood, who appeared in Christmas classic Miracle on 34th Street when she was eight and went on to star in Rebel Without a Cause</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-21 07:00:00" d="2019-08-21 08:00:00"><n u="Darbar Festival">Darbar Festival 2017 (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Debasmita Bhattacharya is joined by Gurdain Rayatt for a blistering and dynamic musical performance at the 2017 Darbar festival in London</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-21 08:00:00" d="2019-08-21 08:30:00"><n u="Auction">Auction III (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In London, Christie's auctions photos of Marilyn Monroe and a painting of Derby Day by William Powell Frith that had been hanging in an unlocked beach hut for 50 years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-21 08:30:00" d="2019-08-21 09:00:00"><n u="Watercolour Challenge">Watercolour Challenge I (28)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Competition in which budding artists are challenged to paint a scene in four hours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-21 09:00:00" d="2019-08-21 10:00:00"><n u="Master Of Photography">Master Of Photography IV (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Home Sweet Home
In a deeply personal task, contestants are sent to their homes and loved ones, and asked to produce a set of three photos that showcase</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-21 10:00:00" d="2019-08-21 10:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected I (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Taste
A dinner party takes a surprising turn when one pretentious guest is challenged to a wine-tasting contest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-21 10:30:00" d="2019-08-21 11:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Skin
Derek Jacobi stars in a twisted tale. A man persuades an unknown artist to tattoo a picture on his back. But when the artist becomes famous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-21 11:00:00" d="2019-08-21 12:00:00"><n u="Sally Wainwright: South Bank Show">Sally Wainwright: South Bank Show (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Melvyn Bragg meets Sally Wainwright, one of the UK's most revered TV writers who has won BAFTA awards for her dramas Last Tango in Halifax and Happy Valley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-21 12:00:00" d="2019-08-21 13:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Gary Cooper">Discovering: Gary Cooper II (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A portrait of Hollywood icon Gary Cooper, whose films include High Noon, Sergeant York and Mr Deeds Goes to Town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-21 13:00:00" d="2019-08-21 14:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Natalie Wood">Discovering: Natalie Wood II (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Portrait of icon Natalie Wood, who appeared in Christmas classic Miracle on 34th Street when she was eight and went on to star in Rebel Without a Cause</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-21 14:00:00" d="2019-08-21 14:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Galloping Foxley
John Mills stars in this twisted tale. A man starts to suffer when he becomes haunted by the memory of the brutal treatment he received in his childhood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-21 14:30:00" d="2019-08-21 15:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Georgy Porgy
Joan Collins stars in a twisted tale. George has problems with female attention, but when a beautiful woman joins his congregation things are set to change</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-21 15:00:00" d="2019-08-21 16:00:00"><n>The Summer Of Love</n>    <k>The story of the cultural, social, and political changes that were brought about following the 1967 Summer of Love in San Francisco</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-21 16:00:00" d="2019-08-21 17:00:00"><n>Elvis And The Girl From Vienna</n>    <k>Trude Forsher was one of Elvis Presley's most trusted confidants in the 50s and this is her account of the King's rise to fame and the most iconic moments in his life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-21 17:00:00" d="2019-08-21 18:00:00"><n u="The Seventies">The Seventies I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>What's Goin' On
American popular music explodes into new formats, while established artists, including Blondie, Billy Joel and KISS find new ways to express themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-21 18:00:00" d="2019-08-21 19:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Spencer Tracy">Discovering: Spencer Tracy II (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Profile of the Hollywood star famous for his 25-year love affair with Katharine Hepburn. Nominated for nine Oscars, his films included Boys Town and Captains Courageous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-21 19:00:00" d="2019-08-21 20:00:00"><n u="Discovering: James Mason">Discovering: James Mason II (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Film critics discuss the career of James Mason. After achieving success in the UK, he moved to Hollywood, where he starred in films such as North By Northwest and Lolita</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-21 20:00:00" d="2019-08-21 21:00:00"><n u="The Sixties">The Sixties I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>85% A Long March to Freedom
An in-depth look into Martin Luther King Jr and his courageous efforts to lead the civil rights movement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-21 21:00:00" d="2019-08-21 22:00:00"><n u="New: The Art Of Architecture">New: The Art Of Architecture I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. A look at Ptolemy Dean's Weston Tower, which lies within Westminster Abbey. What went into designing the most significant addition to this historic site in 240 years?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-21 22:00:00" d="2019-08-21 23:30:00"><n>The Festival That Rocked The World</n>    <k>New. Exclusive interviews and footage tell the epic story of the 1969 Woodstock festival. In a time of civil unrest, half a million people united</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-21 23:30:00" d="2019-08-22 00:00:00"><n u="Santana: Music Icons">Santana: Music Icons II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Musician Carlos Santana became famous in the late 60s and early 70s with his band, Santana, which pioneered a fusion of rock and Latin American jazz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 00:00:00" d="2019-08-22 01:30:00"><n>New: Hamilton: One Shot To Broadway</n>    <k>New. Documentary film lifting the curtain on hip-hop musical sensation Hamilton, and the stars, story and history that brought it to life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 01:30:00" d="2019-08-22 03:15:00"><n>Joe Cocker: Mad Dog With Soul</n>    <k>Documentary charting the rise of Joe Cocker, a gas fitter who played in Sheffield pubs and was catapulted to stardom following a spectacular appearance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 03:15:00" d="2019-08-22 05:00:00"><n>Joan Baez: Live In New York</n>    <k>Joan Baez performs alongside music stars including David Crosby, Damien Rice and Paul Simon in a special concert at New York's Beacon Theatre</k>  </p>
</a>
