<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2019-08-15 22:50:45"><p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 05:00:00" d="2019-08-22 06:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Spencer Tracy">Discovering: Spencer Tracy II (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Profile of the Hollywood star famous for his 25-year love affair with Katharine Hepburn. Nominated for nine Oscars, his films included Boys Town and Captains Courageous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 06:00:00" d="2019-08-22 07:00:00"><n u="Discovering: James Mason">Discovering: James Mason II (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Film critics discuss the career of James Mason. After achieving success in the UK, he moved to Hollywood, where he starred in films such as North By Northwest and Lolita</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 07:00:00" d="2019-08-22 08:00:00"><n u="Maria Callas: Legends Of Opera">Maria Callas: Legends Of Opera I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. A look at the life and career of Maria Callas, who captivated audiences with her iconic opera performances in productions such as Tosca and Norma</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 08:00:00" d="2019-08-22 08:30:00"><n u="Auction">Auction III (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A one-million-pound note printed after World War II comes up for grabs, along with a familiar sculpture of Winston Churchill and President Roosevelt sitting on a bench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 08:30:00" d="2019-08-22 09:00:00"><n u="Watercolour Challenge">Watercolour Challenge I (29)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Competition in which budding artists are challenged to paint a scene in four hours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 09:00:00" d="2019-08-22 10:00:00"><n u="Master Of Photography">Master Of Photography IV (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Women In Power
For the final challenge, the judges have chosen three powerful women that contestants must visually represent as they battle it out to win the grand prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 10:00:00" d="2019-08-22 10:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Galloping Foxley
John Mills stars in this twisted tale. A man starts to suffer when he becomes haunted by the memory of the brutal treatment he received in his childhood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 10:30:00" d="2019-08-22 11:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Georgy Porgy
Joan Collins stars in a twisted tale. George has problems with female attention, but when a beautiful woman joins his congregation things are set to change</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 11:00:00" d="2019-08-22 12:00:00"><n u="Benjamin Clementine: South Bank Show">Benjamin Clementine: South Bank Show (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Melvyn Bragg meets Benjamin Clementine to discuss his rollercoaster ride from busking in Paris to becoming a world-renowned singer-songwriter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 12:00:00" d="2019-08-22 13:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Spencer Tracy">Discovering: Spencer Tracy II (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Profile of the Hollywood star famous for his 25-year love affair with Katharine Hepburn. Nominated for nine Oscars, his films included Boys Town and Captains Courageous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 13:00:00" d="2019-08-22 14:00:00"><n u="Discovering: James Mason">Discovering: James Mason II (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Film critics discuss the career of James Mason. After achieving success in the UK, he moved to Hollywood, where he starred in films such as North By Northwest and Lolita</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 14:00:00" d="2019-08-22 14:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Royal Jelly
Herbert Wise stars in this twisted tale. Mabel's baby is sick and her bee-obsessed husband thinks he has found a remedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 14:30:00" d="2019-08-22 15:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Poison
Andrew Ray stars in Roald Dahl's twisted tale. A poisonous snake keeps a teacher prisoner in India. How can he escape from its evil glare?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 15:00:00" d="2019-08-22 16:00:00"><n>Andre Rieu: Making The Magic</n>    <k>Andre Rieu performs his first ever concert in Bucharest and reveals the secrets behind his magical open air concerts, from the construction of the stage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 16:00:00" d="2019-08-22 17:00:00"><n>Elvis: The Final Hours</n>    <k>Documentary exploring the highs and lows of Elvis Presley's life, as told by the Memphis Mafia - a small group of Elvis's closest friends and confidants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 17:00:00" d="2019-08-22 18:00:00"><n>Sammy Davis Jr: Legends In Concert</n>    <k>A collection of the original Rat-Packer's most memorable stage appearances, including performances of The Birth of the Blues and You Rascal You</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 18:00:00" d="2019-08-22 19:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Marilyn Monroe">Discovering: Marilyn Monroe III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Film critics discuss the life and career of Golden Globe-winning actress Marilyn Monroe, who overcame a troubled childhood to become one of Hollywood's greatest icons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 19:00:00" d="2019-08-22 20:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Frank Sinatra">Discovering: Frank Sinatra III (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An intimate profile of Frank Sinatra, tracing his rise from New Jersey high school dropout to Grammy Award-winning singer and Academy Award-winning actor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 20:00:00" d="2019-08-22 21:00:00"><n u="The Seventies">The Seventies I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The State of the Union is Not Good
America goes from bad to worse as the country deals with one crisis after another throughout the Ford and Carter years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 21:00:00" d="2019-08-22 22:00:00"><n u="New: Robert Wise: The Directors">New: Robert Wise: The Directors III (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. A look at the life and career of the Academy Award-winning director behind The Sound of Music, West Side Story and Star Trek: The Motion Picture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 22:00:00" d="2019-08-22 23:00:00"><n>Ava Gardner: Alegria And Decadence</n>    <k>A look at the rise and fall of Ava Gardner, who turned her back on Hollywood's glamour and glitz in the 50s to move to Spain under Franco's totalitarian dictatorship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-22 23:00:00" d="2019-08-23 00:00:00"><n u="Battle Of The Brass Bands">Battle Of The Brass Bands (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. It's Brighouse and Rastrick vs Fairey Band as the series kicks off with two of the UK's biggest brass bands going head-to-head at The Whit Friday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-23 00:00:00" d="2019-08-23 01:00:00"><n>Josephine Baker: The Story of an Awakening</n>    <k>A look into the fascinating fifty-year career of Josephine Baker, who rose to become an icon and a humanist fighter from a journey plagued by racism and tragedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-23 01:00:00" d="2019-08-23 02:30:00"><n>The Festival That Rocked The World</n>    <k>New. Exclusive interviews and footage tell the epic story of the 1969 Woodstock festival. In a time of civil unrest, half a million people united</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-23 02:30:00" d="2019-08-23 03:45:00"><n>The Who: Sensation - The Story of Tommy</n>    <k>A look at the creation and impact of The Who's seminal album Tommy, featuring interviews with Pete Townshend, Roger Daltrey and the late John Entwistle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-23 03:45:00" d="2019-08-23 05:10:00"><n>The Who: Tommy Live At The Royal Albert Hall</n>    <k>The Who take to the stage at London's Royal Albert Hall to perform their rock opera Tommy live in its entirety for the first time in their long and illustrious career</k>  </p>
</a>
