<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-05-28 04:41:04"><p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-04 05:00:00" d="2020-06-04 06:00:00"><n u="George Cukor: The Directors">George Cukor: The Directors I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A fascinating look at the work of George Cukor, who was a dialogue director in the early days of films with sound, and received an Academy Award in 1964 for My Fair Lady</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-04 06:00:00" d="2020-06-04 06:30:00"><n u="Auction">Auction IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Raphael's Head of a Young Apostle breaks records at an auction at Sotheby's. A desk believed to have been made for Madame de Pompadour also goes under</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-04 06:30:00" d="2020-06-04 07:00:00"><n u="Auction">Auction IV (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A first edition of The Tale of Peter Rabbit stands to fetch ?20,000 in London. Plus, silverware made for the marriage of Titanic victim John Jacob Astor goes on sale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-04 07:00:00" d="2020-06-04 09:00:00"><n>Celtic Woman: Believe</n>    <k>The Irish all-female ensemble give a magical performance in America, featuring incredible visual effects and all their best-loved songs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-04 09:00:00" d="2020-06-04 10:00:00"><n>Rembrandt From The National Gallery, London, and The Rijksmuseum, Amsterdam</n>    <k>New. Film exploring Rembrandt's key works in exhibitions in both London and Amsterdam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-04 10:00:00" d="2020-06-04 10:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Who's Got The Lady?
When a piece of art is stolen, the gallery owner gets his girlfriend to make copies of it to sell. But did the work ever really leave the building?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-04 10:30:00" d="2020-06-04 11:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Skeleton Key
A woman discovers a nasty side to her husband's personality when he goes into hospital before a holiday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-04 11:00:00" d="2020-06-04 12:00:00"><n u="Landscape Artist Of The Year">Landscape Artist Of The Year 2016 II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Frank Skinner and Joan Bakewell search for a new star landscape artist as contestants capture National Trust properties across the country, starting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-04 12:00:00" d="2020-06-04 13:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Maggie Smith">Discovering: Maggie Smith X (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life of Academy Award-winning Maggie Smith. From Harry Potter to Downton Abbey, her huge portfolio makes her one of the UK's most recognisable actresses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-04 13:00:00" d="2020-06-04 14:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Ben Kingsley">Discovering: Ben Kingsley XI (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the Academy Award-winning actor, best known for his starring role in Gandhi. He has also appeared in films such as Shutter Island and Iron Man 3</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-04 14:00:00" d="2020-06-04 14:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected VI (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Passing Opportunity
Frank is struggling financially and will do anything for money. When he meets a rich and successful schoolmate, he realises</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-04 14:30:00" d="2020-06-04 15:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected VI (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Memory Man
Down on his luck, 'Memory Man' Colin agrees to help a shady character remember the number of a station locker. But then Colin becomes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-04 15:00:00" d="2020-06-04 16:00:00"><n u="Trailblazers: Funk">Trailblazers: Funk I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Noddy Holder narrates as the series takes a fascinating trip back to 1960s America to take a look at the evolution of funk music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-04 16:00:00" d="2020-06-04 17:00:00"><n u="Landscape Artist Of The Year">Landscape Artist Of The Year 2016 II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The competition continues as hosts Frank Skinner and Joan Bakewell welcome eight new artists and 50 wildcard entries to the stunning Wray Castle in Cumbria</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-04 17:00:00" d="2020-06-04 18:00:00"><n u="Master Of Photography">Master Of Photography III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>White Landscape
The photographers travel to the spectacular Trentino region of northern Italy, where they must capture the challenging whiteness of the mountains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-04 18:00:00" d="2020-06-04 19:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Helen Mirren">Discovering: Helen Mirren XI (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Acclaimed for her performance as Elizabeth II in The Queen, this is a glimpse into the world of the Academy Award-winning actress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-04 19:00:00" d="2020-06-04 20:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Vanessa Redgrave">Discovering: Vanessa Redgrave XI (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the British Academy Award-winning actress who has starred in a host of films including Julia, Mission: Impossible and Murder on the Orient Express</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-04 20:00:00" d="2020-06-04 21:00:00"><n>The Warner Saga</n>    <k>This eye-opening documentary by Clara and Julia Kuperberg tells the story of the Warner brothers, four sons of Polish immigrants who went on to take over Hollywood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-04 21:00:00" d="2020-06-04 22:00:00"><n u="The Great Film Composers: Music Of The Movies">The Great Film Composers: Music Of The Movies I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Birth of the Film Score
Venture back to the birth of soundtracks. Music scores were played live until the first fully-composed film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-04 22:00:00" d="2020-06-04 23:00:00"><n u="Brian Johnson &amp; Nick Mason">Brian Johnson &amp; Nick Mason I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Pink Floyd drummer Nick Mason gives Brian Johnson a tour of his car collection in the Cotswolds and reveals the secrets behind his band's elaborate live shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-04 23:00:00" d="2020-06-05 02:00:00"><n>Pink Floyd: Classic Albums The Dark Side Of The Moon</n>    <k>Prog rock icons Pink Floyd reflect on the creation of their hugely influential concept album, with rarely seen archive studio footage</k>  </p>
</a>
