<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2021-07-13 05:03:37"><p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 05:00:00" d="2021-07-20 05:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Best Of Everything
Desperate to win the affections of his boss's daughter, Arthur accepts the help of his friend Charlie. But is he ready to count the true cost of love?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 05:30:00" d="2021-07-20 06:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Woman's Help
Henpecked Arthur decides to get rid of his demanding wife once and for all, so long as he gets her money. Unfortunately, his</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 06:00:00" d="2021-07-20 07:00:00"><n u="The Art Of Architecture">The Art Of Architecture I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An in-depth look at Japanese architect Kengo Kuma's first UK project, the magnificent V&amp;A Dundee, including the huge challenges behind its construction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 07:00:00" d="2021-07-20 07:30:00"><n>Gilbert &amp; Sullivan: A Motley Pair</n>    <k>Simon Butteriss explores the success of The Mikado and the rewriting of Ruddigore, while hearing how a sceptical Jonathan Miller set about directing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 07:30:00" d="2021-07-20 08:00:00"><n u="Akram Khan: The South Bank Show Originals">Akram Khan: The South Bank Show Originals IV (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In a reflective look back at a classic episode of The South Bank Show, Melvyn Bragg reveals his admiration for pioneering British dancer Akram Khan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 08:00:00" d="2021-07-20 10:00:00"><n>Callas, Kennedy, Onassis: Two Queens For a King</n>    <k>The story of opera singer Maria Callas, multimillionaire Aristotle Onassis and First Lady Jacqueline Kennedy, who formed a scandalous love triangle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 10:00:00" d="2021-07-20 10:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Vicious Circle
When an elderly lady catches a burglar trying to rob her, she decides to help him go straight. But she has to take a different approach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 10:30:00" d="2021-07-20 11:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Boy Who Talked With Animals
When David rescues a giant turtle, it looks as though he's found a new friend. But there could be more to his pet than meets the eye</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 11:00:00" d="2021-07-20 12:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Judi Dench">Discovering: Judi Dench IX (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look back at the career of Judi Dench, who won an Oscar for her role as Queen Elizabeth in Shakespeare in Love before going on to star as M in eight James Bond movies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 12:00:00" d="2021-07-20 13:00:00"><n u="The Art Of Architecture">The Art Of Architecture I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at how Thomas Heatherwick's unusual and stunning design of many staircases became a mind-blowing tourist attraction in Manhattan, known as the Vessel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 13:00:00" d="2021-07-20 14:00:00"><n u="The Art Show">The Art Show I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Charming Baker examines Jason deCaires Taylor's underwater sculpture in Lanzarote, Sue Tilley explores the appeal of the nude and Will Best and Kate Bryan head to Istanbul</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 14:00:00" d="2021-07-20 14:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Best Of Everything
Desperate to win the affections of his boss's daughter, Arthur accepts the help of his friend Charlie. But is he ready to count the true cost of love?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 14:30:00" d="2021-07-20 15:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Woman's Help
Henpecked Arthur decides to get rid of his demanding wife once and for all, so long as he gets her money. Unfortunately, his</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 15:00:00" d="2021-07-20 16:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Bill Murray">Discovering: Bill Murray X (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at Bill Murray, famed for his BAFTA-winning performance in Lost in Translation, his collaborations with Wes Anderson and roles in Groundhog Day and Ghostbusters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 16:00:00" d="2021-07-20 17:00:00"><n>Muriel Spark By Ian Rankin</n>    <k>Ian Rankin lifts the lid on the life of famous author Murial Spark in a Sky original film examining the events that led her to become one of the great</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 17:00:00" d="2021-07-20 17:30:00"><n u="Music Icons: Singer Writes The Song">Music Icons: Singer Writes The Song IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Explore the shift into songwriting. Its emergence in the 1960s amid political change paved the way for great artists like Cat Stevens and James Taylor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 17:30:00" d="2021-07-20 18:00:00"><n u="Blur: Video Killed The Radio Star">Blur: Video Killed The Radio Star V (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the Britpop band's most famous videos, including Parklife, featuring Phil Daniels, Country House, directed by Damien Hirst, and Coffee &amp; TV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 18:00:00" d="2021-07-20 18:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Shatterproof
Ellen is trapped in a loveless marriage with her wealthy husband. But her plan to kill him backfires when the hitman she hires becomes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 18:30:00" d="2021-07-20 19:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sound Machine
Klausner is a botanist who has invented a machine that can translate the sounds of trees and plants into intelligible speech</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 19:00:00" d="2021-07-20 20:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Jean Simmons">Discovering: Jean Simmons X (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An inside look at the life and career of Emmy and Golden Globe-winning actress Jean Simmons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 20:00:00" d="2021-07-20 21:00:00"><n u="Leonardo: The Works">Leonardo: The Works (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A film marking the 500th anniversary of the world-famous artist's death, with a look at his vast collection of work including The Mona Lisa and The Last Supper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 21:00:00" d="2021-07-20 22:00:00"><n u="Master Of Photography">Master Of Photography III (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sanctuary
It's the final and the three remaining photographers attempt to capture the humanitarian side of the European refugee crisis, before the series winner is chosen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 22:00:00" d="2021-07-20 23:45:00"><n>Cold War Steve Meets The Outside World</n>    <k>Film following the acclaimed Birmingham-based artist, known for his controversial satirical collages, as he embarks on a UK-wide, outdoor art installation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2021-07-20 23:45:00" d="2021-07-21 02:45:00"><n>The Chewing Gum Man: A Portrait Of The Artist Ben Wilson</n>    <k>A intimate look at the creative process of Ben Wilson, who has been creating beautiful works of art on the chewing gum thrown away by Londoners</k>  </p>
</a>
