<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2019-08-10 01:42:49"><p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 05:10:00" d="2019-08-16 06:05:00"><n u="Discovering: Vivien Leigh">Discovering: Vivien Leigh II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the career of Vivien Leigh, who scooped an Oscar as Scarlett O'Hara, famously married star Laurence Olivier and died of tuberculosis aged 53</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 06:05:00" d="2019-08-16 07:00:00"><n u="Discovering: James Cagney">Discovering: James Cagney II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The story of the actor renowned for his roles in gangster films The Public Enemy and White Heat, whose battles with the Hollywood studios changed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 07:00:00" d="2019-08-16 08:00:00"><n u="Andre Rieu: Welcome To My World">Andre Rieu: Welcome To My World (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Maastricht My Hometown
Series exploring the world of Andre Rieu. With heart-warming interviews with Andre and magnificent performances</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 08:00:00" d="2019-08-16 08:30:00"><n u="Auction">Auction III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Memorabilia from the Space Race of the 1960s is being auctioned in New York, while over in London, author Jeffrey Archer is clearing out his art collection</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 08:30:00" d="2019-08-16 09:00:00"><n u="Watercolour Challenge">Watercolour Challenge I (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Competition in which budding artists are challenged to paint a scene in four hours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 09:00:00" d="2019-08-16 10:00:00"><n u="Master Of Photography">Master Of Photography IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Look-Alikes
Important questions around identity are raised as the contestants must produce two portraits of celebrity lookalikes while capturing their true essence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 10:00:00" d="2019-08-16 10:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Neck
A young lady is cut down to size by her husband's loyal butler when it is discovered she is having an affair</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 10:30:00" d="2019-08-16 11:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Edward the Conqueror
When Edward grows tired of his wife Louisa's obsession with a stray cat and decides to get rid of it, Louisa exacts her revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 11:00:00" d="2019-08-16 12:00:00"><n u="Why The Arts Matter: The South Bank Show">Why The Arts Matter: The South Bank Show (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Melvyn Bragg talks to Andria Zafirakou, a teacher at Alperton Community School and the 2018 Global Teacher Prize winner, about why the arts matter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 12:00:00" d="2019-08-16 13:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Vivien Leigh">Discovering: Vivien Leigh II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the career of Vivien Leigh, who scooped an Oscar as Scarlett O'Hara, famously married star Laurence Olivier and died of tuberculosis aged 53</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 13:00:00" d="2019-08-16 14:00:00"><n u="Discovering: James Cagney">Discovering: James Cagney II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The story of the actor renowned for his roles in gangster films The Public Enemy and White Heat, whose battles with the Hollywood studios changed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 14:00:00" d="2019-08-16 14:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Dip in the Pool
An American gambler must come up with a cunning plan to slow down a ship at sea in order to win a bet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 14:30:00" d="2019-08-16 15:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Way Up To Heaven
Mrs Foster exacts an intriguing revenge on her husband after his dawdling causes her to miss a flight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 15:00:00" d="2019-08-16 16:00:00"><n>Queen: Classic Albums</n>    <k>A Night At The Opera: It featured hits Bohemian Rhapsody and You're My Best Friend and propelled the band to superstardom. The story of how Queen created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 16:00:00" d="2019-08-16 17:00:00"><n>Discovering: Queen</n>    <k>Friends and fans of legendary British rock band Queen discuss their admiration for the award-winning quartet and reflect on their remarkable career and enduring hit songs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 17:00:00" d="2019-08-16 18:00:00"><n u="The Eighties">The Eighties I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The AIDS Crisis
A look at how the 1980s saw a mysterious and lethal illness known as AIDS develop into a pandemic with enormous political and cultural consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 18:00:00" d="2019-08-16 19:00:00"><n u="Discovering: John Wayne">Discovering: John Wayne II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An intimate look at the life and career of John Wayne. Born Marion Morrison, the former football player would become one of the most iconic actors of the 20th century</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 19:00:00" d="2019-08-16 20:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Charlton Heston">Discovering: Charlton Heston II (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Leading film critics discuss the career of Charlton Heston. After humble beginnings on stage, he took Hollywood by storm with starring in Ben-Hur and Planet of the Apes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 20:00:00" d="2019-08-16 21:00:00"><n>Elvis Presley: Classic Albums</n>    <k>Elvis Presley: Film revealing how the King created his seminal debut album. Sam Phillips, Keith Richards and BB King are among those discussing the album</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 21:00:00" d="2019-08-16 22:00:00"><n>Elvis And The Girl From Vienna</n>    <k>Trude Forsher was one of Elvis Presley's most trusted confidants in the 50s and this is her account of the King's rise to fame and the most iconic moments in his life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 22:00:00" d="2019-08-16 23:00:00"><n>Elvis: The Final Hours</n>    <k>Documentary exploring the highs and lows of Elvis Presley's life, as told by the Memphis Mafia - a small group of Elvis's closest friends and confidants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-16 23:00:00" d="2019-08-17 00:45:00"><n>The Seven Ages Of Elvis</n>    <k>Forty years on from his death, this entertaining documentary looks at the legacy of Elvis Presley through the lens of seven iconic stages of his life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-17 00:45:00" d="2019-08-17 02:00:00"><n>Elvis '56 Special</n>    <k>Documentary capturing the sights and sounds of the pivotal year in Elvis's journey to become the King of Rock 'n' Roll. Features rare footage, photos and recordings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-17 02:00:00" d="2019-08-17 03:00:00"><n>Elvis Presley: A Legend in Concert</n>    <k>Sensational collection of TV performances from The King. Featuring the notorious screen debut of his famous pelvic gyrations and the time Steve Allen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2019-08-17 03:00:00" d="2019-08-17 05:00:00"><n>The Big Beat: Fats Domino and The Birth of Rock n Roll</n>    <k>This documentary traces how Fats Domino, who passed away in October 2017, paved the way for rock'n'roll with his own brand of New Orleans rhythm and blues</k>  </p>
</a>
