<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-05-27 04:35:58"><p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-03 05:00:00" d="2020-06-03 06:00:00"><n u="Cecil B. DeMille: The Directors">Cecil B. DeMille: The Directors I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the films of Cecil B DeMille, the director who became a giant of the 20th-century film industry, known for epics such as The Ten Commandments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-03 06:00:00" d="2020-06-03 06:30:00"><n u="Auction">Auction IV (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Works by Winston Churchill and LS Lowry go under the hammer in a modern British art sale in London. Petrol-heads gather in Goodwood for a prestigious</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-03 06:30:00" d="2020-06-03 07:00:00"><n u="Auction">Auction IV (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A desk made by famous furniture-maker John Townsend goes under the hammer in New York. Plus, two illuminated manuscripts from the Middle Ages go up for auction in London</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-03 07:00:00" d="2020-06-03 08:45:00"><n>LSO: Sir John Eliot Gardiner Conducts Mendelssohn</n>    <k>Sir John Eliot Gardiner conducts the London Symphony Orchestra and the Monteverdi Choir in this celebration of Felix Mendelssohn's work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-03 08:45:00" d="2020-06-03 10:00:00"><n>Bob Fosse: It's Showtime</n>    <k>A look at the life of Oscar and Emmy-winning film and dance legend Bob Fosse, with insights from the people he inspired throughout his career</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-03 10:00:00" d="2020-06-03 10:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In The Bag
Cara hires safecracker Sam to get back her confiscated jewels. But when she insists on joining him on the job, Sam could be making the biggest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-03 10:30:00" d="2020-06-03 11:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Man With A Fortune
A rich and lonely American ventures to England in search of his long-lost family. But when he meets Jane and her flatmate Eva, things begin to go wrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-03 11:00:00" d="2020-06-03 12:00:00"><n u="The Adventurers Of Modern Art">The Adventurers Of Modern Art I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Midnight in Paris
Paris reawakens from World War II to find that an astonishing work has been created from within its war-torn midst - the film Les Enfants du Paradis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-03 12:00:00" d="2020-06-03 13:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Robert De Niro">Discovering: Robert De Niro X (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life of legendary two-time Academy Award winner Robert De Niro, star of The Godfather Part II, Taxi Driver and Goodfellas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-03 13:00:00" d="2020-06-03 14:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Alain Delon">Discovering: Alain Delon X (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Alain Delon
A glimpse into the life of French star and winner of the 2019 Honorary Palme d'Or, Alain Delon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-03 14:00:00" d="2020-06-03 14:30:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Who's Got The Lady?
When a piece of art is stolen, the gallery owner gets his girlfriend to make copies of it to sell. But did the work ever really leave the building?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-03 14:30:00" d="2020-06-03 15:00:00"><n u="Tales Of The Unexpected">Tales Of The Unexpected V (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Skeleton Key
A woman discovers a nasty side to her husband's personality when he goes into hospital before a holiday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-03 15:00:00" d="2020-06-03 16:00:00"><n u="Trailblazers: Two Tone">Trailblazers: Two Tone I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Narrated by Noddy Holder, the eye-opening series examining the key moments that have shaped musical history turns its attention to Two Tone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-03 16:00:00" d="2020-06-03 17:00:00"><n u="Landscape Artist Of The Year">Landscape Artist Of The Year 2016 II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Frank Skinner and Joan Bakewell search for a new star landscape artist as contestants capture National Trust properties across the country, starting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-03 17:00:00" d="2020-06-03 18:00:00"><n u="Master Of Photography">Master Of Photography III (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Pets and Friends
This week the photographers head to Rome where they are challenged to capture the special bond between pets and their owners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-03 18:00:00" d="2020-06-03 19:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Maggie Smith">Discovering: Maggie Smith X (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life of Academy Award-winning Maggie Smith. From Harry Potter to Downton Abbey, her huge portfolio makes her one of the UK's most recognisable actresses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-03 19:00:00" d="2020-06-03 20:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Ben Kingsley">Discovering: Ben Kingsley XI (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the Academy Award-winning actor, best known for his starring role in Gandhi. He has also appeared in films such as Shutter Island and Iron Man 3</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-03 20:00:00" d="2020-06-03 21:00:00"><n u="The Adventurers Of Modern Art">The Adventurers Of Modern Art I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Midnight in Paris
Paris reawakens from World War II to find that an astonishing work has been created from within its war-torn midst - the film Les Enfants du Paradis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-03 21:00:00" d="2020-06-03 22:00:00"><n>Marcel Duchamp: The Art Of The Possible</n>    <k>New. Film exploring one of the 20th century's most influential modernists and how his revolutionary ideas and philosophies changed the way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-03 22:00:00" d="2020-06-03 23:00:00"><n u="The History Of Comedy">The History Of Comedy I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ripped From the Headlines
An engaging and entertaining look at the origins of topical humour, from the rise of the monologue to the 'fake news' shows of today</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1050" o="2020-06-03 23:00:00" d="2020-06-04 02:00:00"><n u="Comedy Legends: Bob Hope">Comedy Legends: Bob Hope I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Barry Cryer reflects on the life and career of British-born American entertainer Bob Hope, whose remarkable comedy and acting career spanned nearly 80 years</k>  </p>
</a>
