<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="31" t="2020-04-11 04:28:21"><p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 05:00:00" d="2020-04-18 06:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Australia 2004</n>    <k>We revisit the 2004 Australian Grand Prix at Phillip Island. After a tense battle with Sete Gibernau, Valentino Rossi became the first rider</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 06:00:00" d="2020-04-18 07:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Brno 2004</n>    <k>We revisit the 2004 Czech Republic Grand Prix at Brno as Valentino Rossi, Sete Gibernau and Max Biaggi continued their enthralling and unpredictable</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 07:00:00" d="2020-04-18 08:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1974/75</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 30th March 1975, features Arsenal v Stoke, Ipswich v Leicester and Carlisle v Everton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 08:00:00" d="2020-04-18 09:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1974/75</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 20th April 1975, features Tottenham v Chelsea, Norwich v Nottingham Forest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 09:00:00" d="2020-04-18 10:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1974/75</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 27th April 1975, features Arsenal v Tottenham, Portsmouth v Norwich and Luton v Man City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 10:00:00" d="2020-04-18 10:30:00"><n>FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Shrewsbury v Everton 2003</n>    <k>We revisit the 2003 FA Cup third round tie at Gay Meadow between Shrewsbury and Everton. The Shrews, 80 places below the visitors, were managed by Kevin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 10:30:00" d="2020-04-18 11:00:00"><n>FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Luton v Liverpool 2006</n>    <k>We revisit the extraordinary 2006 FA Cup third round tie between Luton and Liverpool at Kenilworth Road. The game featured eight goals, including a 60-yard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 11:00:00" d="2020-04-18 11:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Arsenal v Slavia Prague 2007/08</n>    <k>We revisit the entertaining 2007/08 UEFA Champions League group stage tie between Arsenal and Slavia Prague at the Emirates. The Gunners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 11:30:00" d="2020-04-18 12:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Man Utd v Barcelona 2007/08</n>    <k>We revisit the 2007/08 UEFA Champions League semi-final second leg between Man Utd and Barcelona at Old Trafford. The tie was delicately poised after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 12:00:00" d="2020-04-18 12:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Roma v Arsenal 2008/09</n>    <k>We revisit the 2008/09 UEFA Champions League last 16 second leg between Roma and Arsenal at the Stadio Olimpico. Robin van Persie's goal had given</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 12:30:00" d="2020-04-18 13:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Chelsea v Liverpool 2008/09</n>    <k>We revisit the 2008/09 UEFA Champions League quarter-final second leg between Chelsea and Liverpool at Stamford Bridge. Chelsea were impressive 3-1 first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 13:00:00" d="2020-04-18 14:00:00"><n>WRC Classic: WRC Classic: 2005 Season Review</n>    <k>A look back at the 2005 World Rally Championship. A brutal 16-round season, dominated by Sebastien Loeb, was ultimately marred by tragedy at the Wales Rally GB</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 14:00:00" d="2020-04-18 15:00:00"><n>WRC Classic: WRC Classic: Top 10 Crashes</n>    <k>A countdown of the top ten most spectacular crashes in the history of the World Rally Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 15:00:00" d="2020-04-18 15:30:00"><n>Classic Premiership Rugby: Premiership Rugby Top Tries 15/16</n>    <k>The top tries of the 2015/16 Aviva Premiership campaign</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 15:30:00" d="2020-04-18 16:00:00"><n>Classic Premiership Rugby: Premiership Rugby Top Tries 17/18</n>    <k>The pick of the tries from the 2017/18 Aviva Premiership season. Including, Billy Twelvetrees score for Gloucester against Worcester and Sinoti Sinoti's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 16:00:00" d="2020-04-18 16:30:00"><n>Gallagher Premiership Rugby Union: Premiership Rugby Top Tries 18/19</n>    <k>The pick of the tries from the 2018/19 Gallagher Premiership season. Plus, interviews with Exeter Chiefs duo Henry Slade and Santiago Cordero</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 16:30:00" d="2020-04-18 17:30:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: ODI Cricket Classic: Aus v SL">Cricket Classics: ODI Cricket Classic: Aus v SL 1989</n>    <k>A look back at the first match of the 1989/90 World Series Cup between Australia and Sri Lanka in Melbourne</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 17:30:00" d="2020-04-18 18:30:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v SL">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v SL 1989</n>    <k>We revisit the 2nd match of the 1989/90 World Series Cup between Australia and Sri Lanka at the WACA</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 18:30:00" d="2020-04-18 19:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Chelsea v Arsenal 2018/19</n>    <k>Look back as Chelsea met Arsenal in a highly-entertaining 2018/19 Premier League game at Stamford Bridge. A late Marcos Alonso strike settled a chaotic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 19:00:00" d="2020-04-18 19:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Brighton v Man United 2018/19</n>    <k>Look back as Brighton recorded their first win of the 2018/19 season after an entertaining encounter against Jose Mourinho's Manchester United side at the Amex Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 19:30:00" d="2020-04-18 20:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Wolves v Leicester City 2018/19</n>    <k>Take a look back at some classic Premier League action from the 2018/19 season as Wolves and Leicester played out a seven-goal thriller at Molineux Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 20:00:00" d="2020-04-18 20:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Wolfsburg v Man Utd 2009/10</n>    <k>We revisit the 2009/10 UEFA Champions League group stage clash between Wolfsburg and Manchester United at the Volkswagen Arena. Victory for the United</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 20:30:00" d="2020-04-18 21:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Newcastle v Leverkusen 2002/03</n>    <k>We revisit the 2002/03 UEFA Champions League group stage tie between Newcastle and Leverkusen at St James' Park. Alan Shearer was without</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 21:00:00" d="2020-04-18 21:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: PSG v Barcelona 2014/15</n>    <k>We revisit the 2014/15 UEFA Champions League quarter-final first leg between PSG and Barcelona at the Parc des Princes. PSG had been unbeaten</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 21:30:00" d="2020-04-18 22:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Barcelona v Bayern Munich 2014/15</n>    <k>We revisit the 2014/15 UEFA Champions League semi-final first leg between Barcelona and Bayern Munich, Josep Guardiola's first match at the Nou Camp since leaving the club</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 22:00:00" d="2020-04-19 01:00:00"><n>UFC: UFC: Viewer's Choice</n>    <k>BT Sport viewers can vote for which historic UFC card they want to watch by voting on today's poll at BT Sport's UFC Twitter page</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 01:00:00" d="2020-04-19 01:30:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing</n>    <k>Mike Tyson's Greatest Hits Vol 1. A selection of Mike Tyson's greatest fights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 01:30:00" d="2020-04-19 02:30:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing</n>    <k>Mike Tyson was pound for pound the most dominant boxer during the 1980's. Watch Tyson at his best as he beat opponent after opponent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 02:30:00" d="2020-04-19 03:30:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing</n>    <k>Tyson Raw &amp; Uncut looks at Mike Tyson's unprecedented rise to the pinnacle of world boxing. This episode features his 1986 bout against James Tillis in New York</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 03:30:00" d="2020-04-19 04:00:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing</n>    <k>We revisit the classic 1986 bout between Mike Tyson and Trevor Berbick at the Hilton Hotel in Las Vegas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 04:00:00" d="2020-04-19 05:00:00"><n>WRC Classic: WRC Classic: 2006 Season Review</n>    <k>A look back at the 2006 World Rally Championship. This season was regarded as one of the toughest, with back-to-back rounds in Spain and Corsica</k>  </p>
</a>
