<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2020-05-27 04:31:33"><p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 05:00:00" d="2020-06-03 05:30:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v SA">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v SA 1994</n>    <k>We revisit day four of the 1994 second test series between Australia and South Africa at the Sydney Cricket Ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 05:30:00" d="2020-06-03 06:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v SA">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v SA 1994</n>    <k>We revisit day five of the 1994 second test series between Australia and South Africa at the Sydney Cricket Ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 06:00:00" d="2020-06-03 07:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: ODI Classic Cricket: Aus v NZ">Cricket Classics: ODI Classic Cricket: Aus v NZ 1981</n>    <k>A look back at the 12th match of the 1980/81 World Series Cup between Australia and New Zealand at the Sydney Cricket Ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 07:00:00" d="2020-06-03 08:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1978/79</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 15th April 1979, features Tottenham v QPR, Derby v Nottingham Forest and Leeds v Aston Villa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 08:00:00" d="2020-06-03 09:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1978/79</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 22nd April 1979, features Bolton v Ipswich and West Brom v Wolves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 09:00:00" d="2020-06-03 10:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1978/79</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 29th April 1979, features Crystal Palace v Notts County, Brighton v Blackburn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 10:00:00" d="2020-06-03 11:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1978/79</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 6th May 1979, features Wrexham v Sunderland and Newcastle v Brighton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 11:00:00" d="2020-06-03 11:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Arsenal v Leicester City 2017/18</n>    <k>Take a look back as late drama helped Arsenal fight back to beat Leicester City in a thrilling start to the 2017-18 Premier League season at the Emirates Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 11:30:00" d="2020-06-03 12:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Newcastle v Liverpool 2018/19</n>    <k>Take a look back as title-chasing Liverpool visited Newcastle in the Premier League. Divock Origi's late winner ensured the title race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 12:00:00" d="2020-06-03 12:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Man City v Liverpool 2018/19</n>    <k>Look back to the 2018/19 Premier League season as Manchester City produced a stunning display at the Etihad Stadium against title rivals Liverpool to close</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 12:30:00" d="2020-06-03 13:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Man City v Crystal Palace 2018/19</n>    <k>Relive Man City's Premier League tie with Crystal Palace. Andros Townsend scored one of the goals of the season as Palace claimed their first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 13:00:00" d="2020-06-03 13:30:00"><n u="FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Wrexham v Arsenal">FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Wrexham v Arsenal 1978</n>    <k>We revisit the 1978 FA Cup sixth round tie between Wrexham and Arsenal at the Racecourse Ground. Wrexham had already caused a huge upset by beating</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 13:30:00" d="2020-06-03 14:00:00"><n u="FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Charlton v Ipswich">FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Charlton v Ipswich 1983</n>    <k>We revisit the 1983 FA Cup third round match between Second Division Charlton and Ipswich at the Valley. This five-goal thriller is regarded</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 14:00:00" d="2020-06-03 15:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season: Montpellier v Monaco 2015/16</n>    <k>All the action from that classic five-goal spectacular between Montpellier and Monaco back at the start of the 2015/16 French Ligue 1 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 15:00:00" d="2020-06-03 16:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Eng">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Eng 1987</n>    <k>We revisit the seventh match of the 1986/87 World Series between Australia and England at the Adelaide Oval</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 16:00:00" d="2020-06-03 17:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Le Mans 2008</n>    <k>We revisit the 2008 French Grand Prix at Le Mans which saw a rain-affected race dominated by the Yamaha trio of Valentino Rossi, Jorge Lorenzo and Colin Edwards</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 17:00:00" d="2020-06-03 18:00:00"><n>UEFA Europa League: E Frankfurt v Benfica 2018/19</n>    <k>Eintracht Frankfurt met Benfica in the 2018/19 Europa League quarter-finals. A pulsating first leg saw a Joao Felix hat-trick inspire the visitors</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 18:00:00" d="2020-06-03 19:00:00"><n>UEFA Europa League: Arsenal v Valencia 2018/19</n>    <k>Relive Arsenal's 2018/19 Europa League semi-final home tie with Valencia. Arsenal hoped to avoid a repeat of last year, when they were eliminated at this stage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 19:00:00" d="2020-06-03 19:30:00"><n>Classic Ligue 1: Lyon v Marseille 2009/10</n>    <k>All the action from that incredible 10-goal thriller between Lyon and Marseille back in the 2009/10 Ligue 1 season, as the visitors won the title</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 19:30:00" d="2020-06-03 20:00:00"><n>Classic Ligue 1: Marseille v Lille 2010/11</n>    <k>A look back at the action from that crucial clash between the top two in the French Ligue 1 division as Marseille hosted eventual champions Lille in the 2010/11 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 20:00:00" d="2020-06-03 22:00:00"><n>BT Sport Fight Night: Fight Night: Conlan v Dos Santos</n>    <k>Rising Irish boxing star Michael Conlan takes on Brazil's Adeilson Dos Santos in a mouth-watering fight in front of his home crowd at the SSE Arena in Belfast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 22:00:00" d="2020-06-03 23:00:00"><n>UFC Countdown</n>    <k>Counting down to UFC 250</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 23:00:00" d="2020-06-04 02:00:00"><n>UFC</n>    <k>Action from the UFC</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 02:00:00" d="2020-06-04 03:00:00"><n u="UFC Main Event: UFC: Namajunas v Joanna">UFC Main Event: UFC: Namajunas v Joanna II</n>    <k>We revisit the enthralling strawweight title rematch between Rose Namajunas and Joanna Jedrzejczyk at UFC 223 in Brooklyn, New York</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 03:00:00" d="2020-06-04 04:00:00"><n u="UFC: The Ultimate Fighter: UFC The Ultimate Fighter - Series">UFC: The Ultimate Fighter: UFC The Ultimate Fighter - Series 22</n>    <k>Episode 3. The 22nd series of the Ultimate Fighter sees a United States team, coached by veteran Urijah Faber, take on a European team, headed up by Irish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 04:00:00" d="2020-06-04 05:00:00"><n>Hyundai A-League Highlights</n>    <k>A review of all the goals and talking points from round three of the 2019/20 Hyundai A-League, Australia's top football division</k>  </p>
</a>
