<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2020-04-12 04:27:05"><p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 05:00:00" d="2020-04-19 06:00:00"><n>WRC Classic</n>    <k>A look back at some of the craziest moments from the 2007 season of the World Rally Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 06:00:00" d="2020-04-19 06:30:00"><n>Classic Premiership Rugby: Premiership Rugby Top Tries 15/16</n>    <k>The top tries of the 2015/16 Aviva Premiership campaign</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 06:30:00" d="2020-04-19 07:00:00"><n>Classic Premiership Rugby: Premiership Rugby Top Tries 17/18</n>    <k>The pick of the tries from the 2017/18 Aviva Premiership season. Including, Billy Twelvetrees score for Gloucester against Worcester and Sinoti Sinoti's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 07:00:00" d="2020-04-19 08:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1978/79</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 31st December 1978, features Manchester United v West Brom, Arsenal v Birmingham</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 08:00:00" d="2020-04-19 09:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1978/79</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 7th January 1979, features Sheffield Wednesday v Arsenal and Stoke City v Oldham</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 09:00:00" d="2020-04-19 09:30:00"><n u="FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Arsenal v Millwall">FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Arsenal v Millwall 1995</n>    <k>We revisit the 1995 FA Cup third round replay between Arsenal and Millwall at Highbury. The Gunners were keen to avoid a second straight Cup upset against</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 09:30:00" d="2020-04-19 10:00:00"><n u="FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: C.Palace v Chelsea">FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: C.Palace v Chelsea 1971</n>    <k>We revisit the gripping 1971 FA Cup third round tie between Crystal Palace and Chelsea at Selhurst Park. Some players opted for basketball trainers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 10:00:00" d="2020-04-19 10:30:00"><n u="FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Everton v Liverpool">FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Everton v Liverpool 1981</n>    <k>We revisit the epic 1981 FA Cup fourth round tie between rivals Everton and Liverpool at Goodison Park. Bob Paisley's all-conquering Reds were chasing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 10:30:00" d="2020-04-19 11:00:00"><n u="FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Grimsby v Arsenal">FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Grimsby v Arsenal 1986</n>    <k>We revisit the thrilling 1986 FA Cup third round tie between Grimsby and Arsenal at Blundell Park. Arsenal's side featured youngsters Niall Quinn, Martin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 11:00:00" d="2020-04-19 12:00:00"><n>Bundesliga: Games of the Season: Mainz v Hoffenheim 2016/17</n>    <k>We revisit 2016/17's extraordinary clash between Mainz and Hoffenheim at the Opel Arena. This astonishing match had it all: eight goals, a sending</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 12:00:00" d="2020-04-19 13:00:00"><n>Bundesliga: Games of the Season: E Frankfurt v Hertha B 2016/17</n>    <k>We revisit 2016/17's thriller at the Commerzbank-Arena between Eintracht Frankfurt and Hertha Berlin. This incident-packed epic featured a last-gasp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 13:00:00" d="2020-04-19 14:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season: Dijon v Lyon 2016/17</n>    <k>We revisit 2016/17's thriller between Dijon and Lyon at the Stade Gaston Gerard. Lyon's Alexandre Lacazette, linked with Arsenal, had already netted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 14:00:00" d="2020-04-19 15:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season: Metz v PSG 2016/17</n>    <k>We revisit the 2016/17 Ligue 1 clash between Metz and Paris Saint-Germain at the Stade Saint-Symphorien. PSG desperately needed points to maintain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 15:00:00" d="2020-04-19 16:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League</n>    <k>A look back at a classic Premier League clash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 16:00:00" d="2020-04-19 17:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League</n>    <k>A look back at a classic Premier League clash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 17:00:00" d="2020-04-19 18:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Sachsenring 2003</n>    <k>We revisit the 2003 German Grand Prix at the Sachsenring. Sete Gibernau outfoxed double world champion Valentino Rossi to win his fourth race of the season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 18:00:00" d="2020-04-19 19:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Le Mans 2003</n>    <k>We revisit the dramatic 2003 French Grand Prix at Le Mans, featuring one of the first titanic battles between world champion Valentino Rossi and Spaniard Sete Gibernau</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 19:00:00" d="2020-04-19 20:30:00"><n>European Rugby - Top Ten Games of the Season: Euro Rugby: Games of the Season: 2017</n>    <k>We revisit April's gripping European Champions Cup semi-final between Munster and Saracens at Thomond Park. Saracens were aiming to reach a third Champions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 20:30:00" d="2020-04-19 22:00:00"><n>European Rugby - Top Ten Games of the Season: Euro Rugby: Games of the Season: 2017</n>    <k>We revisit the pulsating European Champions Cup final between Clermont Auvergne and Saracens at BT Murrayfield. Saracens, unbeaten in 17 games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-19 22:00:00" d="2020-04-20 01:00:00"><n>UFC: UFC 249 - Ferguson v Gaethje</n>    <k>Action from UFC 249 as Tony Ferguson and Justin Gaethje meet in the Octagon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-20 01:00:00" d="2020-04-20 02:00:00"><n>Football Classics: Liverpool: Team of the Seventies</n>    <k>A look back at some of the best players, goals and matches from Liverpool's golden era, as the Shankly and Paisley glory years are revisited. 1/2</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-20 02:00:00" d="2020-04-20 03:00:00"><n>Football Classics: Liverpool: Team of the Seventies</n>    <k>A look back at some of the best players, goals and matches from Liverpool's golden era, as the Shankly and Paisley glory years are revisited. 2/2</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-20 03:00:00" d="2020-04-20 04:30:00"><n>Heineken Champions Cup: Leinster v Saracens 2018/19</n>    <k>Relive the 2018/19 Heineken Champions Cup final between Saracens, hoping to win the cup for a third time in four years, and a Leinster side aiming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-20 04:30:00" d="2020-04-20 05:00:00"><n>Heineken Champions Cup: Story of the Champions Cup 18/19</n>    <k>A look back at the most memorable moments from the 2018/19 campaign as Mark McCall's Saracens beat defending champions Leinster to win their third European</k>  </p>
</a>
