<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2020-06-01 04:24:44"><p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 05:00:00" d="2020-06-08 06:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Pak">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Pak 1984</n>    <k>We revisit the fifth match of the 1983/84 World Series Cup between Australia and Pakistan at the Brisbane Cricket Ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 06:00:00" d="2020-06-08 07:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Pak">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Pak 1984</n>    <k>We revisit the 13th match of the 1983/84 World Series Cup between Australia and Pakistan at the Adelaide Oval</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 07:00:00" d="2020-06-08 08:00:00"><n>Football Classics: Liverpool: Team of the Seventies</n>    <k>A look back at some of the best players, goals and matches from Liverpool's golden era, as the Shankly and Paisley glory years are revisited. 1/2</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 08:00:00" d="2020-06-08 09:00:00"><n>Football Classics: Arsenal Classics</n>    <k>Classic Arsenal matches from the football archives, featuring memorable league clashes with Manchester United (1973) and Liverpool (1975). 1/8</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 09:00:00" d="2020-06-08 10:00:00"><n>Football Classics: Chelsea Classics</n>    <k>Classic Chelsea matches from the football archives, featuring memorable league clashes against Manchester City (1972) and Liverpool (1991). 1/8</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 10:00:00" d="2020-06-08 11:00:00"><n>Football Classics: Manchester United Classics</n>    <k>Classic Manchester United matches from the football archives, featuring memorable First Division clashes with Stoke City (1971), Chelsea (1984)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 11:00:00" d="2020-06-08 12:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Premier League Review: 2014/15</n>    <k>A review of the 2014/15 season. Eden Hazard's superb form helped Chelsea clinch their fifth title and newly-promoted Burnley and QPR made immediate returns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 12:00:00" d="2020-06-08 13:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Premier League: Best Goals 2014/15</n>    <k>A look back at the most memorable goals from the 2014/15 season. Sergio Aguero won the Golden Boot with 26 goals, five ahead of Harry Kane and six in front of Diego Costa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 13:00:00" d="2020-06-08 13:30:00"><n u="FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Tottenham v Arsenal">FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Tottenham v Arsenal 1991</n>    <k>We revisit the thrilling 1991 FA Cup semi-final tie between fierce rivals Tottenham and Arsenal. This was the first time that an FA Cup semi-final</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 13:30:00" d="2020-06-08 14:00:00"><n u="FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Liverpool v B'ham">FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Liverpool v B'ham 1995</n>    <k>We revisit the dramatic 1995 FA Cup third round replay between Liverpool and Birmingham at Anfield. Second Division leaders Birmingham held</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 14:00:00" d="2020-06-08 15:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season: PSG v Saint-Etienne 2015/16</n>    <k>We revisit the 2015/16 clash between Paris Saint-Germain and Saint-Etienne at the Parc des Princes. The reigning champions were undefeated in 23 matches</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 15:00:00" d="2020-06-08 16:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Eng">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Eng 1987</n>    <k>We revisit the second final of the 1986/87 World Series between Australia and England at the Sydney Cricket Ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 16:00:00" d="2020-06-08 17:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Assen 2007</n>    <k>We revisit the memorable 2007 Dutch Grand Prix at Assen. Valentino Rossi won after a stunning comeback from 11th while reigning champion Nicky Hayden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 17:00:00" d="2020-06-08 18:30:00"><n>Classic Rugby Revisited: Harlequins v Stade Francais 2011</n>    <k>BT Sport's Ugo Monye looks back at the 2011 European Challenge Cup Final between his Harlequins side and Stade Francais</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 18:30:00" d="2020-06-08 19:00:00"><n u="FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Chelsea v M'boro">FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Chelsea v M'boro 1997</n>    <k>We revisit the 1997 FA Cup final between Chelsea and Middlesbrough. Chelsea, managed by Ruud Gullit, went in to the match hoping to win their first major trophy in 27 years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 19:00:00" d="2020-06-08 19:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Manchester United v Porto 1996/97</n>    <k>The first leg of the 1996/97 UEFA Champions League quarter-final saw Manchester United, featuring Eric Cantona, in what proved to be his final season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 19:30:00" d="2020-06-08 20:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics</n>    <k>We revisit the 1996/97 UEFA Champions League final between Borussia Dortmund and Juventus in Munich. Armed with an expensively assembled squad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 20:00:00" d="2020-06-08 22:00:00"><n>BT Sport Fight Night: Fight Night: Yarde v Sequeira 2018</n>    <k>Anthony Yarde takes on Walter Gabriel Sequeira in a light heavyweight bout in Brentwood, Essex. The British welterweight title is also at stake for Johnny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 22:00:00" d="2020-06-08 23:00:00"><n>Fishing: On The Bank: Fishing: On The Bank - 2016</n>    <k>A look back at the 2016 FIPS World Feeder Fishing Championship from Serbia where England secured a well deserved silver medal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 23:00:00" d="2020-06-08 23:30:00"><n u="Dan Hardy's Open Mat: Dan Hardy's Open Mat: UFC">Dan Hardy's Open Mat: Dan Hardy's Open Mat: UFC 250</n>    <k>UFC commentator and leading analyst Dan Hardy is joined by some of the biggest names in the sport to look ahead to UFC 250</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 23:30:00" d="2020-06-09 02:30:00"><n>UFC: UFC 250 - Nunes v Spencer</n>    <k>Action from UFC 250 as Amanda Nunes and Felicia Spencer headline the card</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-09 02:30:00" d="2020-06-09 03:30:00"><n u="UFC: The Ultimate Fighter: UFC The Ultimate Fighter - Series">UFC: The Ultimate Fighter: UFC The Ultimate Fighter - Series 22</n>    <k>Episode 7. The 22nd series of the Ultimate Fighter sees a United States team, coached by veteran Urijah Faber, take on a European team, headed up by Irish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-09 03:30:00" d="2020-06-09 04:00:00"><n>UFC Ultimate Knockouts</n>    <k>A look at some of the most devastating finishes ever seen inside the octagon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-09 04:00:00" d="2020-06-09 05:00:00"><n>Hyundai A-League Highlights</n>    <k>A review of all the goals and talking points from round six of the 2019/20 Hyundai A-League season</k>  </p>
</a>
