<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-04-16 04:28:59"><p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-23 05:00:00" d="2020-04-23 06:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Suzuka 2001</n>    <k>We revisit the 2001 Japan Grand Prix at the Suzuka Circuit. After a promising yet crash-marred debut season in the 500cc class, Valentino Rossi began</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-23 06:00:00" d="2020-04-23 07:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Valencia 2001</n>    <k>We revisit the 2001 Valencia Grand Prix at the Circuit Ricardo Tormo. Spaniard Sete Gibernau took his first win in the premier class, ahead of Alex Barros</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-23 07:00:00" d="2020-04-23 08:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1978/79</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 7th April 1979, features Leyton Orient v Brighton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-23 08:00:00" d="2020-04-23 09:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1978/79</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 15th April 1979, features Tottenham v QPR, Derby v Nottingham Forest and Leeds v Aston Villa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-23 09:00:00" d="2020-04-23 10:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1978/79</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 22nd April 1979, features Bolton v Ipswich and West Brom v Wolves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-23 10:00:00" d="2020-04-23 11:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1978/79</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 29th April 1979, features Crystal Palace v Notts County, Brighton v Blackburn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-23 11:00:00" d="2020-04-23 12:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League</n>    <k>A look back at a classic Premier League clash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-23 12:00:00" d="2020-04-23 13:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League</n>    <k>A look back at a classic Premier League clash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-23 13:00:00" d="2020-04-23 14:00:00"><n>Bundesliga: Games of the Season: Hoffenheim v Gladbach 2015/16</n>    <k>We revisit the 2015/16 Bundesliga clash between Hoffenheim and Borussia Monchengladbach at the Rhein-Necker Arena</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-23 14:00:00" d="2020-04-23 15:00:00"><n>Bundesliga: Games of the Season</n>    <k>Unbeaten in nine matches under Andre Schubert, Monchengladbach were bidding to become the first team to beat Bayern in the Bundesliga this season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-23 15:00:00" d="2020-04-23 16:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season</n>    <k>We revisit the November clash between Paris Saint-Germain and Toulouse at the Parc des Princes. Reigning champions PSG were looking to extend their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-23 16:00:00" d="2020-04-23 17:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season</n>    <k>We revisit the November clash between Lyon and Montpellier at the Stade de Gerland. Lyon went into the game 13 points behind leaders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-23 17:00:00" d="2020-04-23 18:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Eng">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Eng 1990</n>    <k>We revisit the fifth match of the Benson &amp; Hedges World Series from December 1990 between Australia and England in Perth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-23 18:00:00" d="2020-04-23 19:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Eng">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Eng 1991</n>    <k>We revisit the 11th match of the 1990/91 World Series between Australia and England at the Sydney Cricket Ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-23 19:00:00" d="2020-04-23 19:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Man City v Barcelona 2014/15</n>    <k>We revisit the 2014/15 UEFA Champions League last 16 first leg between Manchester City and Barcelona at the Etihad. Luis Suarez marked his first return</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-23 19:30:00" d="2020-04-23 20:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Bayern Munich v Barcelona 2012/13</n>    <k>A look back at the first leg of the 2012/13 UEFA Champions League semi-final at the Allianz Arena between Jupp Heynckes' Bayern Munich and tournament favourites Barcelona</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-23 20:00:00" d="2020-04-23 20:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Bayern Munich v Porto 2014/15</n>    <k>We revisit the 2014/15 UEFA Champions League quarter-final second leg between Bayern Munich and Porto at the Allianz Arena. Bayern suffered a shock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-23 20:30:00" d="2020-04-23 22:00:00"><n>European Rugby Challenge Cup: Pau v Stade Francais 2017/18</n>    <k>A look back at the 2017/18 European Challenge Cup quarter-final between Pau and defending champions Stade Francais Paris. Both sides were undefeated in the competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-23 22:00:00" d="2020-04-24 01:00:00"><n u="UFC: UFC 210: Cormier v Johnson">UFC: UFC 210: Cormier v Johnson II</n>    <k>Light heavyweight champion Daniel Cormier faces Anthony Johnson in a blockbuster rematch in Buffalo. Plus, Chris Weidman v Gegard Mousasi and Cynthia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-24 01:00:00" d="2020-04-24 04:00:00"><n>UFC: UFC 211: Miocic v Dos Santos</n>    <k>Stipe Miocic and Junior dos Santos go head-to-head for the heavyweight title at UFC 211 in Dallas. Plus, Joanna Jedrzejczyk v Jessica Andrade and Demian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-24 04:00:00" d="2020-04-24 05:00:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing</n>    <k>Tyson Raw &amp; Uncut looks at Mike Tyson's unprecedented rise to the pinnacle of world boxing. This episode features his 1986 bout against Jesse Ferguson in New York</k>  </p>
</a>
