<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2020-04-10 04:29:09"><p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 05:00:00" d="2020-04-17 06:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Laguna Seca 2005</n>    <k>We revisit the 2005 US Grand Prix at Laguna Seca which saw American riders Nicky Hayden and Colin Edwards battling it out with Valentino Rossi in a thrilling contest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 06:00:00" d="2020-04-17 07:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Welkom 2004</n>    <k>We revisit the 2004 South African Grand Prix at Welkom. Valentino Rossi ripped up the formbook with victory in his first race for Yamaha, while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 07:00:00" d="2020-04-17 08:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1974/75</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 16th February 1975, features West Ham v QPR, Ipswich v Aston Villa and Everton v Fulham</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 08:00:00" d="2020-04-17 09:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1974/75</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 23rd February 1975, features Tottenham v Leicester and Burnley v Sheffield United</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 09:00:00" d="2020-04-17 10:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1974/75</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 16th March 1975, features Charlton v Southend, Derby v Stoke and Middlesbrough v Tottenham</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 10:00:00" d="2020-04-17 11:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1974/75</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 23rd March 1975, features Orient v Aston Villa, Luton v Leeds and Burnley v Arsenal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 11:00:00" d="2020-04-17 11:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Man City v Liverpool 2018/19</n>    <k>Look back to the 2018/19 Premier League season as Manchester City produced a stunning display at the Etihad Stadium against title rivals Liverpool to close</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 11:30:00" d="2020-04-17 12:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Man City v Crystal Palace 2018/19</n>    <k>Relive Man City's Premier League tie with Crystal Palace. Andros Townsend scored one of the goals of the season as Palace claimed their first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 12:00:00" d="2020-04-17 12:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Arsenal v Tottenham 2018/19</n>    <k>Relive this scintillating and eventful North London Derby from 2018 as bitter rivals Arsenal and Tottenham met in the Premier League at the Emirates Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 12:30:00" d="2020-04-17 13:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Bournemouth v Chelsea 2018/19</n>    <k>Look back as Bournemouth stunned Chelsea at the Vitality Stadium in the 2018/19 Premier League. Joshua King starred for the Cherries, with two goals and an assist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 13:00:00" d="2020-04-17 14:30:00"><n>Gallagher Premiership Rugby Union: Newcastle v Leicester T 2018/19</n>    <k>Revisit the 2018/19 Gallagher Premiership tie between Leicester Tigers and Newcastle Falcons. A Tigers win all but secured their Premiership status</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 14:30:00" d="2020-04-17 16:00:00"><n>Gallagher Premiership Rugby Union: Exeter Chiefs v Saracens 2018/19</n>    <k>Look back as Exeter Chiefs took on Saracens in the 2018/19 Gallagher Premiership final at Twickenham. The pair had met in two of the last three finals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 16:00:00" d="2020-04-17 17:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: ODI Cricket Classic: Aus v SL">Cricket Classics: ODI Cricket Classic: Aus v SL 1988</n>    <k>A look back at the first match of the 1987/88 World Series Cup between Australia and Sri Lanka in Perth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 17:00:00" d="2020-04-17 18:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: ODI Cricket Classic: Aus v SL">Cricket Classics: ODI Cricket Classic: Aus v SL 1988</n>    <k>A look back at the eighth match of the 1987/88 World Series Cup between Australia and Sri Lanka in Melbourne</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 18:00:00" d="2020-04-17 19:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: ODI Cricket Classic: Aus v SL">Cricket Classics: ODI Cricket Classic: Aus v SL 1988</n>    <k>A look back at the 11th match of the 1987/88 World Series Cup between Australia and Sri Lanka in Sydney</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 19:00:00" d="2020-04-17 20:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League: Manchester City v Tottenham</n>    <k>Relive Man City and Tottenham's Champions League quarter-final. It was a classic at the Etihad with seven goals, five of them coming in 17 pulsating</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 20:00:00" d="2020-04-17 20:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League: UCL Final: Tottenham v Liverpool</n>    <k>Look back as Tottenham met Liverpool in an all-English UEFA Champions League final in Madrid. Spurs hoped to win the trophy for the first time while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 20:30:00" d="2020-04-17 21:00:00"><n u="FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Man Utd v C.Palace">FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Man Utd v C.Palace 1995</n>    <k>We revisit the 1995 FA Cup semi-final replay between Man Utd and Crystal Palace. Tensions were running high following Eric Cantona's infamous kung-fu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 21:00:00" d="2020-04-17 21:30:00"><n u="FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Chelsea v Liverpool">FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Chelsea v Liverpool 1997</n>    <k>We revisit the thrilling 1997 FA Cup fourth round tie between Chelsea and league leaders Liverpool at Stamford Bridge. It had been 27 years since Chelsea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 21:30:00" d="2020-04-17 22:00:00"><n>FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Cardiff v Leeds Utd 2002</n>    <k>We revisit the highly-charged 2002 FA Cup third round tie between Cardiff and top flight leaders Leeds at Ninian Park. The hosts were 53 places below their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 22:00:00" d="2020-04-18 01:00:00"><n u="UFC: UFC 202: Diaz v McGregor">UFC: UFC 202: Diaz v McGregor II</n>    <k>We revisit the eagerly anticipated rematch between Conor McGregor and Nate Diaz at UFC 202 in Las Vegas. This epic encounter has been hailed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 01:00:00" d="2020-04-18 04:00:00"><n>UFC: UFC 203: Miocic v Overeem</n>    <k>We revisit UFC 203 in Cleveland which saw heavyweight champion Stipe Miocic defend his title against challenger Alistair Overeem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 04:00:00" d="2020-04-18 04:30:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing: Classic Boxing: Nelson v McDonnell</n>    <k>We revisit the classic bout between Azumah Nelson and Jim McDonnell in November 1989 at the Royal Albert Hall in London</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-18 04:30:00" d="2020-04-18 05:00:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing: Classic Boxing: Hodkinson v Villasana</n>    <k>We revisit this classic featherweight title bout between Paul Hodkinson and Marcos Villasana in June 1990 at the G-Mex Leisure Centre, Manchester</k>  </p>
</a>
