<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2020-05-11 04:28:33"><p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 05:00:00" d="2020-05-18 06:00:00"><n>WRC Classic: WRC Classic: Top 10 Crashes</n>    <k>A countdown of the top ten most spectacular crashes in the history of the World Rally Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 06:00:00" d="2020-05-18 07:00:00"><n>WRC Classic: WRC: 2010 Down to the Wire</n>    <k>A look back at some classic action from the 2010 World Rally Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 07:00:00" d="2020-05-18 08:00:00"><n>Football Classics: Arsenal Classics</n>    <k>Classic Arsenal matches from the football archives, featuring memorable league clashes with Manchester United (1973) and Liverpool (1975). 1/8</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 08:00:00" d="2020-05-18 09:00:00"><n>Football Classics: Arsenal Classics</n>    <k>Classic Arsenal matches from the football archives, featuring memorable league clashes with Crystal Palace (1971) and Nottingham Forest (1977). 2/8</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 09:00:00" d="2020-05-18 10:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1974/75</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 22nd September 1974, features Arsenal v Luton, Ipswich v Chelsea and Leeds v Sheffield United</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 10:00:00" d="2020-05-18 11:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1974/75</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 13th October 1974, features Arsenal v QPR, Wolves v Carlisle and Sheffield United v Everton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 11:00:00" d="2020-05-18 11:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Fulham v Tottenham 2007/08</n>    <k>We revisit the six-goal 2007/08 Premier League epic between Fulham and Tottenham at Craven Cottage. With pressure mounting on manager Martin Jol, Spurs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 11:30:00" d="2020-05-18 12:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Fulham v Chelsea 2008/09</n>    <k>We revisit the pulsating 2008/09 Premier League clash between London rivals Fulham and Chelsea at Craven Cottage. Fulham looked to extend their unbeaten</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 12:00:00" d="2020-05-18 12:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Crystal Palace v Liverpool 2013/14</n>    <k>We revisit the 2013/14 Premier League classic between Crystal Palace and Liverpool at Selhurst Park. A dramatic Palace comeback all but ended the Reds' title ambitions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 12:30:00" d="2020-05-18 13:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Hull City v Man City 2014/15</n>    <k>We revisit the 2014/15 Premier League encounter at the KC Stadium between Hull and champions Manchester City. It was a difficult afternoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 13:00:00" d="2020-05-18 14:00:00"><n>Bundesliga: Games of the Season: B Dortmund v Frankfurt 2017/18</n>    <k>We revisit Borussia Dortmund's 2017/18 Bundesliga clash with Eintracht Frankfurt as both teams eyed a Champions League spot. The two shared the spoils</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 14:00:00" d="2020-05-18 15:00:00"><n>Bundesliga: Games of the Season: Gladbach v Hoffenheim 2017/18</n>    <k>We look back at Borussia Monchengladbach's 2017/18 Bundesliga clash with Hoffenheim. A Hoffenheim win would've lifted them back into the</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 15:00:00" d="2020-05-18 16:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season: Marseille v Strasbourg 2018/19</n>    <k>We revisit the 2018/19 Ligue 1 clash between Marseille and Strasbourg at the Orange Velodrome. Marseille looked to get back to winning ways after defeat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 16:00:00" d="2020-05-18 17:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season: PSG v Lyon 2018/19</n>    <k>Coverage of the 2018/19 Ligue 1 clash between league leaders PSG and Lyon at the Parc des Princes. The champions were unbeaten in the last 10 meetings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 17:00:00" d="2020-05-18 18:00:00"><n>UEFA Europa League: Ajax v Celtic 2015/16</n>    <k>2015/16 UEFA Europa League action from Group A at the Amsterdam Arena as Celtic travelled to face Ajax</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 18:00:00" d="2020-05-18 19:00:00"><n>UEFA Europa League: Tottenham v Monaco 2015/16</n>    <k>2015/16 UEFA Europa League Group J action at White Hart Lane. Spurs were through but still needed a point to be certain of finishing top</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 19:00:00" d="2020-05-18 19:30:00"><n>Classic Ligue 1: Marseille v Paris Saint-Germain 2012/13</n>    <k>Classic Ligue 1 action from the 2012/13 season as Marseille hosted PSG</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 19:30:00" d="2020-05-18 20:00:00"><n>Classic Ligue 1: Classic Ligue 1: PSG v Brest 12/13</n>    <k>Paris Saint-Germain's penultimate game of the 2012/13 season saw the French giants seal a 3-1 win over the visitors, thanks to a sublime Zlatan Ibrahimovic free-kick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 20:00:00" d="2020-05-18 21:00:00"><n u="ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: Ali v Liston I">ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: Ali v Liston I 1964</n>    <k>Another chance to watch the classic 1964 bout between Muhammad Ali and Sonny Liston in Miami Beach, Florida. The WBA/WBC Heavyweight Championship belts were on the line</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 21:00:00" d="2020-05-18 21:30:00"><n u="ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: Ali v Liston II">ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: Ali v Liston II 1965</n>    <k>Another chance to watch the classic 1965 rematch between Muhammad Ali and Sonny Liston in Lewiston, Maine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 21:30:00" d="2020-05-18 22:00:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing</n>    <k>Cassius Clay Greatest Hits - Vol I. A look back at some of Muhammad Ali's greatest fights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 22:00:00" d="2020-05-19 01:00:00"><n>UFC: UFC 236: Holloway v Poirier</n>    <k>Action from UFC 236 as lightweights Max Holloway and Dustin Poirier do battle for the interim lightweight title at the State Farm Arena in Atlanta</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-19 01:00:00" d="2020-05-19 04:00:00"><n>UFC: UFC 237: Namajunas v Andrade</n>    <k>A look back as Brazil's Jessica Andrade fought reigning champion Rose Namajunas for the strawweight title in front of a home crowd at UFC 237 in Rio de Janeiro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-19 04:00:00" d="2020-05-19 05:00:00"><n>WRC Review: WRC Review: Rally Turkey</n>    <k>Relive the best moments from Rally Turkey, round 11 of the FIA World Rally Championship</k>  </p>
</a>
