<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-05-12 04:30:36"><p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-19 05:00:00" d="2020-05-19 06:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Valencia GP 2011</n>    <k>We revisit the 2011 Valencia Grand Prix at the Circuit Ricardo Tormo. Newly-crowned world champion Casey Stoner was looking to secure his 10th win of the season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-19 06:00:00" d="2020-05-19 07:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Brno 2012</n>    <k>We revisit the historic 2012 Czech Republic Grand Prix in Brno when Cal Crutchlow became the first British rider to stand on the rostrum in a premier-class event for 12 years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-19 07:00:00" d="2020-05-19 08:00:00"><n>Football Classics: Arsenal Classics</n>    <k>Classic Arsenal matches from the football archives, featuring memorable wins over West Ham in the league (1976) and the League Cup quarter-final (1998). 4/8</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-19 08:00:00" d="2020-05-19 09:00:00"><n>Football Classics: Arsenal Classics</n>    <k>Classic Arsenal matches from the football archives, featuring a memorable FA Cup fourth round clash with Coventry City (1977) and a league win over Norwich City (1989). 5/8</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-19 09:00:00" d="2020-05-19 10:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1974/75</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 1st December 1974, features West Ham v Middlesbrough, Sheffield United v Carlisle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-19 10:00:00" d="2020-05-19 11:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1974/75</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 17th November 1974, features West Ham v Wolves, Birmingham v Man City and Newcastle v Chelsea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-19 11:00:00" d="2020-05-19 11:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Manchester Utd v Liverpool 1992/93</n>    <k>We take a look back at this thrilling encounter between Manchester United and Liverpool at Old Trafford. Mark Hughes scored twice late on to earn the hosts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-19 11:30:00" d="2020-05-19 12:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Chelsea v Tottenham 1993/94</n>    <k>We revisit this seven-goal thriller between Chelsea and Tottenham at Stamford Bridge. Mark Stein scored a last-gasp penalty to snatch all three points</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-19 12:00:00" d="2020-05-19 12:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Man City v Man Utd - 1993/94</n>    <k>We take a look back at this clash between the two Manchester rivals. City raced into a two-goal lead but it was the visitors who took the points after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-19 12:30:00" d="2020-05-19 13:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Southampton v Tottenham: 1994/95</n>    <k>We turn back the clock to the 1994/5 Premier League season as Southampton went head-to-head with Gerry Francis' Tottenham in a seven-goal thriller at The Dell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-19 13:00:00" d="2020-05-19 14:00:00"><n>Bundesliga: Games of the Season: B Munich v B Dortmund 2017/18</n>    <k>We revisit the 2017/18 Der Klassiker as Bayern Munich hoped to clinch their sixth consecutive Bundesliga title against Borussia Dortmund</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-19 14:00:00" d="2020-05-19 15:00:00"><n>Bundesliga: Games of the Season: Hamburg v Schalke 2017/18</n>    <k>We look back at the 2017/18 Bundesliga clash between Schalke and Hamburg at the Volksparkstadion. The hosts were looking to register their first league win since November</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-19 15:00:00" d="2020-05-19 16:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season: Saint-Etienne v Angers 2018/19</n>    <k>We revisit the 2018/19 Ligue 1 clash between Saint-Etienne and Angers at Stade Geoffroy-Guichard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-19 16:00:00" d="2020-05-19 17:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season: Lille v Lyon 2018/19</n>    <k>We look back at Lille's encounter with Lyon in the 2018/19 Ligue 1 season at Stade Pierre-Mauroy. Lyon, who sat second in the table, were unbeaten in their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-19 17:00:00" d="2020-05-19 18:00:00"><n>UEFA Europa League: Tottenham v Fiorentina 2015/16</n>    <k>2015/16 Europa League last 32 second leg action between Tottenham and Fiorentina at White Hart Lane. Spurs were favourites after a 1-1 draw in their away leg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-19 18:00:00" d="2020-05-19 19:00:00"><n>UEFA Europa League: Man Utd v Midtjylland 2015/16</n>    <k>2015/16 Europa League last 32 second leg action between Manchester United and Midtjylland at Old Trafford. The Reds suffered a humiliating 2-1 defeat in the first leg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-19 19:00:00" d="2020-05-19 19:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Chelsea v Bayern Munich 2004/05</n>    <k>We revisit the 2004/05 UEFA Champions League quarter-final first leg between Chelsea and Bayern Munich at Stamford Bridge. Frank Lampard inspired the Blues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-19 19:30:00" d="2020-05-19 20:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Bayern Munich v Chelsea 2011/12</n>    <k>We revisit the 2011/12 UEFA Champions League final between Bayern Munich and Chelsea at the Allianz Arena. This was Chelsea's second final, having</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-19 20:00:00" d="2020-05-19 22:00:00"><n>BT Sport Fight Night: Fight Night: Selby v Warrington</n>    <k>Lee Selby attempts to defend his IBF world featherweight title for the fifth time as he takes on bitter rival Josh Warrington in a blockbuster fight at Elland Road</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-19 22:00:00" d="2020-05-20 01:00:00"><n>UFC: UFC Fight Night: Overeem v Harris</n>    <k>UFC Fight Night action as Alistair Overeem faces Walt Harris in Jacksonville</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 01:00:00" d="2020-05-20 04:00:00"><n>UFC: UFC 238: Cejudo v Moraes</n>    <k>A look back as Henry Cejudo and Marlon Moraes clashed for the bantamweight title at UFC 238. Women's flyweight champion Valentina Schevchenko</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 04:00:00" d="2020-05-20 05:00:00"><n>WRC Review: WRC Review: Wales Rally GB</n>    <k>A look back at all the best moments from Wales Rally GB, round 12 of the FIA World Rally Championship</k>  </p>
</a>
