<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-05-13 04:30:38"><p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 05:00:00" d="2020-05-20 06:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Misano 2012</n>    <k>We revisit the thrilling 2012 San Marino Grand Prix when Valentino Rossi produced his best ever ride on the Ducati on a weekend when MotoGP remembered</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 06:00:00" d="2020-05-20 07:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Australia 2012</n>    <k>We revisit the incident-packed 2012 Australian Grand Prix at Phillip Island. Dani Pedrosa needed to finish ahead of fellow Spaniard Jorge Lorenzo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 07:00:00" d="2020-05-20 08:00:00"><n>Football Classics: Arsenal Classics</n>    <k>Classic Arsenal matches from the football archives, featuring a memorable league win over Nottingham Forest (1979) and a League Cup quarter-final clash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 08:00:00" d="2020-05-20 09:00:00"><n>Football Classics: Arsenal Classics</n>    <k>Classic Arsenal matches from the football archives, including memorable league wins against Chelsea (1973) and Manchester United (1991), featuring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 09:00:00" d="2020-05-20 10:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1974/75</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 1st December 1974, features Crystal Palace v Charlton, Newcastle v Man City and Luton v Burnley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 10:00:00" d="2020-05-20 11:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1974/75</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 8th December 1974, features Tottenham v Newcastle, Birmingham v Stoke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 11:00:00" d="2020-05-20 11:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: West Ham v Leicester City 1997/98</n>    <k>We turn the clock back to this epic clash between West Ham and Leicester City at Upton Park. The two sides gave the fans plenty to cheer about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 11:30:00" d="2020-05-20 12:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Leeds v Newcastle: 2001/02</n>    <k>We relive the dramatic 2001/2 Premier League clash between Leeds and Newcastle at Elland Road. A vicious Mark Voduka challenge threatened to overshadow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 12:00:00" d="2020-05-20 12:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Manchester United v Fulham 2003/4</n>    <k>We revisit Fulham's visit to Manchester United from the 2003/4 Premier League Season. United came into the game having only lost one of their nine league</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 12:30:00" d="2020-05-20 13:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Manchester City v Fulham 2007/08</n>    <k>We revisit this Premier League clash between Manchester City and Fulham. The visitors needed all three points to keep alive their hopes of staying in the top flight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 13:00:00" d="2020-05-20 14:00:00"><n>Bundesliga: Games of the Season: Freiburg v Cologne 2017/18</n>    <k>We revisit the 2017/18 Bundesliga clash between Cologne and Freiburg, with Cologne needing a win to stay in the Bundesliga</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 14:00:00" d="2020-05-20 15:00:00"><n>Bundesliga: Games of the Season: Hertha Berlin v RB Leipzig 2017/18</n>    <k>We revisit the 2017/18 Bundesliga clash between Hertha Berlin and RB Leipzig at the Olympiastadion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 15:00:00" d="2020-05-20 16:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season: Bordeaux v PSG 2018/19</n>    <k>Take a look back as Bordeaux host Thomas Tuchel's Paris Saint-Germain in Ligue 1. PSG were looking to extend their record winning-streak in the league to 15 matches</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 16:00:00" d="2020-05-20 17:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season: Nantes v Marseille 2018/19</n>    <k>We look back as Nantes and Marseille met in Ligue 1 at the Stade de la Beaujoire. A late Lucas Ocampos goal gave Marseille all three points during their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 17:00:00" d="2020-05-20 18:00:00"><n>UEFA Europa League: Man Utd v Liverpool 2015/16</n>    <k>Manchester United took on rivals Liverpool in the second leg of the 2015/16 Europa League last 16 at Old Trafford. Liverpool were comfortable 2-0 winners in the first leg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 18:00:00" d="2020-05-20 19:00:00"><n>UEFA Europa League: Liverpool v B Dortmund 2015/16</n>    <k>We revist the 2015/16 UEFA Champions League quarter-final second leg match between Liverpool and Borussia Dortmund at Anfield</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 19:00:00" d="2020-05-20 20:00:00"><n>UEFA Europa League: Liverpool v Villarreal 2015/16</n>    <k>Liverpool took on Villarreal in the 2015/16 Europa League semi-final second leg at Anfield. Jurgen Klopp's side had it all to do after a disappointing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 20:00:00" d="2020-05-20 20:30:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing: Classic Boxing: Hearns v Andries</n>    <k>We travel back to March 1987 to revisit this classic light-heavyweight bout between Tommy Hearns and Dennis Andries at the Cobo Hall. Hearns put on a stone ahead of the fight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 20:30:00" d="2020-05-20 20:45:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing: Classic Boxing: Monzon v Napoles</n>    <k>We revisit this classic bout from 1974 between Carlos Monzon, making his ninth defence of the World Middleweight Championship and Jose Napoles in Puteaux</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 20:45:00" d="2020-05-20 22:00:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing: Muhammad Ali v George Chuvalo</n>    <k>Another chance to watch the classic 1972 bout between Muhammad Ali and George Chuvalo in Vancouver</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-20 22:00:00" d="2020-05-21 01:00:00"><n>UFC: UFC 239: Jones v Santos</n>    <k>A look back as Jon Jones defended his UFC light heavyweight title against Thiago Santos at UFC 239 in Las Vegas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 01:00:00" d="2020-05-21 04:00:00"><n>UFC: UFC 240: Holloway v Edgar</n>    <k>A look back as Max Holloway and Frankie Edgar did battle for the featherweight title at UFC 240 in Canada. This programme may contain flashing images</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 04:00:00" d="2020-05-21 05:00:00"><n>WRC Review</n>    <k>A look back at all the best moments from Rally Spain, round 13 of the FIA World Rally Championship</k>  </p>
</a>
