<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-05-17 04:30:11"><p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-24 05:00:00" d="2020-05-24 06:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Silverstone 2014</n>    <k>We revisit the 2014 British Grand Prix at Silverstone. Marc Marquez was looking to extend his lead at the top of the standings and secure his 11th victory of the season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-24 06:00:00" d="2020-05-24 07:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Australia 2015</n>    <k>We revisit the 2015 Australian Grand Prix at Phillip Island. Marc Marquez was looking to secure his 50th GP win and in the process become the youngest rider ever to do so</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-24 07:00:00" d="2020-05-24 08:00:00"><n>Football Classics: Chelsea Classics</n>    <k>Classic Chelsea matches from the football archives, featuring the 2005 League Cup semi-final at Manchester United and the 1978 FA Cup third round clash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-24 08:00:00" d="2020-05-24 09:00:00"><n>Football Classics: Chelsea Classics</n>    <k>Classic Chelsea matches from the football archives, featuring the 1991 First Division clash with Arsenal and the 1997 League Cup third round match against</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-24 09:00:00" d="2020-05-24 10:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1976/77</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 10th October 1976, features Nottingham Forest v Sheffield United, Bury v Brighton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-24 10:00:00" d="2020-05-24 11:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1976/77</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 24th October 1976, features Leicester v Arsenal, QPR v Sunderland and Luton v Southampton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-24 11:00:00" d="2020-05-24 11:30:00"><n>FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Arsenal v Liverpool 2001</n>    <k>We revisit the 2001 FA Cup final between Arsenal and Liverpool at the Millennium Stadium, the first final in which the managers of both teams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-24 11:30:00" d="2020-05-24 12:00:00"><n>FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Arsenal v Chelsea 2002</n>    <k>We revisit the 2002 FA Cup final between Arsenal and Chelsea. Freddie Ljungberg was aiming to become the first man to score in successive Cup finals since</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-24 12:00:00" d="2020-05-24 12:30:00"><n>FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Arsenal v Southampton 2003</n>    <k>We revisit the 2003 FA Cup final between Arsenal and Southampton at the Millennium Stadium. The final was the first to be played indoors;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-24 12:30:00" d="2020-05-24 13:00:00"><n>FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Man Utd v Millwall 2004</n>    <k>We revisit the 2004 FA Cup final between Manchester United and Millwall. The Lions became only the second team from outside the top flight to reach the final since 1982</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-24 13:00:00" d="2020-05-24 14:00:00"><n>Bundesliga: Games of the Season: E Frankfurt v Fortuna 2018/19</n>    <k>Take a look back as Eintracht Frankfurt hosted Fortuna Dusseldorf at the Commerzbank-Arena in the 2018/19 Bundesliga season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-24 14:00:00" d="2020-05-24 14:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Real Madrid v Valencia 1999/00</n>    <k>A look back at the 1999/00 UEFA Champions League final between Real Madrid and Valencia in Paris. Steve McManaman, signed from Liverpool the previous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-24 14:30:00" d="2020-05-24 15:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: R.Madrid v A.Madrid 2013/14</n>    <k>The 2013/14 UEFA Champions League final in Lisbon saw Real Madrid go head-to-head with arch-rivals Atletico Madrid. Real aimed to become the first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-24 15:00:00" d="2020-05-24 16:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season: PSG v Strasbourg 2018/19</n>    <k>Look back as PSG looked to win the 2018/19 Ligue 1 title against Strasbourg, who were on a high having just won the French League Cup</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-24 16:00:00" d="2020-05-24 17:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season: Lille v PSG 2018/19</n>    <k>Revisit Lille and PSG's six-goal classic from the 2018/19 Ligue 1 season. It was a night to forget for PSG who missed out on lifting the Ligue 1 title</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-24 17:00:00" d="2020-05-24 18:30:00"><n>European Rugby - Top Ten Games of the Season: Glasgow W v Racing 92 2016/17</n>    <k>We revisit 2016/17's European Champions Cup clash between Pool 1 rivals Glasgow Warriors and Racing 92. The Warriors knew that a win here would</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-24 18:30:00" d="2020-05-24 20:00:00"><n>European Rugby - Top Ten Games of the Season: Wasps v Toulouse 2016/17</n>    <k>We revisit 2016/17's European Champions Cup clash between Pool 2 rivals Wasps and Toulouse. A dramatic late try saw Wasps maintain their hopes of reaching the quarter-finals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-24 20:00:00" d="2020-05-24 20:30:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing</n>    <k>Tyson Raw &amp; Uncut looks at Mike Tyson's unprecedented rise to the pinnacle of world boxing. This episode features his 1986 bout against Marvis Frazier</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-24 20:30:00" d="2020-05-24 22:00:00"><n u="ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: Ali v Bonavena">ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: Ali v Bonavena 1970</n>    <k>We revisit the classic 1970 bout between Muhammad Ali and Oscar Bonavena in New York. This bruising encounter saw Ali receive arguably the most punishment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-24 22:00:00" d="2020-05-25 01:00:00"><n>UFC: UFC 247: Jones v Reyes</n>    <k>Another look at the action from UFC 247 as Jon Jones and Dominick Reyes met in the Octagon in Houston. This programme may contain flashing images and scenes of violence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-25 01:00:00" d="2020-05-25 04:00:00"><n>UFC: UFC 248 - Adesanya v Romero</n>    <k>Look back at UFC 248 as reigning middleweight title holder Israel Adesanya and Yoel Romero mee in the Octagon at the T-Mobile Arena in Las Vegas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-25 04:00:00" d="2020-05-25 05:00:00"><n>WRC Review: WRC Review: Rally Mexico 2018</n>    <k>The best of the action from Rally Mexico, the third round of the 2018 FIA World Rally Championship</k>  </p>
</a>
