<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2020-05-28 04:32:55"><p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 05:00:00" d="2020-06-04 06:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: ODI Classic Cricket: Aus v NZ">Cricket Classics: ODI Classic Cricket: Aus v NZ 1986</n>    <k>A look back at the seventh match of the 1986 World Series Cup between Australia and New Zealand at the WACA</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 06:00:00" d="2020-06-04 07:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: ODI Classic Cricket: Aus v NZ">Cricket Classics: ODI Classic Cricket: Aus v NZ 1986</n>    <k>A look back at the twelfth match of the 1985/86 World Series Cup between Australia and New Zealand at the Adelaide Oval</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 07:00:00" d="2020-06-04 08:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1978/79</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 12th May 1979, features the FA Cup final between Arsenal and Manchester United</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 08:00:00" d="2020-06-04 09:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1982/83</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 5th February 1983, features Manchester City v Spurs, Barnsley v Wolves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 09:00:00" d="2020-06-04 10:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1982/83</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 12th February 1983, features Liverpool v Ipswich, Celtic v Aberdeen and Coventry v Manchester City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 10:00:00" d="2020-06-04 11:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1982/83</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 19th February 1983, features Aston Villa v Watford, Everton v Tottenham</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 11:00:00" d="2020-06-04 11:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Arsenal v Tottenham 2018/19</n>    <k>Relive this scintillating and eventful North London Derby from 2018 as bitter rivals Arsenal and Tottenham met in the Premier League at the Emirates Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 11:30:00" d="2020-06-04 12:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Bournemouth v Chelsea 2018/19</n>    <k>Look back as Bournemouth stunned Chelsea at the Vitality Stadium in the 2018/19 Premier League. Joshua King starred for the Cherries, with two goals and an assist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 12:00:00" d="2020-06-04 12:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Chelsea v Arsenal 2018/19</n>    <k>Look back as Chelsea met Arsenal in a highly-entertaining 2018/19 Premier League game at Stamford Bridge. A late Marcos Alonso strike settled a chaotic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 12:30:00" d="2020-06-04 13:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Brighton v Man United 2018/19</n>    <k>Look back as Brighton recorded their first win of the 2018/19 season after an entertaining encounter against Jose Mourinho's Manchester United side at the Amex Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 13:00:00" d="2020-06-04 13:30:00"><n u="FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Brighton v Liverpool">FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Brighton v Liverpool 1984</n>    <k>We revisit the 1984 FA Cup fourth round match between Brighton and Liverpool at the Goldstone Ground. Albion had scored a surprise FA Cup</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 13:30:00" d="2020-06-04 14:00:00"><n u="FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Everton v Telford Utd">FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Everton v Telford Utd 1985</n>    <k>We revisit the 1985 FA Cup fifth round match between Everton and Telford United at Goodison Park. Telford became one of only nine non-league teams to reach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 14:00:00" d="2020-06-04 15:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season: Nantes v PSG 2015/16</n>    <k>We revisit the 2015/16 Ligue 1 clash between Nantes and Paris Saint-Germain at the Stade de la Beaujoire. PSG were looking to extend their unbeaten start to the season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 15:00:00" d="2020-06-04 16:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Eng">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Eng 1987</n>    <k>A look back at some classic ODI cricket action from February 1st 1987 between Australia and England at the Melbourne Cricket Ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 16:00:00" d="2020-06-04 17:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Barcelona 2007</n>    <k>We revisit the epic 2007 Catalunya Grand Prix in Barcelona. Casey Stoner withstood pressure from Valentino Rossi and Dani Pedrosa in the closest race of the season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 17:00:00" d="2020-06-04 18:00:00"><n>UEFA Europa League: Chelsea v E Frankfurt 2018/19</n>    <k>Another chance to see Chelsea's 2018/19 clash with Eintracht Frankfurt in the Europa League semi-finals. 210 minutes weren't enough to separate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 18:00:00" d="2020-06-04 19:00:00"><n>UEFA Europa League: Valencia v Arsenal 2018/19</n>    <k>Look back as Arsenal travelled to Spain with a two-goal lead to face Valencia in the 2018/19 Europa League semi-final second leg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 19:00:00" d="2020-06-04 19:30:00"><n>Classic Ligue 1: Lyon v Paris Saint-Germain 2011/12</n>    <k>Look back at the classic eight-goal thriller between Lyon and Paris Saint-Germain in the 2011/12 French Ligue 1 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 19:30:00" d="2020-06-04 20:00:00"><n>Classic Ligue 1: PSG v Montpellier 2011/12</n>    <k>Look back at the match that ultimately deciphered Montpellier as the 2011/12 French Ligue 1 champions, as they held title rivals Paris Saint-Germain to a 2-2 draw</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 20:00:00" d="2020-06-04 22:00:00"><n>BT Sport Fight Night: Fight Night: Frampton v Jackson</n>    <k>Carl Frampton defends his featherweight title in Belfast against Luke Jackson, on a card that also features Tyson Fury's bout with Francesco Pianeta</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 22:00:00" d="2020-06-04 22:30:00"><n>UFC: Inside the Octagon</n>    <k>A detailed break down of potential tactics ahead of UFC 250</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-04 22:30:00" d="2020-06-05 01:30:00"><n>UFC</n>    <k>Action from the UFC</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 01:30:00" d="2020-06-05 02:30:00"><n>UFC Main Event: UFC 231 - Shevchenko v Joanna</n>    <k>Relive UFC 231 as Valentina Shevchenko took on Joanna Jedrzejczyk for the women's flyweight title in Toronto, Canada</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 02:30:00" d="2020-06-05 03:30:00"><n u="UFC: The Ultimate Fighter: UFC The Ultimate Fighter - Series">UFC: The Ultimate Fighter: UFC The Ultimate Fighter - Series 22</n>    <k>Episode 4. The 22nd series of the Ultimate Fighter sees a United States team, coached by veteran Urijah Faber, take on a European team, headed up by Irish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 03:30:00" d="2020-06-05 04:00:00"><n>UFC: Inside the Octagon</n>    <k>A detailed break down of potential tactics ahead of UFC 250</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 04:00:00" d="2020-06-05 05:00:00"><n>Hyundai A-League Highlights</n>    <k>All the goals and talking points from the latest round of fixtures in the Hyundai A-League</k>  </p>
</a>
