<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-04-13 04:26:32"><p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-20 05:00:00" d="2020-04-20 06:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v SL">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v SL 1990</n>    <k>We revisit the 5th match of the 1989/90 World Series Cup between Australia and Sri Lanka at the Melbourne Cricket Ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-20 06:00:00" d="2020-04-20 07:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v SL">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v SL 1990</n>    <k>We revisit the 11th match of the 1989/90 World Series between Australia and Sri Lanka at the Adelaide Oval</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-20 07:00:00" d="2020-04-20 08:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1978/79</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 14th January 1979, features Arsenal v Nottingham Forest and Leeds v Manchester City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-20 08:00:00" d="2020-04-20 09:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1978/79</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 21st January 1979, features Manchester City v Chelsea and Fulham v Sunderland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-20 09:00:00" d="2020-04-20 10:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1978/79</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 28th January 1979, features Ipswich v Leyton Orient, Newcastle v Wolves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-20 10:00:00" d="2020-04-20 11:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1978/79</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 4th February 1979, features Spurs v Man City, Man United v Arsenal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-20 11:00:00" d="2020-04-20 12:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League</n>    <k>A look back at a classic Premier League clash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-20 12:00:00" d="2020-04-20 13:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League</n>    <k>A look back at a classic Premier League clash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-20 13:00:00" d="2020-04-20 14:00:00"><n>Bundesliga: Games of the Season: E Frankfurt v Cologne 2015/16</n>    <k>We take a look back at the 2015/16 Bundesliga clash between Eintracht Frankfurt and Cologne</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-20 14:00:00" d="2020-04-20 15:00:00"><n>Bundesliga: Games of the Season: Bayern Munich v Wolfsburg 2015/16</n>    <k>We take a look back at the 2015/16 Bundesliga match between Bayern Munich and Wolfsburg at the Allianz Arena</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-20 15:00:00" d="2020-04-20 16:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season: Monaco v PSG 2015/16</n>    <k>Take a look back at Monaco v Paris Saint-Germain from the 2015/16 Ligue 1 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-20 16:00:00" d="2020-04-20 17:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season: Marseille v Bastia 2015/16</n>    <k>We revisit the 2015/16 Ligue 1 match-up between Marseille and Bastia at the Stade Velodrome</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-20 17:00:00" d="2020-04-20 18:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Eng">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Eng 1987</n>    <k>We revisit the one-day international match from January 1987 between Australia and England in Brisbane</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-20 18:00:00" d="2020-04-20 19:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Eng">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Eng 1987</n>    <k>We revisit the fourth match of the 1986/87 World Series between Australia and England at the Sydney Cricket Ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-20 19:00:00" d="2020-04-20 20:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League: Barcelona v PSG 2016/17</n>    <k>We revisit the extraordinary UEFA Champions League last 16 second leg clash between Barcelona and Paris Saint-Germain, featuring one of the competition's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-20 20:00:00" d="2020-04-20 20:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Arsenal v Villarreal 2008/09</n>    <k>We revisit the 2008/09 UEFA Champions League quarter-final second leg between Arsenal and Villarreal at the Emirates. Emmanuel Adebayor's goal secured</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-20 20:30:00" d="2020-04-20 22:00:00"><n>European Rugby Challenge Cup: Newcastle F v Bordeaux 2017/18</n>    <k>A look back as the Newcastle Falcons and Bordeaux Begles clashed in Pool 1 of the 2017/18 European Challenge Cup at Kingston Park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-20 22:00:00" d="2020-04-21 01:00:00"><n>UFC: UFC 205: Alvarez v McGregor</n>    <k>We revisit UFC 205 in New York which saw Conor McGregor challenge Eddie Alvarez for his lightweight title. McGregor was hoping to make history by becoming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-21 01:00:00" d="2020-04-21 04:00:00"><n>UFC: UFC 204: Bisping v Henderson</n>    <k>We revisit UFC 204 in Manchester which saw Michael Bisping defend his middleweight title against fierce rival Dan Henderson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-21 04:00:00" d="2020-04-21 04:30:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing</n>    <k>Tyson Raw &amp; Uncut looks at Mike Tyson's unprecedented rise to the pinnacle of world boxing. This episode features his bouts against Hector Mercedes, Trent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-21 04:30:00" d="2020-04-21 05:00:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing</n>    <k>Tyson Raw &amp; Uncut looks at Mike Tyson's unprecedented rise to the pinnacle of world boxing. This episode features his bouts against Ricardo Spain</k>  </p>
</a>
