<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2020-05-29 04:31:34"><p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 05:00:00" d="2020-06-05 06:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: ODI Classic Cricket: Aus v NZ">Cricket Classics: ODI Classic Cricket: Aus v NZ 1986</n>    <k>We revisit the classic ODI cricket match between Australia and New Zealand in 1986 at Sydney Cricket Ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 06:00:00" d="2020-06-05 07:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v NZ">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v NZ 1988</n>    <k>We revisit the 10th match of the 1988 World Series Cup between Australia and New Zealand in Brisbane</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 07:00:00" d="2020-06-05 08:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1982/83</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 26th February 1983, features Manchester United v Liverpool, Watford v Aston Villa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 08:00:00" d="2020-06-05 08:45:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1982/83</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 5th March 1983, features Liverpool v Stoke, Sunderland v Everton and Notts County v Tottenham</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 08:45:00" d="2020-06-05 09:00:00"><n>Classic MOTD - Thrillers: West Ham v Arsenal 1983/84</n>    <k>We delve into the Match of the Day archives to revisit highlights of the 1983/84 First Division clash between West Ham and Arsenal at the Boleyn Ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 09:00:00" d="2020-06-05 10:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1982/83</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 12th March 1983, features action from the FA Cup as Man United met Everton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 10:00:00" d="2020-06-05 11:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1982/83</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 19th March 1983, features West Ham v Stoke, Oldham v Fulham and Southampton v Manchester City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 11:00:00" d="2020-06-05 11:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Tottenham v Arsenal 2004/05</n>    <k>Only needing a point to clinch the 2003/04 Premier League title, Arsenal made the short trip to White Hart Lane to take on fierce rivals Tottenham in this pulsating clash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 11:30:00" d="2020-06-05 12:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Arsenal v Tottenham 2011/12</n>    <k>We revisit the 2011/12 Premier League classic between Arsenal and Tottenham at the Emirates. This enthralling north London derby saw the Gunners mount a dramatic comeback</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 12:00:00" d="2020-06-05 12:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Tottenham v Arsenal 2010/11</n>    <k>Revisit the 2010/11 Premier League clash between Tottenham and Arsenal. The Gunners' title hopes were dealt a blow as the hosts came from 3-1 down to earn a point</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 12:30:00" d="2020-06-05 13:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Arsenal v Tottenham 2018/19</n>    <k>Relive this scintillating and eventful North London Derby from 2018 as bitter rivals Arsenal and Tottenham met in the Premier League at the Emirates Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 13:00:00" d="2020-06-05 13:30:00"><n u="FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Man Utd v Liverpool">FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Man Utd v Liverpool 1985</n>    <k>We revisit the 1985 FA Cup semi-final tie between Manchester United and Liverpool. Going into this match, Liverpool had only beaten United twice in 20 league encounters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 13:30:00" d="2020-06-05 14:00:00"><n u="FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Everton v Liverpool">FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Everton v Liverpool 1991</n>    <k>We revisit the 1991 FA Cup fifth round replay between Everton and Liverpool at Goodison Park. This eight-goal thriller is regarded</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 14:00:00" d="2020-06-05 15:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season: Guingamp v Monaco 2015/16</n>    <k>We revisit the 2015/16 clash between Guingamp and Monaco at the Stade du Roudourou. The back and forth six-goal thriller was an early contender for game of the season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 15:00:00" d="2020-06-05 16:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Eng">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Eng 1987</n>    <k>We revisit the first final of the 1986/87 Benson &amp; Hedges World Series Cup between Australia and England at the Melbourne Cricket Ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 16:00:00" d="2020-06-05 17:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Losail 2007</n>    <k>We revisit the historic 2007 Qatar Grand Prix at Losail. Casey Stoner was the worthy victor, taking his first ever win in the premier class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 17:00:00" d="2020-06-05 18:30:00"><n>UEFA Europa League: UEL Final: Chelsea v Arsenal 2019</n>    <k>Another chance to see the 2018/19 UEFA Europa League final between London rivals Arsenal and Chelsea. The Blues were looking to add a fifth European trophy to their cabinet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 18:30:00" d="2020-06-05 19:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Arsenal v Chelsea 2003/04</n>    <k>A look back at the second leg of the 2003/04 UEFA Champions League quarter-final between Arsenal and Chelsea at Highbury. The visitors had not beaten</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 19:00:00" d="2020-06-05 19:30:00"><n>Classic Ligue 1: Marseille v Paris Saint-Germain 2012/13</n>    <k>Classic Ligue 1 action from the 2012/13 season as Marseille hosted PSG</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 19:30:00" d="2020-06-05 20:01:00"><n>Classic Ligue 1: PSG v Brest 12/13</n>    <k>Paris Saint-Germain's penultimate game of the 2012/13 season saw the French giants seal a 3-1 win over the visitors, thanks to a sublime Zlatan Ibrahimovic free-kick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 20:01:00" d="2020-06-05 22:00:00"><n>BT Sport Fight Night: Fight Night: Smith v Munguia</n>    <k>Liam Smith travels to Las Vegas to take on Jaime Munguia for the WBO Junior Middleweight title. Smith gets a first shot at reclaiming the</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-05 22:00:00" d="2020-06-06 01:00:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing</n>    <k>Ringside - Rivalries I. A selection of the most famous rivalries in the history of boxing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 01:00:00" d="2020-06-06 03:00:00"><n>AFL: AFL: Richmond v GWS Giants 2019</n>    <k>Richmond face GWS Giants in the Grand Final of the AFL at the MCG. The Tigers are looking to win their second title in three years, while GWS star in their first ever final</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 03:00:00" d="2020-06-06 04:00:00"><n u="ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: Pazienza v Duran II">ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: Pazienza v Duran II 1995</n>    <k>We revisit the classic 1995 rematch between Vinny Pazienza and Roberto Duran</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 04:00:00" d="2020-06-06 05:00:00"><n>Hyundai A-League Highlights</n>    <k>A review of all the goals and talking points from this weekend's Hyundai A-League games</k>  </p>
</a>
