<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2020-05-31 04:30:58"><p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 05:00:00" d="2020-06-07 06:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: ODI Cricket Classic: Aus v NZ">Cricket Classics: ODI Cricket Classic: Aus v NZ 1991</n>    <k>A look back at the first final of the 1990/91 World Series Cup between Australia and New Zealand at the Sydney Cricket Ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 06:00:00" d="2020-06-07 07:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: ODI Cricket Classic: Aus v NZ">Cricket Classics: ODI Cricket Classic: Aus v NZ 1991</n>    <k>A look back at the second final of the 1990/91 World Series Cup between Australia and New Zealand at the Melbourne Cricket Ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 07:00:00" d="2020-06-07 08:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1982/83</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 24th April 1983, features Fulham v Leicester, Aberdeen v Celtic, Liverpool</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 08:00:00" d="2020-06-07 09:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1982/83</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 30th April 1983, features Tottenham v Liverpool, Sunderland v Birmingham</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 09:00:00" d="2020-06-07 10:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1982/83</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 7th May 1983, features Fulham v Carlisle, Oldham v Leicester, Birmingham v Spurs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 10:00:00" d="2020-06-07 11:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1982/83</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 15th May 1983, features Derby v Fulham, Leicester v Burnley, Bury v Wimbledon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 11:00:00" d="2020-06-07 12:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Premier League Review: 2013/14</n>    <k>A review of the 2013/14 season. Manchester City clinched their second Premier League title, Jose Mourinho returned to Chelsea and Tony Pulis masterminded</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 12:00:00" d="2020-06-07 13:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Premier League: Best Goals 2013/14</n>    <k>A look back at the top goals from the 2013/14 season. Luis Suarez - in his final season at Anfield - finished top scorer with 31 goals, 10 ahead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 13:00:00" d="2020-06-07 14:30:00"><n>ODI Cricket Highlights: Australia v England - 2nd ODI 2018</n>    <k>A look back at the 2nd ODI between Australia and England from The Gabba in Brisbane. The tourists were looking to go 2-0 up in the series after a thrilling 1st ODI victory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 14:30:00" d="2020-06-07 16:00:00"><n>European Rugby - Top Ten Games of the Season: Clermont v Saracens 2016/17</n>    <k>We revisit the 2016/17 European Champions Cup final between Clermont Auvergne and Saracens at BT Murrayfield. Saracens, unbeaten in 17 games, were looking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 16:00:00" d="2020-06-07 17:01:00"><n u="MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Donington">MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Donington 1993</n>    <k>We revisit the incident-packed 1993 British Grand Prix at Donington as the battle for the title raged on between Americans and arch-rivals Kevin Schwantz and Wayne Rainey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 17:01:00" d="2020-06-07 17:30:00"><n>Gallagher Premiership Rugby Highlights: Aviva Premiership: Top Tries 16/17</n>    <k>The pick of the best tries from the 2016/17 Aviva Premiership campaign, including efforts from Jimmy Gopperth and JP Pietersen. Plus, interviews</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 17:30:00" d="2020-06-07 18:00:00"><n>Premier League Legends: PL Legends: David Ginola</n>    <k>The Premier League career of David Ginola, the charismatic French winger who made 195 appearances during spells with Newcastle United, Tottenham Hotspur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 18:00:00" d="2020-06-07 18:30:00"><n>Premier League Legends: PL Legends: Jamie Carragher</n>    <k>A look at the remarkable footballing journey of Jamie Carragher, who devoted his entire playing career to Liverpool, making an incredible 508 appearances for the Reds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 18:30:00" d="2020-06-07 19:00:00"><n>Classics in Europe: Liverpool v AZ Alkmaar 1981/82</n>    <k>We revisit the second leg of the 1981/82 European Cup second round between Liverpool and AZ Alkmaar. The first leg finished 2-2 thanks to goals from David</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 19:00:00" d="2020-06-07 19:30:00"><n u="FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Man Utd v Liverpool">FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Man Utd v Liverpool 1996</n>    <k>We revisit the 1996 FA Cup final between Manchester United and Liverpool. Eric Cantona was looking to become the first captain from outside the British</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 19:30:00" d="2020-06-07 20:00:00"><n u="UEFA Champions League - Classics: UCL: Ajax v Juventus">UEFA Champions League - Classics: UCL: Ajax v Juventus 1996</n>    <k>We revisit the 1996 final between Ajax and Juventus in Rome. Juve's talented side included Didier Deschamps, Antonio Conte and Gianluca Vialli</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 20:00:00" d="2020-06-07 22:00:00"><n>BT Sport Fight Night: Fight Night: Catterall v Davies</n>    <k>Jack Catterall and Ohara Davies meet in a super-lightweight bout at the Morningside Arena, Leicester. Heavyweight prospect Daniel Dubois and Olympian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 22:00:00" d="2020-06-08 01:00:00"><n>UFC: UFC 250 - Nunes v Spencer</n>    <k>Action from UFC 250 as Amanda Nunes and Felicia Spencer headline the card</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 01:00:00" d="2020-06-08 02:00:00"><n>UFC Main Event</n>    <k>Relive UFC 236 as Kelvin Gastelum took on Israel Adesanya for the middleweight title in Atlanta, Georgia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 02:00:00" d="2020-06-08 03:00:00"><n u="UFC: The Ultimate Fighter: UFC The Ultimate Fighter - Series">UFC: The Ultimate Fighter: UFC The Ultimate Fighter - Series 22</n>    <k>Episode 6. The 22nd series of the Ultimate Fighter sees a United States team, coached by veteran Urijah Faber, take on a European team, headed up by Irish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 03:00:00" d="2020-06-08 03:30:00"><n>UFC Ultimate Knockouts</n>    <k>Revisit some of UFC's most surprising and memorable knockouts. Featuring Junior Dos Santos, The Korean Zombie, Ronda Rousey, Jeremy Stephens, Darren</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 03:30:00" d="2020-06-08 04:00:00"><n>UFC Ultimate Knockouts</n>    <k>A compilation of some of the most devastating knee knockouts ever seen inside the octagon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-08 04:00:00" d="2020-06-08 05:00:00"><n>WRC Review: WRC Review: Rally Australia 2018</n>    <k>A look back at the best action from Rally Australia, as the 2018 World Rally Championship drew to a close</k>  </p>
</a>
