<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="28" t="2020-05-26 04:31:36"><p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 05:15:00" d="2020-06-02 05:30:00"><n>Sport in Focus: Ashes Masterclasses</n>    <k>Adam Gilchrist talks Michael Vaughan and Ricky Ponting through the art of wicket-keeping, drawing on his experiences keeping to Shane Warne and Glenn McGrath</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 05:30:00" d="2020-06-02 06:01:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v SA">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v SA 1994</n>    <k>We revisit day one of the 1994 second test series between Australia and South Africa at the Sydney Cricket Ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 06:01:00" d="2020-06-02 06:30:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v SA">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v SA 1994</n>    <k>We revisit day two of the 1994 second test series between Australia and South Africa at the Sydney Cricket Ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 06:30:00" d="2020-06-02 07:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v SA">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v SA 1994</n>    <k>We revisit day three of the 1994 second test series between Australia and South Africa at the Sydney Cricket Ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 07:00:00" d="2020-06-02 08:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1978/79</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 17th March 1979, features Nottingham Forest's clash with Southampton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 08:00:00" d="2020-06-02 09:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1978/79</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 24th March 1979, features West Ham v Newcastle, Cardiff v Stoke and Middlesbrough v Birmingham</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 09:00:00" d="2020-06-02 10:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1978/79</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 1st April 1979, features Liverpool v Manchester United and Aberdeen v Rangers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 10:00:00" d="2020-06-02 11:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1978/79</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 7th April 1979, features Leyton Orient v Brighton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 11:00:00" d="2020-06-02 11:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Liverpool v Tottenham 2017/18</n>    <k>Relive one of the most frantic finales to a game in recent Premier League history as Tottenham rescued a 2-2 draw with Liverpool in a stunning game at Anfield</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 11:30:00" d="2020-06-02 12:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Liverpool v Man City 2017/18</n>    <k>Relive one of the games of the 2017/18 Premier League season as Liverpool ended Manchester City's unbeaten run in a thrilling encounter with the league leaders at Anfield</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 12:00:00" d="2020-06-02 12:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Arsenal v Liverpool 2017/18</n>    <k>Revisit this incredible Premier League encounter between Arsenal and Liverpool at the Emirates Stadium. The Gunners scored three goals in just five second-half minutes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 12:30:00" d="2020-06-02 13:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Chelsea v Burnley 2017/18</n>    <k>Relive the 2017/18 Premier League tie between Chelsea and Sean Dyche's Burnley. The game had two red cards and five goals as Chelsea's title defence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 13:00:00" d="2020-06-02 13:30:00"><n u="FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Sunderland v Arsenal">FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Sunderland v Arsenal 1973</n>    <k>We revisit the 1973 FA Cup semi-final between Second Division side Sunderland and Arsenal at Hillsborough. This was the Black Cats' first semi-final</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 13:30:00" d="2020-06-02 14:00:00"><n u="FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Man Utd v Leeds">FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Man Utd v Leeds 1977</n>    <k>We revisit the 1977 FA Cup semi-final between Man Utd and Leeds Utd at Hillsborough. Continued crowd trouble throughout helped to cement the fierce rivalry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 14:00:00" d="2020-06-02 15:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season: Marseille v Bastia 2015/16</n>    <k>We revisit the 2015/16 Ligue 1 match-up between Marseille and Bastia at the Stade Velodrome</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 15:00:00" d="2020-06-02 16:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Eng">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Eng 1987</n>    <k>We revisit the fourth match of the 1986/87 World Series between Australia and England at the Sydney Cricket Ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 16:00:00" d="2020-06-02 17:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Losail 2008</n>    <k>We revisit the 2008 Qatar Grand Prix at the Losail International Circuit, the first ever night race. Casey Stoner began his title defence, while James</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 17:00:00" d="2020-06-02 18:00:00"><n>UEFA Europa League: Arsenal v Napoli 2018/19</n>    <k>Look back as Arsenal faced Napoli in the first leg of their 2018/19 Europa League quarter-final at the Emirates. The Gunners took the initiative against</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 18:00:00" d="2020-06-02 19:00:00"><n>UEFA Europa League: Chelsea v Slavia Prague 2018/19</n>    <k>Look back as Chelsea met Slavia Prague in the 2018/19 Europa League quarter-finals second leg. A late Marcos Alonso goal in Prague gave the Blues a slender</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 19:00:00" d="2020-06-02 19:30:00"><n>Classic Ligue 1: Lyon v Saint-Etienne 2005/06</n>    <k>A look back at an emphatic 4-0 win for Lyon over rivals Saint-Etienne in their 2005/06 French Ligue 1 title winning season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 19:30:00" d="2020-06-02 20:00:00"><n>Classic Ligue 1: Marseille v Rennes 2009/10</n>    <k>Your chance to look back on Marseille's 3-1 win over Rennes in their 2009/10 French Ligue 1 title winning season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 20:00:00" d="2020-06-02 22:00:00"><n>BT Sport Fight Night: Fight Night: Fury v Seferi</n>    <k>Tyson Fury made his return to the ring following nearly three years away from action as he faced Sefer Seferi at the Manchester Arena. Terry Flanagan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-02 22:00:00" d="2020-06-03 01:00:00"><n>UFC</n>    <k>Action from the UFC</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 01:00:00" d="2020-06-03 02:00:00"><n>UFC Main Event: UFC Main Event: Adesanya v Silva</n>    <k>We revisit UFC 234 at Rod Laver Arena in Melbourne, Australia, as rising star Israel Adesanya took on Brazil's Anderson Silva for the middleweight crown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 02:00:00" d="2020-06-03 03:00:00"><n u="UFC: The Ultimate Fighter: UFC The Ultimate Fighter - Series">UFC: The Ultimate Fighter: UFC The Ultimate Fighter - Series 22</n>    <k>Episode 2. The 22nd series of the Ultimate Fighter sees a United States team, coached by veteran Urijah Faber, take on a European team, headed up by Irish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 03:00:00" d="2020-06-03 03:30:00"><n>UFC Ultimate Knockouts</n>    <k>Revisit the greatest knockouts to take place inside the octagon in 2016, featuring Garbrandt v Almeida, Miocic v Werdum, Woodley v Lawler and Bisping v Rockhold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 03:30:00" d="2020-06-03 04:00:00"><n>UFC Ultimate Knockouts</n>    <k>Revisit some of UFC's most surprising and memorable knockouts. Featuring Junior Dos Santos, The Korean Zombie, Ronda Rousey, Jeremy Stephens, Darren Elkins and Nikita Krylov</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-03 04:00:00" d="2020-06-03 05:00:00"><n>Hyundai A-League Highlights</n>    <k>A review of all the goals and talking points from this weekend's Hyundai A-League games</k>  </p>
</a>
