<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2020-05-14 04:46:12"><p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 05:00:00" d="2020-05-21 06:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Brno 2003</n>    <k>We revisit the epic 2003 Czech Republic Grand Prix in Brno. A win for Sete Gibernau boosted his title chances as he dominated to finish ahead of Valentino</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 06:00:00" d="2020-05-21 07:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Losail 2013</n>    <k>We revisit the 2013 Qatar Grand Prix at the Losail International Circuit. After two wretched years in the Ducati team, Valentino Rossi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 07:00:00" d="2020-05-21 08:00:00"><n>Football Classics: Arsenal Classics</n>    <k>Classic Arsenal matches from the football archives, featuring memorable league victories against Liverpool (1990) and Aston Villa (1988). 8/8</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 08:00:00" d="2020-05-21 09:00:00"><n>Football Classics: Chelsea Classics</n>    <k>Classic Chelsea matches from the football archives, featuring memorable league clashes against Manchester City (1972) and Liverpool (1991). 1/8</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 09:00:00" d="2020-05-21 10:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1974/75</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 29th December 1974, features Millwall v Portsmouth, Sheffield Unitedv Arsenal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 10:00:00" d="2020-05-21 11:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1974/75</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 12th January 1975, features QPR v Burnley, Coventry v Wolves and Ipswich v Middlesbrough</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 11:00:00" d="2020-05-21 11:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Arsenal v Fulham 2012/13</n>    <k>We take a look back at this epic Premier League clash from the 2012/13 season as Arsenal and Fulham play out a six-goal thriller at the Emirates Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 11:30:00" d="2020-05-21 12:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Stoke City v Southampton 2012/13</n>    <k>We revisit a thriller at the Britannia between Stoke City and Southampton from the 2012/13 campaign. The Potters were undefeated in their previous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 12:00:00" d="2020-05-21 12:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Cardiff v Manchester City 2013/14</n>    <k>We look back as Cardiff City entertained Manchester City in August 2013. The hosts were hoping to stun the 2011-12 champions and claim their first victory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 12:30:00" d="2020-05-21 13:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Arsenal v Liverpool 2017/18</n>    <k>Revisit this incredible Premier League encounter between Arsenal and Liverpool at the Emirates Stadium. The Gunners scored three goals in just five second-half minutes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 13:00:00" d="2020-05-21 13:30:00"><n>FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Arsenal v Chelsea 2017</n>    <k>We revisit the 2017 FA Cup final between Arsenal and Chelsea. Under-pressure Gunners boss, Arsene Wenger, was aiming to become the most successful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 13:30:00" d="2020-05-21 14:00:00"><n>FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Chelsea v Man Utd 2018</n>    <k>We revisit the 2018 FA Cup final between Chelsea and Manchester United. Manchester United were aiming to win the trophy a record-equaling 13 times</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 14:00:00" d="2020-05-21 14:30:00"><n>The Emirates FA Cup: FA Cup: Man City v Watford</n>    <k>Relive the goal-laden 2018/19 Emirates FA Cup final between Manchester City, who were chasing a domestic treble, and Javi Gracia's Watford. City hadn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 14:30:00" d="2020-05-21 15:30:00"><n>The Emirates FA Cup: The FA Cup: Behind The Dream</n>    <k>A collection of stories from The FA Cup. From the extra preliminary round all the way to the final, profiling the characters taking part in the world's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 15:30:00" d="2020-05-21 16:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Stories of the Finals</n>    <k>We take a look back at Manchester United's historic UEFA Champions League final win over Bayern Munich in 1999 and Liverpool's epic victory over AC Milan in 2005</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 16:00:00" d="2020-05-21 17:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season: Monaco v Strasbourg 2018/19</n>    <k>Relive all the action as Monaco met Strasbourg at the Stade Louis II in Ligue 1. Struggling Monaco were looking to end a 10-game winless run at home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 17:00:00" d="2020-05-21 18:30:00"><n>UEFA Europa League: Liverpool v Sevilla 2015/16</n>    <k>Liverpool faced holders Sevilla in the 2015/16 Europa League final at St Jakob-Park in Basel. The Reds had won eight of the 11 European finals that they had appeared in</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 18:30:00" d="2020-05-21 19:30:00"><n>UEFA Europa League: Man Utd v Fenerbahce 2016/17</n>    <k>Manchester United hosted Fenerbahce in Group A of the 2016/17 Europa League at Old Trafford, as Fenerbahce's Robin Van Persie was reunited with his former club</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 19:30:00" d="2020-05-21 20:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Stories of the Finals</n>    <k>Take a look back at the 2009 final between Barcelona and Manchester United. Plus, relive the first ever all-Spanish final in European Cup history between</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 20:00:00" d="2020-05-21 20:30:00"><n u="ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: Laing v Mittee">ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: Laing v Mittee 1987</n>    <k>We revisit this classic clash from March 1987 as Kirkland Laing and Sylvester Mittee went head-to-head for the vacant BBBofC British welterweight title in London</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 20:30:00" d="2020-05-21 21:00:00"><n u="ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: Bruno v Bugner">ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: Bruno v Bugner 1987</n>    <k>We rewind the clock to the heavyweight clash between Australian Joe Bugner and home-favourite Frank Bruno at White Hart Lane in 1987</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 21:00:00" d="2020-05-21 21:30:00"><n u="ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: McGuigan v McDonnell">ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: McGuigan v McDonnell 1989</n>    <k>We revisit the classic bout between Barry McGuigan and Jim McDonnell in May 1989 at the G-Mex Centre, Manchester</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 21:30:00" d="2020-05-21 22:00:00"><n u="ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: McCrory v Lumumba">ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: McCrory v Lumumba 1989</n>    <k>We revisit this epic IBF world cruiserweight title bout from June 1989 between Glenn 'Gentleman' McCrory and Patrick 'Killer' Lumumba at the Louisa Centre in County Durham</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-21 22:00:00" d="2020-05-22 01:00:00"><n u="UFC: UFC 241 - Cormier v Miocic">UFC: UFC 241 - Cormier v Miocic 2</n>    <k>A look back at UFC 241 as Heavyweight champion Daniel Cormier defended his title in a hotly-anticipated rematch against Stipe Miocic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-22 01:00:00" d="2020-05-22 04:00:00"><n>UFC: UFC 242 - Khabib v Poirier</n>    <k>All the action from UFC 242 as Khabib Nurmagomedov fought Dustin Poirier in Abu Dhabi. This show may contain flashing images and scenes of violence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-22 04:00:00" d="2020-05-22 04:30:00"><n>WRC Review: WRC Review: Rally Estonia 2019</n>    <k>Relive the best action from the World Rally Championship Promotional Event in Estonia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-22 04:30:00" d="2020-05-22 05:00:00"><n>WRC Classic: WRC Classic: WRC19 Rewind</n>    <k>A look back at some of the most extraordinary moments from the World Rally Championship in recent years, including the incredible moment Ott Tanak's Fiesta</k>  </p>
</a>
