<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2020-04-09 04:28:43"><p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-16 05:00:00" d="2020-04-16 06:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Jerez 2005</n>    <k>We revisit the 2005 Spanish Grand Prix at Jerez which saw home favourite Sete Gibernau and world champion Valentino Rossi embroiled in a fierce duel during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-16 06:00:00" d="2020-04-16 07:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Mugello 2005</n>    <k>We revisit the 2005 Italian Grand Prix at Mugello as Valentino Rossi locked horns with Max Biaggi, Loris Capirossi and Marco Melandri for</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-16 07:00:00" d="2020-04-16 08:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1974/75</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 12th January 1975, features QPR v Burnley, Coventry v Wolves and Ipswich v Middlesbrough</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-16 08:00:00" d="2020-04-16 09:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1974/75</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 26th January 1975, features West Ham v Swindon, Coventry v Arsenal and Leeds v Wimbledon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-16 09:00:00" d="2020-04-16 10:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1974/75</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 2nd February 1975, features Arsenal v Liverpool, Southend v Preston and Stoke v Man City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-16 10:00:00" d="2020-04-16 11:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1974/75</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-16 11:00:00" d="2020-04-16 11:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Arsenal v Liverpool 2017/18</n>    <k>Revisit this incredible Premier League encounter between Arsenal and Liverpool at the Emirates Stadium. The Gunners scored three goals in just five second-half minutes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-16 11:30:00" d="2020-04-16 12:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Chelsea v Burnley 2017/18</n>    <k>Relive the 2017/18 Premier League tie between Chelsea and Sean Dyche's Burnley. The game had two red cards and five goals as Chelsea's title defence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-16 12:00:00" d="2020-04-16 12:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Arsenal v Leicester City 2017/18</n>    <k>Take a look back as late drama helped Arsenal fight back to beat Leicester City in a thrilling start to the 2017-18 Premier League season at the Emirates Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-16 12:30:00" d="2020-04-16 13:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Newcastle v Liverpool 2018/19</n>    <k>Take a look back as title-chasing Liverpool visited Newcastle in the Premier League. Divock Origi's late winner ensured the title race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-16 13:00:00" d="2020-04-16 14:30:00"><n>Gallagher Premiership Rugby Union: Northampton Saints v Exeter Chiefs</n>    <k>Northampton Saints and Exeter Chiefs clash in the Gallagher Premiership at Franklin's Gardens. Exeter ended Saracens' unbeaten run last time out to return</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-16 14:30:00" d="2020-04-16 16:00:00"><n>Gallagher Premiership Rugby Union: Northampton Saints v Gloucester</n>    <k>Relive the Gallagher Premiership clash between Northampton Saints and Gloucester from April 2019. The Saints had lost just once at Franklin's Gardens since early December</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-16 16:00:00" d="2020-04-16 17:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Pak">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Pak 1993</n>    <k>We revisit the 11th match of the 1992/93 World Series between Australia and Pakistan at the Melbourne Cricket Ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-16 17:00:00" d="2020-04-16 18:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Pak">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v Pak 1993</n>    <k>We revisit the 12th match of the 1992/93 World Series between Australia and Pakistan at the Sydney Cricket Ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-16 18:00:00" d="2020-04-16 19:00:00"><n>WRC Classic: WRC Classic: 2004 Season Review</n>    <k>A look back at the 2004 World Rally Championship. A gruelling 16-round season saw Sebastien Loeb establish himself as the man to beat ahead of a star-studded chasing pack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-16 19:00:00" d="2020-04-16 19:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Liverpool v Chelsea 2004/05</n>    <k>We revisit the dramatic 2004/05 UEFA Champions League semi-final second leg between Liverpool and Chelsea at Anfield. The tie was finely poised after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-16 19:30:00" d="2020-04-16 20:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Celtic v Manchester United 2006/07</n>    <k>We revisit the 2006/07 UEFA Champions League group stage tie between Celtic and Man Utd at Parkhead. A win for Celtic would guarantee a place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-16 20:00:00" d="2020-04-16 20:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: R.Madrid v A.Madrid 2013/14</n>    <k>The 2013/14 UEFA Champions League final in Lisbon saw Real Madrid go head-to-head with arch-rivals Atletico Madrid. Real aimed to become the first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-16 20:30:00" d="2020-04-16 21:00:00"><n u="FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Everton v Liverpool">FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Everton v Liverpool 1991</n>    <k>We revisit the 1991 FA Cup fifth round replay between Everton and Liverpool at Goodison Park. This eight-goal thriller is regarded</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-16 21:00:00" d="2020-04-16 21:30:00"><n u="FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Tottenham v Arsenal">FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Tottenham v Arsenal 1991</n>    <k>We revisit the thrilling 1991 FA Cup semi-final tie between fierce rivals Tottenham and Arsenal. This was the first time that an FA Cup semi-final</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-16 21:30:00" d="2020-04-16 22:00:00"><n u="FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Liverpool v B'ham">FA Cup Classics: FA Cup: Liverpool v B'ham 1995</n>    <k>We revisit the dramatic 1995 FA Cup third round replay between Liverpool and Birmingham at Anfield. Second Division leaders Birmingham held</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-16 22:00:00" d="2020-04-17 01:00:00"><n>UFC: UFC 200: Tate v Nunes</n>    <k>We revisit UFC 200 in Las Vegas which saw Miesha Tate defend her bantamweight title against Amanda Nunes. Plus, returning WWE superstar Brock Lesnar took on Mark Hunt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 01:00:00" d="2020-04-17 04:00:00"><n>UFC: UFC 201: Lawler v Woodley</n>    <k>We revisit UFC 201 from Atlanta which featured the highly-anticipated welterweight title bout between champion Robbie Lawler and challenger Tyron Woodley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 04:00:00" d="2020-04-17 04:30:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing: Classic Boxing: McGuigan v McDonnell</n>    <k>We revisit the classic bout between Barry McGuigan and Jim McDonnell in May 1989 at the G-Mex Centre, Manchester</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-04-17 04:30:00" d="2020-04-17 05:00:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing: Classic Boxing: McCrory v Lumumba</n>    <k>We revisit this epic IBF world cruiserweight title bout from June 1989 between Glenn 'Gentleman' McCrory and Patrick 'Killer' Lumumba at the Louisa Centre in County Durham</k>  </p>
</a>
