<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2020-05-30 04:31:18"><p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 05:00:00" d="2020-06-06 06:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v NZ">Cricket Classics: Cricket Classics: Aus v NZ 1988</n>    <k>A look back at the enthralling second final of the 1987/88 World Series Cup between Australia and New Zealand at Sydney Cricket Ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 06:00:00" d="2020-06-06 07:00:00"><n u="Cricket Classics: ODI Cricket Classic: Aus v NZ">Cricket Classics: ODI Cricket Classic: Aus v NZ 1990</n>    <k>A look back at the 10th match of the 1990/91 World Series Cup between Australia and New Zealand at the Bellerive Oval</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 07:00:00" d="2020-06-06 08:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1982/83</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 26th March 1983, features Fulham v Grimsby, Norwich v West Ham and Nottingham</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 08:00:00" d="2020-06-06 09:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1982/83</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 9th April 1983, features Luton Town v Aston Villa, Newcastle v Blackburn and West Brom v Watford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 09:00:00" d="2020-06-06 10:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1982/83</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 16th April 1983, features FA Cup action as Sheffield Wednesday met Brighton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 10:00:00" d="2020-06-06 11:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Premier League Review: 2012/13</n>    <k>A review of the 2012/13 season. Sir Alex Ferguson ended his managerial career as Manchester United clinched their 13th Premier League title</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 11:00:00" d="2020-06-06 12:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Premier League: Best Goals 2012/13</n>    <k>A look back at the top strikes from the 2012/13 season. Robin van Persie finished top of the charts with 26 goals, three ahead of Luis Suarez</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 12:00:00" d="2020-06-06 13:30:00"><n>ODI Cricket Highlights: Australia v England - 1st ODI 2018</n>    <k>A look back at the opening ODI between Australia and England at the MCG. The tourists were set a target of 305 after Aaron Finch starred for Australia with a score of 107</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 13:30:00" d="2020-06-06 15:00:00"><n>European Rugby - Top Ten Games of the Season: Munster Rugby v Saracens 2016/17</n>    <k>We revisit the 2016/17 European Champions Cup semi-final between Munster and Saracens at Thomond Park. Saracens were aiming to reach a third Champions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 15:00:00" d="2020-06-06 17:30:00"><n>Live Bundesliga: Eintracht Frankfurt v Mainz</n>    <k>Eintracht Frankfurt v FSV Mainz 05 (Kick-off 2.30pm). Coverage of the German top-flight clash at Commerzbank-Arena</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 17:30:00" d="2020-06-06 18:00:00"><n>Premier League Legends: PL Legends: Peter Schmeichel</n>    <k>An in-depth look at five-time Premier League champion Peter Schmeichel, who is seen as a real contender for the greatest goalkeeper to have ever played</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 18:00:00" d="2020-06-06 18:30:00"><n>Premier League Legends: PL Legends: Robert Pires</n>    <k>This episode profiles Robert Pires, who was an ever-present and iconic figure in Arsenal's Invincibles team and went on to make 189 appearances for the Gunners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 18:30:00" d="2020-06-06 20:00:00"><n>BT Sport Fight Night: Warrington v Frampton</n>    <k>Josh Warrington defends his IBF world featherweight title against Carl Frampton at the Manchester Arena</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 20:00:00" d="2020-06-06 20:15:00"><n>No Filter Boxing: Warrington v Frampton: Review</n>    <k>A behind-the-scenes look at one of the fights of 2018 as Josh Warrington put his IBF featherweight world title on the line against Carl Frampton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 20:15:00" d="2020-06-06 20:30:00"><n>Sport in Focus: Sport in Focus: Dubois v Jones</n>    <k>Take a look back as Daniel Dubois continued his devastating knockout streak against fellow Brit David Jones in February 2018 at York Hall in London</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 20:30:00" d="2020-06-06 21:00:00"><n u="Classics in Europe: Liverpool v Aberdeen">Classics in Europe: Liverpool v Aberdeen 1980</n>    <k>With a 1-0 first leg deficit to overturn, a 38-year-old Alex Ferguson took his Aberdeen side to Anfield to face Liverpool in the second round of the 1980 European Cup</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 21:00:00" d="2020-06-06 21:30:00"><n>Classics in Europe: Dundee United v Roma 1983/84</n>    <k>We revisit the first leg of the 1983/84 European Cup semi-finals as Dundee United, playing in their first and only top flight European campaign</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 21:30:00" d="2020-06-06 22:00:00"><n u="Classics in Europe: Nottingham Forest v Liverpool">Classics in Europe: Nottingham Forest v Liverpool 1978</n>    <k>Brian Clough's Nottingham Forest hosted holders Liverpool, boasting the likes of Kenny Dalglish, in this enthralling European Cup first round clash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 22:00:00" d="2020-06-06 22:31:00"><n>UFC Fight Camp: SC: UFC Fight Camp</n>    <k>Exclusive access, interviews and features with fighters, analysis from experts and the best from the world of UFC ahead of 250</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 22:31:00" d="2020-06-06 23:00:00"><n>Classic Premiership Rugby: Premiership Rugby Top Tries 15/16</n>    <k>The top tries of the 2015/16 Aviva Premiership campaign</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-06 23:00:00" d="2020-06-07 00:00:00"><n u="MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Donington">MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Donington 1992</n>    <k>We revisit the thrilling 1992 British Grand Prix at Donington. Having announced that he would retire at the end of the season, Wayne Gardner scored</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 00:00:00" d="2020-06-07 03:00:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing</n>    <k>Ringside - Rivalries II. A selection of the most famous rivalries in the history of boxing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 03:00:00" d="2020-06-07 04:15:00"><n u="ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: Ali v Lyle">ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: Ali v Lyle 1975</n>    <k>Another chance to see the classic 1975 fight between Muhammad Ali and Ron Lyle in Las Vegas. Lyle later claimed he was `robbed of the greatest honour in all sport'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 04:15:00" d="2020-06-07 04:30:00"><n u="ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: Ali v Quarry I">ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: Ali v Quarry I 1970</n>    <k>Another chance to watch the classic 1970 bout between Muhammad Ali and Jerry Quarry in Atlanta. The fight marked Ali's return to the ring after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-06-07 04:30:00" d="2020-06-07 05:00:00"><n u="ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: Ali v Liston II">ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: Ali v Liston II 1965</n>    <k>Another chance to watch the classic 1965 rematch between Muhammad Ali and Sonny Liston in Lewiston, Maine</k>  </p>
</a>
