<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2019-07-11 00:18:51"><p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-17 05:00:00" d="2019-07-17 05:30:00"><n>Bundesliga Special: Bundesliga Special Robben &amp; Ribery</n>    <k>A look at the remarkable Bundesliga journeys of Arjen Robben and Franck Ribery, two Bayern Munich icons, who will both be moving on from the club at the end of the season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-17 05:30:00" d="2019-07-17 06:30:00"><n>Nine for IX: Let Them Wear Towels</n>    <k>The documentary examines how female sports writers battled for equal access to male locker rooms. Part of ESPN's Nine for IX series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-17 06:30:00" d="2019-07-17 07:00:00"><n>Bundesliga Special</n>    <k>The Bundesliga has more French players in it than ever before and this week we look at World Cup winners Corentin Tolisso and Benjamin Pavard who ply their trade in Germany</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-17 07:00:00" d="2019-07-17 08:00:00"><n>MotoGP Highlights</n>    <k>The best of the action from the Grand Prix of Spain, round four of the 2019 season. Spanish trio Marc Marquez, Alex Rins and Maverick Vinales</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-17 08:00:00" d="2019-07-17 09:00:00"><n>MotoGP Highlights</n>    <k>The best of the action from the Grand Prix of France, round five of the season. Marc Marquez, winner of five of the last six titles, put in another</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-17 09:00:00" d="2019-07-17 10:00:00"><n>MotoGP Highlights</n>    <k>A round-up of all the action from the Grand Prix of Italy, round six of the 2019 season. Home favourite Danilo Petrucci claimed his first MotoGP</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-17 10:00:00" d="2019-07-17 11:00:00"><n>MotoGP Films: MotoGP Films: Moto2 &amp; Moto3 Review 2013</n>    <k>A look back at the blistering 2013 season in Moto2 and Moto3</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-17 11:00:00" d="2019-07-17 12:00:00"><n>MotoGP Films: MotoGP Films: MotoGP 2013 Review</n>    <k>A look back at the 2013 season, featuring racing action, interviews and behind-the-scenes coverage. British hope Cal Crutchlow was among the riders battling for glory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-17 12:00:00" d="2019-07-17 14:00:00"><n>SGB Premiership: SGB: Peterborough v Belle Vue</n>    <k>Action from the SGB Premiership as Peterborough host Belle Vue at the East of England Showground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-17 14:00:00" d="2019-07-17 15:00:00"><n>British RallyCross Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from round three of the British Rallycross Championship at Pembrey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-17 15:00:00" d="2019-07-17 16:00:00"><n>Formula E Championship: Formula E Championship Highlights</n>    <k>All the thrills and spills from the Formula E Championship season finale in New York, USA</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-17 16:00:00" d="2019-07-17 17:00:00"><n>Euroformula Open Championship</n>    <k>Highlights of races one and two from round six of the Euroformula Championship at The Red Bull Ring in Austria</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-17 17:00:00" d="2019-07-17 17:30:00"><n>Irish Rally Review</n>    <k>Highlights of the Donegal International Rally, part of the Irish Rally series. (2/2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-17 17:30:00" d="2019-07-17 18:30:00"><n>Fishing: On The Bank</n>    <k>Highlights of the 2018 World Predator Classic hosted by the city of Hellevoetsluis in the Netherlands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-17 18:30:00" d="2019-07-17 19:00:00"><n>BT Sport Reload</n>    <k>The best bits from BT Sport from the last week, exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-17 19:00:00" d="2019-07-17 20:00:00"><n>Virgin Australia Supercars Championship Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from race 17 of the Virgin Australia Supercars Championship in Townsville</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-17 20:00:00" d="2019-07-17 21:00:00"><n>Virgin Australia Supercars Championship Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from race 18 of the Virgin Australia Supercars Championship in Townsville</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-17 21:00:00" d="2019-07-17 22:00:00"><n>UEFA Women's Champions League: Lyon Women v Barcelona Women</n>    <k>Lyon Women and Barcelona Women face-off in the final of the UEFA Women's Champions League in Budapest, Hungary. Lyon are hoping to lift the trophy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-17 22:00:00" d="2019-07-18 00:00:00"><n>SGB Premiership: SGB: Peterborough v Belle Vue</n>    <k>Action from the SGB Premiership as Peterborough host Belle Vue at the East of England Showground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-18 00:00:00" d="2019-07-18 01:00:00"><n>UFC Main Event</n>    <k>Relive all the action from UFC 235 as Jon Jones made his return to the Octagon to fight Anthony Smith in a light heavyweight bout at the T-Mobile Arena in Las Vegas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-18 01:00:00" d="2019-07-18 02:00:00"><n>UFC: The Ultimate Fighter</n>    <k>Anthony Pettis and Gilbert Melendez lead 16 fighters to a shot at UFC glory. In this episode, Urijah Faber steps in as Team Pettis' temporary coach for the day (S20, Ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-18 02:00:00" d="2019-07-18 03:00:00"><n>UFC: The Ultimate Fighter</n>    <k>Anthony Pettis and Gilbert Melendez lead 16 fighters to a shot at UFC glory. This week, a serious injury for Justine Kish means she has to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-18 03:00:00" d="2019-07-18 04:00:00"><n>UFC: The Ultimate Fighter</n>    <k>Anthony Pettis and Gilbert Melendez lead 16 fighters to a shot at UFC glory. In this episode, Tecia Torres continues to struggle to get along</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2019-07-18 04:00:00" d="2019-07-18 05:00:00"><n>UFC: The Ultimate Fighter</n>    <k>Anthony Pettis and Gilbert Melendez lead 16 fighters to a shot at UFC glory. In this episode, Team Melandez's losing streak creates a total divide in the camp (S20, Ep7)</k>  </p>
</a>
