<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-05-10 04:20:46"><p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-17 05:00:00" d="2020-05-17 06:00:00"><n>WRC Classic: WRC Classic: 2007 Craziest Moments</n>    <k>A look back at some of the craziest moments from the 2007 season of the World Rally Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-17 06:00:00" d="2020-05-17 07:00:00"><n>WRC Classic: WRC History: The Modern Era</n>    <k>A look back at the modern history of the World Rally Championship between 1987 and 2008</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-17 07:00:00" d="2020-05-17 08:00:00"><n>Football Classics: Football Classics: Play-Off Passion</n>    <k>A look back at classic play-off games from the football archives, including Charlton v Sunderland (1998), Swindon v Leicester (1993) and Leicester v Derby (1994). 1/2</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-17 08:00:00" d="2020-05-17 09:00:00"><n>Football Classics: Football Classics: Play-Off Passion</n>    <k>A look back at classic play-off games from the archives, including Gillingham v Manchester City (1999), Gillingham v Wigan (2000) and Birmingham v Norwich (2002). 2/2</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-17 09:00:00" d="2020-05-17 10:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1974/75</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 8th September 1974, features Fulham v York, Man Utd v Nottingham Forest and Notts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-17 10:00:00" d="2020-05-17 11:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1974/75</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 15th September 1974, features Chelsea v Arsenal, Newcastle v Carlisle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-17 11:00:00" d="2020-05-17 11:30:00"><n u="FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Arsenal v Sheff Weds">FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Arsenal v Sheff Weds 1993</n>    <k>We revisit the 1993 FA Cup final replay between Arsenal and Sheffield Wednesday. The original match finished 1-1, with a goal apiece from Ian Wright and David Hirst</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-17 11:30:00" d="2020-05-17 12:00:00"><n u="FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Chelsea v Man Utd">FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Chelsea v Man Utd 1994</n>    <k>We revisit the 1994 FA Cup final between Chelsea and Manchester United, who were looking to win the competition for an eighth time, matching the record</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-17 12:00:00" d="2020-05-17 12:30:00"><n u="FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Everton v Man Utd">FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Everton v Man Utd 1995</n>    <k>We revisit the 1995 FA Cup final between Everton and holders Manchester United. United were looking to avoid having their first barren season for six years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-17 12:30:00" d="2020-05-17 13:00:00"><n u="FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Man Utd v Liverpool">FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Man Utd v Liverpool 1996</n>    <k>We revisit the 1996 FA Cup final between Manchester United and Liverpool. Eric Cantona was looking to become the first captain from outside the British</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-17 13:00:00" d="2020-05-17 14:00:00"><n>Bundesliga: Games of the Season: Bayern M v Hoffenheim 2017/18</n>    <k>We look back at Bayern Munich's clash with Hoffenheim. Bayern Munich will be out for revenge when they meet Hoffenheim having lost the last two Bundesliga</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-17 14:00:00" d="2020-05-17 14:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Barcelona v Arsenal 2005/06</n>    <k>The 2005/06 UEFA Champions League final in Paris saw Arsenal face a pre-Lionel Messi Barcelona, then under the command of Frank Rijkaard, and featuring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-17 14:30:00" d="2020-05-17 15:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Barcelona v Arsenal 2009/10</n>    <k>We revisit the 2009/10 UEFA Champions League quarter-final second leg between Barcelona and Arsenal at the Nou Camp. An entertaining first leg ended</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-17 15:00:00" d="2020-05-17 16:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season: Lyon v Marseille 2018/19</n>    <k>We revisit the 2018/19 Ligue 1 season as Lyon hosted Marseille at the Groupama Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-17 16:00:00" d="2020-05-17 17:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season: PSG v Reims 2018/19</n>    <k>Relive all the action from the 2018/19 Ligue 1 season as PSG hosted Reims at the Parc des Princes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-17 17:00:00" d="2020-05-17 18:30:00"><n>European Rugby - Top Ten Games of the Season: Toulouse v Wasps 2016/17</n>    <k>We revisit 2016/17's enthralling European Champions Cup clash between Pool 2 rivals Toulouse and Wasps. This dramatic encounter featured a crucial last-gasp conversion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-17 18:30:00" d="2020-05-17 20:00:00"><n>European Rugby - Top Ten Games of the Season: Munster v Leicester Tigers 2016/17</n>    <k>We revisit 2016/17's European Champions Cup clash between Pool 1 rivals Munster and Leicester Tigers. The match saw the visitors suffer their worst-ever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-17 20:00:00" d="2020-05-17 20:15:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing: Classic Boxing: Monzon v Napoles</n>    <k>We revisit this classic bout from 1974 between Carlos Monzon, making his ninth defence of the World Middleweight Championship and Jose Napoles in Puteaux</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-17 20:15:00" d="2020-05-17 20:45:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing: Classic Boxing: Ali v Blin</n>    <k>We revisit this classic heavyweight bout from December 1971 as Muhammad Ali travelled to Zurich in Switzerland on a mission to become the first man to stop Juergen Blin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-17 20:45:00" d="2020-05-17 22:00:00"><n u="ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: Ali v Frazier III">ESPN Classic Boxing: Boxing: Ali v Frazier III 1975</n>    <k>We revisit the epic 1975 bout between Muhammad Ali and Joe Frazier in the Philippines. Dubbed the `Thrilla in Manilla', the fight is regarded</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-17 22:00:00" d="2020-05-18 01:00:00"><n>UFC: UFC Fight Night: Overeem v Harris</n>    <k>UFC Fight Night action as Alistair Overeem faces Walt Harris in Jacksonville</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 01:00:00" d="2020-05-18 04:00:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing</n>    <k>Ringside - Rivalries II. A selection of the most famous rivalries in the history of boxing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-18 04:00:00" d="2020-05-18 05:00:00"><n>WRC Classic: Greatest Drivers: Carlos Sainz</n>    <k>A look at the incredible career of two-time former World Rally champion Carlos Sainz. Sainz, who also finished runner-up four times, holds the WRC record</k>  </p>
</a>
