<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-05-16 04:44:39"><p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-23 05:00:00" d="2020-05-23 06:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Losail 2014</n>    <k>We revisit the 2014 Qatar Grand Prix at the Losail International Circuit. This thrilling season-opener saw an epic duel between Honda's Marc Marquez</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-23 06:00:00" d="2020-05-23 07:00:00"><n>MotoGP Classics: MotoGP Classics: Barcelona 2014</n>    <k>We revisit the 2014 Catalan Grand Prix in Barcelona. This thriller saw an epic three-way battle for the top of the podium between Marc Marquez, Valentino</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-23 07:00:00" d="2020-05-23 08:00:00"><n>Football Classics: Chelsea Classics</n>    <k>Classic Chelsea matches from the football archives, featuring the 1982 FA Cup fifth round clash against Liverpool and the 1998 League Cup third round</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-23 08:00:00" d="2020-05-23 09:00:00"><n>Football Classics: Chelsea Classics</n>    <k>Classic Chelsea matches from the football archives, featuring memorable league clashes against Crystal Palace (1972) and Manchester United (1990). 5/8</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-23 09:00:00" d="2020-05-23 10:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1976/77</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 22nd August 1976, features Tranmere v Chester, Arsenal v Bristol City and Ipswich v Tottenham</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-23 10:00:00" d="2020-05-23 11:00:00"><n>The Big Match Revisited: The Big Match Revisited - 1976/77</n>    <k>A look back at some classic editions of The Big Match. This episode, from 3rd October 1976, features Brighton v Crystal Palace, Leeds v Manchester United</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-23 11:00:00" d="2020-05-23 11:30:00"><n u="FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Chelsea v M'boro">FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Chelsea v M'boro 1997</n>    <k>We revisit the 1997 FA Cup final between Chelsea and Middlesbrough. Chelsea, managed by Ruud Gullit, went in to the match hoping to win their first major trophy in 27 years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-23 11:30:00" d="2020-05-23 12:00:00"><n u="FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Arsenal v Newcastle">FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Arsenal v Newcastle 1998</n>    <k>We revisit the 1998 FA Cup final between Arsenal and Newcastle. The Gunners were looking to emulate the famous 1971 league and cup double winning side</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-23 12:00:00" d="2020-05-23 12:30:00"><n u="FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Man Utd v Newcastle">FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Man Utd v Newcastle 1999</n>    <k>We revisit the 1999 FA Cup final between Manchester United and Newcastle. The Reds entered the match as Premier League champions having clinched the title</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-23 12:30:00" d="2020-05-23 13:00:00"><n>FA Cup Final Classics: FA Cup: Chelsea v Aston Villa 2000</n>    <k>We revisit the 2000 FA Cup final between Aston Villa and Chelsea, the last final to be played at the old Wembley Stadium. This was Aston Villa's first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-23 13:00:00" d="2020-05-23 14:00:00"><n>Bundesliga: Games of the Season: Leverkusen v Dortmund 2018/19</n>    <k>Look back as Bayer Leverkusen locked horns with Borussia Dortmund at the BayArena. England forward Jadon Sancho had started the 2018/19 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-23 14:00:00" d="2020-05-23 15:00:00"><n>Bundesliga: Games of the Season: Dortmund v Augsburg 2018/19</n>    <k>We revisit the seven-goal thriller between Borussia Dortmund and Augsburg at Signal Iduna Park in the 2018/19 season. Dortmund came into this</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-23 15:00:00" d="2020-05-23 16:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season: Lyon v Montpellier 2018/19</n>    <k>All the action as Lyon and Montpellier squared-off at the Groupama Stadium in the 2018/19 season. The last three meetings between the two sides in Ligue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-23 16:00:00" d="2020-05-23 17:00:00"><n>Ligue 1: Games of the Season: Nantes v Lille 2018/19</n>    <k>Take a look back at the action as Nantes welcomed Lille to the Stade de la Beaujoire in the 2018/19 Ligue 1 season. Lille were on a seven-match unbeaten</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-23 17:00:00" d="2020-05-23 18:00:00"><n>UEFA Europa League: Man Utd v Anderlecht 2016/17</n>    <k>Manchester United hosted Anderlecht in the second leg of the 2016/17 UEFA Europa League quarter-finals. The first leg ended 1-1 after a late Anderlecht equaliser</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-23 18:00:00" d="2020-05-23 19:30:00"><n>UEFA Europa League: Ajax v Manchester United 2016/17</n>    <k>We revisit the 2017 UEFA Europa League final as Manchester United tried to win the competition for the first time against Ajax. A win would</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-23 19:30:00" d="2020-05-23 20:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Stories of the Finals</n>    <k>We take a look back at Marseille's UEFA Champions League final against AC Milan's famous team in 1993 and Barcelona's victory over Juventus in the 2015 final</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-23 20:00:00" d="2020-05-23 20:30:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing</n>    <k>Tyson Raw &amp; Uncut looks at Mike Tyson's unprecedented rise to the pinnacle of world boxing. This episode features his 19th professional fight against Steve Zouski in 1986</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-23 20:30:00" d="2020-05-23 21:30:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing</n>    <k>Tyson Raw &amp; Uncut looks at Mike Tyson's unprecedented rise to the pinnacle of world boxing. This episode features his 1986 bout against James Tillis in New York</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-23 21:30:00" d="2020-05-23 22:00:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing</n>    <k>Tyson Raw &amp; Uncut looks at Mike Tyson's unprecedented rise to the pinnacle of world boxing. This episode features his 1986 bouts against William Hosea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-23 22:00:00" d="2020-05-24 01:00:00"><n>UFC: UFC 244 - Masvidal v Diaz</n>    <k>Look back at the action from UFC 244 as Jorge Masvidal and Nate Diaz met in the Octagon at Madison Square Garden. This programme may contain flashing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-24 01:00:00" d="2020-05-24 04:00:00"><n>UFC: UFC 246: McGregor v Cowboy</n>    <k>Another chance to relive Conor McGregor's emphatic return to the Octagon in his hotly-anticipated clash with Donald 'Cowboy' Cerrone at UFC 246 in Las Vegas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1051" o="2020-05-24 04:00:00" d="2020-05-24 05:00:00"><n>WRC Review: WRC Review: Rally Sweden 2018</n>    <k>The best of the action from the Rally Sweden, round two of the 2018 FIA World Rally Championship</k>  </p>
</a>
