<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="35" t="2021-07-08 05:06:10"><p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 05:00:00" d="2021-07-13 06:00:00"><n>Best Premier League Goals 98/99</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic action from the Premier League archive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 06:00:00" d="2021-07-13 06:30:00"><n>Best PL Goals: Chelsea/Man Utd</n><t>O</t>    <k>Enjoy some of the best goals from past clashes between Chelsea and Manchester United in the Premier League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 06:30:00" d="2021-07-13 07:00:00"><n>Didier Drogba: PL 100 Club</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest goalscorers in Barclays Premier League history. This episode features the best of Didier Drogba's 100 top-flight goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 07:00:00" d="2021-07-13 07:15:00"><n>PL Greatest: Arsenal/Charlton 2001</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the Premier League. Here, Arsenal take on Charlton Athletic at Highbury back in 2001 on a memorable afternoon for the Addicks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 07:15:00" d="2021-07-13 07:30:00"><n u="PL Greatest: Coventry/Man Utd">PL Greatest: Coventry/Man Utd 1997</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at the greatest Premier League game for each club, as voted for by fans. Here, for Coventry City, the stunning late comeback 3-2 win over Manchester</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 07:30:00" d="2021-07-13 07:45:00"><n u="PL Greatest:Everton/Wimbledon">PL Greatest:Everton/Wimbledon 1994</n><t>O</t>    <k>Everton: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for each of the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. For Everton, the 3-2 win over Wimbledon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 07:45:00" d="2021-07-13 08:00:00"><n>PL Greatest: Man City/Fulham 2008</n><t>O</t>    <k>Fulham: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for each of the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. For Fulham, the 3-2 fightback at</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 08:00:00" d="2021-07-13 08:30:00"><n>PL Legends: Zola</n><t>O</t>    <k>Series profiling some of the greatest players to grace the Premier League. Here the focus is on former Chelsea forward Gianfranco Zola</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 08:30:00" d="2021-07-13 09:00:00"><n>PL Legends: Neville</n><t>O</t>    <k>Series profiling some of the greatest players to grace the Premier League. Here the focus is on former Manchester United full-back Gary Neville</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 09:00:00" d="2021-07-13 09:30:00"><n>Best PL Goals: Man Utd/Newcastle</n><t>O</t>    <k>Take a look back at some of the best goals from Premier League meetings between Manchester United and Newcastle United</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 09:30:00" d="2021-07-13 10:00:00"><n>Best PL Goals: Manchester United</n><t>O</t>    <k>Enjoy the best Premier League goals scored by Manchester United over the years. See strikes from legends of the game including Ryan Giggs, David Beckham and more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 10:00:00" d="2021-07-13 10:30:00"><n>PL 100 Club: Peter Crouch</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of the players to have bagged 100 goals or more in the Premier League. Here, a look at Peter Crouch, who has scored across a career</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 10:30:00" d="2021-07-13 11:00:00"><n>PL 100 Club: Sergio Aguero</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of the players to have bagged 100 goals or more in the Premier League. Here, a look at Sergio Aguero, who has scored over 100 times during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 11:00:00" d="2021-07-13 13:00:00"><n>PL Retro: Leicester v Man United</n><t>O</t>    <k>A classic Premier League match as Leicester City hosted Manchester United at the King Power Stadium in 2014. Down 3-1, the Foxes would make a remarkable comeback</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 13:00:00" d="2021-07-13 13:30:00"><n>Soccerbox: John Barnes</n><t>O</t>    <k>Gary Neville sits down with Liverpool legend John Barnes as they look back at some of the most memorable matches from their careers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 13:30:00" d="2021-07-13 14:00:00"><n>Soccerbox: Matt Le Tissier</n><t>O</t>    <k>Gary Neville sits down with Southampton great Matt Le Tissier as they relive some of the most compelling matches where they played each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 14:00:00" d="2021-07-13 16:00:00"><n>PL Years: Man Utd's Treble</n><t>O</t>    <k>Take a look back at all the most memorable moments from the 1998-99 campaign. It was a season to savour for Manchester United as they took home the treble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 16:00:00" d="2021-07-13 16:15:00"><n>PL Greatest: Man City/Fulham 2008</n><t>O</t>    <k>Fulham: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for each of the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. For Fulham, the 3-2 fightback at</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 16:15:00" d="2021-07-13 16:30:00"><n u="PL Greatest: Ipswich/Man Utd">PL Greatest: Ipswich/Man Utd 1994</n><t>O</t>    <k>Ipswich: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for each of the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. Here, for Ipswich Town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 16:30:00" d="2021-07-13 16:45:00"><n>PL Greatest: M'boro/Man City 2008</n><t>O</t>    <k>Middlesbrough: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for each of the league's 49 clubs, as voted for by fans. Here, for Middlesbrough, the 8-1 hammering</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 16:45:00" d="2021-07-13 17:00:00"><n u="PL Greatest:Newcastle/Man Utd">PL Greatest:Newcastle/Man Utd 1996</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic game from the Premier League. Here, Newcastle United enjoy a memorable afternoon at St James' Park as they rip apart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 17:00:00" d="2021-07-13 18:00:00"><n>Best Premier League Goals 99/00</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic action from the Premier League archive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 18:00:00" d="2021-07-13 20:00:00"><n>Premier League 2020/21</n><t>O</t>    <k>West Bromwich Albion take on Brighton &amp; Hove Albion at The Hawthorns in Saturday action from the Premier League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 20:00:00" d="2021-07-13 21:45:00"><n>Premier League 2020/21</n><t>O</t>    <k>West Ham United take on Chelsea in Saturday action from the Premier League. The last time these two teams met, Thiago Silva and Tammy Abraham earned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 21:45:00" d="2021-07-13 22:00:00"><n>Matchday Plus: Chelsea v Man City</n><t>O</t>    <k>Take an alternative look at the clash between Chelsea and Man City at Stamford Bridge and head behind the scenes to experience the full flavour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 22:00:00" d="2021-07-13 22:30:00"><n>Soccerbox: Sol Campbell</n><t>O</t>    <k>Gary Neville sits down with Sol Campbell as they relive some of the most compelling matches from their storied careers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 22:30:00" d="2021-07-13 23:00:00"><n>Gary Neville's Soccerbox: Zola</n><t>O</t>    <k>Gary Neville sits down with Chelsea great Gianfranco Zola to discuss their time in the game and some of the most notable matches in which they played</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 23:00:00" d="2021-07-13 23:30:00"><n>PL Icons: Fernando Torres</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some of the iconic stars to have graced the Premier League. Here, remember former Liverpool and Chelsea forward Fernando Torres - a prolific</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-13 23:30:00" d="2021-07-14 01:30:00"><n>PL Retro: Arsenal v Tottenham 2010</n><t>O</t>    <k>A classic north London derby as Arsenal and Tottenham Hotspur went head to head at the Emirates Stadium in 2010. Spurs were looking for their first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 01:30:00" d="2021-07-14 02:00:00"><n>Premier League Icons: Gareth Bale</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some of the most iconic players to have graced the Premier League. Here, the focus is on former Southampton and Tottenham winger Gareth Bale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 02:00:00" d="2021-07-14 04:00:00"><n>Premier League Years 1999/00</n><t>O</t>    <k>Take a look back at all the most memorable moments from the 1999-2000 season. Alex Ferguson's Red Devils were the team everybody feared</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 04:00:00" d="2021-07-14 04:15:00"><n>PL Greatest: Man Utd/Norwich 2015</n><t>O</t>    <k>Norwich: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for each of the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. Here, for Norwich City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 04:15:00" d="2021-07-14 04:30:00"><n u="PL Greatest:Sheff Weds/N Forest">PL Greatest:Sheff Weds/N Forest 95</n><t>O</t>    <k>Nott'm Forest: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. For Nottingham Forest, the 7-1 win at Sheffield</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 04:30:00" d="2021-07-14 04:45:00"><n u="PL Greatest: Oldham/So'ton">PL Greatest: Oldham/So'ton 1993</n><t>O</t>    <k>Oldham: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. For Oldham Athletic, the 4-3 win over Southampton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 04:45:00" d="2021-07-14 05:00:00"><n>PL Greatest: P'mouth/So'ton 2005</n><t>O</t>    <k>Portsmouth: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for each of the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. For Portsmouth, the 4-1 win over local rivals</k>  </p>
</a>
