<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="40" t="2019-07-11 00:21:06"><p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 05:00:00" d="2019-07-15 06:00:00"><n>Best Premier League Goals 01/02</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Premier League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 06:00:00" d="2019-07-15 06:30:00"><n>Best PL Goals: Tottenham v Chelsea</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to look back at some of the best goals from previous Premier League meetings between Tottenham and Chelsea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 06:30:00" d="2019-07-15 07:00:00"><n>PL 100 Club: Emile Heskey</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest goalscorers in Premier League history. Here the focus is on former Leicester City and Liverpool striker Emile Heskey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 07:00:00" d="2019-07-15 07:15:00"><n>PL Greatest: United v Spurs '12</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic Premier League match. Here, rewind to 2012 and a thrilling five-goal game between Man Utd and Tottenham Hotspur at Old Trafford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 07:15:00" d="2019-07-15 07:30:00"><n>PL Greatest: Spurs v United '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic Premier League match. Here, a look back to 2017 and a clash between Tottenham Hotspur and Manchester United in Spurs' final</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 07:30:00" d="2019-07-15 07:45:00"><n>PL Greatest: United v Spurs '09</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic Premier League match. Here, a look back to 2009 and a seven-goal thriller between Manchester United and Spurs at Old Trafford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 07:45:00" d="2019-07-15 08:00:00"><n>PL Greatest: Spurs v United '98</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic Premier League match. Here, a look back to 1998 and a four-goal thriller between Spurs and Man Utd at White Hart Lane</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 08:00:00" d="2019-07-15 08:30:00"><n>PL Legends: David Ginola</n><t>O</t>    <k>A profile of former Newcastle United and Tottenham midfielder David Ginola. Capped 17 times for France, Ginola was famed for his Gallic flair and silky skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 08:30:00" d="2019-07-15 09:00:00"><n>PL Legends: Juninho</n><t>O</t>    <k>Series profiling some of the greatest players to grace the Premier League. Here the focus is on Middlesbrough's Brazilian midfielder Juninho</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 09:00:00" d="2019-07-15 09:30:00"><n>Best PL Goals: Liverpool/Man Utd</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at some of the best Premier League goals scored in matches between rivals Liverpool and Manchester United</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 09:30:00" d="2019-07-15 10:00:00"><n>Best PL Goals: Chelsea/Man Utd</n><t>O</t>    <k>Enjoy some of the best goals from past clashes between Chelsea and Manchester United in the Premier League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 10:00:00" d="2019-07-15 10:30:00"><n>Robbie Fowler: PL 100 Club</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest goalscorers in Premier League history. This episode features the best of Robbie Fowler's 162 goals. Tweet your favourite #pl100club</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 10:30:00" d="2019-07-15 11:00:00"><n>Thierry Henry: PL 100 Club</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest goalscorers in Premier League history. This episode features the best of Thierry Henry's 175 top-flight goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 11:00:00" d="2019-07-15 13:00:00"><n>Premier League Years 1992/93</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at all of the most memorable moments from the inaugural 1992-93 season in the Premier League. Tottenham's Teddy Sheringham was the league's top scorer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 13:00:00" d="2019-07-15 14:00:00"><n>Best Premier League Goals 11/12</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic action from the Premier League. Here, a collection of some of the best goals from the 2011-2012 Premier League season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 14:00:00" d="2019-07-15 16:00:00"><n>Premier League Years 1993/94</n><t>O</t>    <k>Take a look at all the memorable moments from the 1993-94 Premier League season. Manchester United were targeting their second successive title after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 16:00:00" d="2019-07-15 17:00:00"><n>Best Premier League Goals 06/07</n><t>O</t>    <k>Enjoy some of the best goals scored in years gone by in the Premier League. Here, the best strikes from the dramatic 2006-07 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 17:00:00" d="2019-07-15 17:15:00"><n>PL Greatest: Spurs v United '96</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic Premier League match. Here, rewind to 1996 and a memorable match between Tottenham and Manchester United at White Hart Lane</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 17:15:00" d="2019-07-15 17:30:00"><n>PL Greatest: Spurs v United '01</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic Premier League match. Here, rewind to 2001 and a thrilling eight-goal encounter between Tottenham and Man Utd at White Hart Lane</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 17:30:00" d="2019-07-15 17:45:00"><n>PL Greatest: United v Spurs '12</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic Premier League match. Here, rewind to 2012 and a thrilling five-goal game between Man Utd and Tottenham Hotspur at Old Trafford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 17:45:00" d="2019-07-15 18:00:00"><n>PL Greatest: Spurs v United '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic Premier League match. Here, a look back to 2017 and a clash between Tottenham Hotspur and Manchester United in Spurs' final</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 18:00:00" d="2019-07-15 18:30:00"><n>Paul Scholes: PL 100 Club</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest goalscorers in Barclays Premier League history. This episode features the best of Paul Scholes' 107 top-flight goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 18:30:00" d="2019-07-15 19:00:00"><n>Teddy Sheringham: PL 100 Club</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest goalscorers in Barclays Premier League history. This episode features the best of Teddy Sheringham's 146 goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 19:00:00" d="2019-07-15 21:00:00"><n>Premier League Years 1994/95</n><t>O</t>    <k>Take a look at all the most memorable moments from the 1994-95 Premier League season. Kenny Dalglish's Blackburn side were the league's surprise package this year</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 21:00:00" d="2019-07-15 21:30:00"><n>PL: Match Highlights</n><t>O</t>    <k>The first north London derby of Unai Emery's Arsenal reign arrives at the Emirates Stadium as the Gunners take on Tottenham Hotspur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 21:30:00" d="2019-07-15 22:00:00"><n>PL: Match Highlights</n><t>O</t>    <k>Chelsea host Brighton and Hove Albion at Stamford Bridge in the Premier League. The Blues won 2-1 in the reverse fixture earlier in the season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 22:00:00" d="2019-07-15 22:30:00"><n>PL: Match Highlights</n><t>O</t>    <k>Chelsea take on Everton at Stamford Bridge in the Premier League. Maurizio Sarri's Blues extended their unbeaten league start to 11 games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 22:30:00" d="2019-07-15 23:00:00"><n>PL: Match Highlights</n><t>O</t>    <k>Derby Day begins as Chelsea face Fulham at Stamford Bridge. Chelsea are looking to respond after losing at Spurs, Fulham are aiming for a second win under</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 23:00:00" d="2019-07-15 23:15:00"><n>PL Greatest: Man Utd 2-1 Spurs 99'</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic Premier League match. Here, rewind to 1999 as Manchester United looked to secure the Premier League title against Tottenham Hotspur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 23:15:00" d="2019-07-15 23:30:00"><n u="PL Greatest Games:Spurs/Chelsea">PL Greatest Games:Spurs/Chelsea 08</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive a classic match from the Premier League. Here, Spurs and Chelsea go head-to-head at White Hart Lane in an end-to-end encounter that produced eight goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 23:30:00" d="2019-07-15 23:45:00"><n>PL Greatest Games:Man Utd/Man City</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic action from the Premier League. Here, a memorable Manchester derby at Old Trafford back in the 2011-12 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-15 23:45:00" d="2019-07-16 00:00:00"><n u="PL Greatest Games:Man U/Arsenal">PL Greatest Games:Man U/Arsenal 01</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic action from the Premier League. Here, Manchester United versus Arsenal back in the 2000-01 season in a one-sided game that saw seven goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-16 00:00:00" d="2019-07-16 00:30:00"><n>Gary Neville's Soccerbox: Henry</n><t>O</t>    <k>Gary Neville sits down with Arsenal icon Thierry Henry as they relive some of the most compelling matches that the two shared during their careers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-16 00:30:00" d="2019-07-16 01:00:00"><n>Best PL Goals: Merseyside Derby</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some of the best goals scored in seasons gone by in the Premier League. Here, a Merseyside derby special with all the best goals in matches</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-16 01:00:00" d="2019-07-16 02:00:00"><n>Best Premier League Goals 05/06</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Premier League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-16 02:00:00" d="2019-07-16 04:00:00"><n>Premier League Years 1995/96</n><t>O</t>    <k>Take a look back at all of the most memorable moments from the 1995-96 Premier League season, with classic music from the time, major news headlines and more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-16 04:00:00" d="2019-07-16 04:15:00"><n u="Best of Wenger: L'pool/Arsenal">Best of Wenger: L'pool/Arsenal 09</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember a classic match from the Premier League. Here, Liverpool and Arsenal play out an absolute thriller at Anfield that saw Arsenal striker Andrey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-16 04:15:00" d="2019-07-16 04:30:00"><n u="PL Greatest Games:Arsenal/Spurs">PL Greatest Games:Arsenal/Spurs 08</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the Premier League. Here, Arsenal meet Tottenham Hotspur in the north London derby in 2008-09 season, in a match</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-16 04:30:00" d="2019-07-16 04:45:00"><n>Best of Wenger: Man U/Arsenal '98</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember a classic match from the Premier League. Here, Arsenal visit Alex Ferguson's Manchester United at Old Trafford back in the 1997-98 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2019-07-16 04:45:00" d="2019-07-16 05:00:00"><n>PL Greatest: Man Utd/Everton 2012</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the Premier League. Here, Man Utd host Everton at Old Trafford in a captivating eight-goal thriller back in 2012</k>  </p>
</a>
