<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="35" t="2021-07-09 07:14:49"><p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 05:00:00" d="2021-07-14 06:00:00"><n>Best Premier League Goals 01/02</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Premier League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 06:00:00" d="2021-07-14 06:30:00"><n>Best PL Goals: Manchester City</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at the very best goals scored by Manchester City in the history of the Premier League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 06:30:00" d="2021-07-14 07:00:00"><n>Teddy Sheringham: PL 100 Club</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest goalscorers in Barclays Premier League history. This episode features the best of Teddy Sheringham's 146 goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 07:00:00" d="2021-07-14 07:15:00"><n>PL Greatest: QPR/Liverpool 2012</n><t>O</t>    <k>QPR: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for each of the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. For QPR, the 3-2 win over Liverpool that saw Rangers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 07:15:00" d="2021-07-14 07:30:00"><n>PL Greatest Games:Reading/WHU '07</n><t>O</t>    <k>Reading: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for each of the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. Here, for Reading, the 6-0 hammering</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 07:30:00" d="2021-07-14 07:45:00"><n>PL Greatest:Sheff Utd/Arsenal 2006</n><t>O</t>    <k>Sheff Utd: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for each of the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. For Sheffield United, the 1-0 win over Arsenal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 07:45:00" d="2021-07-14 08:00:00"><n u="PL Greatest: Sheff Weds/Man U">PL Greatest: Sheff Weds/Man U 1998</n><t>O</t>    <k>Sheff Wed: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for each of the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. Here, for Sheffield Wednesday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 08:00:00" d="2021-07-14 08:30:00"><n>PL Legends: Sol Campbell</n><t>O</t>    <k>Series profiling some of the greatest players to grace the Premier League. Here the focus is on former Tottenham Hotspur and Arsenal defender Sol Campbell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 08:30:00" d="2021-07-14 09:00:00"><n>PL Legends: Robert Pires</n><t>O</t>    <k>Series profiling some of the greatest players to have graced the Premier League. Here the focus is on former Arsenal winger Robert Pires</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 09:00:00" d="2021-07-14 09:30:00"><n>Best PL Goals: Liverpool</n><t>O</t>    <k>Enjoy a selection of the very best goals scored in the Premier League by Liverpool, including memorable strikes by Steven Gerrard, Luis Suarez and many more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 09:30:00" d="2021-07-14 10:00:00"><n>Best PL Goals: Chelsea</n><t>O</t>    <k>Enjoy a selection of the very best goals scored in the Premier League by Chelsea, including memorable strikes from Didier Drogba, Frank Lampard, Eden Hazard and others</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 10:00:00" d="2021-07-14 10:30:00"><n>Robbie Fowler: PL 100 Club</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest goalscorers in Premier League history. This episode features the best of Robbie Fowler's 162 goals. Tweet your favourite #pl100club</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 10:30:00" d="2021-07-14 11:00:00"><n>Thierry Henry: PL 100 Club</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest goalscorers in Premier League history. This episode features the best of Thierry Henry's 175 top-flight goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 11:00:00" d="2021-07-14 13:00:00"><n u="PL Retro:N.Forest v Liverpool">PL Retro:N.Forest v Liverpool 1992</n><t>O</t>    <k>Look back at a classic match as Nottingham Forest met Liverpool at the start of the 1992-93 season. It was a piece of history - the Premier League's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 13:00:00" d="2021-07-14 13:30:00"><n>Gary Neville's Soccerbox: Pires</n><t>O</t>    <k>Gary Neville sits down with Arsenal legend Robert Pires to talk through their time in the game and some of the most memorable matches in which they played</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 13:30:00" d="2021-07-14 14:00:00"><n>Gary Neville's Soccerbox: Owen</n><t>O</t>    <k>Gary Neville sits down with former Liverpool and England striker Michael Owen to discuss their time in the game and some of the most notable matches in which they played</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 14:00:00" d="2021-07-14 16:00:00"><n>Premier League Years 2000/01</n><t>O</t>    <k>Take a look back at all of the most memorable moments from the 2000-01 Premier League season. Arsenal, Liverpool and Manchester United tussled for the title</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 16:00:00" d="2021-07-14 16:15:00"><n u="PL Greatest: Sheff Weds/Man U">PL Greatest: Sheff Weds/Man U 1998</n><t>O</t>    <k>Sheff Wed: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for each of the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. Here, for Sheffield Wednesday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 16:15:00" d="2021-07-14 16:30:00"><n>PL Greatest Games:Stoke/L'Pool '15</n><t>O</t>    <k>Stoke: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for each of the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. For Stoke City, the 6-1 win over Liverpool</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 16:30:00" d="2021-07-14 16:45:00"><n>PL Greatest: N'castle/S'land 2013</n><t>O</t>    <k>Sunderland: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. For Sunderland, the 3-0 win at rivals Newcastle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 16:45:00" d="2021-07-14 17:00:00"><n>PL Greatest Games:WHU/Man Utd '16</n><t>O</t>    <k>West Ham: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for each of the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. Here, for West Ham, their 3-2 win</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 17:00:00" d="2021-07-14 18:00:00"><n>Best Premier League Goals 05/06</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Premier League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 18:00:00" d="2021-07-14 20:00:00"><n>Premier League 2020/21</n><t>O</t>    <k>Fans make their long-awaited return to Premier League football as West Ham United welcome Ole Gunnar Solskjaer's Manchester United to the London Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 20:00:00" d="2021-07-14 21:45:00"><n>Premier League 2020/21</n><t>O</t>    <k>Arsenal and Liverpool go head to head in a huge clash from the Premier League. The Gunners will move to within a point of Liverpool with a win here</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 21:45:00" d="2021-07-14 22:00:00"><n>Matchday Plus: Arsenal v Man Utd</n><t>O</t>    <k>Take an alternative look at the clash between Arsenal and Manchester United, as Sky Sports takes you behind the scenes to experience the full flavour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 22:00:00" d="2021-07-14 22:30:00"><n>PL 100: Thierry Henry</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of the players to have bagged 100 goals or more in the Premier League. Here, take a look at Thierry Henry, considered one of the greatest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 22:30:00" d="2021-07-14 23:00:00"><n>Gary Neville's Soccerbox: Berbatov</n><t>O</t>    <k>Gary Neville sits down with former teammate and opponent Dimitar Berbatov to discuss their time in the game and some of the most notable matches in which they played</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 23:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:30:00"><n>Premier League Icons: Luis Suarez</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at some of the most iconic players to have graced the Premier League. Here, the focus is on former Liverpool forward Luis Suarez - a highly skilled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-14 23:30:00" d="2021-07-15 01:30:00"><n>PL Retro: Portsmouth v Southampton</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at a memorable Premier League clash from 2005, as Southampton and manager Harry Redknapp returned to face his old side and fierce rivals Portsmouth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-15 01:30:00" d="2021-07-15 02:00:00"><n>PL Icons: Ruud Van Nistelrooy</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at some of the most iconic players to have graced the Premier League. Here, the focus is on former Man Utd forward Ruud van Nistelrooy - a prolific</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-15 02:00:00" d="2021-07-15 04:00:00"><n>Premier League Years 2001/02</n><t>O</t>    <k>Take a look at all the most memorable moments from the 2001-02 Premier League season. It was a memorable one for a certain North London side</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-15 04:00:00" d="2021-07-15 04:15:00"><n>PL Greatest Games:Wigan/Arsenal'10</n><t>O</t>    <k>Wigan: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for each of the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. Here, for Wigan Athletic, their late comeback</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-15 04:15:00" d="2021-07-15 04:30:00"><n u="PL Greatest:Arsenal/Wimbledon">PL Greatest:Arsenal/Wimbledon 1997</n><t>O</t>    <k>Wimbledon: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for each of the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. Here, for Wimbledon, their 1-0 victory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-15 04:30:00" d="2021-07-15 04:45:00"><n>PL Greatest Games:Wolves/Leics '03</n><t>O</t>    <k>Wolves: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for each of the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. For Wolves, their incredible 4-3 comeback</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1056" o="2021-07-15 04:45:00" d="2021-07-15 05:00:00"><n>PL Greatest:Bournemouth/L'Pool '16</n><t>O</t>    <k>Bournemouth: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for each of the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. Here, for Bournemouth, their stunning</k>  </p>
</a>
