<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="32" t="2021-07-08 05:04:29"><p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 05:00:00" d="2021-07-13 06:00:00"><n u="Stop Search Seize">Stop Search Seize I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Ireland's Customs teams as they, with the help of the Irish police, try to stop organised smugglers from bringing drugs, cars and even exotic animals into the country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 06:00:00" d="2021-07-13 07:00:00"><n u="S.W.A.T.">S.W.A.T. III (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Hotel LA
The SWAT team must protect a hotel full of civilians when a joint task force mission with the LAPD Gang Division goes badly wrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 07:00:00" d="2021-07-13 07:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama X (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Calculon 2.0
Celebrated robot actor Calculon is given a second stab at stardom when Bender and Fry take extreme measures to bring him back from the dead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 07:30:00" d="2021-07-13 08:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama X (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Assie Come Home
When Bender is 'bot jacked' and left with just his eyes and mouth, it falls to Fry and Leela to track down their pal's stolen body parts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 08:00:00" d="2021-07-13 08:30:00"><n u="Baby Animals">Baby Animals I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mother's Darlings
Most animals are born defenceless, but under the protection and guidance of their mothers, they soon become masters of their own universes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 08:30:00" d="2021-07-13 09:00:00"><n u="Baby Animals">Baby Animals I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The More The Merrier
Growing up with brothers and sisters makes life a little sweeter, and time spent together helps these baby animals explore and learn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 09:00:00" d="2021-07-13 09:30:00"><n u="Monkey Business">Monkey Business III (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Dr Alison Cronin's team at the Monkey World Ape Rescue Centre in Dorset as they rehabilitate abused primates and support overseas projects to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 09:30:00" d="2021-07-13 10:00:00"><n u="Monkey Business">Monkey Business III (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Dr Alison Cronin's team at the Monkey World Ape Rescue Centre in Dorset as they rehabilitate abused primates and support overseas projects to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 10:00:00" d="2021-07-13 10:30:00"><n u="Motorway Patrol">Motorway Patrol IV (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series from New Zealand following the madness and mayhem faced by intrepid officers as they pull over motorists for a variety of suspected offences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 10:30:00" d="2021-07-13 11:00:00"><n u="Motorway Patrol">Motorway Patrol IV (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series from New Zealand following the madness and mayhem faced by intrepid officers as they pull over motorists for a variety of suspected offences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 11:00:00" d="2021-07-13 12:00:00"><n u="Stop Search Seize">Stop Search Seize I (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Ireland's Customs teams as they, with the help of the Irish police, try to stop organised smugglers from bringing drugs, cars and even exotic animals into the country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 12:00:00" d="2021-07-13 13:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles XI (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Commitment Issues
The team investigate the murder of a naval warfare engineer at a poetry event. Callen asks Nell to help in a worldwide search for Anna</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 13:00:00" d="2021-07-13 14:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles XI (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% The Circle
Anna returns with a dangerous warning for Callen, who must work with an archenemy to bust an underground trafficking ring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 14:00:00" d="2021-07-13 15:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 VI (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Hoa 'inea (Misery Loves Company)
Steve McGarrett and the team investigate a double murder. They also revisit their Valentine's Day disasters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 15:00:00" d="2021-07-13 16:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 VI (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ke Koa Lokomaika'I (The Good Soldier)
McGarrett partners with a young man whose only friend has been murdered. Plus, the FBI question Danny's mother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 16:00:00" d="2021-07-13 17:00:00"><n u="S.W.A.T.">S.W.A.T. III (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Stigma
When their former unit leader Buck goes off the grid, Hondo and the team confront their emotional difficulties as they race to save him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 17:00:00" d="2021-07-13 17:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VIII (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Blindsided
Family pride is at stake as Luke decides to run against Manny for class president. Meanwhile, Cam takes in a star high school football player</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 17:30:00" d="2021-07-13 18:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VIII (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Weathering Heights
Phil is invited to appear in a real estate segment for the local news and gets to meet his weatherman hero, Rainer Shine (Nathan Fillion)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 18:00:00" d="2021-07-13 18:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n>    <k>Homer's Triple Bypass: Years of over-indulgence finally take their toll on Homer, who discovers that he needs a triple heart bypass</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 18:30:00" d="2021-07-13 19:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama X (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Calculon 2.0
Celebrated robot actor Calculon is given a second stab at stardom when Bender and Fry take extreme measures to bring him back from the dead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 19:00:00" d="2021-07-13 19:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama X (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Assie Come Home
When Bender is 'bot jacked' and left with just his eyes and mouth, it falls to Fry and Leela to track down their pal's stolen body parts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 19:30:00" d="2021-07-13 20:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n>    <k>I Love Lisa: When Ralph, the school nerd, fails to receive a Valentine's Card, Lisa gives him one out of pity - and he falls instantly in love with her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 20:00:00" d="2021-07-13 20:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n>    <k>Duffless: How will Homer cope with a 30 day abstinence from his favourite drink? Meanwhile, Lisa pits her brother against a hamster in her latest scientific experiment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 20:30:00" d="2021-07-13 21:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n>    <k>Last Exit To Springfield: Homer stands up for what he believes in. Featuring the guest voice of Dr Joyce Brothers as herself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 21:00:00" d="2021-07-13 22:00:00"><n u="New: Supergirl">New: Supergirl VI (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Phantom Menaces
Supergirl makes a new ally, while Lena and Lex battle for control of Luthor Corp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 22:00:00" d="2021-07-13 23:00:00"><n u="An Idiot Abroad">An Idiot Abroad 2 (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Karl Comes Home
Mr Pilkington is back in Blighty and reunites with Ricky Gervais and Stephen Merchant to reflect on his experiences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-13 23:00:00" d="2021-07-14 00:15:00"><n>Russell Howard: Dingledodies</n>    <k>The comedian and Mock the Week star heads to Brighton Dome for a huge stand-up gig as part of his sell-out 2009 tour, which played to over 125,000 people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 00:15:00" d="2021-07-14 01:15:00"><n u="Prodigal Son">Prodigal Son II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Bad Manners
Malcolm and Ainsley both race to find the killer in the 'Debutante Slayings', but Ainsley's persistence has Malcolm worried</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 01:15:00" d="2021-07-14 02:10:00"><n u="MacGyver">MacGyver V (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Golden Lancehead + Venom + Pole Vault + Blood + Baggage: Mac and a friend's secret experimental cancer treatment is stolen as criminals ransack their lab</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 02:10:00" d="2021-07-14 03:05:00"><n u="DC's Legends Of Tomorrow">DC's Legends Of Tomorrow VI (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Meat - The Legends
With Spooner on board, Ava hopes her special powers will lead them to the aliens that are spread out across the timeline</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 03:05:00" d="2021-07-14 04:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars VII (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Road Crime Unit make a surprise discovery after pulling over a car, and dog handler Steve pursues a suspect. Meanwhile, the Tactical Aid Group raid a flat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 04:00:00" d="2021-07-14 05:00:00"><n u="Night Cops">Night Cops II (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cut through the yellow tape and accompany officers up and down the country who work the toughest shift of all: the night shift</k>  </p>
</a>
