<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="33" t="2019-08-10 01:39:29"><p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 05:00:00" d="2019-08-16 05:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama III (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Bendin' In The Wind
A blast from the past as Fry and Bender salvage a vintage Volkswagen bus from the turbulent 1960s and return it to its tie-dyed glory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 05:30:00" d="2019-08-16 06:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama III (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Time Keeps On Slipping
When the Professor creates a mutant team to take on the Harlem Globetrotters, he disrupts the time/space continuum, with eye-opening results</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 06:00:00" d="2019-08-16 06:30:00"><n u="Rspca Animal Rescue">Rspca Animal Rescue IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Moving series following RSPCA workers in Australia as they work to help animals in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 06:30:00" d="2019-08-16 07:00:00"><n u="Rspca Animal Rescue">Rspca Animal Rescue IV (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Moving series following RSPCA workers in Australia as they work to help animals in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 07:00:00" d="2019-08-16 07:30:00"><n u="Animal House">Animal House IV (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series shining a spotlight on the staff at SPCA Auckland, who dedicate their days to the care and protection of the region's animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 07:30:00" d="2019-08-16 08:00:00"><n u="Animal House">Animal House IV (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series shining a spotlight on the staff at SPCA Auckland, who dedicate their days to the care and protection of the region's animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 08:00:00" d="2019-08-16 08:30:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life IV (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Series four of the insightful documentary following the day-to-day dramas of looking after over 240 monkeys, chimps, orangutans and other primates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 08:30:00" d="2019-08-16 09:00:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life IV (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Series four of the insightful documentary following the day-to-day dramas of looking after over 240 monkeys, chimps, orangutans and other primates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 09:00:00" d="2019-08-16 10:00:00"><n u="The Dog Whisperer">The Dog Whisperer II (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Renowned dog trainer Cesar Millan helps owners of unruly and disobedient pets in an attempt to make their lives a little easier</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 10:00:00" d="2019-08-16 11:00:00"><n u="Supergirl">Supergirl II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Adventures of Supergirl
Kara teams up with her cousin to stop a new threat in Central City. Superhero action-adventure drama starring Melissa Benoist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 11:00:00" d="2019-08-16 12:00:00"><n u="The Flash">The Flash III (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>I Know Who You Are
Killer Frost gets in Team Flash's way when they encounter one of their last chances to stop Savitar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 12:00:00" d="2019-08-16 13:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VIII (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Hot Water
The team are left scrambling for answers when the mole compromises the NCIS. Planted evidence leads to Callen, Sam, Granger and Deeks's arrests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 13:00:00" d="2019-08-16 14:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VIII (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Under Siege
The mole kidnaps one of the NCIS agents. Plus, the team are left completely in the dark when Hetty goes rogue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 14:00:00" d="2019-08-16 15:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 V (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Poina 'ole (Not Forgotten)
McGarrett and the gang investigate the murder of a neurosurgeon, uncovering a set of clues that shed light on a decades-old case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 15:00:00" d="2019-08-16 16:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 V (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>La Po'ino (Doomsday)
The team are reunited with Joe White (guest star Terry O'Quinn) when a patient infected with a lethal strain of bird flu is kidnapped</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 16:00:00" d="2019-08-16 17:00:00"><n u="MacGyver">MacGyver II (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>UFO + Area 51
Mac and Riley wind up in big trouble as they investigate a mysterious object that's crash landed in the Nevada desert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 17:00:00" d="2019-08-16 17:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VII (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% The Party
Luke and Manny are left in charge when the family go out. But when the fire alarm goes off, Claire starts to suspect the boys are throwing a party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 17:30:00" d="2019-08-16 18:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VII (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Man Shouldn't Lie
Claire and the kids desperately try to hide a dog from Phil. Meanwhile, Jay finds himself in a pickle with Gloria</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 18:00:00" d="2019-08-16 18:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXI (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% The Squirt &amp; the Whale
Lisa befriends a beached blue whale but bad news awaits. Meanwhile, hilarity ensues when Homer receives a scary bill and takes drastic measures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 18:30:00" d="2019-08-16 19:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama III (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% I Dated A Robot
In his quest to live out his fantasies, Fry downloads a virtual Lucy Liu humanoid ('Liubot'), with whom he falls in love. Lucy Liu guest stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 19:00:00" d="2019-08-16 19:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Roswell That Ends Well
When the Planet Express ship travels through time to Roswell, New Mexico in 1947, Fry becomes his own progeny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 19:30:00" d="2019-08-16 20:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXII (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% The Fool Monty
Mr Burns is given just six weeks to live and, when an incident leaves the OAP without his memory, Springfield's residents decide to exact their revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 20:00:00" d="2019-08-16 20:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXII (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% How Munched Is That Birdie In The Window
Things aren't looking good for Santa's Little Helper after an incident involving a pigeon. Oscar winner Rachel Weisz guest stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 20:30:00" d="2019-08-16 21:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXII (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Flaming Moe
Moe tries to keep his 'straightness' secret when he opens a gay bar, and Skinner falls for a new teacher. Guest starring Kristen Wiig and Alyson Hannigan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 21:00:00" d="2019-08-16 21:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Great Expectations
Edward Norton and Elizabeth Banks guest star as Claire tries to find Phil the perfect anniversary gift</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 21:30:00" d="2019-08-16 22:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Fizbo
Calamity ensues as the Dunphys throw Luke a party. It's a memorable day, especially when Cam shows up as Fizbo the clown. Derogatory language/flashing images</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 22:00:00" d="2019-08-16 23:00:00"><n>Carpool Karaoke: When Corden Met McCartney Live from Liverpool</n>    <k>Loved Sir Paul's Carpool Karaoke this summer? Tune in for extra footage as he and James Corden sing more songs and put on a surprise gig</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 23:00:00" d="2019-08-17 00:00:00"><n u="A League Of Their Own">A League Of Their Own XIV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Get ready for more laughs, wacky challenges and studio chaos as James Corden and the boys team up with Fearne Cotton, Jimmy Anderson and Joe Cole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 00:00:00" d="2019-08-17 01:00:00"><n u="The Russell Howard Hour">The Russell Howard Hour I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Russell as he mocks the madness of the news and talks Ku Klux Klan with blues musician Daryl Davis. Musical comedy from Harry and Chris</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 01:00:00" d="2019-08-17 02:00:00"><n u="Manifest">Manifest I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Turbulence
Ben and Michaela fear a link between a shocking murder and Flight 828. Meanwhile, Ben struggles to accept the life Grace led in his absence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 02:00:00" d="2019-08-17 03:00:00"><n u="Brit Cops: Rapid Response">Brit Cops: Rapid Response III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Action-packed documentary following rapid response officers, the fastest cops in Britain, as they crack down on crime. Time is of the essence!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 03:00:00" d="2019-08-17 04:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars VII (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Put your seatbelt on and accompany Britain's elite as they take to the road, applying the brakes to motorists with relaxed attitudes to the law</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 04:00:00" d="2019-08-17 05:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 V (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>E 'Imi Pono (Searching for the Truth)
The team look into the murder of a journalist with ties to a Congolese warlord. Oscar nominee Barkhad Abdi guest stars</k>  </p>
</a>
