<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2019-08-11 01:29:08"><p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 05:00:00" d="2019-08-17 05:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama III (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% I Dated A Robot
In his quest to live out his fantasies, Fry downloads a virtual Lucy Liu humanoid ('Liubot'), with whom he falls in love. Lucy Liu guest stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 05:30:00" d="2019-08-17 06:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Roswell That Ends Well
When the Planet Express ship travels through time to Roswell, New Mexico in 1947, Fry becomes his own progeny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 06:00:00" d="2019-08-17 06:30:00"><n u="Rspca Animal Rescue">Rspca Animal Rescue IV (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Moving series following RSPCA workers across Australia as they work to help animals in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 06:30:00" d="2019-08-17 07:00:00"><n u="Rspca Animal Rescue">Rspca Animal Rescue IV (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Moving series following RSPCA workers across Australia as they work to help animals in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 07:00:00" d="2019-08-17 07:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VII (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% White Christmas
Eager to have a picture-perfect Christmas, Gloria rents a cabin in the mountains for the family. But not everything goes quite to plan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 07:30:00" d="2019-08-17 08:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VII (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Playdates
Haley, Alex and Luke scramble to arrange a surprise for Uncle Mitchell's birthday. Things get awkward when Gloria and Jay organise a playdate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 08:00:00" d="2019-08-17 08:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VII (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Spread Your Wings
Claire and the kids hatch a secret plan to help the ducklings fly the nest. Meanwhile, Gloria and Manny orchestrate a hot pepper heist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 08:30:00" d="2019-08-17 09:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VII (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Clean Away
Phil and Luke hold Claire back as she tries to declutter. Cameron panics when Jay decides to take up a new hobby and Gloria tries her hand at golf</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 09:00:00" d="2019-08-17 11:00:00"><n>Premier League Years 17/18</n>    <k>A chance to look back on a memorable 2017-18 Premier League season. Pep Guardiola's Man City would stun pundits and fans alike, winning the title at a canter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 11:00:00" d="2019-08-17 11:30:00"><n u="New: What's Up TV S16">New: What's Up TV S16 XVI (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Nicole meets Koomz, the man behind viral track Mariah and Buffy chats to comedians Katherine Ryan and Josh Widdicombe. With Marcus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 11:30:00" d="2019-08-17 13:00:00"><n>Soccer AM - Live</n>    <k>John Fendley and Jimmy Bullard are joined by guests from the world of sport and entertainment for the Saturday morning football show, with regular</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 13:00:00" d="2019-08-17 13:15:00"><n>PL Greatest Games:Man Utd/Man City</n>    <k>A chance to relive some classic action from the Premier League. Here, a memorable Manchester derby at Old Trafford back in the 2011-12 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 13:15:00" d="2019-08-17 14:15:00"><n u="Football's Funniest Moments">Football's Funniest Moments 5</n>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. From Gary Neville's stint at Valencia to Alan Pardew's dance moves, fans choose football's funniest moments. With David James, Jamie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 14:15:00" d="2019-08-17 18:00:00"><n>Live Intl: WAL v ENG</n>    <k>Eddie Jones' England continue their preparations for the Rugby World Cup as they take on fierce rivals Wales at the Principality Stadium in Cardiff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 18:00:00" d="2019-08-17 18:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXI (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% To Surveil with Love
Civil liberties are suspended after an incident involving Homer's unattended gym bag. Actor and comedian Eddie Izzard guest stars as the Queen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 18:30:00" d="2019-08-17 19:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXI (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Moe Letter Blues
Moe stirs up marital strife, informing Homer, Apu and Rev Lovejoy that he's run away with one of their wives. Has he really turned from friend to foe?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 19:00:00" d="2019-08-17 19:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXI (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% The Bob Next Door
New neighbour Walt Warren proves popular with everyone except Bart, who's convinced he's his nemesis, Sideshow Bob, in disguise. Kelsey Grammer guests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 19:30:00" d="2019-08-17 20:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXI (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Judge me Tender
Dream maker/breaker Simon Cowell heads to Springfield. Mo's pint-pulling days appear to be over when he discovers a knack for judging talent contests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 20:00:00" d="2019-08-17 20:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXII (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Elementary School Musical
Glee stars Lea Michele, Cory Monteith and Amber Riley, plus Flight of the Conchords, guest star when Lisa goes to a performing arts camp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 20:30:00" d="2019-08-17 21:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXII (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Loan-A-Lisa
When Grampa divvys up his savings between the family, Marge buys a designer handbag, while Lisa donates her money to a charity to help young entrepreneurs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 21:00:00" d="2019-08-17 22:00:00"><n u="A League Of Their Own">A League Of Their Own XIV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Get ready for more laughs, wacky challenges and studio chaos as James Corden and the boys team up with Fearne Cotton, Jimmy Anderson and Joe Cole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-17 22:00:00" d="2019-08-18 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Deja Vu</n><t>F</t>    <k>A ferry bomb leads cop Denzel Washington on a time travelling mission to save a key witness. Tony Scott directs this terrific sci-fi thriller</k>  </p>
</a>
