<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="31" t="2019-07-11 00:20:56"><p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 05:00:00" d="2019-07-15 06:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars VI (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Brimming with real-life thrills and spills, Road Wars provides an exclusive insight into the admirable efforts of the Proactive Unit in their war against crime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 06:00:00" d="2019-07-15 07:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars VI (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>While the Thames Valley Police provide a fascinating insight into car crime and its prevention, video footage captures dangerous drivers in action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 07:00:00" d="2019-07-15 07:30:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life II (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The first primates arrive at the Vietnam rescue centre to begin their rehabilitation. Back on home soil, Paddy's chimpanzee group welcome a new addition into the fold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 07:30:00" d="2019-07-15 08:00:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life II (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A tense day of introductions is in store for Monkey World's chimpanzees and gibbons. Plus, the team embark on their biggest and most ambitious mission yet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 08:00:00" d="2019-07-15 08:30:00"><n u="Animal">Animal 999 II (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Go behind the scenes at the Scottish SPCA, the country's leading animal charity, as cameras follow the work of its inspectors and rescue officers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 08:30:00" d="2019-07-15 09:00:00"><n u="Animal">Animal 999 III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Go behind the scenes at the SPCA and follow its dedicated team of rescue officers and inspectors as they save, rehome and care for animals all over Scotland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 09:00:00" d="2019-07-15 09:30:00"><n u="Rspca Animal Rescue">Rspca Animal Rescue II (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Moving series following RSPCA workers across Australia as they work to help animals in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 09:30:00" d="2019-07-15 10:00:00"><n u="Rspca Animal Rescue">Rspca Animal Rescue III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Moving series following RSPCA workers across Australia as they work to help animals in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 10:00:00" d="2019-07-15 11:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars VII (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Dog handler Darryl attempts to defuse a pub fight, the Tactical Aid Group execute two flat raids and the Road Crime Unit are in hot pursuit of a dangerous driver</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 11:00:00" d="2019-07-15 11:30:00"><n u="Highway Patrol">Highway Patrol V (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series following Australia's traffic enforcers, facing high-speed chases, explosive crashes and out-of-control drunk drivers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 11:30:00" d="2019-07-15 12:00:00"><n u="Highway Patrol">Highway Patrol V (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series following Australia's traffic enforcers, facing high-speed chases, explosive crashes and out-of-control drunk drivers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 12:00:00" d="2019-07-15 13:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VI (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% The 3rd Choir
Callen and the gang race into action after learning that a figure from their past is targeting a member of the team. Plus, Nate Getz returns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 13:00:00" d="2019-07-15 14:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VI (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Black Budget
Callen and Sam head south of the border to find an employee who managed to escape a professional shooting at the Department of Defense</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 14:00:00" d="2019-07-15 15:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 VIII (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>He lokomaika'i ka manu o Kaiona (Kind is the Bird of Kaiona): McGarrett and Jerry join Catherine Rollins in a race to stop a suspected terrorist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 15:00:00" d="2019-07-15 16:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 VIII (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ahuwale ka nane huna (The Answer to the Riddle is Seen): Harry Langford needs help when a British royal runs away. Plus, a mysterious tape shows up at 5-0 HQ</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 16:00:00" d="2019-07-15 17:00:00"><n u="MacGyver">MacGyver I (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Compass
Mac helps a scientist and old university friend when she is forced to fake her own death in order stop someone from killing her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 17:00:00" d="2019-07-15 17:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family V (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Spring-a-Ding-Fling
While Cam's thunder is stolen by a popular teacher's return, Mitch doesn't know what to make of his former college pal-turned-new boss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 17:30:00" d="2019-07-15 18:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family V (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Other People's Children
A leisurely day at the museum proves to be anything but for Cam, Mitch and Manny. Phil helps Andy with his anniversary gift</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 18:00:00" d="2019-07-15 18:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XV (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% Marge Vs Singles, Seniors, Childless Couples and Teens and Gays: When the childless sectors of society mount a campaign against kids, Marge takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 18:30:00" d="2019-07-15 19:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama X (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Forty Percent Leadbelly
Bender's hopes of being a folk singer are reignited when he crosses paths with his idol, Silicon Red, in a space prison</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 19:00:00" d="2019-07-15 19:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama X (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% The Inhuman Torch
Bender is transformed into a hero after becoming a firefighter and pulling off a series of rescue attempts. Suspicions are aroused, though</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 19:30:00" d="2019-07-15 20:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XV (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% Diatribe of a Mad Housewife
Homer relishes the critical acclaim Marge receives for a novel she writes. until he discovers the plot. With Tom Clancy and Thomas Pynchon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 20:00:00" d="2019-07-15 20:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XV (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% Margical History Tour
Marge gives the kids a colourful history lesson with the help of some locals. Homer becomes Henry VIII, while Bart plays boy genius Mozart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 20:30:00" d="2019-07-15 21:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XV (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% Milhouse Doesn't Live Here Anymore
When Milhouse and his mother relocate to Capital City, Bart strikes up a friendship with Lisa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 21:00:00" d="2019-07-15 23:30:00" c="1"><n u="Superman">Superman III</n><t>F</t>    <k>50% Tech whizz Richard Pryor helps develop a red kryptonite which splits Superman (Christopher Reeve) in two. Will his heroic or evil side win out?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-15 23:30:00" d="2019-07-16 00:30:00"><n u="A League Of Their Own">A League Of Their Own XIII (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>With just 45 minutes left of the series, James and co sub ex-England left back Ashley Cole, swimming champ Ellie Simmonds and comedian Rob Beckett into the fun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 00:30:00" d="2019-07-16 01:30:00"><n u="Rob &amp; Romesh Vs Anthony Joshua">Rob &amp; Romesh Vs Anthony Joshua I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>. Revisited. The boys meet heavyweight champ Anthony Joshua, watch him in action and chat to his boxer mate Tony Bellew</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 01:30:00" d="2019-07-16 02:30:00"><n u="Brit Cops: Law &amp; Disorder">Brit Cops: Law &amp; Disorder IV (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series charting the exploits of the City of London police, charged with safeguarding the Square Mile at the heart of the crime-ridden capital</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 02:30:00" d="2019-07-16 03:30:00"><n u="Warrior">Warrior I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. John Chinaman
Ah Sahm's fate lies in the hands of an unexpected ally when his actions earn him the cold shoulder from the Hop Wei</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 03:30:00" d="2019-07-16 04:30:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars VI (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Thames Valley Police provide a fascinating insight into car crime and its prevention. Plus, shocking video footage captures dangerous drivers in action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 04:30:00" d="2019-07-16 05:00:00"><n u="Motorway Patrol">Motorway Patrol IX (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series from New Zealand following the madness and mayhem faced by intrepid officers as they pull over motorists for a variety of suspected offences</k>  </p>
</a>
