<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="33" t="2019-08-15 22:50:25"><p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 05:00:00" d="2019-08-22 05:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IV (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Where The Buggalo Roam
Amy's boyfriend Kif tries to impress her parents by going after those who rustled their 'buggalo' livestock on Mars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 05:30:00" d="2019-08-22 06:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% A Pharoah To Remember
Bender's longing to be remembered motivates him to become a tyrannical Pharaoh on Osiris 4</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 06:00:00" d="2019-08-22 06:30:00"><n u="Rspca Animal Rescue">Rspca Animal Rescue IV (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Moving series following RSPCA workers across Australia as they work to help animals in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 06:30:00" d="2019-08-22 07:00:00"><n u="Rspca Animal Rescue">Rspca Animal Rescue IV (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Moving series following RSPCA workers across Australia as they work to help animals in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 07:00:00" d="2019-08-22 07:30:00"><n u="Animal House">Animal House V (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series shining a spotlight on the staff at SPCA Auckland, who dedicate their days to the care and protection of the region's animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 07:30:00" d="2019-08-22 08:00:00"><n u="Animal House">Animal House V (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series shining a spotlight on the staff at SPCA Auckland, who dedicate their days to the care and protection of the region's animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 08:00:00" d="2019-08-22 08:30:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life V (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Tensions are high as Sammy, one of the park's most popular chimps, goes under the knife. Capuchin Babe goes cherry-picking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 08:30:00" d="2019-08-22 09:00:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life V (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>It's a big day for baby golden-cheeked gibbon Mikado as he's introduced to his new foster mum Alex, and Gordon's orang-utan group have</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 09:00:00" d="2019-08-22 10:00:00"><n u="The Dog Whisperer">The Dog Whisperer III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Molly, Jane And Genoa
Cesar helps an American Eskimo dog/border collie mix with a fear of the outside world and a golden retriever that seems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 10:00:00" d="2019-08-22 11:00:00"><n u="Supergirl">Supergirl II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Crossfire
Supergirl takes on a ruthless new gang that is armed with dangerous alien technology. Meanwhile, Mon-El gets a job as an intern at CatCo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 11:00:00" d="2019-08-22 12:00:00"><n u="The Flash">The Flash IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mixed Signals
Our superhero speedster has plenty on his plate. Six months in the Speed Force has taken its toll on his love life and a menacing meta shows up in town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 12:00:00" d="2019-08-22 13:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VIII (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Battle Scars
The NCIS team up with Hetty's former Vietnam War colleagues when a decorated Navy captain is suspected of kidnap</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 13:00:00" d="2019-08-22 14:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VIII (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Golden Days
The team continue to work with Hetty's former Vietnam War colleagues as they begin a risky investigation into a gold heist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 14:00:00" d="2019-08-22 15:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 VII (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>He Moho Hou (New Player)
FBI profiler Alicia Brown is forced to join McGarrett in the hunt for the chess-piece killer when she finds a body in her bed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 15:00:00" d="2019-08-22 16:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 VII (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ke Ku 'Ana (The Stand)
Five-0 uncover a dangerous threat when a cache of guns disappears. Plus, Adam's release reunites him and Kono</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 16:00:00" d="2019-08-22 17:00:00"><n u="MacGyver">MacGyver III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bozer + Booze + Back To School
The team go undercover to smoke out a deep-cover operative who's recruiting students for deadly attacks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 17:00:00" d="2019-08-22 17:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VIII (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Weathering Heights
Phil is invited to appear in a real estate segment for the local news and gets to meet his weatherman hero, Rainer Shine (Nathan Fillion)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 17:30:00" d="2019-08-22 18:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VIII (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Halloween 4
The Revenge of Rod Skyhook: Luke's party gets an unexpected jumpstart, Cam faces off with his Halloween nemesis and Jay clashes with an old enemy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 18:00:00" d="2019-08-22 18:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXII (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Blue and the Gray
After finding her first grey hair, Marge decides to embrace middle age. Homie spices up Moe's love life too by becoming his official 'wing man'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 18:30:00" d="2019-08-22 19:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IV (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Godfellas
When Bender is accidentally shot into the heavens, he becomes god to a race of tiny aliens. Can he cut the celestial mustard? Probably not</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 19:00:00" d="2019-08-22 19:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IV (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Future Shock
A cryogenically frozen 1980s guy is thawed, becomes the CEO of the failing Planet Express company, and threatens to have it gutted by its largest competitor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 19:30:00" d="2019-08-22 20:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIII (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Falcon and the D'ohman
Homer gets into a spot of bother with a terrorist, before the future of 'it' couple 'Nedna' is revealed. Guest starring Touch's Kiefer Sutherland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 20:00:00" d="2019-08-22 20:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIII (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Bart Stops To Smell The Roosevelts
Principal Skinner has had enough of Bart's mischief- making and challenges Superintendent Chalmers to take over his education</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 20:30:00" d="2019-08-22 21:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIII (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Treehouse of Horror XXII
In keeping with tradition, the cartoon classic serves a selection of spine-tingling tales. Something wicked (and wickedly funny) this way comes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 21:00:00" d="2019-08-22 22:00:00"><n u="An Idiot Abroad">An Idiot Abroad 2 (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Trans-Siberian Express
The next 'thing to do' for Karl to, er, do is a trip aboard the Trans-Siberian Express. Surprises are in store</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 22:00:00" d="2019-08-22 23:00:00"><n u="New: A League Of Their Own">New: A League Of Their Own XIV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. James Corden referees as Freddie Flintoff, Jamie Redknapp and Romesh Ranganathan are joined by Laura Woods, Tony Bellew and Robin van Persie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 23:00:00" d="2019-08-23 00:00:00"><n u="Brassic">Brassic I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Vinnie's plan to steal a tiny horse is thwarted by a jar of chloroform and a pigeon. A Sky original starring Joe Gilgun and Michelle Keegan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-23 00:00:00" d="2019-08-23 01:00:00"><n u="Brassic">Brassic I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Needing cash for stripper Big Sandy's funeral, the lads decide to rob her boss's safe - but plans go awry when they get trapped in a sewer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-23 01:00:00" d="2019-08-23 01:30:00"><n u="The Reluctant Landlord">The Reluctant Landlord I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Romesh agrees to put Lemon's mum (Alison Steadman) up in his spare room. But it all gets awkward when he and Natasha plan a date night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-23 01:30:00" d="2019-08-23 02:00:00"><n u="The Reluctant Landlord">The Reluctant Landlord I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Romesh is on red alert when he hears a mystery shopper is on the prowl. Julie ends up in a strange situation when Natasha borrows a dog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-23 02:00:00" d="2019-08-23 03:00:00"><n u="Warrior">Warrior I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Chinese Boxing
Chinatown gets ready for an elite warrior clash as the Hop Wei and Long Zii face off to settle a score. Ah Sahm receives a warning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-23 03:00:00" d="2019-08-23 04:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 V (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Luapo'i (Prey)
The Five-0 investigate the murder of a bounty hunter who had just apprehended a dangerous killer. Plus, Danny's wife reveals a shocking secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-23 04:00:00" d="2019-08-23 05:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VIII (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Uncaged
Sam's wife Michelle is held hostage by kidnappers, who in return for her life demand the release of Sam's archenemy, terrorist Tahir Khaled</k>  </p>
</a>
