<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="31" t="2019-08-15 22:49:06"><p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 05:00:00" d="2019-08-21 05:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IV (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Love And Rocket
As Valentine's Day approaches, Bender's romance with the Planet Express ship puts the crew in jeopardy. Guest starring Sigourney Weaver and Lucy Liu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 05:30:00" d="2019-08-21 06:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IV (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Leela's Homeworld
After being named 'Orphan Of The Year', Leela finally learns the truth about her parents and her own identity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 06:00:00" d="2019-08-21 06:30:00"><n u="Rspca Animal Rescue">Rspca Animal Rescue IV (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Moving series following RSPCA workers across Australia as they work to help animals in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 06:30:00" d="2019-08-21 07:00:00"><n u="Rspca Animal Rescue">Rspca Animal Rescue IV (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Moving series following RSPCA workers across Australia as they work to help animals in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 07:00:00" d="2019-08-21 07:30:00"><n u="Animal House">Animal House IV (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series shining a spotlight on the staff at SPCA Auckland, who dedicate their days to the care and protection of the region's animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 07:30:00" d="2019-08-21 08:00:00"><n u="Animal House">Animal House V (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series shining a spotlight on the staff at SPCA Auckland, who dedicate their days to the care and protection of the region's animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 08:00:00" d="2019-08-21 08:30:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life V (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mike has his hands full when he collects baby golden-cheeked gibbon Mikado from France. Rescued squirrel monkey Fidget settles into his new home with the ladies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 08:30:00" d="2019-08-21 09:00:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life V (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>It's handbags at dawn in the orang-utan nursery as new arrival Oshine meets foster mum A-mei. Proud woolly monkey Piquita becomes a new mum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 09:00:00" d="2019-08-21 10:00:00"><n u="The Dog Whisperer">The Dog Whisperer III (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Buster, Holli And Spike &amp; Belle
Cesar Millan cures more troublesome pooches including Buster, an eight-year-old blue heeler/Australian shepherd</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 10:00:00" d="2019-08-21 11:00:00"><n u="Supergirl">Supergirl II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Survivors
When Kara and Alex investigate the murder of an unregistered alien, the trail leads to a brutal alien fight club</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 11:00:00" d="2019-08-21 12:00:00"><n u="The Flash">The Flash IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Flash Reborn
The fastest man alive blasts back for a fourth series. Cisco pulls Barry out of the Speed Force but he emerges a very different man</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 12:00:00" d="2019-08-21 13:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VIII (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% 727
Sam and Callen go undercover on a flight to Tokyo as they seek to stop an engineer from selling classified schematics of a guided missile destroyer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 13:00:00" d="2019-08-21 14:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VIII (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% From Havana with Love
The team head undercover when a man claims his defence contractor wife is selling navy secrets to a foreign government</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 14:00:00" d="2019-08-21 15:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 V (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Makekaua (Until We Die)
Disaster looms in this explosive season finale when, on the eve of Kono's wedding, someone threatens to detonate a nuclear bomb</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 15:00:00" d="2019-08-21 16:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 VII (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>No Ke Ali'i' Wahine A Me Ka Aina (For Queen and Country): Five-0 must work with a rogue MI6 agent to halt a European terrorist plot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 16:00:00" d="2019-08-21 17:00:00"><n u="MacGyver">MacGyver III (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bravo Lead + Loyalty + Friendship
Mac and co mount an off-the-books rescue when Jack's old Delta buddy gets wrongly accused of terrorism</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 17:00:00" d="2019-08-21 17:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VIII (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% A Stereotypical Day
Jay tries to make a good impression on his new neighbours, while Cam and Mitchell attempt to teach Lily a message of acceptance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 17:30:00" d="2019-08-21 18:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VIII (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Blindsided
Family pride is at stake as Luke decides to run against Manny for class president. Meanwhile, Cam takes in a star high school football player</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 18:00:00" d="2019-08-21 18:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXII (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Homer The Father
While Homer picks up parenting tips from a sitcom, Bart becomes involved in trading nuclear secrets. Writers James Lipton and David Mamet guest star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 18:30:00" d="2019-08-21 19:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IV (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Where The Buggalo Roam
Amy's boyfriend Kif tries to impress her parents by going after those who rustled their 'buggalo' livestock on Mars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 19:00:00" d="2019-08-21 19:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% A Pharoah To Remember
Bender's longing to be remembered motivates him to become a tyrannical Pharaoh on Osiris 4</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 19:30:00" d="2019-08-21 20:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXII (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Homer Scissorhands
Homer adds an unlikely string to his bow, and somehow becomes the hottest hairdresser in town. Plus, Lisa is suspicious of Milhouse's new girlfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 20:00:00" d="2019-08-21 20:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXII (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% 500 Keys
After getting her hands on a collection of keys to every door in Springfield, Lisa uncovers an old mystery connected to a hidden classroom beneath the school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 20:30:00" d="2019-08-21 21:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXII (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Ned-Liest Catch
Mrs Krabappel and Flanders begin a whirlwind romance in this 22nd season finale. Things start to unravel, however, when Ned finds out Edna's 'number'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 21:00:00" d="2019-08-21 22:00:00"><n u="S.W.A.T.">S.W.A.T. II (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Day Off
A hostage crisis gets all the more complicated when one of the captives turns out to be a wanted felon. Hondo's sister sends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 22:00:00" d="2019-08-21 23:00:00"><n u="New: The Blacklist">New: The Blacklist VI (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Bastien Moreau
Conclusion: Cooper puts his reputation on the line as he makes an appeal to the White House. Liz's hunt for The Corsican</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-21 23:00:00" d="2019-08-22 01:00:00"><n>New: KEVIN PIETERSEN: STORY OF A GENIUS</n>    <k>A man who entertained, amazed and divided - Kevin Pietersen was rarely out of the headlines throughout his stunning England career. This is his story. Sky original</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 01:00:00" d="2019-08-22 02:00:00"><n u="A League Of Their Own">A League Of Their Own XIV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Get ready for more laughs, wacky challenges and studio chaos as James Corden and the boys team up with Fearne Cotton, Jimmy Anderson and Joe Cole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 02:00:00" d="2019-08-22 03:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 V (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ho'amoano (Chasing Yesterday)
Three married men must retrace their steps from a wild night on the town to help the Five-0 solve a brutal murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 03:00:00" d="2019-08-22 04:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars VII (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Put your seatbelt on and accompany Britain's elite as they take to the road, applying the brakes to motorists with relaxed attitudes to the law</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-22 04:00:00" d="2019-08-22 05:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars VII (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Put your seatbelt on and accompany Britain's elite as they take to the road, applying the brakes to motorists with relaxed attitudes to the law</k>  </p>
</a>
