<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2019-07-11 00:20:56"><p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 05:00:00" d="2019-07-17 06:00:00"><n u="Babylon">Babylon 5 III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% Voices of Authority
A new ally enters the fight against the shadows and Sheridan's actions are questioned on Earth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 06:00:00" d="2019-07-17 07:00:00"><n u="Stargate SG-1">Stargate SG-1 II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Gamekeeper
The SG-1 team members are pulled into a virtual reality loop where they relive terrifying moments in their lives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 07:00:00" d="2019-07-17 07:30:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life II (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Baby chimp Rodders needs to have a tooth removed after a rough playing session, and John examines the leg that ape Jimmy nearly lost</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 07:30:00" d="2019-07-17 08:00:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life II (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cheeky chimp Seamus makes the jump from the nursery to the bachelor pad. Trouble looms for toddler orangutan Aris, too, when he's drawn into a fight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 08:00:00" d="2019-07-17 08:30:00"><n u="Animal">Animal 999 III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ride along with rescue workers from the SPCA, Scotland's leading animal charity, and discover how their work helps to protect, care and rehome animals across the country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 08:30:00" d="2019-07-17 09:00:00"><n u="Animal">Animal 999 III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Follow the incredible work of the SPCA as its team of rescue officers, inspectors, vets and care staff ensure the wellbeing of thousands of animals every year</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 09:00:00" d="2019-07-17 09:30:00"><n u="Rspca Animal Rescue">Rspca Animal Rescue III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Moving series following RSPCA workers across Australia as they work to help animals in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 09:30:00" d="2019-07-17 10:00:00"><n u="Rspca Animal Rescue">Rspca Animal Rescue III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Moving series following RSPCA workers across Australia as they work to help animals in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 10:00:00" d="2019-07-17 11:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars VII (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Thames Valley Police provide a fascinating insight into car crime and its prevention. Plus, shocking video footage captures dangerous drivers in action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 11:00:00" d="2019-07-17 11:30:00"><n u="Highway Patrol Australia">Highway Patrol Australia I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series following Australia's traffic enforcers. Officers face high-speed chases, defiant hooligans, explosive crashes and out-of-control drunk drivers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 11:30:00" d="2019-07-17 12:00:00"><n u="Highway Patrol Australia">Highway Patrol Australia I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series following Australia's traffic enforcers. Officers face high-speed chases, defiant hooligans, explosive crashes and out-of-control drunk drivers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 12:00:00" d="2019-07-17 13:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VI (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% The Grey Man
The team investigate the murder of a homeless man, who is identified as a former marine and CIA agent with connections to the Mexican cartel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 13:00:00" d="2019-07-17 14:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VI (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Traitor
Paranoia sweeps through the team when Granger is poisoned by the mole, prompting Hetty to order a lockdown while everyone is investigated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 14:00:00" d="2019-07-17 15:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 VIII (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ka Lala Kaukonakona Haki 'Ole I Ka Pa A Ka Makani Kona: Steve joins Junior and his SEAL team on a personal mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 15:00:00" d="2019-07-17 16:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>La O Na Makuahine (Mother's Day)
Season three begins and Mrs McGarrett has got a lot of explaining to do. Chin Ho's gut-wrenching decision, meanwhile, has tragic results</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 16:00:00" d="2019-07-17 17:00:00"><n u="MacGyver">MacGyver I (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cigar Cutter
Murdoc escalates his plan to wreak revenge on Mac when he recruits a former cellmate to help him kill every agent in the Phoenix Complex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 17:00:00" d="2019-07-17 17:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family V (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Australia
Get ready for another eventful family holiday as the Pritchett-Dunphy-Tuckers head Down Under</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 17:30:00" d="2019-07-17 18:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family V (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Sleeper
Phil is forced to spin a lie after missing a repairman's call, and Claire accuses Cam of being snobby. Gloria organises the family photo shoot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 18:00:00" d="2019-07-17 18:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XV (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% Diatribe of a Mad Housewife
Homer relishes the critical acclaim Marge receives for a novel she writes. until he discovers the plot. With Tom Clancy and Thomas Pynchon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 18:30:00" d="2019-07-17 19:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama X (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Assie Come Home
When Bender is 'bot jacked' and left with just his eyes and mouth, it falls to Fry and Leela to track down their pal's stolen body parts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 19:00:00" d="2019-07-17 19:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama X (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Leela and the Genestalk
Leela is in for a shock when she develops a set of tentacles. It's a grim discovery that leads her to a secret genetic engineering lab</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 19:30:00" d="2019-07-17 20:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XV (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% Wandering Juvie
Sarah Michelle Gellar (Buffy) is Gina, a tough inmate at the Springfield Correctional Facility. When Bart is sent down, the pair become friends. sort of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 20:00:00" d="2019-07-17 20:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XV (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% My Big Fat Geek Wedding
When Mrs Krabappel calls off her wedding to Principal Skinner, Marge and Homer step in with relationship advice. Like they can talk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 20:30:00" d="2019-07-17 21:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XV (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% Catch 'Em if you Can
Bart and Lisa pursue Homer and Marge after they sneak away on a second honeymoon. Meanwhile, Grampa catches the eye of a dashing Cuban man</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 21:00:00" d="2019-07-17 22:00:00"><n u="S.W.A.T.">S.W.A.T. II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Saving Face
Hondo's got his suspicions when Nia Wells's ex-husband asks for help catching a fugitive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 22:00:00" d="2019-07-17 23:00:00"><n u="New: The Blacklist">New: The Blacklist VI (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. General Shiro
Red and Dembe call in Glenn to help them stack the jury in Red's favour. The taskforce investigates when weaponised</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 23:00:00" d="2019-07-18 00:00:00"><n u="The Force: Manchester">The Force: Manchester II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Fast-paced series following the 999 work of Greater Manchester Police. Officers have a tough time getting to the truth when they are called to a fight in Stockport</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-18 00:00:00" d="2019-07-18 00:30:00"><n>Whyte Hot</n>    <k>A special programme looking at British boxer Dillian Whyte's rise in boxing and his career so far as he prepares to do battle with Oscar Rivas at London's O2</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-18 00:30:00" d="2019-07-18 01:00:00"><n>Heavyweight KO's: The Best Of</n>    <k>A special programme looking ahead to the Dillian Whyte v Oscar Rivas heavyweight fight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-18 01:00:00" d="2019-07-18 02:00:00"><n u="A League Of Their Own">A League Of Their Own XIII (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>With just 45 minutes left of the series, James and co sub ex-England left back Ashley Cole, swimming champ Ellie Simmonds and comedian Rob Beckett into the fun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-18 02:00:00" d="2019-07-18 03:00:00"><n u="An Idiot Abroad">An Idiot Abroad (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>82% Mexico
Karl Pilkington journeys to Mexico where he'll visit Chichen Itza. But first, he tries his hand at wrestling and being a cowboy, and hunts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-18 03:00:00" d="2019-07-18 04:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars VI (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In an action-packed instalment, Kev and Waller deal with a drug addict in Windsor, and Simon confronts a driver with a few unpleasant surprises up his sleeve</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-18 04:00:00" d="2019-07-18 04:30:00"><n u="Motorway Patrol">Motorway Patrol IX (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series from New Zealand following the madness and mayhem faced by intrepid officers as they pull over motorists for a variety of suspected offences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-18 04:30:00" d="2019-07-18 05:00:00"><n u="Motorway Patrol">Motorway Patrol IX (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series from New Zealand following the madness and mayhem faced by intrepid officers as they pull over motorists for a variety of suspected offences</k>  </p>
</a>
