<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2020-05-15 04:57:33"><p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 05:00:00" d="2020-05-22 06:00:00"><n u="Caught On Dashcam">Caught On Dashcam II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Outrageous road disasters and highway hijinks, captured in video via people's in-vehicle dash-board cameras</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 06:00:00" d="2020-05-22 06:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IV (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Leela's Homeworld
After being named 'Orphan Of The Year', Leela finally learns the truth about her parents and her own identity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 06:30:00" d="2020-05-22 07:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IV (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Where The Buggalo Roam
Amy's boyfriend Kif tries to impress her parents by going after those who rustled their 'buggalo' livestock on Mars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 07:00:00" d="2020-05-22 07:30:00"><n u="Monkey Business">Monkey Business IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Dr Alison Cronin's team at the Monkey World Ape Rescue Centre in Dorset as they rehabilitate abused primates and support overseas projects to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 07:30:00" d="2020-05-22 08:00:00"><n u="Monkey Business">Monkey Business IV (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Dr Alison Cronin's team at the Monkey World Ape Rescue Centre in Dorset as they rehabilitate abused primates and support overseas projects to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 08:00:00" d="2020-05-22 08:30:00"><n u="Animal House">Animal House I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series shining a spotlight on the staff at SPCA Auckland, who dedicate their days to the care and protection of the region's animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 08:30:00" d="2020-05-22 09:00:00"><n u="Animal House">Animal House I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series shining a spotlight on the staff at SPCA Auckland, who dedicate their days to the care and protection of the region's animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 09:00:00" d="2020-05-22 10:00:00"><n u="The Dog Whisperer">The Dog Whisperer V (32)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Desperate Housedogs
A once peaceful cul-de-sac is full of tension. Can Cesar curb the Desperate Housedog drama?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 10:00:00" d="2020-05-22 11:00:00"><n u="Brit Cops: Law &amp; Disorder">Brit Cops: Law &amp; Disorder IV (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series charting the exploits of the City of London police, charged with safeguarding the Square Mile at the heart of the crime-ridden capital</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 11:00:00" d="2020-05-22 12:00:00"><n u="Caught On Dashcam">Caught On Dashcam II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Outrageous road disasters and highway hijinks, captured on video via people's in-vehicle dashboard cameras</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 12:00:00" d="2020-05-22 13:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Killshot
Callen and the team investigate when a defence contractor is murdered. In a twisty tale, the clues lead them to a suspect with ties to NCIS Director Leon Vance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 13:00:00" d="2020-05-22 14:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Keepin' it Real
There's no shortage of thrills and spills in another high- octane instalment. Callen and co investigate when a wealthy businessman plummets to his death</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 14:00:00" d="2020-05-22 15:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 VIII (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Na la 'ilio (Dog Days)
McGarrett gets a visit from an ex-SEAL who's keen to join the task force. And, an ambushed drugs bust leaves just one unlikely witness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 15:00:00" d="2020-05-22 16:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 VIII (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Kau ka 'onohi ali'i i luna (The Royal Eyes Rest Above): McGarrett rushes into a bank heist, where he makes a potentially tragic error in the heat of the moment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 16:00:00" d="2020-05-22 17:00:00"><n u="S.W.A.T.">S.W.A.T. II (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Trigger Creep
There's a gunman at large in Los Angeles and SWAT must work out the next place he will strike. Meanwhile, Jessica gets an unexpected offer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 17:00:00" d="2020-05-22 17:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family IV (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% My Hero
Mitch's ex invites the whole family to a fundraising event at the local roller rink. Plus, Luke and Manny need inspiration for an essay assignment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 17:30:00" d="2020-05-22 18:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family IV (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Games People Play
Phil decides to take the family on a road trip, and Jay and Gloria enjoy a snooping session while searching for Manny's misplaced backpack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 18:00:00" d="2020-05-22 18:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% When Flanders Failed
Marge annoys Homer when she tells him that she admires Ned Flanders for working hard and being able to provide his family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 18:30:00" d="2020-05-22 19:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% A Pharoah To Remember
Bender's longing to be remembered motivates him to become a tyrannical Pharaoh on Osiris 4</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 19:00:00" d="2020-05-22 19:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IV (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Godfellas
When Bender is accidentally shot into the heavens, he becomes god to a race of tiny aliens. Can he cut the celestial mustard? Probably not</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 19:30:00" d="2020-05-22 20:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons III (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Radio Bart
Using his Superstar Celebrity microphone, Bart tricks all of Springfield into believing that a child has fallen down a well. Featuring the voice of Sting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 20:00:00" d="2020-05-22 20:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons III (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Lisa the Greek
Lisa accurately predicts the winners of sporting events on which Homer gambles so she can be closer to her father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 20:30:00" d="2020-05-22 21:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons III (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Homer Alone
When Marge reaches breaking point, she leaves for a much needed vacation, leaving the rest of the family to realise how much she does for them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 21:00:00" d="2020-05-22 21:30:00"><n u="New: The Simpsons">New: The Simpsons XXXI (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. The Hateful Eight-Year-Olds
Lisa meets a fellow horse-lover but then falls into a circle of snooty girls. Homer takes Marge on a romantic cruise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 21:30:00" d="2020-05-22 22:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Pilot
This skewed US sitcom celebrates the drama and dysfunction of three left-field families. A twisted tour of relative chaos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 22:00:00" d="2020-05-22 23:00:00"><n u="New: Manifest">New: Manifest II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Return Trip
Ben and Saanvi work together to organise a surprising family reunion for an emotionally shut-off Flight 828 passenger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-22 23:00:00" d="2020-05-23 02:00:00"><n u="New: Redknapp's Home Fixture">New: Redknapp's Home Fixture I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. With anecdotes and interviews, Harry and Jamie Redknapp are with co-host Tom Davis speaking to sporting greats, asking the questions</k>  </p>
</a>
