<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="32" t="2019-08-09 01:41:08"><p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 05:00:00" d="2019-08-15 05:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama III (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% The Cyber House Rules
Tired of feeling like an outcast, Leela has a second eye grafted onto her face. Bender adopts 12 children</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 05:30:00" d="2019-08-15 06:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama III (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Insane In The Mainframe
When Fry and Bender are mistaken for bank robbers, they are sentenced to time in an insane asylum for robots</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 06:00:00" d="2019-08-15 06:30:00"><n u="Rspca Animal Rescue">Rspca Animal Rescue IV (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Moving series following RSPCA workers in Australia as they work to help animals in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 06:30:00" d="2019-08-15 07:00:00"><n u="Rspca Animal Rescue">Rspca Animal Rescue IV (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Moving series following RSPCA workers in Australia as they work to help animals in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 07:00:00" d="2019-08-15 07:30:00"><n u="Animal House">Animal House IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series shining a spotlight on the staff at SPCA Auckland, who dedicate their days to the care and protection of the region's animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 07:30:00" d="2019-08-15 08:00:00"><n u="Animal House">Animal House IV (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series shining a spotlight on the staff at SPCA Auckland, who dedicate their days to the care and protection of the region's animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 08:00:00" d="2019-08-15 08:30:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life IV (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Series four of the insightful documentary following the day-to-day dramas of looking after over 240 monkeys, chimps, orangutans and other primates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 08:30:00" d="2019-08-15 09:00:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life IV (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Series four of the insightful documentary following the day-to-day dramas of looking after over 240 monkeys, chimps, orangutans and other primates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 09:00:00" d="2019-08-15 10:00:00"><n u="Supergirl">Supergirl I (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Myriad
Kara, Maxwell Lord and Cat Grant must pull together to save the city as Non and Indigo put their devastating plan into motion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 10:00:00" d="2019-08-15 11:00:00"><n u="Supergirl">Supergirl I (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Better Angels
As Non ups the stakes, Supergirl says her goodbyes in preparation for her greatest and most dangerous test yet. Season finale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 11:00:00" d="2019-08-15 12:00:00"><n>The Flash</n>    <k>The Once and Future Flash: Barry travels to 2024 in the hope of discovering Savitar's identity, where he encounters future versions of his Team Flash friends. (S3, ep,19)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 12:00:00" d="2019-08-15 13:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VIII (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Tidings we bring
The team are on the case when a Navy lieutenant commander disappears while working for the NSA</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 13:00:00" d="2019-08-15 14:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VIII (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Kulinda
When a navy reservist is killed, Sam is sent undercover at a private security firm, which has links to several crime organisations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 14:00:00" d="2019-08-15 15:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 V (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Wawahi Moe'uhane (Broken Dreams)
The team need the help of an old-school private investigator when they attempt to solve the murder of an escort</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 15:00:00" d="2019-08-15 16:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 V (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ua 'aihue (Stolen)
Kono and Chin go undercover as art buyers to solve the murder of a tourist who was unwittingly transporting a stolen Van Gogh painting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 16:00:00" d="2019-08-15 17:00:00"><n u="MacGyver">MacGyver II (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Wind + Water
MacGyver winds up a hostage in a Puerto Rico bank robbery, when thieves attempt to steal millions from the bank his mate manages</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 17:00:00" d="2019-08-15 17:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VII (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% The Cover-Up
Phil gets an attractive new client and tries to keep her a secret from Claire. Meanwhile, Claire gets attention from her hot new yoga teacher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 17:30:00" d="2019-08-15 18:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VII (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Express Yourself
Cameron's emotional sister Pam proves too much for Mitchell. Plus, Phil and Claire struggle to stay awake during a spontaneous trip to Paris</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 18:00:00" d="2019-08-15 18:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXI (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Chief of Hearts
Bromance blossoms between Homer and Chief Wiggum when the former is sentenced to community service. Marge proves that mothers don't always know best, too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 18:30:00" d="2019-08-15 19:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama III (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Bendin' In The Wind
A blast from the past as Fry and Bender salvage a vintage Volkswagen bus from the turbulent 1960s and return it to its tie-dyed glory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 19:00:00" d="2019-08-15 19:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama III (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Time Keeps On Slipping
When the Professor creates a mutant team to take on the Harlem Globetrotters, he disrupts the time/space continuum, with eye-opening results</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 19:30:00" d="2019-08-15 20:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXII (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Moneybart
When Lisa signs up to coach Bart's baseball team, the pair discover that siblings and sport don't mix. Watch out for Banksy's unique title sequence too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 20:00:00" d="2019-08-15 20:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXII (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Treehouse of Horror
A trio of smartly scripted and spirited Halloween tales. Guest starring Harry Potter himself, Daniel Radcliffe, and House's Hugh Laurie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 20:30:00" d="2019-08-15 21:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXII (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Lisa Simpson This Isn't Your Life
Lisa decides that she doesn't want to end up like her mum, Marge. Plus, dethroning Nelson, Bart becomes the playground's reigning bully</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 21:00:00" d="2019-08-15 22:00:00"><n u="An Idiot Abroad">An Idiot Abroad 2 (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Desert Island
Digging out his passport for series two, Karl works through the 'Bucket List'. First up is a night on a private island</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 22:00:00" d="2019-08-15 23:00:00"><n u="New: A League Of Their Own">New: A League Of Their Own XIV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Get ready for more laughs, wacky challenges and studio chaos as James Corden and the boys team up with Fearne Cotton, Jimmy Anderson and Joe Cole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-15 23:00:00" d="2019-08-16 01:00:00"><n>Micky Flanagan - An' Another Fing Live</n>    <k>Marriage, Saga holidays and Mary Berry get the Micky treatment in the cockney comic's sell-out stand-up show from the O2 Arena</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 01:00:00" d="2019-08-16 01:30:00"><n u="The Reluctant Landlord">The Reluctant Landlord I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Pulling pints proves tough work for Romesh Ranganathan when he takes over his late dad's pub. Comedy with Nick Helm and Sian Gibson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 01:30:00" d="2019-08-16 02:00:00"><n u="The Reluctant Landlord">The Reluctant Landlord I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Romesh announces a speciality curry night with a fab local chef. But his plan goes up in smoke when he trusts Lemon to do the cooking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 02:00:00" d="2019-08-16 03:00:00"><n u="Warrior">Warrior I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. They Don't Pay Us Enough to Think
A bloodbath on Chinatown's streets leads the Hop Wei and Long Xii to consider an unusual way to end the hostilities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 03:00:00" d="2019-08-16 04:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars VII (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Put your seatbelt on and accompany Britain's elite as they take to the road, applying the brakes to motorists with relaxed attitudes to the law</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-16 04:00:00" d="2019-08-16 05:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars VII (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Put your seatbelt on and accompany Britain's elite as they take to the road, applying the brakes to motorists with relaxed attitudes to the law</k>  </p>
</a>
