<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="30" t="2020-04-10 04:36:36"><p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 05:00:00" d="2020-04-17 05:30:00"><n u="Ninja Warrior">Ninja Warrior VII (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The world's top athletes and wrestlers compete alongside amateurs in one of the most demanding physical challenges ever devised</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 05:30:00" d="2020-04-17 06:00:00"><n u="Ninja Warrior">Ninja Warrior VII (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The world's top athletes and wrestlers compete alongside amateurs in one of the most demanding physical challenges ever devised</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 06:00:00" d="2020-04-17 06:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IX (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Viva Mars Vegas
The Planet Express crew escape to Mars Vegas for the weekend, only to run afoul of the Robot Mafia, who are looking to recover a debt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 06:30:00" d="2020-04-17 07:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IX (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% 31st Century Fox
Bender's excitement for an upcoming fox hunt is nipped in the bud when he finds out the prey is robotic. Guest starring Patrick Stewart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 07:00:00" d="2020-04-17 07:30:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life XI (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The vets are called over concerns for the health of young chimp, Bart. The woolly monkey move continues with eleven of the primates swapping homes in one day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 07:30:00" d="2020-04-17 08:00:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life XI (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Alison responds to a request from the police to rescue a neglected marmoset. The siamang gibbons have a training session and it's pumpkins in the mist for the chimps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 08:00:00" d="2020-04-17 08:30:00"><n u="Wild Vets">Wild Vets III (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Series three of the documentary charting the challenging work of New Zealand's vets as they treat an array of colourful critters in zoos and wildlife parks down under</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 08:30:00" d="2020-04-17 09:00:00"><n u="Animal">Animal 999 I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Go behind the scenes of the Scottish SPCA with its inspectors and rescue officers. Staff are called out when a family of ducks strays into danger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 09:00:00" d="2020-04-17 09:30:00"><n u="Moominvalley">Moominvalley I (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Midwinter Ancestor
Moomintroll faces his toughest challenge yet when he wakes up too early from hibernation. To survive the perils of winter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 09:30:00" d="2020-04-17 09:55:00"><n u="Moominvalley">Moominvalley I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Spring Tune
Snufkin's return journey to Moominvalley is disrupted by an overly friendly forest creature. Is it time to hurry back and see his friend Moomintroll?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 09:55:00" d="2020-04-17 10:10:00"><n u="SO Beano!">SO Beano! I (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Superheroes
Joseph reveals his alter-ego Hype Man, plus Nim and Emma interview the closest thing to a real-life superhero, martial artist Jesse-Jane McParland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 10:10:00" d="2020-04-17 10:30:00"><n u="Where's Wally">Where's Wally I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Wanderer in Paris
Odlulu has a magical shrinking key and sets her sights on the Tour de France</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 10:30:00" d="2020-04-17 10:45:00"><n u="Play Your Pets Right">Play Your Pets Right I (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Waffle vs Tara, Footballing Budgie
Excitable dogs Waffle and Tara prove just how distracting the Temptation Gauntlet can be, plus footballing budgie Frankie!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 10:45:00" d="2020-04-17 11:00:00"><n u="Fyi: For Your Info">Fyi: For Your Info I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Kids! Get totally up to date with this special news show just for you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 11:00:00" d="2020-04-17 12:00:00"><n u="The Dog Whisperer">The Dog Whisperer V (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Hyde &amp; Vada And Nacho
Series following renowned dog trainer Cesar Millan. Cesar helps a couple who are struggling to control their two overly aggressive wolf hybrids</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 12:00:00" d="2020-04-17 13:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VIII (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Old Tricks
The kidnapping of a care home resident sends the NCIS team on the trail of two con artists. Callen faces up to his dad about his illegal activities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 13:00:00" d="2020-04-17 14:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VIII (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Queen Pin
Sam embarks on a high-risk undercover operation to take down an elusive drug lord. Callen and Anna are ordered to escort a prisoner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 14:00:00" d="2020-04-17 15:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 V (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ka Hanu Malu (Inside Job)
McGarrett is reunited with Aunt Deb (Carol Burnett), who returns to the island with a new fiance. Also guest starring Frankie Valli</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 15:00:00" d="2020-04-17 16:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 V (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ke Koho Mamao Aku (Longshot)
Christmas proves far from merry for the Five-0 when they make their way to the Big Island to solve a cowboy's murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 16:00:00" d="2020-04-17 17:00:00"><n u="S.W.A.T.">S.W.A.T. I (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Crews
SWAT team up with the FBI when Hondo's informant friend is killed. But Jessica's alarm bells ring when their task force leader starts acting strangely</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 17:00:00" d="2020-04-17 17:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family II (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Good Cop Bad Dog
Claire and Phil swap parenting roles, and Mitchell has a dilemma on his hands when Cameron falls ill. Fred Savage directs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 17:30:00" d="2020-04-17 18:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family II (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% See You Next Fall
A chain of events, involving Botox and a tantrum or two, mean the family may miss Alex's graduation from middle school. Mild bad language</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 18:00:00" d="2020-04-17 18:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIII (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Bart Stops To Smell The Roosevelts
Principal Skinner has had enough of Bart's mischief- making and challenges Superintendent Chalmers to take over his education</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 18:30:00" d="2020-04-17 19:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IX (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Naturama
Season nine draws to a close with the Planet Express crew reimagined as various creatures, great and small, for a wildlife documentary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 19:00:00" d="2020-04-17 19:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Space Pilot 3000
A pizza delivery boy named Fry awakens from a state of suspended animation and finds himself in a futuristic world populated by aliens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 19:30:00" d="2020-04-17 20:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIII (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Daughter also Rises
Lisa falls in love, and Bart and Milhouse debunk some legends. Michael Cera and MythBusters' Jamie Hynemanand Adam Savage guest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 20:00:00" d="2020-04-17 20:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIII (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% At Long Last Leave
Crack open the Duff beers as the cartoon classic celebrates its milestone 500th episode by evicting Homer and co from Springfield</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 20:30:00" d="2020-04-17 21:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIII (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Exit Through the Kwik-E Mart
Bart gets his Banksy on by going undercover as a graffiti artist, while Apu worries when a hip health-food superstore opens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 21:00:00" d="2020-04-17 21:30:00"><n u="New: The Simpsons">New: The Simpsons XXXI (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Screenless. Marge put a screen time limit on the rest of the family, but soon realises that she may be the one who is addicted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-17 21:30:00" d="2020-04-18 00:30:00"><n u="New: Modern Family">New: Modern Family XI (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Spuds
Phil and Claire take Haley and Dylan to dinner to reassure them that their parenting skills are up to par. Meanwhile, Lily has a first date</k>  </p>
</a>
