<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2020-04-16 04:36:15"><p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 05:30:00" d="2020-04-23 06:00:00"><n u="Ninja Warrior">Ninja Warrior X (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The world's top athletes and wrestlers compete alongside amateurs in one of the most demanding physical challenges ever devised</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 06:00:00" d="2020-04-23 06:30:00"><n u="Ninja Warrior">Ninja Warrior X (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The world's top athletes and wrestlers compete alongside amateurs in one of the most demanding physical challenges ever devised</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 06:30:00" d="2020-04-23 07:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% My Three Suns
Fry finds himself the ruler of an alien world after he accidentally consumes the planet's emperor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 07:00:00" d="2020-04-23 07:30:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life XI (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Bruce the loris is in hospital for a check-up while the team have to make a tough decision about the future of capuchin Tau</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 07:30:00" d="2020-04-23 08:00:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life XI (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Alison collects a squirrel monkey that needs a new home. Also, can baby woolly Cosmo summon up the courage to take on the great outdoors?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 08:00:00" d="2020-04-23 08:30:00"><n u="Animal">Animal 999 I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>SPCA staff try to build up an emaciated seal's strength so it can rejoin its family in the sea, and three baby hedgehogs fight for life at the Penicuik centre</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 08:30:00" d="2020-04-23 09:00:00"><n u="Animal">Animal 999 II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Scottish SPCA goes to the rescue of a seal pup that's stranded on a beach. Plus, staff check up on a Jack Russell terrier that's suffering from a huge tumour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 09:00:00" d="2020-04-23 10:00:00"><n u="The Dog Whisperer">The Dog Whisperer V (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Chloe, Hobo, Ali and Maxwell
Horse whisperer Pat Parelli and dog trainer Cesar Millan team up to help staff at a riding centre tame their uncontrollable animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 10:00:00" d="2020-04-23 11:00:00"><n u="Big Cats An Amazing Animal Family">Big Cats An Amazing Animal Family (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Patrick Aryee comes within a whisker of some of Earth's most majestic predators on a stunning journey through the feline family tree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 11:00:00" d="2020-04-23 11:30:00"><n u="Highway Patrol">Highway Patrol V (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series following Australia's traffic enforcers, facing high-speed chases, explosive crashes and out-of-control drunk drivers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 11:30:00" d="2020-04-23 12:00:00"><n u="Highway Patrol">Highway Patrol V (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series following Australia's traffic enforcers, facing high-speed chases, explosive crashes and out-of-control drunk drivers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 12:00:00" d="2020-04-23 13:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles IX (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Party Crashers
A new boss steps in and shakes up the team. Hetty mysteriously vanishes, while Sam urges Callen to find a new partner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 13:00:00" d="2020-04-23 14:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles IX (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Se Murio El Payaso
The daughter of a notorious counterfeiter rocks up in LA, meaning Sam must go undercover as a financier</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 14:00:00" d="2020-04-23 15:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 V (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ike Hanau (Instinct)
Grover goes with his gut instinct to determine whether the demise of a friend's wife was a tragic accident or murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 15:00:00" d="2020-04-23 16:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 V (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mo'o Olelo Pu (Sharing Traditions)
Alarm bells ring when Kono's solo outrigger trip around the Hawaiian islands turns into a dramatic fight for survival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 16:00:00" d="2020-04-23 17:00:00"><n u="S.W.A.T.">S.W.A.T. I (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Source
A biological attack, a shoot-out, a crisis for Jim - it's all happening as SWAT protect a journalist who's got on the wrong side of some powerful men</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 17:00:00" d="2020-04-23 17:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Go Bullfrogs!
Phil spends quality time with Haley, taking her on a college tour of his old alma mater. Gloria and Jay have 'the talk' with Manny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 17:30:00" d="2020-04-23 18:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family III (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Treehouse
Gloria gives Jay an ultimatum, Cam takes a bet too far and Phil builds a treehouse. Guest starring Chazz Palminteri, Kevin Hart and Leslie Mann</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 18:00:00" d="2020-04-23 18:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIII (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Totally Fun Thing That Bart Will Never Do
The chaos-causing clan enjoy the ultimate cruise, until Bart decides to make the holiday last a lot longer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 18:30:00" d="2020-04-23 19:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% A Big Piece Of Garbage
A colossal chunk of stinking garbage threatens to destroy New New York City. Featuring the guest voice of inventor Ron Popeil as himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 19:00:00" d="2020-04-23 19:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Hell Is Other Robots
Bender turns to religion after becoming addicted to electricity. Featuring the voices of The Beastie Boys and Dan Castellaneta (voice of Homer Simpson)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 19:30:00" d="2020-04-23 20:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXX (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Baby You Can't Drive My Car
A self-driving car company brings its fun offices to Springfield. And that means big trouble for the power plant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 20:00:00" d="2020-04-23 20:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXX (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% From Russia Without Love
Bart, Nelson and Milhouse go all out with their pranks when they order Moe a mail-order bride on the Dark Web</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 20:30:00" d="2020-04-23 21:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXX (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Werking Mum
Marge stumbles into a new job as a plastic pot-selling drag queen when ambitious hairdresser Julio gives her a makeover. With the voice of RuPaul</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 21:00:00" d="2020-04-23 21:05:00"><n>Clap For Our Carers</n>    <k>Dermot Murnaghan with coverage from around the UK of the second Clap For Our Carers event in support of NHS workers fighting coronavirus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-23 21:05:00" d="2020-04-24 00:05:00"><n u="New: DC's Legends Of Tomorrow">New: DC's Legends Of Tomorrow V (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. A Head Of Her Time
With Sara away on business, Ava is in charge of the team as they take on their latest Encore, Marie Antoinette</k>  </p>
</a>
