<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="33" t="2019-07-11 00:20:56"><p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 05:00:00" d="2019-07-16 06:00:00"><n u="Babylon">Babylon 5 III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% Passing Through Gethsemane
Lyta Alexander returns as Kosh's aide. One of the monks starts having terrifying visions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 06:00:00" d="2019-07-16 07:00:00"><n u="Stargate SG-1">Stargate SG-1 II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Prisoners
After helping a murderer, the SG-1 team is banished to a penal world where an unusual ruler holds the key to their return home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 07:00:00" d="2019-07-16 07:30:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life II (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Chimp Seamus surprises staff by managing to control his wild side, and the newborn woolly monkey meets other members of its species for the first time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 07:30:00" d="2019-07-16 08:00:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life II (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Old habit dies hard as Seamus's period of calm comes to an abrupt end. Problems arise, meanwhile, when the team make arrangements for their trip to Chile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 08:00:00" d="2019-07-16 08:30:00"><n u="Animal">Animal 999 III (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Follow the SPCA and its dedicated team of rescue officers and inspectors as they make it their prime mission to protect pets and wild animals all over Scotland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 08:30:00" d="2019-07-16 09:00:00"><n u="Animal">Animal 999 III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Go behind the scenes at the Scottish SPCA, the country's leading animal charity, as cameras follow the work of its inspectors and rescue officers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 09:00:00" d="2019-07-16 09:30:00"><n u="Rspca Animal Rescue">Rspca Animal Rescue I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Moving series following RSPCA workers across Australia as they work to help animals in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 09:30:00" d="2019-07-16 10:00:00"><n u="Rspca Animal Rescue">Rspca Animal Rescue III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Moving series following RSPCA workers across Australia as they work to help animals in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 10:00:00" d="2019-07-16 11:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars VII (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A car thief causes chaos in Torquay, the Road Crime Unit track a Mercedes Benz loaded with cocaine in Plymouth, and it's training day for the Tactical Aid Group</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 11:00:00" d="2019-07-16 11:30:00"><n u="Highway Patrol">Highway Patrol V (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series following Australia's traffic enforcers, facing high-speed chases, explosive crashes and out-of-control drunk drivers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 11:30:00" d="2019-07-16 12:00:00"><n u="Highway Patrol Australia">Highway Patrol Australia I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series following Australia's traffic enforcers. Officers face high-speed chases, defiant hooligans, explosive crashes and out-of-control drunk drivers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 12:00:00" d="2019-07-16 13:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VI (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% SEAL Hunter
Shockwaves ripple through the team when Sam is arrested for a murder he swears he didn't commit. Directed by series star Chris O'Donnell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 13:00:00" d="2019-07-16 14:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VI (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Leipei
When a man is killed by a small drone, the team uncover a connection to a terrorist group planning their next attack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 14:00:00" d="2019-07-16 15:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 VIII (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Kopi wale no i ka i'a a 'eu no ka ilo. (Though the Fish is Well Salted, the Maggots Crawl): Five-0 help Duke when kidnappers force him to steal evidence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 15:00:00" d="2019-07-16 16:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 VIII (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ka Hana a ka makua, o ka hana no ia a keiki (What Parents Do, Children Will Do): Five-0 take on the mob when Junior's friend witnesses a hit on a former boss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 16:00:00" d="2019-07-16 17:00:00"><n u="MacGyver">MacGyver I (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Hole Puncher
Mac poses as psychopath Murdoc when the team intercepts a terror group's message ordering Murdoc to carry out an assassination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 17:00:00" d="2019-07-16 17:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family V (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Vegas
Minus the kids, the clans make their way to Sin City when Jay scores some luxury hotel rooms for free. Stephen Merchant guest stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 17:30:00" d="2019-07-16 18:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family V (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% A Hard Jay's Night
Plans for a chilled evening at Jay's turn out to be anything but. Plus, Mitch doesn't like a wedding gift made by Cam's dad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 18:00:00" d="2019-07-16 18:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XV (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% I, (Annoyed Grunt)-Bot
Bart enters his new robot into the Robot Rumble TV show without realising that it's Homer in a costume. Meanwhile, Lisa has cat trouble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 18:30:00" d="2019-07-16 19:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama X (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Saturday Morning Fun Pit
In one of the show's most out-there outings, the Planet Express crew secure roles in a trio of Saturday morning-style cartoons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 19:00:00" d="2019-07-16 19:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama X (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Calculon 2.0
Celebrated robot actor Calculon is given a second stab at stardom when Bender and Fry take extreme measures to bring him back from the dead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 19:30:00" d="2019-07-16 20:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XV (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% Smart &amp; Smarter
Guest star Simon Cowell is on form as the acid tongued interviewer at Miss Wickerbottom's Pre-Nursery. Will the caustic supervisor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 20:00:00" d="2019-07-16 20:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XV (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% The Ziff Who Came to Dinner
When Homer discovers Marge's old flame Artie Ziff living in the attic, a poker game ends in jail for Homer and romance for Artie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 20:30:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XV (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% Co-Dependent's Day
After a trip to a vineyard, Homer and Marge are three sheets to the wind. Drunk driver Homer crashes the car. so how come it's Marge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 22:00:00"><n>A League Of Their Own</n>    <k>Can't get enough of James and the boys? Neither can we. That's why the series goes to extra time, with all the outtakes, pranks and wind-ups we were never meant to see</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 22:00:00" d="2019-07-16 23:00:00"><n u="Rob &amp; Romesh Vs The NFL">Rob &amp; Romesh Vs The NFL I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Comedian mates Rob and Romesh meet and train with some of the NFL's biggest stars. Then, they get kitted up for a match in front of 80,000 people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-16 23:00:00" d="2019-07-17 00:00:00"><n u="New: Warrior">New: Warrior I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. The White Mountain
Big Bill spies a way to pay off his gambling debts. As Mai Ling meets with a rival tong, Ah Sahm is left contemplating a tempting offer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 00:00:00" d="2019-07-17 01:00:00"><n u="Micky Flanagan's Detour De France">Micky Flanagan's Detour De France I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>France is famous for its fizz and food, so it would be rude of Micky and Noel not to indulge in both. Noel also takes on a huge cycling challenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 01:00:00" d="2019-07-17 02:00:00"><n u="Brit Cops: Law &amp; Disorder">Brit Cops: Law &amp; Disorder IV (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series charting the exploits of the City of London police, charged with safeguarding the Square Mile at the heart of the crime-ridden capital</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 02:00:00" d="2019-07-17 03:00:00"><n u="The Blacklist">The Blacklist VI (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. The Ethicist
While Red's away getting his psychiatric assessment, Liz gets to work tracking down a Blacklister who may know a thing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 03:00:00" d="2019-07-17 04:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars VI (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Revealing the grit that goes into policing Britain's streets, tonight's instalment features a drugs raid, a confrontation with a drink driver and a firestarter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 04:00:00" d="2019-07-17 04:30:00"><n u="Motorway Patrol">Motorway Patrol IX (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series from New Zealand following the madness and mayhem faced by intrepid officers as they pull over motorists for a variety of suspected offences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-07-17 04:30:00" d="2019-07-17 05:00:00"><n u="Motorway Patrol">Motorway Patrol IX (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series from New Zealand following the madness and mayhem faced by intrepid officers as they pull over motorists for a variety of suspected offences</k>  </p>
</a>
