<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2019-08-13 02:24:54"><p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 05:00:00" d="2019-08-19 06:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Thames Valley Police provide a fascinating insight into car crime and its prevention. Plus, shocking video footage captures dangerous drivers in action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 06:00:00" d="2019-08-19 07:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Thames Valley Police provide a fascinating insight into car crime and its prevention. Plus, shocking video footage captures dangerous drivers in action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 07:00:00" d="2019-08-19 07:30:00"><n u="Animal House">Animal House IV (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series shining a spotlight on the staff at SPCA Auckland, who dedicate their days to the care and protection of the region's animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 07:30:00" d="2019-08-19 08:00:00"><n u="Animal House">Animal House IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series shining a spotlight on the staff at SPCA Auckland, who dedicate their days to the care and protection of the region's animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 08:00:00" d="2019-08-19 08:30:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life V (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Alison goes to the rescue of a squirrel monkey pet, desperate for a new home. Paddy's chimp group go mad for mangoes, and there's news of a weighty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 08:30:00" d="2019-08-19 09:00:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life V (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The team are in South Africa preparing to transport a very overweight orang-utan back to the UK, but things don't go according to plan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 09:00:00" d="2019-08-19 10:00:00"><n u="The Dog Whisperer">The Dog Whisperer II (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Renowned dog trainer Cesar Millan helps owners of unruly and disobedient pets in an attempt to make their lives a little easier</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 10:00:00" d="2019-08-19 11:00:00"><n u="Supergirl">Supergirl II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. The Last Children of Krypton
Cadmus attacks National City with a kryptonite powered villain who attempts to seriously hurt Supergirl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 11:00:00" d="2019-08-19 12:00:00"><n u="The Flash">The Flash III (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cause and Effect
Barry goes to desperate lengths to stop Savitar. Plus, Killer Frost returns armed with an intriguing proposition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 12:00:00" d="2019-08-19 13:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VIII (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Payback
Tensions in the team run high as one agent undergoes torture from the mole. Meanwhile, another uncovers a shocking betrayal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 13:00:00" d="2019-08-19 14:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VIII (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Old Tricks
The kidnapping of a care home resident sends the NCIS team on the trail of two con artists. Callen faces up to his dad about his illegal activities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 14:00:00" d="2019-08-19 15:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 V (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Powehiwehi (Blackout)
Kono has a close encounter with an elusive criminal, before making a decision about her relationship with Adam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 15:00:00" d="2019-08-19 16:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 V (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Kuka'awale (Stakeout)
McGarrett and Danno keep tabs on a woman involved in a diamond robbery. Directed by series star Daniel Dae Kim</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 16:00:00" d="2019-08-19 17:00:00"><n u="MacGyver">MacGyver II (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>MacGyver+ MacGyver
Mac tries to tell Matty he's quitting. But he's in for a shocking surprise. Gripping season finale guest starring Tate Donovan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 17:00:00" d="2019-08-19 17:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VII (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Promposal
Asking a girl to the prom gets even more nerve-wrecking for Luke and Manny when Cam and Mitch decide to interfere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 17:30:00" d="2019-08-19 18:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VII (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Crazy Train
An eventful journey is in store for the Pritchett-Dunphy-Tuckers as they board the train for DeDe's wedding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 18:00:00" d="2019-08-19 18:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXII (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Donnie Fatso
Following an incident involving recycling responsibilities and a bit of bribery, Homer goes undercover to bring down Fat Tony</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 18:30:00" d="2019-08-19 19:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% A Tale Of Two Santas
When the gang accidentally freeze Santa (who is a robot intent on destroying Christmas), Fry revives the traditional image</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 19:00:00" d="2019-08-19 19:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IV (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Anthology Of Interest #2
When the Professor fine tunes his 'What If' machine, Bender discovers what life would be like as a human, and Fry experiences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 19:30:00" d="2019-08-19 20:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXII (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Homer The Father
While Homer picks up parenting tips from a sitcom, Bart becomes involved in trading nuclear secrets. Writers James Lipton and David Mamet guest star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 20:00:00" d="2019-08-19 20:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXII (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Blue and the Gray
After finding her first grey hair, Marge decides to embrace middle age. Homie spices up Moe's love life too by becoming his official 'wing man'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 20:30:00" d="2019-08-19 21:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXII (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Angry Dad
The Movie: Homer and Bart clash when their cartoon is bought by a studio. Ricky Gervais, Russell Brand and Oscar winners Nick Park and Halle Berry guest star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 21:00:00" d="2019-08-19 22:00:00"><n>Carpool Karaoke: When Corden Met McCartney Live from Liverpool</n>    <k>Loved Sir Paul's Carpool Karaoke this summer? Tune in for extra footage as he and James Corden sing more songs and put on a surprise gig</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-19 22:00:00" d="2019-08-20 00:20:00" c="1"><n>New: Ghost Rider</n><t>F</t>    <k>Motorbike stuntman Nicolas Cage does a deal with the Devil and becomes a skull-faced avenger on two fiery wheels. Sci-fi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 00:20:00" d="2019-08-20 01:20:00"><n u="Manifest">Manifest I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Turbulence
Ben and Michaela fear a link between a shocking murder and Flight 828. Meanwhile, Ben struggles to accept the life Grace led in his absence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 01:20:00" d="2019-08-20 02:20:00"><n u="Brit Cops: Rapid Response">Brit Cops: Rapid Response III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Action-packed documentary following rapid response officers, the fastest cops in Britain, as they crack down on crime. Time is of the essence!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 02:20:00" d="2019-08-20 03:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars III (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Thames Valley Police get into the driving seat in the fight against crime. Follow officers as they deal with robberies, street fights and domestic violence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 03:00:00" d="2019-08-20 04:00:00"><n u="Warrior">Warrior I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. They Don't Pay Us Enough to Think
A bloodbath on Chinatown's streets leads the Hop Wei and Long Xii to consider an unusual way to end the hostilities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 04:00:00" d="2019-08-20 05:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 V (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Nanahu (Embers)
Five-0 need outside help to track down an arsonist targeting couples. Plus, Danno takes Amber on a romantic getaway</k>  </p>
</a>
