<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="33" t="2021-07-09 07:13:59"><p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 05:00:00" d="2021-07-14 06:00:00"><n u="Stop Search Seize">Stop Search Seize I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Ireland's Customs teams as they, with the help of the Irish police, try to stop organised smugglers from bringing drugs, cars and even exotic animals into the country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 06:00:00" d="2021-07-14 07:00:00"><n u="S.W.A.T.">S.W.A.T. III (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Stigma
When their former unit leader Buck goes off the grid, Hondo and the team confront their emotional difficulties as they race to save him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 07:00:00" d="2021-07-14 07:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama X (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Leela and the Genestalk
Leela is in for a shock when she develops a set of tentacles. It's a grim discovery that leads her to a secret genetic engineering lab</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 07:30:00" d="2021-07-14 08:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama X (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Game of Tones
Fry travels back in time (via his dreams) to 31 December 1999 to decipher the meaning behind a mysterious alien melody</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 08:00:00" d="2021-07-14 08:30:00"><n u="Baby Animals">Baby Animals I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Fresh Meat
There's no time to lie about and relax for some baby animals. If they want to avoid being someone else's prey, they have to hit the ground running</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 08:30:00" d="2021-07-14 09:00:00"><n u="Baby Animals">Baby Animals I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lil' Hunters
You can't be a predator if you don't know how to hunt. See how little lions, cheetahs and other small carnivores harness their skills through play</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 09:00:00" d="2021-07-14 09:30:00"><n u="Monkey Business">Monkey Business III (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Dr Alison Cronin's team at the Monkey World Ape Rescue Centre in Dorset as they rehabilitate abused primates and support overseas projects to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 09:30:00" d="2021-07-14 10:00:00"><n u="Monkey Business">Monkey Business III (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Dr Alison Cronin's team at the Monkey World Ape Rescue Centre in Dorset as they rehabilitate abused primates and support overseas projects to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 10:00:00" d="2021-07-14 10:30:00"><n u="Motorway Patrol">Motorway Patrol IV (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series from New Zealand following the madness and mayhem faced by intrepid officers as they pull over motorists for a variety of suspected offences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 10:30:00" d="2021-07-14 11:00:00"><n u="Motorway Patrol">Motorway Patrol IV (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series from New Zealand following the madness and mayhem faced by intrepid officers as they pull over motorists for a variety of suspected offences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 11:00:00" d="2021-07-14 12:00:00"><n u="Stop Search Seize">Stop Search Seize I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Ireland's Customs teams as they, with the help of the Irish police, try to stop organised smugglers from bringing drugs, cars and even exotic animals into the country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 12:00:00" d="2021-07-14 13:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles XI (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Watch Over Me
An FBI agent is killed while searching for an undercover operative - leaving NCIS to find the missing target before the criminals do</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 13:00:00" d="2021-07-14 14:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles XI (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Missing Time
NCIS investigates the disappearance of a UFO-investigating officer in the Department of Defense. Anna makes a bold decision</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 14:00:00" d="2021-07-14 15:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 VI (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ka Pohaku Kihi Pa'a (The Solid Cornerstone)
When the task force's long-time informant is accused of murder, McGarrett brings in an old friend to defend him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 15:00:00" d="2021-07-14 16:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 VI (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Waiwai (Assets)
McGarrett and Five-0 search for a Russian spy who throws the life of one of their own into jeopardy when he steals NSA secrets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 16:00:00" d="2021-07-14 17:00:00"><n u="S.W.A.T.">S.W.A.T. III (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Vice
The team searches for an escaped convict who plans to kill Tan - and every member of law enforcement who helped put him in the cell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 17:00:00" d="2021-07-14 17:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VIII (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Halloween 4
The Revenge of Rod Skyhook: Luke's party gets an unexpected jumpstart, Cam faces off with his Halloween nemesis and Jay clashes with an old enemy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 17:30:00" d="2021-07-14 18:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VIII (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Grab it
Mitchell is thrown into the spotlight when Cam fails to fill him in on his play. Phil threatens to spoil Jay's favourite place in the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 18:00:00" d="2021-07-14 18:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n>    <k>Marge vs The Monorail: Leonard Nimoy lends his voice to a hilarious tale in which an unscrupulous profiteer sells the people of Springfield a defective monorail system</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 18:30:00" d="2021-07-14 19:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama X (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Leela and the Genestalk
Leela is in for a shock when she develops a set of tentacles. It's a grim discovery that leads her to a secret genetic engineering lab</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 19:00:00" d="2021-07-14 19:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama X (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Game of Tones
Fry travels back in time (via his dreams) to 31 December 1999 to decipher the meaning behind a mysterious alien melody</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 19:30:00" d="2021-07-14 20:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n>    <k>So It's Come To This: Family and friends reminisce about Homer's life after Bart's April Fool's Day prank puts him in hospital</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 20:00:00" d="2021-07-14 20:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n>    <k>The Front: Lisa and Bart compose a script full of gratuitous violence and submit it to the producers of 'Itchy &amp; Scratchy'. Featuring the guest voice of Brooke Shields</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 20:30:00" d="2021-07-14 21:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n>    <k>Whacking Day: Citizens of Springfield beat out all the snakes in the area and herd them to their certain death, but Bart, Lisa and special guest star Barry White save the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 21:00:00" d="2021-07-14 22:00:00"><n u="New: DC's Legends Of Tomorrow">New: DC's Legends Of Tomorrow VI (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. The Ex-Factor
The Legends are in 2045 trying to defeat an alien warrior, which leaves Zari no choice but to enter a popular singing competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 22:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:00:00"><n u="New: Prodigal Son">New: Prodigal Son II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Head Case
While the team investigates the murder of an architect, Bright is knocked out and falls into a dream state in which nothing is as it seems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-14 23:00:00" d="2021-07-15 00:00:00"><n u="Rob &amp; Romesh Vs Andy Murray">Rob &amp; Romesh Vs Andy Murray III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. The comedy duo serve up a special with Sir Andy Murray, as he pushes them to the limit in a tennis session and takes them out road cycling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-15 00:00:00" d="2021-07-15 00:30:00"><n u="Breeders">Breeders II (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. No Excuses
Ally and Paul's marriage is in crisis, while an increasingly troubled Luke refuses to go to school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-15 00:30:00" d="2021-07-15 01:30:00"><n u="S.W.A.T.">S.W.A.T. IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Under Fire
The SWAT team hunts a sniper who is targeting LA's Fire Department. Meanwhile, the rivalry between Chris, Street and Tan heats up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-15 01:30:00" d="2021-07-15 02:30:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars VII (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Dog handler Steve deals with an aggressive assailant; the Road Crime Unit pull over a BMW loaded with drugs; and the Tactical Aid Group kit up and prepare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-15 02:30:00" d="2021-07-15 03:30:00"><n>The Force: Manchester S02</n>    <k>Officers are called to a disturbance at a hostel, and a dispute spirals out of control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-15 03:30:00" d="2021-07-15 04:30:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles XI (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Alsiyasun
While on a mission, Fatima is captured and held for ransom. The race is on as Callen and Sam entrust an undercover CIA operative to rescue her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-15 04:30:00" d="2021-07-15 05:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars III (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Thames Valley Police provide a fascinating insight into car crime and its prevention. Plus, shocking video footage captures dangerous drivers in action</k>  </p>
</a>
