<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2019-08-13 02:25:01"><p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 05:00:00" d="2019-08-20 05:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% A Tale Of Two Santas
When the gang accidentally freeze Santa (who is a robot intent on destroying Christmas), Fry revives the traditional image</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 05:30:00" d="2019-08-20 06:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IV (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Anthology Of Interest #2
When the Professor fine tunes his 'What If' machine, Bender discovers what life would be like as a human, and Fry experiences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 06:00:00" d="2019-08-20 06:30:00"><n u="Rspca Animal Rescue">Rspca Animal Rescue IV (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Moving series following RSPCA workers across Australia as they work to help animals in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 06:30:00" d="2019-08-20 07:00:00"><n u="Rspca Animal Rescue">Rspca Animal Rescue IV (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Moving series following RSPCA workers across Australia as they work to help animals in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 07:00:00" d="2019-08-20 07:30:00"><n u="Animal House">Animal House IV (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series shining a spotlight on the staff at SPCA Auckland, who dedicate their days to the care and protection of the region's animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 07:30:00" d="2019-08-20 08:00:00"><n u="Animal House">Animal House IV (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series shining a spotlight on the staff at SPCA Auckland, who dedicate their days to the care and protection of the region's animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 08:00:00" d="2019-08-20 08:30:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life V (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>There's a problem at the airport with the transportation of overweight orang-utan Oshine from South Africa - will she make it onto the plane?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 08:30:00" d="2019-08-20 09:00:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life V (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>There's some exciting news at the woolly monkey house. New arrival Oshine has and eventful first night in the orang-utan nursery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 09:00:00" d="2019-08-20 10:00:00"><n u="The Dog Whisperer">The Dog Whisperer III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Kobe, Banjo And Kisses
Cesar works his magic on a one-eyed Australian shepherd who bites people and lunges at strangers, and a rescued coonhound afraid of people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 10:00:00" d="2019-08-20 11:00:00"><n u="Supergirl">Supergirl II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Welcome to Earth
Supergirl and the DEO are assigned to protect the President (Lynda Carter) after she becomes the victim of a terrifying attack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 11:00:00" d="2019-08-20 12:00:00"><n u="The Flash">The Flash III (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Infantino Street
With just 24 hours left before Savitar murders Iris, Barry realises his last hope of saving the woman he loves rests with Captain Cold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 12:00:00" d="2019-08-20 13:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VIII (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Queen Pin
Sam embarks on a high-risk undercover operation to take down an elusive drug lord. Callen and Anna are ordered to escort a prisoner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 13:00:00" d="2019-08-20 14:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VIII (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Getaway
The cyber office's Dave Flynn arrives to run ops when the US treasury is hacked and Nell and Eric are sent undercover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 14:00:00" d="2019-08-20 15:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 V (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ike Hanau (Instinct)
Grover goes with his gut instinct to determine whether the demise of a friend's wife was a tragic accident or murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 15:00:00" d="2019-08-20 16:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 V (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mo'o Olelo Pu (Sharing Traditions)
Alarm bells ring when Kono's solo outrigger trip around the Hawaiian islands turns into a dramatic fight for survival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 16:00:00" d="2019-08-20 17:00:00"><n u="MacGyver">MacGyver III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Improvise
Mac's quit but his mate Jack is about to bring him right back into the action. He's in danger and that calls for some deadly DIY</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 17:00:00" d="2019-08-20 17:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VII (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Double Click
Phil catches Luke in a compromising position. Meanwhile, Cam and Mitch make plans to spend the summer apart. Last in series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 17:30:00" d="2019-08-20 18:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VIII (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% A Tale of Three Cities
The Golden Globe and Emmy award-winning comedy returns for season eight as all three families recount their unique holiday experiences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 18:00:00" d="2019-08-20 18:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXII (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Moms I'd Like To Forget
While Bart sets out to uncover the origins of a sword-shaped scar on his hand, Marge reconnects with three friends she fell out with years ago</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 18:30:00" d="2019-08-20 19:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IV (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Love And Rocket
As Valentine's Day approaches, Bender's romance with the Planet Express ship puts the crew in jeopardy. Guest starring Sigourney Weaver and Lucy Liu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 19:00:00" d="2019-08-20 19:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IV (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Leela's Homeworld
After being named 'Orphan Of The Year', Leela finally learns the truth about her parents and her own identity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 19:30:00" d="2019-08-20 20:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXII (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Scorpion's Tale
When Lisa discovers wild flowers with special, happy powers, Bart hatches a money-making scheme. Iconoclastic director Werner Herzog guests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 20:00:00" d="2019-08-20 20:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXII (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Great Simpsina
Lisa becomes an apprentice to the Great Raymondo. Guest starring Martin Landau, Jack McBrayer and a trio of magicians, including David Copperfield</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 20:30:00" d="2019-08-20 21:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXII (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Real Housewives Of Fat Tony
Marge has her reservations when Fat Tony and sister Selma embark on a whirlwind romance. Will a trip to the Jersey Shore calm her fears?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 21:00:00" d="2019-08-20 22:00:00"><n u="A League Of Their Own">A League Of Their Own XIV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Get ready for more laughs, wacky challenges and studio chaos as James Corden and the boys team up with Fearne Cotton, Jimmy Anderson and Joe Cole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2019-08-20 22:00:00" d="2019-08-21 01:00:00"><n u="New: Manifest">New: Manifest I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Unclaimed Baggage
A mysterious message leads Saanvi and Ben to a secret about Flight 828. Michaela is given reason to question the nature of the callings</k>  </p>
</a>
