<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2020-05-27 04:35:57"><p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 05:00:00" d="2020-06-03 06:00:00"><n u="Sun, Sea And A&amp;E">Sun, Sea And A&amp;E I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Maureen's Big Fat Knee
Documentary series following the misfortunes of British holidaymakers who find themselves recuperating in hospital rather than soaking up the sun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 06:00:00" d="2020-06-03 06:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama V (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% The Sting
Leela has a strange experience after being stung by killer bees while on a mission to collect ordinary honey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 06:30:00" d="2020-06-03 07:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama V (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Farnsworth Parabox
The Planet Express crew goes to a parallel universe made accessible by Professor Farnsworth's latest experiment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 07:00:00" d="2020-06-03 07:30:00"><n u="Monkey Business">Monkey Business V (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Dr Alison Cronin's team at the Monkey World Ape Rescue Centre in Dorset as they rehabilitate abused primates and support overseas projects to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 07:30:00" d="2020-06-03 08:00:00"><n u="Monkey Business">Monkey Business V (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Dr Alison Cronin's team at the Monkey World Ape Rescue Centre in Dorset as they rehabilitate abused primates and support overseas projects to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 08:00:00" d="2020-06-03 08:30:00"><n u="Animal House">Animal House II (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series shining a spotlight on the staff at SPCA Auckland, who dedicate their days to the care and protection of the region's animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 08:30:00" d="2020-06-03 09:00:00"><n u="Animal House">Animal House II (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series shining a spotlight on the staff at SPCA Auckland, who dedicate their days to the care and protection of the region's animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 09:00:00" d="2020-06-03 10:00:00"><n u="The Dog Whisperer">The Dog Whisperer VI (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Snickers and Maury
An Australian Shepherd behaves aggressively after being attacked by a couple of dogs, and a shelter dog won't stop biting and snapping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 10:00:00" d="2020-06-03 10:30:00"><n u="Motorbike Cops">Motorbike Cops I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Australia's traffic cops on their daily jobs and get an inside look into what goes into policing the country's roads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 10:30:00" d="2020-06-03 11:00:00"><n u="Motorbike Cops">Motorbike Cops I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Join Australia's traffic cops on their daily jobs and get an inside look into what goes into policing the country's roads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 11:00:00" d="2020-06-03 12:00:00"><n u="Sun, Sea And A&amp;E">Sun, Sea And A&amp;E II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bomb
Documentary series following the misfortunes of British holidaymakers who find themselves recuperating in hospital rather than soaking up the sun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 12:00:00" d="2020-06-03 13:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles II (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Bounty
When a former Army Sergeant responsible for hunting down high-value targets is discovered dead, Callen, Hanna and co believe terrorist leaders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 13:00:00" d="2020-06-03 14:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles II (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Absolution
The first of a thrilling two-parter. After an antique dealer's murder, the team embark on a mission to recover a black book containing top secret information</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 14:00:00" d="2020-06-03 15:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 VIII (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Kopi wale no i ka i'a a 'eu no ka ilo. (Though the Fish is Well Salted, the Maggots Crawl): Five-0 help Duke when kidnappers force him to steal evidence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 15:00:00" d="2020-06-03 16:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 VIII (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ka Hana a ka makua, o ka hana no ia a keiki (What Parents Do, Children Will Do): Five-0 take on the mob when Junior's friend witnesses a hit on a former boss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 16:00:00" d="2020-06-03 17:00:00"><n u="Magnum P.I.">Magnum P.I. I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Cat who Cried Wolf
There's moggies and murder for Magnum as the hunt for a girl's missing cat leads our charming PI to a dead FBI agent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 17:00:00" d="2020-06-03 17:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family V (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Under Pressure
Gloria settles a score with a mean mum, and Mitch tries to out-green his neighbour. Guest starring Jesse Eisenberg. Moderate bad language/flashing images</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 17:30:00" d="2020-06-03 18:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family V (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Three Dinners
While Jay struggles to digest some news from best pal Shorty, Cam and Mitch take a break from the wedding planning to enjoy a romantic dinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 18:00:00" d="2020-06-03 18:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIV (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Love Is A Many-Splintered Thing
Bart is reunited with Mary, and Homer finds himself in the doghouse. Guest starring Zooey Deschanel and Benedict Cumberbatch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 18:30:00" d="2020-06-03 19:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama V (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% 300 Big Boys
When every Earthican receives a windfall of three hundred dollars, each decides to spend it in a unique way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 19:00:00" d="2020-06-03 19:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama V (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Spanish Fry
When Fry succeeds in retrieving his nose, which was taken by aliens, a more precious appendage of his is placed in peril</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 19:30:00" d="2020-06-03 20:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIV (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Pulpit Friction
Reverend Lovejoy is pushed out by a savvy new arrival, and there's a mix-up involving Marge's wedding dress. Guest starring Edward Norton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 20:00:00" d="2020-06-03 20:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIV (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Fabulous Faker Boy
Marge books Bart in for piano lessons, and a distraught Homer becomes completely bald. Guest starring Jane Krakowski and Bill Hader</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 20:30:00" d="2020-06-03 21:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIV (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Saga Of Carl
Friendships are tested when Carl skips town with $200,000, winnings from a lottery ticket he bought with Homer, Moe and Lenny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 21:00:00" d="2020-06-03 22:00:00"><n u="Rob &amp; Romesh Vs Fashion">Rob &amp; Romesh Vs Fashion I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Rob and Romesh strut their stuff on the catwalk and meet male model David Gandy. Then, it's off to NYC to try and bag a gig on a real-life runway</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 22:00:00" d="2020-06-03 23:00:00"><n u="A League Of Their Own">A League Of Their Own XII (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Sir Bradley Wiggins, Jimmy Carr and Sara Cox join the fun. John Barnes and Kevin Pietersen team up with Jamie and Freddie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-03 23:00:00" d="2020-06-04 02:00:00"><n u="New: Code">New: Code 404 I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. With Major's AI finally living up to the hype, Carver and Kelly come clean about their relationship. Series finale</k>  </p>
</a>
