<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2020-05-12 04:37:49"><p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 05:00:00" d="2020-05-19 06:00:00"><n u="Caught On Dashcam">Caught On Dashcam I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A countdown of the most incredible, hilarious and spectacular real life crashes in the world - all caught on dashcam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 06:00:00" d="2020-05-19 06:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama III (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Time Keeps On Slipping
When the Professor creates a mutant team to take on the Harlem Globetrotters, he disrupts the time/space continuum, with eye-opening results</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 06:30:00" d="2020-05-19 07:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama III (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% I Dated A Robot
In his quest to live out his fantasies, Fry downloads a virtual Lucy Liu humanoid ('Liubot'), with whom he falls in love. Lucy Liu guest stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 07:00:00" d="2020-05-19 07:30:00"><n u="Monkey Business">Monkey Business IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Dr Alison Cronin's team at the Monkey World Ape Rescue Centre in Dorset as they rehabilitate abused primates and support overseas projects to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 07:30:00" d="2020-05-19 08:00:00"><n u="Monkey Business">Monkey Business IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Dr Alison Cronin's team at the Monkey World Ape Rescue Centre in Dorset as they rehabilitate abused primates and support overseas projects to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 08:00:00" d="2020-05-19 08:30:00"><n u="Animal">Animal 999 VI (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Fascinating insight into the work that goes on behind the scenes at Scotland's leading animal welfare organisation, the Scottish SPCA</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 08:30:00" d="2020-05-19 09:00:00"><n u="Animal">Animal 999 VI (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Fascinating insight into the work that goes on behind the scenes at Scotland's leading animal welfare organisation, the Scottish SPCA</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 09:00:00" d="2020-05-19 10:00:00"><n u="The Dog Whisperer">The Dog Whisperer V (29)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cesar Down Under
Cesar travels to Australia, and helps a physical trainer who coaches some of Australia's best athletes but cannot keep his Great Dane in line</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 10:00:00" d="2020-05-19 11:00:00"><n u="Brit Cops: Law &amp; Disorder">Brit Cops: Law &amp; Disorder IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series charting the exploits of the City of London police, charged with safeguarding the Square Mile at the heart of the crime-ridden capital</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 11:00:00" d="2020-05-19 12:00:00"><n u="Caught On Dashcam">Caught On Dashcam II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Outrageous road disasters and highway hijinks, captured in video via people's in-vehicle dash-board cameras</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 12:00:00" d="2020-05-19 13:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles X (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% New &amp; Exclusive. No More Secrets
It's time for an off-the-books NCIS mission when Callen finds out Anna Kolcheck is hiding out in Cuba</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 13:00:00" d="2020-05-19 14:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles X (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% New &amp; Exclusive. The Guardian
Sam and Callen race to help Navy Captain Harm Rabb when ISIS sympathisers set their sights on military bases</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 14:00:00" d="2020-05-19 15:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 VII (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>E Malama Pono (Handle With Care)
Having finally found the deadly uranium, Danny and McGarrett begin the near-impossible task of extracting it from the jungle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 15:00:00" d="2020-05-19 16:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 VII (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Huikau Na Makau A Ka Lawai'a (The Fishhooks Of The Fishers Become Entangled): Five-0 joins forces with PI Harry Brown when a wealthy woman is kidnapped</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 16:00:00" d="2020-05-19 17:00:00"><n u="S.W.A.T.">S.W.A.T. II (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cash Flow
Hondo has a tense reunion with a fellow marine as SWAT hunt an escape convict. Meanwhile, Chris prepares for a difficult goodbye</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 17:00:00" d="2020-05-19 17:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family IV (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Bad Hair Day
Phil is bitten by the green-eyed monster after gate-crashing Claire's college reunion, while Cam's elaborate photo shoot ends in disaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 17:30:00" d="2020-05-19 18:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family IV (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Best Men
Mitch and Cam's best gal pal, Sal (guest star Elizabeth Banks) is back with a bombshell, and Phil steps in to help Luke woo a girl he likes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 18:00:00" d="2020-05-19 18:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons II (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% While attending a comic book convention Bart finds the very first issue of 'Radio-Active Man' on sale for $100 and talks Milhouse and Martin into sharing in the cost</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 18:30:00" d="2020-05-19 19:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Roswell That Ends Well
When the Planet Express ship travels through time to Roswell, New Mexico in 1947, Fry becomes his own progeny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 19:00:00" d="2020-05-19 19:30:00"><n u="Futurama Xmas">Futurama Xmas IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Tale Of Two Santas
When the gang accidentally freeze Santa (who is a robot intent on destroying Christmas), Fry revives the traditional image</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 19:30:00" d="2020-05-19 20:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Bart the Murderer
Bart is befriended by a couple of mobsters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 20:00:00" d="2020-05-19 20:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Homer Defined
Homer falls asleep on the job, unaware that a nuclear meltdown is occurring in the plant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 20:30:00" d="2020-05-19 21:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Like Father, Like Clown
Bart and Lisa try to reunite Krusty The Clown with his estranged father, Rabbi Krustofski (Jackie Mason)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 21:00:00" d="2020-05-19 22:00:00"><n u="New: The Flash">New: The Flash VI (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. So Long And Goodnight
Black Hole hires Rag Doll to kill Joe. But despite Singh's pleas to put him in Witness Protection, Joe continues his investigation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 22:00:00" d="2020-05-19 23:00:00"><n u="New: Rob &amp; Romesh Vs Cricket - South Africa">New: Rob &amp; Romesh Vs Cricket - South Africa II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. The guys go to South Africa to follow England's cricket team. There's commentary, a lesson with Kevin Pietersen - and even a safari</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-05-19 23:00:00" d="2020-05-20 02:00:00" c="1"><n>I Now Pronounce You Chuck &amp; Larry</n><t>F</t>    <k>60% NY fireman Adam Sandler dreams up a benefits scam - to pretend to be gay. But can he keep up the charade? Comedy with Jessica Biel</k>  </p>
</a>
