<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2020-04-15 04:27:42"><p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 05:00:00" d="2020-04-22 05:30:00"><n u="Ninja Warrior">Ninja Warrior IX (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The world's top athletes and wrestlers compete alongside amateurs in one of the most demanding physical challenges ever devised</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 05:30:00" d="2020-04-22 06:00:00"><n u="Ninja Warrior">Ninja Warrior IX (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The world's top athletes and wrestlers compete alongside amateurs in one of the most demanding physical challenges ever devised</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 06:00:00" d="2020-04-22 06:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Love's Labour's Lost In Space
Leela finds herself the object of a starship captain's amorous advances</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 06:30:00" d="2020-04-22 07:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Fear Of A Bot Planet
Fry and Leela find themselves trapped on a planet ruled by human-hating robots</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 07:00:00" d="2020-04-22 07:30:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life XI (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Rescued marmoset Amy has her day in court while elderly golden-cheeked gibbon Alex causes concern. For the squirrel monkeys, the chase is on for a sweet treat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 07:30:00" d="2020-04-22 08:00:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life XI (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>It's dentist day for ring-tailed lemur Houdini and stump-tailed macaque Maureen. Benny and Nia meet The Odd Couple and the primate care staff name Xingu's baby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 08:00:00" d="2020-04-22 08:30:00"><n u="Animal">Animal 999 I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A ferret is on the loose in Huntly, Aberdeenshire, a Staffordshire bull terrier causes concern in Glasgow and two newly hatched owlets face a fight for their lives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 08:30:00" d="2020-04-22 09:00:00"><n u="Animal">Animal 999 I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Pilot whales are in danger of becoming beached on South Uist, horses risk being poisoned by the toxic ragwort weed, and inspectors check in at a farming show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 09:00:00" d="2020-04-22 10:00:00"><n u="The Dog Whisperer">The Dog Whisperer V (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Charlotte, Elvis and Jack
Cesar helps opera star Eileen Davidson and World Poker Tour host Vince Van Patten with their unruly pooch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 10:00:00" d="2020-04-22 11:00:00"><n u="Monkeys: An Amazing Animal..">Monkeys: An Amazing Animal.. (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>. amily. Patrick Aryee examines the new world monkeys from Central and South America and their evolutionary journey dating back more than 40 million years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 11:00:00" d="2020-04-22 11:30:00"><n u="Highway Patrol">Highway Patrol V (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series following Australia's traffic enforcers, facing high-speed chases, explosive crashes and out-of-control drunk drivers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 11:30:00" d="2020-04-22 12:00:00"><n u="Highway Patrol">Highway Patrol V (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series following Australia's traffic enforcers, facing high-speed chases, explosive crashes and out-of-control drunk drivers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 12:00:00" d="2020-04-22 13:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VIII (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Golden Days
The team continue to work with Hetty's former Vietnam War colleagues as they begin a risky investigation into a gold heist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 13:00:00" d="2020-04-22 14:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VIII (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Unleashed
Following the kidnapping of his wife, Sam goes rogue in the hope of stopping terrorist Tahir Khaled once and for all. Season finale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 14:00:00" d="2020-04-22 15:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 V (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Powehiwehi (Blackout)
Kono has a close encounter with an elusive criminal, before making a decision about her relationship with Adam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 15:00:00" d="2020-04-22 16:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 V (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Kuka'awale (Stakeout)
McGarrett and Danno keep tabs on a woman involved in a diamond robbery. Directed by series star Daniel Dae Kim</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 16:00:00" d="2020-04-22 17:00:00"><n u="S.W.A.T.">S.W.A.T. I (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Patrol
Hondo's forced to face up to his dad after years of resentment. Out on patrol, Mumford makes Chris a surprising offer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 17:00:00" d="2020-04-22 17:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Door To Door
Jay helps Manny with a fundraiser involving wrapping paper, and Claire stresses over a stop sign. David Cross (Arrested Development) guests. Mild bad language</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 17:30:00" d="2020-04-22 18:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Hit And Run
All the men in the family are angry: while Jay is frustrated at work, Mitch and Cam are involved in a fender bender</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 18:00:00" d="2020-04-22 18:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIII (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Beware My Cheating Bart
While Bart falls for a girl whose boyfriend happens to be the school bully, Homer uses his new treadmill to catch up on a Lost-inspired TV show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 18:30:00" d="2020-04-22 19:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% A Fishful Of Dollars
Fry discovers that a small amount of money left in his old bank account has accumulated into a fortune. Featuring the guest voice of Pamela Anderson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 19:00:00" d="2020-04-22 19:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% My Three Suns
Fry finds himself the ruler of an alien world after he accidentally consumes the planet's emperor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 19:30:00" d="2020-04-22 20:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXX (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Heartbreak Hotel
Marge and Homer's marriage is tested as they swap Springfield for a tropical island in a bid to win a million bucks on Marge's fave TV show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 20:00:00" d="2020-04-22 20:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXX (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% My Way or the Highway to Heaven
As the Springfield crowd recall their divine encounters, God and St Peter question what it takes to enter the Pearly Gates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 20:30:00" d="2020-04-22 21:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXX (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Treehouse of Horror XXIX
There's a trio of terror as the town's overrun by plant body-snatchers. Lisa snaps and Homer and Cthulhu clash in fishy circumstances</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-22 21:00:00" d="2020-04-23 00:00:00"><n u="Rob &amp; Romesh Vs Usain Bolt">Rob &amp; Romesh Vs Usain Bolt I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Comedian mates Rob Beckett and Romesh Ranganathan head to Jamaica to meet sprint legend Usain Bolt - the fastest man ever to have lived</k>  </p>
</a>
