<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2021-07-10 05:02:40"><p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 05:00:00" d="2021-07-17 06:00:00"><n u="Stop Search Seize">Stop Search Seize I (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Ireland's Customs teams as they, with the help of the Irish police, try to stop organised smugglers from bringing drugs, cars and even exotic animals into the country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 06:00:00" d="2021-07-17 07:00:00"><n u="S.W.A.T.">S.W.A.T. III (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Diablo
In the season three finale, the team searches for a group of drug smugglers who crash a plane in a Los Angeles suburb and flee</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 07:00:00" d="2021-07-17 07:30:00"><n u="Monkey Business">Monkey Business III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Dr Alison Cronin's team at the Monkey World Ape Rescue Centre in Dorset as they rehabilitate abused primates and support overseas projects to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 07:30:00" d="2021-07-17 08:00:00"><n u="Monkey Business">Monkey Business III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Dr Alison Cronin's team at the Monkey World Ape Rescue Centre in Dorset as they rehabilitate abused primates and support overseas projects to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 08:00:00" d="2021-07-17 08:30:00"><n u="Monkey Business">Monkey Business III (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Dr Alison Cronin's team at the Monkey World Ape Rescue Centre in Dorset as they rehabilitate abused primates and support overseas projects to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 08:30:00" d="2021-07-17 09:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VIII (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% A Tale of Three Cities
The Golden Globe and Emmy award-winning comedy returns for season eight as all three families recount their unique holiday experiences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 09:00:00" d="2021-07-17 09:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VIII (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% A Stereotypical Day
Jay tries to make a good impression on his new neighbours, while Cam and Mitchell attempt to teach Lily a message of acceptance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 09:30:00" d="2021-07-17 10:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VIII (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Blindsided
Family pride is at stake as Luke decides to run against Manny for class president. Meanwhile, Cam takes in a star high school football player</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 10:00:00" d="2021-07-17 10:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VIII (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Weathering Heights
Phil is invited to appear in a real estate segment for the local news and gets to meet his weatherman hero, Rainer Shine (Nathan Fillion)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 10:30:00" d="2021-07-17 11:30:00"><n u="Supergirl">Supergirl VI (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Phantom Menaces
Supergirl makes a new ally, while Lena and Lex battle for control of Luthor Corp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 11:30:00" d="2021-07-17 12:30:00"><n u="The Flash">The Flash VII (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Mother
As Eva becomes more powerful, Barry and team must find a way to stop her, with help from an unexpected source</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 12:30:00" d="2021-07-17 14:10:00"><n u="Live British F1: Practice">Live British F1: Practice 2</n>    <k>The second practice from the British Grand Prix at Silverstone. This will be the weekend's final practice session as F1 trial a new format</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 14:10:00" d="2021-07-17 14:35:00"><n>The Simpsons</n>    <k>Brother From The Same Planet: Tired of being let down by Homer, Bart applies to 'Bigger Brothers', telling them he is the son of a hardened drinker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 14:35:00" d="2021-07-17 15:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n>    <k>I Love Lisa: When Ralph, the school nerd, fails to receive a Valentine's Card, Lisa gives him one out of pity - and he falls instantly in love with her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 15:00:00" d="2021-07-17 15:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n>    <k>Duffless: How will Homer cope with a 30 day abstinence from his favourite drink? Meanwhile, Lisa pits her brother against a hamster in her latest scientific experiment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 15:30:00" d="2021-07-17 16:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n>    <k>Last Exit To Springfield: Homer stands up for what he believes in. Featuring the guest voice of Dr Joyce Brothers as herself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 16:00:00" d="2021-07-17 16:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n>    <k>So It's Come To This: Family and friends reminisce about Homer's life after Bart's April Fool's Day prank puts him in hospital</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 16:30:00" d="2021-07-17 17:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n>    <k>The Front: Lisa and Bart compose a script full of gratuitous violence and submit it to the producers of 'Itchy &amp; Scratchy'. Featuring the guest voice of Brooke Shields</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 17:00:00" d="2021-07-17 21:00:00"><n>Live British &amp; Irish Lions Series</n>    <k>The British &amp; Irish Lions continue their tour of South Africa as they take on the Stormers in Cape Town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 21:00:00" d="2021-07-17 22:00:00"><n u="Rob &amp; Romesh Vs Team GB - Part">Rob &amp; Romesh Vs Team GB - Part 1 III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. It's Olympic year, so Rob and Romesh try their hand at weightlifting, hockey and slalom canoe to see if they too could be part of Team GB</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 22:00:00" d="2021-07-18 00:05:00" c="1"><n>Edge Of Tomorrow</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% When aliens invade Earth, army officer Tom Cruise gets stuck in a time-loop that sees him doing battle with them again and again. Sci-fi action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-18 00:05:00" d="2021-07-18 03:05:00"><n>British F1: Sprint Qualifying Hlts</n>    <k>The new Formula 1 Sprint Qualifying session makes its debut at Silverstone for the 2021 British Grand Prix, as the grid is decided for Sunday's race</k>  </p>
</a>
