<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="30" t="2021-07-09 07:14:27"><p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 05:00:00" d="2021-07-16 06:00:00"><n u="Stop Search Seize">Stop Search Seize I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Ireland's Customs teams as they, with the help of the Irish police, try to stop organised smugglers from bringing drugs, cars and even exotic animals into the country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 06:00:00" d="2021-07-16 07:00:00"><n u="S.W.A.T.">S.W.A.T. III (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Wild Ones
The SWAT team pursues a couple reminiscent of Bonnie and Clyde, as the duo hunt for a set of rare chest pieces worth millions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 07:00:00" d="2021-07-16 07:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% The Series Has Landed
Fry eagerly anticipates his first visit to the moon. only to realise that it is home to a cheesy amusement park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 07:30:00" d="2021-07-16 08:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% I, Roommate
Fry and Bender become a futuristic odd couple when they attempt to share an apartment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 08:00:00" d="2021-07-16 08:30:00"><n u="Baby Animals">Baby Animals II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Surrogate Families
Losing their mums can be deadly for young mammals. But these orphaned creatures got lucky when conservationists stepped in</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 08:30:00" d="2021-07-16 09:00:00"><n u="Baby Animals">Baby Animals II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Herd Mentality
Sticking together means surviving for these animals who find safety from predators in numbers. But what's it like to grow up in a big group?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 09:00:00" d="2021-07-16 09:30:00"><n u="Monkey Business">Monkey Business IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Dr Alison Cronin's team at the Monkey World Ape Rescue Centre in Dorset as they rehabilitate abused primates and support overseas projects to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 09:30:00" d="2021-07-16 10:00:00"><n u="Monkey Business">Monkey Business IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Dr Alison Cronin's team at the Monkey World Ape Rescue Centre in Dorset as they rehabilitate abused primates and support overseas projects to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 10:00:00" d="2021-07-16 10:30:00"><n u="Motorway Patrol">Motorway Patrol V (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series from New Zealand following the madness and mayhem faced by intrepid officers as they pull over motorists for a variety of suspected offences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 10:30:00" d="2021-07-16 11:00:00"><n u="Motorway Patrol">Motorway Patrol V (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series from New Zealand following the madness and mayhem faced by intrepid officers as they pull over motorists for a variety of suspected offences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 11:00:00" d="2021-07-16 12:00:00"><n u="Stop Search Seize">Stop Search Seize I (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Ireland's Customs teams as they, with the help of the Irish police, try to stop organised smugglers from bringing drugs, cars and even exotic animals into the country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 12:00:00" d="2021-07-16 13:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles XI (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Murder Of Crows
NCIS helps a tech operator look for her missing ex-partner, whom they fear is working with gun runners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 13:00:00" d="2021-07-16 14:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles XI (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Code Of Conduct
Sam, Callen and Rountree travel to Afghanistan for a sensitive case after two SEALs claim their chief murdered an unarmed prisoner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 14:00:00" d="2021-07-16 15:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 VI (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ka Haunaele (Rampage)
Five-0 investigate the theft of an advanced piece of military technology. Jerry helps his sister with another important mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 15:00:00" d="2021-07-16 16:45:00"><n u="Live British F1: Practice">Live British F1: Practice 1</n>    <k>The Formula 1 season arrives at Silverstone for the opening practice session from the 2021 British Grand Prix</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 16:45:00" d="2021-07-16 17:00:00"><n>Futurama-Welcome To The World of Tomorrow</n>    <k>Take a sneak peek behind the scenes at the making of Matt Groening's hit animation series Futurama. Narrated by Tania Bryer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 17:00:00" d="2021-07-16 17:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VIII (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Snow Ball
A simple error threatens everything when Manny and Luke put on a fancy winter ball at the school. Mitchell gets a wake-up call when he offers to help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 17:30:00" d="2021-07-16 18:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family VIII (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Ringmaster Keifth
Mitch gets a shock when Cam calls a concierge to save his ruined New Year's Day feast. Phil's dad Frank causes waves when he brings a date</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 18:00:00" d="2021-07-16 18:25:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXXI (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Todd, Todd, Why Hast Thou Forsaken Me?
A faithless Flanders gets sent to live with Homer. Can a spell with the Simpsons scare him back into God's arms?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 18:25:00" d="2021-07-16 20:30:00"><n>Live British F1: Qualifying</n>    <k>Qualifying at the 2021 British Grand Prix at Silverstone, as drivers compete to get on pole position ahead of Sunday's race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 20:30:00" d="2021-07-16 21:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XIII (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Homer The Moe
Moe turns the bar into a hangout for Springfield's 'beautiful people', forcing Homer to start a bar of his own inside his garage. REM guest voice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 21:00:00" d="2021-07-16 21:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XIII (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% A Hunka Hunka Burns In Love
Burns tries to prove that he's still 'got it' when he falls in love with a short order cook. Julia-Louise Dreyfus guest stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 21:30:00" d="2021-07-16 22:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XIII (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Blunder Years
When Homer is hypnotised, his memory of a traumatic event in his past unearths the mystery of the death of Smithers' father. Paul Newman guest voices</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 22:00:00" d="2021-07-16 23:00:00"><n u="New: Manifest">New: Manifest III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Tailfin
Ben and Vance go on an international mission to finally solve the mystery of Flight 828. Newlyweds Michaela and Zeke have an intense calling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-16 23:00:00" d="2021-07-17 00:45:00"><n>British F1 GP: Qualifying Hlts</n>    <k>As part of a new format, the qualifying session from the British Grand Prix decides the order for the new Sprint Qualifying on Saturday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 00:45:00" d="2021-07-17 01:45:00"><n u="Rob &amp; Romesh Vs Team GB - Part">Rob &amp; Romesh Vs Team GB - Part 1 III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. It's Olympic year, so Rob and Romesh try their hand at weightlifting, hockey and slalom canoe to see if they too could be part of Team GB</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 01:45:00" d="2021-07-17 02:45:00"><n u="A League Of Their Own">A League Of Their Own XIV (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Funnyman David Walliams comes on as host as Freddie, Jamie and Romesh team up with comedian Jimmy Carr, gymnast Max Whitlock and presenter Helen Skelton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 02:45:00" d="2021-07-17 03:40:00"><n>The Force: Manchester S02</n>    <k>Documentary series following the UK's second largest police force, Greater Manchester Police, as they tackle crime and battle to keep the streets safe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 03:40:00" d="2021-07-17 04:30:00"><n u="Cop Squad">Cop Squad I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sharing shifts with Cambridgeshire's police force, this documentary reveals what life on the beat is really like</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2021-07-17 04:30:00" d="2021-07-17 05:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Thames Valley Police provide a fascinating insight into car crime and its prevention. Plus, shocking video footage captures dangerous drivers in action</k>  </p>
</a>
