<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2020-05-28 04:40:58"><p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 05:30:00" d="2020-06-04 06:30:00"><n u="Sun, Sea And A&amp;E">Sun, Sea And A&amp;E II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bomb
Documentary series following the misfortunes of British holidaymakers who find themselves recuperating in hospital rather than soaking up the sun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 06:30:00" d="2020-06-04 07:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama V (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Spanish Fry
When Fry succeeds in retrieving his nose, which was taken by aliens, a more precious appendage of his is placed in peril</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 07:00:00" d="2020-06-04 07:30:00"><n u="Monkey Business">Monkey Business V (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Dr Alison Cronin's team at the Monkey World Ape Rescue Centre in Dorset as they rehabilitate abused primates and support overseas projects to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 07:30:00" d="2020-06-04 08:00:00"><n u="Monkey Business">Monkey Business V (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Dr Alison Cronin's team at the Monkey World Ape Rescue Centre in Dorset as they rehabilitate abused primates and support overseas projects to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 08:00:00" d="2020-06-04 08:30:00"><n u="Animal House">Animal House II (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series shining a spotlight on the staff at SPCA Auckland, who dedicate their days to the care and protection of the region's animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 08:30:00" d="2020-06-04 09:00:00"><n u="Animal House">Animal House II (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series shining a spotlight on the staff at SPCA Auckland, who dedicate their days to the care and protection of the region's animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 09:00:00" d="2020-06-04 10:00:00"><n u="The Dog Whisperer">The Dog Whisperer VI (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>India, Jagger and Axl
Cesar meets an aggressive Manchester Terrier; a Wheaton Terrier with poor social skills and a dog who is afraid of the ocean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 10:00:00" d="2020-06-04 10:30:00"><n u="Motorbike Cops">Motorbike Cops I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Join Australia's traffic cops on their daily jobs and get an inside look into what goes into policing the country's roads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 10:30:00" d="2020-06-04 11:00:00"><n u="Highway Cops">Highway Cops I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary following the men and women who help keep motorists safe on some of the most perilous highways and byways of New Zealand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 11:00:00" d="2020-06-04 12:00:00"><n u="Sun, Sea And A&amp;E">Sun, Sea And A&amp;E II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Swine Flu
Documentary series following the misfortunes of British holidaymakers who find themselves recuperating in hospital rather than soaking up the sun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 12:00:00" d="2020-06-04 13:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles II (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Deliverance
Time is of the essence in the concluding chapter of this thrilling two-parter. Hetty and the NCIS team continue their search for the elusive black book</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 13:00:00" d="2020-06-04 14:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles II (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Disorder
When two men are killed in a shootout, the team's key witness is a former Navy Intelligence Officer with post traumatic stress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 14:00:00" d="2020-06-04 15:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 VIII (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ka Lala Kaukonakona Haki 'Ole I Ka Pa A Ka Makani Kona: Steve joins Junior and his SEAL team on a personal mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 15:00:00" d="2020-06-04 16:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 VIII (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Waiho wale kahiko (Ancients Exposed)
A nuclear attack sub spells trouble for Five-0. And things get worse when they uncover a Russian spy ring. Season finale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 16:00:00" d="2020-06-04 17:00:00"><n u="Magnum P.I.">Magnum P.I. I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Die He Said
The case brings back bad SEAL team memories for Magnum as he desperately tries to find a dying man's estranged brother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 17:00:00" d="2020-06-04 17:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family V (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% ISpy
Claire persuades Phil to help her spy on Luke, and Gloria's suspicions are aroused by Jay's sleep talking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 17:30:00" d="2020-06-04 18:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family V (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% The Feud
Phil, Jay and Luke wage war against three generations of Thorpes, while Gloria starts to worry about Manny's lack of self-confidence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 18:00:00" d="2020-06-04 18:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIV (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% New &amp; Exclusive. Hardly Kirk-ing
Bart and Milhouse sample the perks of adulthood, while Marge tries to protect Maggie from the dangers of children's television</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 18:30:00" d="2020-06-04 19:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama V (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Bend Her
It's the 3004 Olympics and there's all kinds of cheating going on. Bender will do whatever it takes to win gold, even if it means having a sex change</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 19:00:00" d="2020-06-04 19:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama V (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Obsoletely Fabulous
Bender suffers from robot envy when a new machine makes him look inadequate. He can be upgraded but that means a personality transplant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 19:30:00" d="2020-06-04 20:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIV (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Dangers On A Train
Marge and Homer overcome a few hiccups to celebrate their 10th wedding anniversary. Family Guy creator Seth MacFarlane guest stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 20:00:00" d="2020-06-04 20:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons X (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Lard of the Dance
Homer thinks he can make a fortune by recycling grease and Lisa helps to organise a school dance. Featuring the guest voice of Lisa Kudrow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 20:30:00" d="2020-06-04 21:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons X (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Wizard of Evergreen Terrace
Homer experiences a mid-life crisis and is inspired to become an inventor. Featuring the voice of William Daniels as Kit the Car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 21:00:00" d="2020-06-04 21:05:00"><n>Clap For Our Carers</n>    <k>Coverage from around the UK as we Clap For Our Carers in support of NHS workers fighting coronavirus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 21:05:00" d="2020-06-04 22:00:00"><n u="New: DC's Legends Of Tomorrow">New: DC's Legends Of Tomorrow V (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Ship Broken
Everyone is desperate to use the Loom of Fate, but the team face a tough decision as they choose who to bring back first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 22:00:00" d="2020-06-04 23:00:00"><n u="New: The Blacklist">New: The Blacklist VII (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Hannah Hayes
The Task Force investigates the unexplained disappearance and sudden re-emergence of a governor. Red and Dembe go into surveillance mode</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-06-04 23:00:00" d="2020-06-05 02:00:00"><n u="New: Brassic">New: Brassic 2 II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Ordered by McCann to sell all the weed they have grown, the lads decide to throw a music festival in Jim's field. Adult themes</k>  </p>
</a>
