<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="30" t="2020-04-09 04:35:56"><p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 05:00:00" d="2020-04-16 05:30:00"><n u="Ninja Warrior">Ninja Warrior V (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The world's top athletes and wrestlers compete alongside amateurs in one of the most demanding physical challenges ever devised</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 05:30:00" d="2020-04-16 06:00:00"><n u="Ninja Warrior">Ninja Warrior VII (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The world's top athletes and wrestlers compete alongside amateurs in one of the most demanding physical challenges ever devised</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 06:00:00" d="2020-04-16 06:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IX (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Fun on a Bun
Wires are crossed during a team outing to Oktoberfest when Fry is involved in a horrific sausage-making accident</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 06:30:00" d="2020-04-16 07:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IX (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Near-Death Wish
Professor Farnsworth is far from overjoyed to be reunited with his parents, but can't help feeling jealous when they bond with Fry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 07:00:00" d="2020-04-16 07:30:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life XI (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Jeremy comes to the rescue of three squirrel monkeys while Sonny's capuchin group test out their revamped enclosure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 07:30:00" d="2020-04-16 08:00:00"><n u="Monkey Life">Monkey Life XI (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Health checks on the new three rescued squirrel monkeys cause concern. Baby orangutan Mimi takes her next step to becoming a full member of the nursery group</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 08:00:00" d="2020-04-16 08:30:00"><n u="Wild Vets">Wild Vets III (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Series three of the documentary charting the challenging work of New Zealand's vets as they treat an array of colourful critters in zoos and wildlife parks down under</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 08:30:00" d="2020-04-16 09:00:00"><n u="Wild Vets">Wild Vets III (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Series three of the documentary charting the challenging work of New Zealand's vets as they treat an array of colourful critters in zoos and wildlife parks down under</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 09:00:00" d="2020-04-16 09:30:00"><n u="Moominvalley">Moominvalley I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ghost Story
Moomintroll uses the services of a little ghost to convince Snork Maiden that he is brave. But when his trick backfires, Moomintroll</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 09:30:00" d="2020-04-16 10:00:00"><n u="Moominvalley">Moominvalley I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Invisible Child
The Moomin family's attempts to help a shy girl only make things worse. Can Moomintroll learn to listen long enough to understand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 10:00:00" d="2020-04-16 10:15:00"><n u="SO Beano!">SO Beano! I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Circus
The gang join the circus, but Emma and Joe need to practice. They promise to improve their performance, but what sort of trick will they reveal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 10:15:00" d="2020-04-16 10:35:00"><n u="Where's Wally">Where's Wally I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Little Trouble in Big China
It's the Lunar New Year and a stone dragon has been brought to life. Wally and Wenda must find a way to tame the dragon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 10:35:00" d="2020-04-16 10:50:00"><n u="Play Your Pets Right">Play Your Pets Right I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cat vs Chihuahua, Happy Harry
Who's best at licking meat paste off a window - cat or chihuahua? Plus, Happy Harry the dog impresses us with his spectacular cup-stacking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 10:50:00" d="2020-04-16 11:00:00"><n u="Bad Nature">Bad Nature I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Burrowing Owls &amp; Aphid Farmers
Baz the meerkat finds a strange owl who lives underground, and Monty the lion meets an ant who squeezes liquid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 11:00:00" d="2020-04-16 12:00:00"><n u="The Dog Whisperer">The Dog Whisperer V (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Stanley, Shoven and Leo
Cesar gets tough with a vicious Chihuahua/Pomeranian mix, who may be small but has bitten two girls on the face, requiring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 12:00:00" d="2020-04-16 13:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VIII (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Under Siege
The mole kidnaps one of the NCIS agents. Plus, the team are left completely in the dark when Hetty goes rogue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 13:00:00" d="2020-04-16 14:00:00"><n u="NCIS: Los Angeles">NCIS: Los Angeles VIII (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% Payback
Tensions in the team run high as one agent undergoes torture from the mole. Meanwhile, another uncovers a shocking betrayal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 14:00:00" d="2020-04-16 15:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 V (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ka Makuakane (Family Man)
The team investigate the kidnapping of a Navy SEAL's daughter. Plus, Danno receives shocking news about his brother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 15:00:00" d="2020-04-16 16:00:00"><n u="Hawaii Five-0">Hawaii Five-0 V (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ho'olina (Legacy)
Emotions run high when, after crossing paths with a young woman, McGarrett attempts to unravel a mystery from his late father's past</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 16:00:00" d="2020-04-16 17:00:00"><n u="S.W.A.T.">S.W.A.T. I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ghost
Hondo and the team race the clock when Luca spots a serial killer everyone thought was dead. Jessica's forced to act when she gets a threatening letter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 17:00:00" d="2020-04-16 17:30:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family II (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Someone To Watch Over Lily
Mitch and Cam have a big decision to make, one that involves a spot of sleuthing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 17:30:00" d="2020-04-16 18:00:00"><n u="Modern Family">Modern Family II (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Mother's Day
Claire and Gloria's plan to spend time with their kids in the outdoors backfires and Phil witnesses an unexpected moment of weakness from Jay</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 18:00:00" d="2020-04-16 18:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIII (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Falcon and the D'ohman
Homer gets into a spot of bother with a terrorist, before the future of 'it' couple 'Nedna' is revealed. Guest starring Kiefer Sutherland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 18:30:00" d="2020-04-16 19:00:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IX (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% Viva Mars Vegas
The Planet Express crew escape to Mars Vegas for the weekend, only to run afoul of the Robot Mafia, who are looking to recover a debt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 19:00:00" d="2020-04-16 19:30:00"><n u="Futurama">Futurama IX (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>84% 31st Century Fox
Bender's excitement for an upcoming fox hunt is nipped in the bud when he finds out the prey is robotic. Guest starring Patrick Stewart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 19:30:00" d="2020-04-16 20:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIII (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Politically Inept, With Homer Simpson
After an impassioned video goes viral, Homer shakes up the world of politics. Rocker Ted Nugent guest stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 20:00:00" d="2020-04-16 20:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIII (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The D'oh-Cial Network
Lisa comes up with an online phenomenon, and Patty and Selma enter the 2012 Olympic Games. The Social Network's Armie Hammer guests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 20:30:00" d="2020-04-16 21:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIII (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Moes Goes from Rags to Riches
Moe's best bud and beloved bar rag recounts his thousand-year journey to Springfield. Oscar winner Jeremy Irons guest stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 21:00:00" d="2020-04-16 21:05:00"><n>Clap For Our Carers</n>    <k>Dermot Murnaghan with coverage from around the UK of the second Clap For Our Carers event in support of NHS workers fighting coronavirus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1059" o="2020-04-16 21:05:00" d="2020-04-17 00:05:00"><n u="New: DC's Legends Of Tomorrow">New: DC's Legends Of Tomorrow V (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Miss Me, Kiss Me, Love Me
A blip lands the Legends in 1947 Los Angeles, putting them on the trail of infamous gangster Benjamin 'Bugsy' Siegel</k>  </p>
</a>
