<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2021-07-08 05:04:43"><p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-13 05:10:00" d="2021-07-13 06:05:00"><n u="Richard E Grant's Hotel Secrets">Richard E Grant's Hotel Secrets II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Berlin
Richard E Grant explores classic hotels, pleasure palaces and hipster havens in the German capital</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-13 06:05:00" d="2021-07-13 07:00:00"><n u="Richard E Grant's Hotel Secrets">Richard E Grant's Hotel Secrets II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New Orleans
The actor visits the finest hotels in the Big Easy, including the Monteleone, popular with writers such as F Scott Fitzgerald</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-13 07:00:00" d="2021-07-13 08:00:00"><n u="The British">The British (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% War and Peace
The factual series closes with the turbulent and triumphant 20th century. CGI and drama re-create World War I and Queen Elizabeth II's coronation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-13 08:00:00" d="2021-07-13 09:00:00"><n u="Elementary">Elementary II (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>79% No Lack of Void
The anthrax poisoning of a pickpocket sets Holmes and Watson on an urgent race to prevent a potentially devastating epidemic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-13 09:00:00" d="2021-07-13 10:00:00"><n u="Elementary">Elementary II (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>79% The Man with the Twisted Lip
Sherlock's brother Mycroft (guest star Rhys Ifans) causes tension between Holmes and Watson amid a serious kidnapping case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-13 10:00:00" d="2021-07-13 11:05:00"><n u="Six Feet Under">Six Feet Under II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Driving Mr Mossback
Nate and Claire collect a body from Seattle, where they stay with Nate's ex-lover Lisa. Meanwhile, Brenda is dragged into her parents' marital troubles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-13 11:05:00" d="2021-07-13 12:10:00"><n u="Six Feet Under">Six Feet Under II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% The Invisible Woman
Ruth is troubled by the death of a woman with no friends or family. Brenda starts writing a novel, and work worries leave Keith</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-13 12:10:00" d="2021-07-13 13:20:00"><n u="Boardwalk Empire">Boardwalk Empire I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% Broadway Limited
As Nucky's new bootlegging deal with Chalky White leads to bloodshed, Agent Van Alden closes in on Jimmy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-13 13:20:00" d="2021-07-13 14:30:00"><n u="Boardwalk Empire">Boardwalk Empire I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% Anastasia
As Jimmy and Al Capone stir up trouble in Chicago, Nucky demands that Elias solves the murder of Chalky White's employee</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-13 14:30:00" d="2021-07-13 15:30:00"><n u="Elementary">Elementary II (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>79% Paint It Black
Lucy Liu directs this especially tense episode, in which brothers Sherlock and Mycroft join forces on a case with life-or-death consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-13 15:30:00" d="2021-07-13 16:30:00"><n u="Elementary">Elementary II (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>79% Art In the Blood. A seemingly routine murder case gets an international twist when Holmes crosses paths with MI6. Also, Joan rethinks her future with Mycroft</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-13 16:30:00" d="2021-07-13 17:35:00"><n u="Dexter">Dexter IV (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Blinded By The Light
While Dexter juggles everyday marriage and parenting problems, the Trinity Killer strikes again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-13 17:35:00" d="2021-07-13 18:40:00"><n u="Dexter">Dexter IV (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Dex Takes A Holiday
With his family away, Dexter is free to unleash his inner killer, and he's found his next victim</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-13 18:40:00" d="2021-07-13 19:45:00"><n u="The Sopranos">The Sopranos V (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% The Test Dream
Tony is troubled by a dream about his old football coach, until he receives some big news from Chris</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-13 19:45:00" d="2021-07-13 20:50:00"><n u="The Sopranos">The Sopranos V (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% Long Term Parking
With Tony B still missing, tensions between New York and New Jersey are at an all-time high</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-13 20:50:00" d="2021-07-13 22:00:00"><n u="Game Of Thrones">Game Of Thrones VI (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Broken Man
As the High Sparrow eyes a new target, Jaime meets a hero, Arya makes a plan and the North is reminded</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-13 22:00:00" d="2021-07-13 23:05:00"><n u="New: City On A Hill">New: City On A Hill II (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Pax Bostonia
As Boston mourns another loss, Decourcy pursues justice in and out of the courtroom. Season finale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-13 23:05:00" d="2021-07-14 00:05:00"><n u="Totti: One Captain">Totti: One Captain I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. For 'the Captain', the much-feared forties have arrived, as has the opportunity, at the last Derby, to announce his retirement. Italian with subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 00:05:00" d="2021-07-14 01:10:00"><n u="Six Feet Under">Six Feet Under V (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Hold My Hand
Unhappy with Claire's carefree behaviour, Ruth freezes her trust fund, inadvertently pushing her further toward Billy's destabilising influence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 01:10:00" d="2021-07-14 02:15:00"><n u="Six Feet Under">Six Feet Under V (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Time Flies
It's Nate's 40th birthday and Brenda has a big surprise in store. Meanwhile, Claire finally gets fed up of Billy's erratic behaviour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 02:15:00" d="2021-07-14 03:20:00"><n u="True Blood">True Blood III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bad Blood
Sookie gets little help from Eric as she searches for a missing Bill. Meanwhile, Andy persuades Jason to keep quiet about Eggs' death</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 03:20:00" d="2021-07-14 03:55:00"><n u="Californication">Californication V (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>82% Perverts &amp; ______
Hank stays with Karen and Becca while looking for a new agent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 03:55:00" d="2021-07-14 04:30:00"><n u="Californication">Californication V (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>82% The Party
Hank gets ready to leave LA but one last drink leads to a series of unexpected events</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 04:30:00" d="2021-07-14 05:05:00"><n u="Californication">Californication V (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>82% Hell Ain't a Bad Place to Be
Hank has new hope in reuniting with Karen, but a visit from his ex-girlfriend Carrie puts this in jeopardy</k>  </p>
</a>
