<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2020-05-13 04:36:09"><p id_tv="1060" o="2020-05-20 05:15:00" d="2020-05-20 06:05:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing VII (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Institutional Memory
CJ and Will face uncertain futures as the Bartlet team prepare to leave the White House and make way for the Santos administration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-05-20 06:05:00" d="2020-05-20 07:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing VII (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Tomorrow
As the multi-award-winning political drama concludes, Santos prepares to be sworn into office as Bartlet and the team look back on their time in the White House</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-05-20 07:00:00" d="2020-05-20 08:00:00"><n u="Urban Secrets">Urban Secrets (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In Newcastle, Alan discovers the hidden gems of this great north eastern city, meeting Toon Army legend Peter Beardsley and comedian Sarah Millican along the way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-05-20 08:00:00" d="2020-05-20 09:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace VI (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Dollar and a Dream
When a lottery winner vanishes after a camping trip, the investigation leads the team to suspect foul play</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-05-20 09:00:00" d="2020-05-20 10:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace VI (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Driven
While the team investigates the disappearance of a truck driver who saved a boy's life, an FBI psychiatrist is brought in for a mandatory evaluation of Jack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-05-20 10:00:00" d="2020-05-20 11:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace VI (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Satellites
In the season six finale, five people with an odd connection are abducted from a coffee shop at the same time. Meanwhile, Sam prepares to give birth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-05-20 11:00:00" d="2020-05-20 12:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing VII (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Institutional Memory
CJ and Will face uncertain futures as the Bartlet team prepare to leave the White House and make way for the Santos administration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-05-20 12:00:00" d="2020-05-20 13:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing VII (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Tomorrow
As the multi-award-winning political drama concludes, Santos prepares to be sworn into office as Bartlet and the team look back on their time in the White House</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-05-20 13:00:00" d="2020-05-20 14:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods V (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Occupational Hazards
Erin worries she's in danger when her apartment is broken into and her colleague is attacked. Elsewhere, Jamie and Eddie discover a bomb</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-05-20 14:00:00" d="2020-05-20 15:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation IX (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>77% Mascara
Ray takes a personal interest when one of his former students turns up dead. The trail leads him to the world of 'Luchadores', Mexican semi-pro wrestling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-05-20 15:00:00" d="2020-05-20 16:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing VII (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Ticket
Bartlet's White House reign is almost over and Santos's campaign is looking in good shape, although he's worried about his running mate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-05-20 16:00:00" d="2020-05-20 17:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing VII (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Mommy Problem
Santos hires a tough media consultant to help the campaign, which is impacted by Bartlet's decisions about the NASA security leak</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-05-20 17:00:00" d="2020-05-20 18:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace VII (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Closure
Season seven begins as the team searches for a man whose daughter vanished years earlier. Jack, meanwhile, must adjust to a new boss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-05-20 18:00:00" d="2020-05-20 19:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace VII (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>22 x 42
The team investigates when a female executive at a high-end clothing company is abducted from a taxi after attending a party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-05-20 19:00:00" d="2020-05-20 20:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace VII (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Last Call
Jack and the team is called in when a white-collar criminal vanishes while on his way to testify in a case against a former business partner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-05-20 20:00:00" d="2020-05-20 21:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation IX (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>77% The Descent Of Man
When a sky diver is paralysed after his chute failed to properly deploy, several people are suspected, but the diver's past makes it more complicated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-05-20 21:00:00" d="2020-05-20 22:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods V (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Bad Company
While Eddie goes on her first undercover assignment, Frank helps an old friend meet the person who killed her family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-05-20 22:00:00" d="2020-05-21 01:00:00"><n>Manhunter</n>    <k>Classic Michael Mann thriller with Tom Noonan. FBI profiler Will Graham returns to service to pursue a deranged serial killer named 'the Tooth Fairy' by the media</k>  </p>
</a>
