<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2019-08-13 02:25:34"><p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 05:15:00" d="2019-08-19 06:10:00"><n u="Urban Secrets">Urban Secrets (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Experience actor Alan Cumming's tour of the UK, as he uncovers the secrets of Britain's cities. Beginning in London, he travels from St Paul's Cathedral to Soho</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 06:10:00" d="2019-08-19 07:00:00"><n u="Urban Secrets">Urban Secrets (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Alan Cumming's tour of the UK continues as he uncovers more secrets in urban areas. This week, he's in Brighton where he travels from the toy museum to the Royal Pavilion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 07:00:00" d="2019-08-19 08:00:00"><n u="Storm City">Storm City (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Braving the elements, Ben Fogle demonstrates how destructive high-speed winds can be through a series of spectacular reconstructions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 08:00:00" d="2019-08-19 09:00:00"><n u="The Guest Wing">The Guest Wing (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lord and Lady Fitzalan Howard launch a boot camp fitness weekend at Carlton Towers, Selby, while Maunsel House in Somerset plays host to a murder mystery event</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 09:00:00" d="2019-08-19 10:00:00"><n u="Fish Town">Fish Town (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series offering an eye-opening insight into the working lives of the residents of Brixham, Devon, one of UK's oldest and busiest fishing ports</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 10:00:00" d="2019-08-19 11:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Steve McQueen">Discovering: Steve McQueen IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Leading film critics discuss the life and career of Steve McQueen, who starred in films such as The Magnificent Seven, The Great Escape, Bullit and The Getaway</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 11:00:00" d="2019-08-19 12:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Process Stories
Election results from Orange County leave Sam in a delicate position, while Andy Wyatt's success gives Toby cause for concern</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 12:00:00" d="2019-08-19 13:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Swiss Diplomacy
When a 15-year-old Iranian boy needs medical treatment he can only get in the US, the politics of the situation prove complicated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 13:00:00" d="2019-08-19 14:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Doppelganger II
A previous case is revisited when a woman disappears from a shelter whose manager is the identical twin of a man arrested five months earlier for murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 14:00:00" d="2019-08-19 15:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Trials
When a juror in a murder trial vanishes, suspicion falls on the defendant, a gang member who could get a mistrial if the man is not found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 15:00:00" d="2019-08-19 16:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods V (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Occupational Hazards
Erin worries she's in danger when her apartment is broken into and her colleague is attacked. Elsewhere, Jamie and Eddie discover a bomb</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 16:00:00" d="2019-08-19 17:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Arctic Radar
As Sam leaves, he recommends Will Bailey to be Toby's new speechwriter. Elsewhere, Donna asks Josh for some help on the romance front</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 17:00:00" d="2019-08-19 18:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Holy Night
It's two days before Christmas and the White House is inundated with visitors, including Toby's father and Zoey Bartlet and her new boyfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 18:00:00" d="2019-08-19 19:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Malone v Malone
As the team celebrates the holidays with an office party, Jack endures a traumatic deposition in his custody battle for his daughters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 19:00:00" d="2019-08-19 20:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>4.0
When an academically gifted student vanishes, the team uncovers a secret that may have a connection with her disappearance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 20:00:00" d="2019-08-19 21:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation IX (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>78% A Space Oddity
When the producer of a science fiction show is murdered at a Las Vegas convention, Hodges and Wendy find a connection with each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 21:00:00" d="2019-08-19 22:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods V (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Bad Company
While Eddie goes on her first undercover assignment, Frank helps an old friend meet the person who killed her family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 22:00:00" d="2019-08-19 23:10:00"><n u="New: Succession">New: Succession II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Vaulter
Roman and Kendall compete to fix Vaulter. Meanwhile, Greg wonders if ATN is the right fit for him and Shiv brings Tom in on her future</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 23:10:00" d="2019-08-19 23:45:00"><n u="New: Last Week Tonight With John Oliver">New: Last Week Tonight With John Oliver VI (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. British comedian John Oliver takes a tongue-in-cheek look at breaking news and current affairs stories in his Emmy Award-winning series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 23:45:00" d="2019-08-20 00:55:00"><n u="Real Time With Bill Maher">Real Time With Bill Maher XVII (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% New &amp; Exclusive. Comic Bill Maher invites three guests from diverse parts of the political spectrum for a lively discussion of the week's events</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 00:55:00" d="2019-08-20 02:00:00"><n u="Euphoria">Euphoria I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Stuntin' Like My Daddy
Rue struggles to put the past behind her on her first day back at school. Kat finds a video of herself online</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 02:00:00" d="2019-08-20 03:15:00"><n u="Six Feet Under">Six Feet Under V (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Everyone's Waiting
In the last ever episode of the award-winning drama, Brenda gives birth to a girl she names Willa. Meanwhile, Ruth is forced to confront her grief</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 03:15:00" d="2019-08-20 03:50:00"><n u="Ballers">Ballers IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% Rough Ride
Hit comedy starring Dwayne Johnson. Spencer weighs the pros and cons of acquiring an extreme sports outlet. Guest starring Russell Brand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 03:50:00" d="2019-08-20 04:25:00"><n u="Girls">Girls III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>She Said Ok
Marnie goes into control-freak mode while organising Hannah's 25th birthday. Meanwhile, Adam's eccentric sister unexpectedly comes to visit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 04:25:00" d="2019-08-20 05:00:00"><n u="Girls">Girls III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Dead Inside
As the award-winning comedy continues, Hannah deals with an untimely death, while Marnie's online video causes her further humiliation</k>  </p>
</a>
