<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2020-05-26 04:34:31"><p id_tv="1060" o="2020-06-02 05:10:00" d="2020-06-02 06:05:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing VII (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Election Day, Part 2
As a tense election night drags on, the Santos camp is rocked by tragedy while voters across the country continue to cast their ballots</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-06-02 06:05:00" d="2020-06-02 07:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing VII (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Requiem
In a poignant instalment, former West Wing staff and advisors reunite to say farewell to one of their own and reminisce about days gone by</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-06-02 07:00:00" d="2020-06-02 08:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace VI (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Res Ipsa
When a distraught mother vanishes, the team thinks she may be searching for her son, who she believes is being held prisoner in Guatemala</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-06-02 08:00:00" d="2020-06-02 09:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace VI (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Baggage
The team investigates when a woman disappears soon after her boyfriend is killed by the police. Her gang-leader brother is their number one suspect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-06-02 09:00:00" d="2020-06-02 10:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace VI (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Run
When a woman vanishes during a shootout at an office, popular opinion is that she disappeared to keep a dark secret from being revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-06-02 10:00:00" d="2020-06-02 11:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing VII (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Election Day, Part 2
As a tense election night drags on, the Santos camp is rocked by tragedy while voters across the country continue to cast their ballots</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-06-02 11:00:00" d="2020-06-02 12:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing VII (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Requiem
In a poignant instalment, former West Wing staff and advisors reunite to say farewell to one of their own and reminisce about days gone by</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-06-02 12:00:00" d="2020-06-02 13:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods VII (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Mob Rules
Danny and Frank look to get justice for a colleague after he is beaten by a mob outside his home. Eddie and Jamie witness a dishonest arrest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-06-02 13:00:00" d="2020-06-02 14:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation X (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>77% Coup De Grace
Las Vegas-based forensic drama. A cop is accidentally shot by a fellow officer but the CSI's investigation reveals that the killing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-06-02 14:00:00" d="2020-06-02 15:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing VII (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Transition
While Sam (Rob Lowe) returns to the White House, a stressed Josh reaches breaking point and the president-elect learns about his new job</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-06-02 15:00:00" d="2020-06-02 16:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing VII (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Last Hurrah
As Santos is distracted with selecting a new vice president, Helen is overwhelmed by the responsibility of becoming the new first lady</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-06-02 16:00:00" d="2020-06-02 17:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation VIII (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>77% Who And What
Special crossover episode between CSI and Without a Trace. The CSIs work with the FBI to investigate the murders of a young boy and a woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-06-02 17:00:00" d="2020-06-02 18:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace VI (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Where and Why
In a crossover episode concluding a story from CSI: Crime Scene Investigation, Jack works with Gil Grissom (William Petersen) to track</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-06-02 18:00:00" d="2020-06-02 19:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace VI (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Absalom
The team investigates when a college student vanishes not long after making racist comments during a class discussion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-06-02 19:00:00" d="2020-06-02 20:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace VI (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Fight/Flight
When an ultimate fighter vanishes after winning a bout, the team learns that the man had many enemies, including one that was recently released from jail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-06-02 20:00:00" d="2020-06-02 21:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation X (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>77% Death And The Maiden
Las Vegas-based forensic drama. Two apparently unrelated cases of murder turn out to be linked to a single revenge plot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-06-02 21:00:00" d="2020-06-02 22:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods VII (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% For The Community
Erin and Anthony try to prevent the deportation of a community activist, and Frank must decide if the NYPD will participate in a gang raid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-06-02 22:00:00" d="2020-06-03 01:00:00"><n>New: Jarhead</n>    <k>Sam Mendes war drama based on US Marine Anthony Swofford's memoirs. A sniper in the Gulf War struggles with the possibility his girlfriend may be cheating back home</k>  </p>
</a>
