<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2019-07-11 00:20:57"><p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-15 05:20:00" d="2019-07-15 06:10:00"><n>The British</n>    <k>People Power: Stars including Tim Roth and Tracey Emin explore the rampage and rebellion of medieval Britain during the Black Death and Peasants' Revolt. (Ep 2 of 7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-15 06:10:00" d="2019-07-15 07:00:00"><n u="The British">The British (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% Revolution
The factual series charges forwards to the Tudor and Stuart dynasties. CGI and guest stars give fresh insights on Henry VIII and the English Civil War</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-15 07:00:00" d="2019-07-15 08:00:00"><n u="The Guest Wing">The Guest Wing (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lord and Lady Fitzalan Howard launch a boot camp fitness weekend at Carlton Towers, Selby, while Maunsel House in Somerset plays host to a murder mystery event</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-15 08:00:00" d="2019-07-15 09:00:00"><n u="Richard E Grant's Hotel Secrets">Richard E Grant's Hotel Secrets (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>French Riviera
Richard E Grant takes a sneaky peek inside the finest hotels on the Cote d'Azur, which have welcomed lovestruck film stars and honeymooning royals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-15 09:00:00" d="2019-07-15 10:00:00"><n u="The British">The British (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% Superpower
Stars Lily Cole and Dougray Scott explore the pioneering age of invention and exploration that made Britain the biggest power in the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-15 10:00:00" d="2019-07-15 11:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Judy Garland">Discovering: Judy Garland II (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the tumultuous life and glittering 40-year career of the actress, singer and entertainer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-15 11:00:00" d="2019-07-15 12:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% The Midterms
With things beginning to look up, Sam cautions the team not to rest on their laurels as all eyes turn to the mid-terms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-15 12:00:00" d="2019-07-15 13:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% In This White House
When Sam is shown up on national TV by a young Republican lawyer, Bartlet insists on hiring her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-15 13:00:00" d="2019-07-15 14:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Suspect
When a 17-year-old vanishes from his private school campus, the MPU team discover that the headmaster may be involved</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-15 14:00:00" d="2019-07-15 15:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Silent Partner
Jack and his team investigate the disappearance of the vice president of an investment banking firm who vanished at an airport</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-15 15:00:00" d="2019-07-15 16:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods IV (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% Unfinished Business
While Danny searches for a Marine veteran he believes is displaying symptoms of PTSD, Frank reopens the case of a young girl's murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-15 16:00:00" d="2019-07-15 17:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% And It's Surely to Their Credit
Leo attempts to protect Ainsley, while Sam tries to persuade Josh to sue the hate group behind the shooting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-15 17:00:00" d="2019-07-15 18:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% The Lame Duck Congress
The team try to encourage Bartlet to call a special session of Congress, while Sam and Ainsley teach each other a thing or two</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-15 18:00:00" d="2019-07-15 19:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Snatch Back
The team investigates several suspects when the child of a prominent assistant district attorney vanishes in a public park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-15 19:00:00" d="2019-07-15 20:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Little Big Man
The team searches for a teenager who went missing in a bad neighbourhood after an encounter with a bully. Crime drama starring Anthony LaPaglia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-15 20:00:00" d="2019-07-15 21:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation VIII (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>78% Grissom's Divine Comedy
The team investigate the deaths of several witnesses for a grand jury case against a dangerous gang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-15 21:00:00" d="2019-07-15 22:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods IV (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% Manhattan Queens
Danny and Baez investigate the death of a popular drag queen from a reality TV show. Series star Donnie Wahlberg directs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-15 22:00:00" d="2019-07-15 23:10:00"><n u="New: Big Little Lies">New: Big Little Lies II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. The Bad Mother
Celeste is blindsided by Mary Louise and Bonnie looks for relief from her guilt. Renata finds out Gordon's missteps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-15 23:10:00" d="2019-07-15 23:45:00"><n u="New: Divorce">New: Divorce III (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Miami
Frances and Robert's lives spin them in unexpected directions as Robert admits to wedding nerves and Frances prepares for a weekend getaway with Henry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-15 23:45:00" d="2019-07-16 01:40:00"><n>Meth Storm</n>    <k>A look at meth addiction in rural America, focusing on the users, dealers and families caught in the war between the DEA and the drug cartels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 01:40:00" d="2019-07-16 02:50:00"><n>Deadwood</n>    <k>Boy The Earth Talks To: The series comes to an uncomfortable end with a sham marriage, a slit throat and a hanging. A filthily good finale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 02:50:00" d="2019-07-16 04:00:00"><n u="Six Feet Under">Six Feet Under II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% In Place of Anger
As Nate and David fend off a fresh offer from Kroehner, Ruth's estranged sister (Emmy-winning guest star Patricia Clarkson) pays an unexpected visit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 04:00:00" d="2019-07-16 04:35:00"><n u="Divorce">Divorce III (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Miami
Frances and Robert's lives spin them in unexpected directions as Robert admits to wedding nerves and Frances prepares for a weekend getaway with Henry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 04:35:00" d="2019-07-16 05:10:00"><n u="Black Monday">Black Monday I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% New &amp; Exclusive. Mo takes Blair on his bachelor party, while Dawn discovers that she is a very important guest at Tiff's bachelorette party. Keith has a tough decision</k>  </p>
</a>
