<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2019-08-10 01:42:55"><p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 05:10:00" d="2019-08-16 06:05:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Game On
As Bartlet and Ritchie go head to head in a debate, Sam's mission leads to a career-altering decision</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 06:05:00" d="2019-08-16 07:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Election Night
It's election day, but Charlie has more concerns about the president's physical health than his political well-being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 07:00:00" d="2019-08-16 08:00:00"><n u="Storm City">Storm City (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>It's man versus Mother Nature as Ben Fogle explores the devastating impact of extreme weather, starting with the chaos caused by snow and ice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 08:00:00" d="2019-08-16 09:00:00"><n u="The Guest Wing">The Guest Wing (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Go behind the beautiful facades of some of the country's finest stately homes to discover how 21st-century aristocrats have adapted to life in credit-crunch Britain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 09:00:00" d="2019-08-16 10:00:00"><n>Attenborough At 90 Behind The Lens</n>    <k>As Sir David Attenborough turns 90, this intimate film presents new interviews, eye-opening behind-the-scenes footage and extraordinary clips</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 10:00:00" d="2019-08-16 11:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Sidney Poitier">Discovering: Sidney Poitier IV (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Leading film critics look at the life and career of Sidney Poitier who, in 1964, became the first black Academy Award winner for Best Actor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 11:00:00" d="2019-08-16 12:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Game On
As Bartlet and Ritchie go head to head in a debate, Sam's mission leads to a career-altering decision</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 12:00:00" d="2019-08-16 13:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Election Night
It's election day, but Charlie has more concerns about the president's physical health than his political well-being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 13:00:00" d="2019-08-16 14:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Nickel And Dimed, Part 1
When a single mother leaves her three-year-old son with a babysitter and vanishes, the investigation personally affects Samantha</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 14:00:00" d="2019-08-16 15:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Nickel And Dimed, Part 2
Conclusion of a two-part story. Samantha goes undercover in a bid to find a missing mother who is involved with drug traffickers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 15:00:00" d="2019-08-16 16:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods V (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% In the Box
When Baez is held at gunpoint in an interrogation room, Danny must try to meet the hostage taker's demands before it's too late</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 16:00:00" d="2019-08-16 17:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Process Stories
Election results from Orange County leave Sam in a delicate position, while Andy Wyatt's success gives Toby cause for concern</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 17:00:00" d="2019-08-16 18:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Swiss Diplomacy
When a 15-year-old Iranian boy needs medical treatment he can only get in the US, the politics of the situation prove complicated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 18:00:00" d="2019-08-16 19:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Doppelganger II
A previous case is revisited when a woman disappears from a shelter whose manager is the identical twin of a man arrested five months earlier for murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 19:00:00" d="2019-08-16 20:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Trials
When a juror in a murder trial vanishes, suspicion falls on the defendant, a gang member who could get a mistrial if the man is not found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 20:00:00" d="2019-08-16 21:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation IX (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>78% The Descent Of Man
When a sky diver is paralysed after his chute failed to properly deploy, several people are suspected, but the diver's past makes it more complicated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 21:00:00" d="2019-08-16 22:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods V (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Occupational Hazards
Erin worries she's in danger when her apartment is broken into and her colleague is attacked. Elsewhere, Jamie and Eddie discover a bomb</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 22:00:00" d="2019-08-16 23:10:00"><n u="Succession">Succession II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. The Summer Palace
Kendall tries to make amends with his dad and Logan gets stark advice from his banker. Shiv wonders if her father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 23:10:00" d="2019-08-17 00:20:00"><n u="The Affair">The Affair III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The captivating drama returns for its third series, with Noah adapting to a new life three years after the events of the trial. But someone is watching him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 00:20:00" d="2019-08-17 01:25:00"><n u="The Affair">The Affair III (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The compelling drama jumps back one year to see Noah deliver a stern request to Helen, while in Montauk Alison finds her worst fears have been realised</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 01:25:00" d="2019-08-17 02:30:00"><n u="The Affair">The Affair III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Golden Globe-winning drama continues. Juliette finds Noah an alluring prospect, but a terrifying event shatters all hope of an easy affair</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 02:30:00" d="2019-08-17 03:45:00"><n u="The Affair">The Affair III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cole finds himself put into a difficult situation by Alison's return, while she looks to reconnect with her daughter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 03:45:00" d="2019-08-17 05:00:00"><n u="Six Feet Under">Six Feet Under V (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Static
As David struggles to cope with his grief, Keith sends him away to recover. Meanwhile, Brenda goes into labour after Ruth decides to fight her for custody of Maya</k>  </p>
</a>
