<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2019-08-15 22:50:52"><p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-21 05:05:00" d="2019-08-21 06:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Guns Not Butter
While Danny Concannon comes close to the truth in the Sharif affair, Charlie wants to help a female soldier who needs financial assistance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-21 06:00:00" d="2019-08-21 07:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% The Long Goodbye
When CJ returns home to Dayton, Ohio, to give a talk at her high school reunion, she makes a sad discovery about her father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-21 07:00:00" d="2019-08-21 08:00:00"><n u="Storm City">Storm City (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Earthquakes are a geological hazard as old as the earth itself and, in this final episode, Ben Fogle discovers how they wreak so much havoc</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-21 08:00:00" d="2019-08-21 09:00:00"><n u="The Guest Wing">The Guest Wing (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Carlton Towers hosts a British culinary weekend for eager tourists, while a group of budding wine connoisseurs arrive at Chillingham Castle for a tasting weekend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-21 09:00:00" d="2019-08-21 10:00:00"><n u="Fish Town">Fish Town (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Dreams become a reality when 17-year-old Logan takes to the high seas as an apprentice deck hand. Plus, landlady Pat enjoys a trip down memory lane</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-21 10:00:00" d="2019-08-21 11:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Edward G Robinson">Discovering: Edward G Robinson IV (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the career of Edward G Robinson, who played a range of film roles, from a gangster in Little Caesar to an Israelite in The Ten Commandments (1956)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-21 11:00:00" d="2019-08-21 12:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Guns Not Butter
While Danny Concannon comes close to the truth in the Sharif affair, Charlie wants to help a female soldier who needs financial assistance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-21 12:00:00" d="2019-08-21 13:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% The Long Goodbye
When CJ returns home to Dayton, Ohio, to give a talk at her high school reunion, she makes a sad discovery about her father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-21 13:00:00" d="2019-08-21 14:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Penitence
The team is called in to search for a prisoner who is thought to have escaped two weeks before he was up for parole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-21 14:00:00" d="2019-08-21 15:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Volcano
An autistic boy vanishes during a school trip to a museum, leaving behind his wrist locator, which is found cut and discarded</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-21 15:00:00" d="2019-08-21 16:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods V (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Through the Looking Glass
Frank clashes with a journalist who refuses to reveal a source who has admitted to murder. Plus, Danny works with troubled teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-21 16:00:00" d="2019-08-21 17:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (14) (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Inauguration
Escalating genocide in a remote African country gets Bartlet thinking ahead of his second presidential inauguration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-21 17:00:00" d="2019-08-21 18:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (15) (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Inauguration
Over There
Will Bailey's work on the inaugural address makes quite an impression, while Danny's reporting makes a splash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-21 18:00:00" d="2019-08-21 19:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Party Girl
The Missing Persons Unit is called into action when a young and beautiful publishing heiress vanishes while on her way to a party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-21 19:00:00" d="2019-08-21 20:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Manhunt
When Martin witnesses the abduction of a boy but is unable to stop the kidnapper, he becomes determined to find the missing child</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-21 20:00:00" d="2019-08-21 21:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation IX (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>78% The Gone Dead Train
Las Vegas-based forensic drama. A spate of unusual deaths lead the team to suspect that a public health crisis may be emerging</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-21 21:00:00" d="2019-08-21 22:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods V (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Payback
Danny and Baez investigate the murder of a celebrity chef, while Frank faces a moral dilemma when an old friend asks for a favour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-21 22:00:00" d="2019-08-21 23:10:00"><n u="New: Der Pass">New: Der Pass I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Ellie and Gedeon break the law when they set a trap for the killer. But they aren't the only ones playing games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-21 23:10:00" d="2019-08-22 01:10:00"><n u="Native Son">Native Son (2019)</n>    <k>A young black man's life spirals when he's hired as a driver for a wealthy white businessman. A modern take on Richard Wright's haunting novel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-22 01:10:00" d="2019-08-22 02:20:00"><n u="Euphoria">Euphoria I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Made You Look
Jules asks Rue to help her take suggestive photos for a boy online. Rue is confronted about her lies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-22 02:20:00" d="2019-08-22 02:55:00"><n u="Ballers">Ballers IV (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% Forgiving is Living
Spencer and Joe find themselves in a crisis. Ricky considers his motivations in ending his retirement. Jason turns to Donna for help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-22 02:55:00" d="2019-08-22 03:30:00"><n u="Girls">Girls III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Only Child
Hannah mixes with the big shots of the book world at her editor's funeral. Meanwhile, Ray gives Marnie some frank advice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-22 03:30:00" d="2019-08-22 05:15:00"><n>Bright Lights: Starring Carrie Fisher and Debbie Reynolds</n>    <k>An intimate, Emmy-nominated portrait of the late Hollywood mother and daughter, as they share a compound in what would be their final years together</k>  </p>
</a>
