<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2019-08-11 01:39:12"><p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 05:00:00" d="2019-08-17 06:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Process Stories
Election results from Orange County leave Sam in a delicate position, while Andy Wyatt's success gives Toby cause for concern</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 06:00:00" d="2019-08-17 07:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Swiss Diplomacy
When a 15-year-old Iranian boy needs medical treatment he can only get in the US, the politics of the situation prove complicated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 07:00:00" d="2019-08-17 08:00:00"><n u="The British">The British (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% Superpower
Stars Lily Cole and Dougray Scott explore the pioneering age of invention and exploration that made Britain the biggest power in the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 08:00:00" d="2019-08-17 09:00:00"><n u="Richard E Grant's Hotel Secrets">Richard E Grant's Hotel Secrets I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Living &amp; Dying
Richard E Grant checks into opulent hotels where the rich and famous have lived, died and fallen in love, including The Dorchester in London</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 09:00:00" d="2019-08-17 09:30:00"><n>David Attenborough: Micro Monsters</n>    <k>Conflict: Sir David Attenborough explores the macroscopic world of bugs and, in this first episode, finds out how its residents outwit their enemies to survive. (Ep 1 of 6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 09:30:00" d="2019-08-17 10:00:00"><n>David Attenborough: Micro Monsters</n>    <k>Predator: It's a bug-eat-bug world out there, and the documentary continues with a look at how the various critters defuse the defences of their prey. (Ep 2 of 6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 10:00:00" d="2019-08-17 10:30:00"><n>David Attenborough: Micro Monsters</n>    <k>Courtship: Dating is just as tricky a business in the insect world, and Sir David Attenborough finds out how certain bugs choose and then woo their partners. (Ep 3 of 6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 10:30:00" d="2019-08-17 11:00:00"><n>David Attenborough: Micro Monsters</n>    <k>Reproduction: Sir David Attenborough reveals how different bugs usher in the next generation, including the butterfly and harvestman spider. (Ep 4 of 6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 11:00:00" d="2019-08-17 11:30:00"><n>David Attenborough: Micro Monsters</n>    <k>Family: Join Sir David Attenborough as he zooms in on a set of bugs who prefer cooperation to conflict, from the burrowing cockroach to a queen bee. (Ep 5 of 6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 11:30:00" d="2019-08-17 12:00:00"><n>David Attenborough: Micro Monsters</n>    <k>Colony: Before departing the insect world, Sir David Attenborough takes a tour of its vast colonies, which rival human megacities in both size and complexity. (Ep 6 of 6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 12:00:00" d="2019-08-17 13:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation IX (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>78% Kill Me If You Can
Las Vegas-based forensic drama. The CSIs investigate three different crimes that seem unrelated, but each case's evidence brings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 13:00:00" d="2019-08-17 14:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation IX (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>78% Turn, Turn, Turn
Las Vegas-based forensic drama. Nick is repeatedly called to a low-budget motel where a third murder has occurred over the course of a year</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 14:00:00" d="2019-08-17 15:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation IX (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>78% No Way Out
Forensic drama. The investigation of a shootout in a neighbourhood cul-de-sac takes a turn when Langston and Riley are held hostage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 15:00:00" d="2019-08-17 16:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation IX (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>78% Mascara
Ray takes a personal interest when one of his former students turns up dead. The trail leads him to the world of 'Luchadores', Mexican semi-pro wrestling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 16:00:00" d="2019-08-17 17:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation IX (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>78% The Descent Of Man
When a sky diver is paralysed after his chute failed to properly deploy, several people are suspected, but the diver's past makes it more complicated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 17:00:00" d="2019-08-17 18:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace II (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bait
The team investigate when a millionaire's wife and their two children vanish from their yacht, which is discovered with only the body of the murdered captain on board</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 18:00:00" d="2019-08-17 19:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In The Dark
Season three of the US crime drama. While Jack comes to terms with Maria's request for a divorce, the team investigate the disappearance of two young women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 19:00:00" d="2019-08-17 20:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Thou Shalt Not. 
The disappearance of a nurse driving home late at night is investigated. Elsewhere, tension mounts as Jack reports to Vivian as a subordinate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 20:00:00" d="2019-08-17 21:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Light Years
The team searches for a man who believes that he was abducted by aliens when he was young. Meanwhile, Jack prepares for a bitter and hostile divorce from Maria</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 21:00:00" d="2019-08-17 22:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Upstairs, Downstairs
The team investigate when a wealthy couple's nanny vanishes on the night she was fired after being accused of stealing from the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-17 22:00:00" d="2019-08-18 01:00:00"><n u="The Affair">The Affair III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Alison spends a day with a wistful Noah on Block Island, just as he finds his problems returning with a force</k>  </p>
</a>
