<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="17" t="2020-04-16 04:36:26"><p id_tv="1060" o="2020-04-23 05:00:00" d="2020-04-23 06:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing VI (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Hubbert Peak
New press secretary Annabeth Schott (Kristin Chenoweth) must fight off the impression she's too young for the job. Elsewhere, Leo gives CJ strict orders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-04-23 06:00:00" d="2020-04-23 07:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing VI (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Dover Test
Annabeth is put to the test when an American soldier dies on the Gaza peacekeeping mission. Meanwhile, Charlie begins his new White House job</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-04-23 07:00:00" d="2020-04-23 08:00:00"><n u="Fish Town">Fish Town (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Dreams become a reality when 17-year-old Logan takes to the high seas as an apprentice deck hand. Plus, landlady Pat enjoys a trip down memory lane</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-04-23 08:00:00" d="2020-04-23 09:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Safe
When the team investigate the disappearance of a high school student, Vivian complains that Jack is treating her too cautiously after her recovery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-04-23 09:00:00" d="2020-04-23 10:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace IV (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>From The Ashes
A new agent, Elena Delgado, joins the FBI's Missing Persons Unit but soon finds that her NYPD vice training runs contrary to the team's usual methods</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-04-23 10:00:00" d="2020-04-23 11:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace IV (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lost Time
Jack and Vivian revisit an old case when new evidence suggests that a college professor serving time for killing a student might be innocent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-04-23 11:00:00" d="2020-04-23 12:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing VI (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Hubbert Peak
New press secretary Annabeth Schott (Kristin Chenoweth) must fight off the impression she's too young for the job. Elsewhere, Leo gives CJ strict orders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-04-23 12:00:00" d="2020-04-23 13:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing VI (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Dover Test
Annabeth is put to the test when an American soldier dies on the Gaza peacekeeping mission. Meanwhile, Charlie begins his new White House job</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-04-23 13:00:00" d="2020-04-23 14:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods IV (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Custody Battle
Erin investigates a case in which an on-duty police officer is accused of killing a suspect while in custody</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-04-23 14:00:00" d="2020-04-23 15:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation VIII (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>77% Two And A Half Deaths
When a famous sitcom actress is murdered, the CSIs travel to Los Angeles and enter the strange world of Hollywood comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-04-23 15:00:00" d="2020-04-23 16:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing VI (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% A Change Is Gonna Come
While Bartlet inadvertently causes problems for himself ahead of an upcoming China summit, Josh receives an interesting offer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-04-23 16:00:00" d="2020-04-23 17:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing VI (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% In The Room
Arnold Vinick (Alan Alda) announces his presidential candidacy, while Josh thinks about an offer and Bartlet's health becomes a problem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-04-23 17:00:00" d="2020-04-23 18:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace IV (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Viuda Negra
When a wealthy American is kidnapped and held for ransom while on holiday with his wife in Mexico, Jack and Danny go south of the border to investigate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-04-23 18:00:00" d="2020-04-23 19:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace IV (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Day In The Life
The team's latest case unfolds from the point of view of parents whose son went to an arcade on his bike in the evening and never came home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-04-23 19:00:00" d="2020-04-23 20:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace IV (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Freefall
Jack leads the search for an old friend in the Bureau who disappears after his inexperienced partner is murdered. Meanwhile, Martin sustains an injury</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-04-23 20:00:00" d="2020-04-23 21:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation VIII (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>77% For Gedda
When a private investigator turns up dead in what looks like a Mafia hit, Warrick finds himself under suspicion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2020-04-23 21:00:00" d="2020-04-24 00:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods IV (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Above And Beyond
When a detective from Danny's precinct is killed while working undercover, Frank discovers that he was hiding a dark secret</k>  </p>
</a>
