<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2019-07-11 00:20:57"><p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 05:10:00" d="2019-07-16 06:05:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% And It's Surely to Their Credit
Leo attempts to protect Ainsley, while Sam tries to persuade Josh to sue the hate group behind the shooting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 06:05:00" d="2019-07-16 07:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% The Lame Duck Congress
The team try to encourage Bartlet to call a special session of Congress, while Sam and Ainsley teach each other a thing or two</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 07:00:00" d="2019-07-16 08:00:00"><n u="The Guest Wing">The Guest Wing (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>At Chillingham Castle, the staff manage their relationship with eccentric baronet Sir Humphry Wakefield, while Carlton Towers welcomes the Afghan Hound Dog Show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 08:00:00" d="2019-07-16 09:00:00"><n u="Richard E Grant's Hotel Secrets">Richard E Grant's Hotel Secrets II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Miami
The lively travelogue returns as Richard E Grant visits more extravagant, scandalous and exclusive hotels, beginning in Miami</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 09:00:00" d="2019-07-16 10:00:00"><n u="The British">The British (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% Tale of Two Cities
The factual series explores the heaven and hell of Victorian London. Using CGI and drama, the vice, crime and poverty of the city is laid bare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 10:00:00" d="2019-07-16 11:00:00"><n u="Discovering: David Niven">Discovering: David Niven II (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A portrait of Hollywood's quintessential Englishman, whose career included acclaimed roles in films Separate Tables, A Matter of Life and Death and Around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 11:00:00" d="2019-07-16 12:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% And It's Surely to Their Credit
Leo attempts to protect Ainsley, while Sam tries to persuade Josh to sue the hate group behind the shooting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 12:00:00" d="2019-07-16 13:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% The Lame Duck Congress
The team try to encourage Bartlet to call a special session of Congress, while Sam and Ainsley teach each other a thing or two</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 13:00:00" d="2019-07-16 14:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Snatch Back
The team investigates several suspects when the child of a prominent assistant district attorney vanishes in a public park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 14:00:00" d="2019-07-16 15:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Little Big Man
The team searches for a teenager who went missing in a bad neighbourhood after an encounter with a bully. Crime drama starring Anthony LaPaglia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 15:00:00" d="2019-07-16 16:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods IV (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% Manhattan Queens
Danny and Baez investigate the death of a popular drag queen from a reality TV show. Series star Donnie Wahlberg directs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 16:00:00" d="2019-07-16 17:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing II (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% The Portland Trip
Leo causes concern at the White House while the president heads to Portland to deliver an educational address</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 17:00:00" d="2019-07-16 18:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing II (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Shibboleth
The president must decide how to treat a shipload of immigrants, while Toby pushes him to appoint Leo's sister to a national educational post</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 18:00:00" d="2019-07-16 19:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In Extremis
When a doctor of Saudi Arabian descent with an exemplary record mysteriously vanishes, Martin is quick to suspect the man of having terrorist connections</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 19:00:00" d="2019-07-16 20:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Midnight Sun
The MPU is called in when a man leaves home with his daughter, planning to take her to school and to open his dry-cleaning store, but they both vanish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 20:00:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation VIII (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>78% A Thousand Days On Earth
In a particularly disturbing case, the CSIs investigate the death of a three-year-old girl whose identity remains unknown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 22:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods IV (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% Open Secrets
Danny and Baez investigate the disappearance of a young girl, while Frank clashes with the inspector over access to classified information</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 22:00:00" d="2019-07-16 23:10:00"><n u="Active Shooter: America. Under Fire">Active Shooter: America. Under Fire I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>San Bernadino, California
A 2015 attack in San Bernardino, California forces the shocked community to confront questions of homegrown terrorism</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 23:10:00" d="2019-07-16 23:45:00"><n u="New: Crashing">New: Crashing III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Mom And Kat
Pete introduces girlfriend Kat to his parents while on tour and then feels trapped between the women in his life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-16 23:45:00" d="2019-07-17 00:20:00"><n u="New: Crashing">New: Crashing III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. The Viewing Party
Pete and Kat head to a viewing party so they can watch his ex Ali's late-night spot on Seth Meyers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 00:20:00" d="2019-07-17 01:20:00"><n u="Gomorrah">Gomorrah IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. The cocaine delay forces the Forcella boys to resort to desperate lengths to survive. Meanwhile, Sangue Blu faces a leadership crisis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 01:20:00" d="2019-07-17 02:20:00"><n u="Gomorrah">Gomorrah IV (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. An unforeseen event drags Genny back into the past, throws his new company into the spotlight and threatens the airport's construction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 02:20:00" d="2019-07-17 03:30:00"><n u="Six Feet Under">Six Feet Under II (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Back To The Garden
Claire spends the weekend with Sarah and her free-spirited friends. Nate bonds with a female rabbi and an emergency with Taylor brings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 03:30:00" d="2019-07-17 04:35:00"><n u="Six Feet Under">Six Feet Under II (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% It's the Most Wonderful Time of the Year
Christmas, and a year on from Nathaniel's death, the Fishers recall their final moments with him. Also, Brenda's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 04:35:00" d="2019-07-17 05:05:00"><n>Yesterday: Special</n>    <k>A special look at Danny Boyle's witty British comedy Yesterday, starring Lily James, Himesh Patel and Ed Sheeran</k>  </p>
</a>
