<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2019-07-11 00:20:57"><p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 05:05:00" d="2019-07-17 06:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing II (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% The Portland Trip
Leo causes concern at the White House while the president heads to Portland to deliver an educational address</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 06:00:00" d="2019-07-17 07:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing II (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Shibboleth
The president must decide how to treat a shipload of immigrants, while Toby pushes him to appoint Leo's sister to a national educational post</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 07:00:00" d="2019-07-17 08:00:00"><n u="The Guest Wing">The Guest Wing (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Carlton Towers hosts a British culinary weekend for eager tourists, while a group of budding wine connoisseurs arrive at Chillingham Castle for a tasting weekend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 08:00:00" d="2019-07-17 09:00:00"><n u="Richard E Grant's Hotel Secrets">Richard E Grant's Hotel Secrets II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Hong Kong
The actor visits Hong Kong's most extravagant hotels, including the Ritz-Carlton, home to the world's highest swimming pool</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 09:00:00" d="2019-07-17 10:00:00"><n u="The British">The British (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% War and Peace
The factual series closes with the turbulent and triumphant 20th century. CGI and drama re-create World War I and Queen Elizabeth II's coronation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 10:00:00" d="2019-07-17 11:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Gary Cooper">Discovering: Gary Cooper II (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A portrait of Hollywood icon Gary Cooper, whose films include High Noon, Sergeant York and Mr Deeds Goes to Town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 11:00:00" d="2019-07-17 12:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing II (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% The Portland Trip
Leo causes concern at the White House while the president heads to Portland to deliver an educational address</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 12:00:00" d="2019-07-17 13:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing II (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Shibboleth
The president must decide how to treat a shipload of immigrants, while Toby pushes him to appoint Leo's sister to a national educational post</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 13:00:00" d="2019-07-17 14:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In Extremis
When a doctor of Saudi Arabian descent with an exemplary record mysteriously vanishes, Martin is quick to suspect the man of having terrorist connections</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 14:00:00" d="2019-07-17 15:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Midnight Sun
The MPU is called in when a man leaves home with his daughter, planning to take her to school and to open his dry-cleaning store, but they both vanish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 15:00:00" d="2019-07-17 16:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods IV (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% Open Secrets
Danny and Baez investigate the disappearance of a young girl, while Frank clashes with the inspector over access to classified information</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 16:00:00" d="2019-07-17 17:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing II (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Galileo
Crises abound on a hectic day at the White House. Not only is a Russian missile silo allegedly on fire, a US fighter plane is also missing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 17:00:00" d="2019-07-17 18:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing II (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Noel
While Josh isn't feeling overly merry, the president is full of seasonal cheer and wants to sign his own Christmas cards</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 18:00:00" d="2019-07-17 19:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Maple Street
The team investigate when a 13-year-old girl disappears on her way to school and the only clue is her discarded video camera</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 19:00:00" d="2019-07-17 20:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace I (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Underground Railroad
Jack and his team search for a missing pregnant woman who has a medical condition that could lead to her death if she's not found within 24 hours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 20:00:00" d="2019-07-17 21:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation VIII (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>78% Drops Out
When the team investigate the murder of a woman found in an apartment building, a man known to the CSIs becomes a key suspect - even though he's behind bars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 21:00:00" d="2019-07-17 22:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods IV (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% Insult To Injury
Danny rushes to find a woman who calls him threatening to kill herself. Frank attends his grandson's school trip and clashes with a demanding mother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 22:00:00" d="2019-07-17 22:55:00"><n u="New: Gomorrah">New: Gomorrah IV (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. The Capaccios strike out at Sangue Blu as they set out to conquer Forcella. An isolated Enzo risks not only losing his turf, but also his men's loyalty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 22:55:00" d="2019-07-17 23:50:00"><n u="New: Gomorrah">New: Gomorrah IV (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Having realised the cause of all of her misfortunes, Patrizia is forced to face up to a life-changing decision</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-17 23:50:00" d="2019-07-18 00:25:00"><n u="Black Monday">Black Monday I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% New &amp; Exclusive. Take a glimpse into Mo's past, while Blair and Dawn undergo some necessary detective work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-18 00:25:00" d="2019-07-18 01:25:00"><n u="Riviera">Riviera 2 II (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Things take a horrifying turn after Georgina learns some surprising news about Nico. The pressure gets to Irina, and Jeff's loyalty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-18 01:25:00" d="2019-07-18 02:35:00"><n u="Six Feet Under">Six Feet Under II (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Someone Else's Eyes
As Lisa contacts Nate, and Brenda continues her hands-on research, their engagement becomes more uncertain than ever. Plus, Nikolai</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-18 02:35:00" d="2019-07-18 03:45:00"><n u="Six Feet Under">Six Feet Under II (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% The Secret
With Nate still reeling from Lisa's revelation, Melissa leads Brenda further astray. Claire ponders her future, and Karla causes more strife</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-07-18 03:45:00" d="2019-07-18 05:00:00"><n u="True Detective">True Detective I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Long Bright Dark
Two mismatched cops are dispatched to a hideous Louisiana crime scene</k>  </p>
</a>
