<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2021-07-09 07:14:49"><p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 05:05:00" d="2021-07-14 06:00:00"><n u="Richard E Grant's Hotel Secrets">Richard E Grant's Hotel Secrets II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Tokyo
Richard E Grant visits the most luxurious hotels in the Japanese capital, as well as checking out the city's love hotels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 06:00:00" d="2021-07-14 07:00:00"><n u="Richard E Grant's Hotel Secrets">Richard E Grant's Hotel Secrets II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Venice
In the final episode of the series, Richard travels to Italy to explore the most exclusive and exciting hotels in the Floating City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 07:00:00" d="2021-07-14 08:00:00"><n u="Fish Town">Fish Town (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series offering an eye-opening insight into the working lives of the residents of Brixham, Devon, one of UK's oldest and busiest fishing ports</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 08:00:00" d="2021-07-14 09:00:00"><n u="Elementary">Elementary II (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>79% Paint It Black
Lucy Liu directs this especially tense episode, in which brothers Sherlock and Mycroft join forces on a case with life-or-death consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 09:00:00" d="2021-07-14 10:00:00"><n u="Elementary">Elementary II (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>79% Art In the Blood. A seemingly routine murder case gets an international twist when Holmes crosses paths with MI6. Also, Joan rethinks her future with Mycroft</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 10:00:00" d="2021-07-14 11:05:00"><n u="Six Feet Under">Six Feet Under II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% In Place of Anger
As Nate and David fend off a fresh offer from Kroehner, Ruth's estranged sister (Emmy-winning guest star Patricia Clarkson) pays an unexpected visit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 11:05:00" d="2021-07-14 12:10:00"><n u="Six Feet Under">Six Feet Under II (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Back To The Garden
Claire spends the weekend with Sarah and her free-spirited friends. Nate bonds with a female rabbi and an emergency with Taylor brings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 12:10:00" d="2021-07-14 13:20:00"><n u="Boardwalk Empire">Boardwalk Empire I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% Nights in Ballygran
When Nucky Thompson fails to shut down a bootlegging operation, Margaret Schroeder takes matters into her own hands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 13:20:00" d="2021-07-14 14:30:00"><n u="Boardwalk Empire">Boardwalk Empire I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% Family Limitation
Nucky goes on the warpath when one of his cronies is attacked, while Jimmy and Al set up a meeting with their rivals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 14:30:00" d="2021-07-14 15:30:00"><n u="Elementary">Elementary II (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>79% The Grand Experiment
In the season two finale, Holmes and Watson join forces to disprove the murder and treason charges levied at Sherlock's brother Mycroft</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 15:30:00" d="2021-07-14 16:30:00"><n u="Elementary">Elementary III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>79% Enough Nemesis To Go Around
The slick crime drama returns. Sherlock tries to build bridges with Watson as he returns to New York with a new apprentice in tow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 16:30:00" d="2021-07-14 17:35:00"><n u="Dexter">Dexter IV (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Dirty Harry
Debra is an emotional wreck following the shooting, and Dexter is on the trail of the Trinity Killer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 17:35:00" d="2021-07-14 18:40:00"><n u="Dexter">Dexter IV (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>If I Had A Hammer
Dexter attempts to stay one step ahead of the police investigation of the Trinity Killer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 18:40:00" d="2021-07-14 19:45:00"><n u="The Sopranos">The Sopranos V (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% All Due Respect
Tony faces serious pressure from his own crew to deliver Tony B to New York. Season finale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 19:45:00" d="2021-07-14 20:50:00"><n u="The Sopranos">The Sopranos VI (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% Members Only
Tony worries about Johnny Sack's trial and the effect it's having on the New York and Jersey families</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 20:50:00" d="2021-07-14 22:00:00"><n u="Game Of Thrones">Game Of Thrones VI (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>No One
While Jaime weighs his options, Cersei answers a request and Tyrion's plans begin to bear fruit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 22:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:00:00"><n u="New: Totti: One Captain">New: Totti: One Captain I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Former inmate Marco watches Totti playing his last match. Little does he know he will be back to play in the 2026 Championship. Italian with subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-14 23:00:00" d="2021-07-15 00:10:00"><n u="The Wire">The Wire V (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>React Quotes
Marlo meets Vondas, who shows him some tricks of the trade. Meanwhile, McNulty's serial killer makes the news</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 00:10:00" d="2021-07-15 01:20:00"><n u="The Wire">The Wire V (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Dickensian Aspect
Carcetti makes a rousing promise to protect the homeless as Scott spends a night on the streets. Meanwhile, Marlo hunts for Omar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 01:20:00" d="2021-07-15 02:35:00"><n u="The Wire">The Wire V (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Took
Templeton gets a call from the serial killer as McNulty's web of lies spins further out of control. Omar sends Marlo a message</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 02:35:00" d="2021-07-15 03:50:00"><n u="True Blood">True Blood III (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Beautifully Broken
The vampire king of Mississippi lays out his plans to increase his grip on the South, while Sam visits his birth family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 03:50:00" d="2021-07-15 04:25:00"><n u="Californication">Californication VII (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>82% Levon
After his short-lived tour with Atticus, Hank is eager to reunite with the love of his life, but things with Karen don't go quite as planned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 04:25:00" d="2021-07-15 05:00:00"><n u="Californication">Californication VII (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>82% Julia
Hank's first day in the Santa Monica Cop writer's room brings aggravation from his new co-workers. Meanwhile, Karen gets an unexpected surprise</k>  </p>
</a>
