<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="28" t="2019-08-13 02:25:27"><p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-18 05:05:00" d="2019-08-18 06:00:00"><n u="Fish Town">Fish Town (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>This insightful documentary series returns to shore and comes to an end. The fishermen spend some quality time with their loved ones, and Logan has a big decision to make</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-18 06:00:00" d="2019-08-18 07:00:00"><n u="The British">The British (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% Treasure Island
This factual series tells the story of our nation through CGI, re-enactments &amp; interviews with famous faces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-18 07:00:00" d="2019-08-18 08:00:00"><n u="The British">The British (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% Tale of Two Cities
The factual series explores the heaven and hell of Victorian London. Using CGI and drama, the vice, crime and poverty of the city is laid bare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-18 08:00:00" d="2019-08-18 09:00:00"><n u="Richard E Grant's Hotel Secrets">Richard E Grant's Hotel Secrets I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Scandal
Richard E Grant uncovers scandals lurking behind the closed doors of the world's most famous hotels, and talks to former Hollywood madam Heidi Fleiss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-18 09:00:00" d="2019-08-18 10:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>American Goddess
The team are called in when the winner of an extreme-makeover reality contest vanishes at the height of her fame. Saved by the Bell's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-18 10:00:00" d="2019-08-18 11:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Nickel And Dimed, Part 1
When a single mother leaves her three-year-old son with a babysitter and vanishes, the investigation personally affects Samantha</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-18 11:00:00" d="2019-08-18 12:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Nickel And Dimed, Part 2
Conclusion of a two-part story. Samantha goes undercover in a bid to find a missing mother who is involved with drug traffickers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-18 12:00:00" d="2019-08-18 13:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Doppelganger II
A previous case is revisited when a woman disappears from a shelter whose manager is the identical twin of a man arrested five months earlier for murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-18 13:00:00" d="2019-08-18 14:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Trials
When a juror in a murder trial vanishes, suspicion falls on the defendant, a gang member who could get a mistrial if the man is not found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-18 14:00:00" d="2019-08-18 14:30:00"><n>David Attenborough: Micro Monsters</n>    <k>Conflict: Sir David Attenborough explores the macroscopic world of bugs and, in this first episode, finds out how its residents outwit their enemies to survive. (Ep 1 of 6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-18 14:30:00" d="2019-08-18 15:00:00"><n>David Attenborough: Micro Monsters</n>    <k>Predator: It's a bug-eat-bug world out there, and the documentary continues with a look at how the various critters defuse the defences of their prey. (Ep 2 of 6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-18 15:00:00" d="2019-08-18 15:30:00"><n>David Attenborough: Micro Monsters</n>    <k>Courtship: Dating is just as tricky a business in the insect world, and Sir David Attenborough finds out how certain bugs choose and then woo their partners. (Ep 3 of 6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-18 15:30:00" d="2019-08-18 16:00:00"><n>David Attenborough: Micro Monsters</n>    <k>Reproduction: Sir David Attenborough reveals how different bugs usher in the next generation, including the butterfly and harvestman spider. (Ep 4 of 6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-18 16:00:00" d="2019-08-18 16:30:00"><n>David Attenborough: Micro Monsters</n>    <k>Family: Join Sir David Attenborough as he zooms in on a set of bugs who prefer cooperation to conflict, from the burrowing cockroach to a queen bee. (Ep 5 of 6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-18 16:30:00" d="2019-08-18 17:00:00"><n>David Attenborough: Micro Monsters</n>    <k>Colony: Before departing the insect world, Sir David Attenborough takes a tour of its vast colonies, which rival human megacities in both size and complexity. (Ep 6 of 6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-18 17:00:00" d="2019-08-18 18:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods V (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Love Stories
Danny and Baez investigate when a hitman is shot while committing a burglary. Erin doubts herself when a 12-year-old murder case is reopened</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-18 18:00:00" d="2019-08-18 19:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods V (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% The Poor Door
Danny and Baez are called in to investigate a murder in a luxury building, while Frank takes issue with a detective friend of Gormley's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-18 19:00:00" d="2019-08-18 20:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods V (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Power Players
When a star witness in a double murder trial drops out, Erin must bring a protected mob informant back to New York and keep him safe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-18 20:00:00" d="2019-08-18 21:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods V (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% In the Box
When Baez is held at gunpoint in an interrogation room, Danny must try to meet the hostage taker's demands before it's too late</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-18 21:00:00" d="2019-08-18 22:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods V (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Occupational Hazards
Erin worries she's in danger when her apartment is broken into and her colleague is attacked. Elsewhere, Jamie and Eddie discover a bomb</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-18 22:00:00" d="2019-08-18 23:10:00"><n u="New: Real Time With Bill Maher">New: Real Time With Bill Maher XVII (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Comic Bill Maher invites three guests from diverse parts of the political spectrum for a lively discussion of the week's events</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-18 23:10:00" d="2019-08-19 00:20:00"><n u="Euphoria">Euphoria I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Stuntin' Like My Daddy
Rue struggles to put the past behind her on her first day back at school. Kat finds a video of herself online</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 00:20:00" d="2019-08-19 01:30:00"><n u="Succession">Succession II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. The Summer Palace
Kendall tries to make amends with his dad and Logan gets stark advice from his banker. Shiv wonders if her father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 01:30:00" d="2019-08-19 02:05:00"><n u="Last Week Tonight With John Oliver">Last Week Tonight With John Oliver VI (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>90% New &amp; Exclusive. British comedian John Oliver takes a tongue-in-cheek look at breaking news and current affairs stories in his Emmy Award-winning series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 02:05:00" d="2019-08-19 03:00:00"><n u="Active Shooter: America. Under Fire">Active Shooter: America. Under Fire I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Santa Monica, California
A shooter's 2013 rampage through Santa Monica kills six. With little apparent motive, what sparked this killing spree?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 03:00:00" d="2019-08-19 04:10:00"><n u="New: Succession">New: Succession II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Vaulter
Roman and Kendall compete to fix Vaulter. Meanwhile, Greg wonders if ATN is the right fit for him and Shiv brings Tom in on her future</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 04:10:00" d="2019-08-19 04:45:00"><n u="Divorce">Divorce III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Knock Knock
Frances and Robert face the realities of post-divorce life as each of their relationships reach a moment of truth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-19 04:45:00" d="2019-08-19 05:15:00"><n u="Alan Partridge's Mid Morning Matters">Alan Partridge's Mid Morning Matters II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Alan is joined in the studio by a controversial and outspoken author promoting his latest book</k>  </p>
</a>
