<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2019-08-15 22:50:58"><p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-22 05:15:00" d="2019-08-22 06:10:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (14) (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Inauguration
Escalating genocide in a remote African country gets Bartlet thinking ahead of his second presidential inauguration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-22 06:10:00" d="2019-08-22 07:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (15) (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Inauguration
Over There
Will Bailey's work on the inaugural address makes quite an impression, while Danny's reporting makes a splash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-22 07:00:00" d="2019-08-22 08:00:00"><n u="The British">The British (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% Treasure Island
This factual series tells the story of our nation through CGI, re-enactments &amp; interviews with famous faces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-22 08:00:00" d="2019-08-22 09:00:00"><n u="The Guest Wing">The Guest Wing (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The majestic Muncaster Castle takes centre stage in this penultimate instalment as the Pennington family discuss the struggles of keeping a stately home afloat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-22 09:00:00" d="2019-08-22 10:00:00"><n u="Fish Town">Fish Town (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Competition is fierce as local merchant Robert and wife Kelly open up a fish and chip restaurant. Plus, follow the journey of the turbot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-22 10:00:00" d="2019-08-22 11:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Jack Lemmon">Discovering: Jack Lemmon IV (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A fascinating look at the life and career of two-time Oscar winner Jack Lemmon, who was known for his roles in films such as Some Like it Hot and The Odd Couple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-22 11:00:00" d="2019-08-22 12:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (14) (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Inauguration
Escalating genocide in a remote African country gets Bartlet thinking ahead of his second presidential inauguration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-22 12:00:00" d="2019-08-22 13:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (15) (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Inauguration
Over There
Will Bailey's work on the inaugural address makes quite an impression, while Danny's reporting makes a splash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-22 13:00:00" d="2019-08-22 14:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Party Girl
The Missing Persons Unit is called into action when a young and beautiful publishing heiress vanishes while on her way to a party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-22 14:00:00" d="2019-08-22 15:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Manhunt
When Martin witnesses the abduction of a boy but is unable to stop the kidnapper, he becomes determined to find the missing child</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-22 15:00:00" d="2019-08-22 16:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods V (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Payback
Danny and Baez investigate the murder of a celebrity chef, while Frank faces a moral dilemma when an old friend asks for a favour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-22 16:00:00" d="2019-08-22 17:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% The California 47th
The president flies to California to campaign for Sam, but the Republicans' new tax proposal makes it a tough time to be visiting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-22 17:00:00" d="2019-08-22 18:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Red Haven's on Fire
When Josh shuts down the first lady's budget request, she hires a chief of staff. Will, meanwhile, terrorises his interns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-22 18:00:00" d="2019-08-22 19:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lone Star
When an estate agent vanishes, clues about his disappearance reveal a secret life and lead the detectives to a slavery and prostitution ring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-22 19:00:00" d="2019-08-22 20:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Transitions
While the team investigate the disappearance of a woman that could be the result of a hate crime, Vivian tries to hide her condition from her colleagues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-22 20:00:00" d="2019-08-22 21:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation IX (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>78% Hog Heaven
Las Vegas-based forensic drama. An undercover cop's biker gang turn against him when his cover is unexpectedly blown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-22 21:00:00" d="2019-08-22 22:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods V (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% New Rules
In the first of the two-part season finale, Frank pulls out all the stops to catch the killer of a colleague who's gunned down in a gang hit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-22 22:00:00" d="2019-08-23 00:00:00"><n u="Fahrenheit">Fahrenheit 451</n>    <k>Michael B Jordan and Michael Shannon star in an adaptation of Ray Bradbury's classic dystopian novel, depicting a future where books are burned, history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-23 00:00:00" d="2019-08-23 01:10:00"><n u="The Sopranos">The Sopranos V (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% In Camelot
Phil gets on the wrong side of Tony, while JT learns that it's not wise to mix business and friendship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-23 01:10:00" d="2019-08-23 02:20:00"><n u="The Sopranos">The Sopranos V (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% Marco Polo
Tony B ponders an offer to get involved with New York. Elsewhere, a reconciliation could be on the cards</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-23 02:20:00" d="2019-08-23 02:55:00"><n u="Last Week Tonight With John Oliver">Last Week Tonight With John Oliver VI (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>90% New &amp; Exclusive. British comedian John Oliver takes a tongue-in-cheek look at breaking news and current affairs stories in his Emmy Award-winning series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-23 02:55:00" d="2019-08-23 03:30:00"><n u="Ballers">Ballers IV (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% Doink
Spencer looks to elevate the SportsX TV brand, while Joe weighs a new offer. Charles is encouraged by Julie to bring more flair to his job</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-23 03:30:00" d="2019-08-23 04:05:00"><n u="Ballers">Ballers IV (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% No Small Talk
Spencer recruits Q to help him leverage a deal. With Reggie in tow, Joe talks business with some extreme skateboarders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-23 04:05:00" d="2019-08-23 04:40:00"><n u="Girls">Girls III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Free Snacks
Hannah gets a job writing advertorials for GQ, while Shoshanna and Marnie both see Ray in a new light</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-23 04:40:00" d="2019-08-23 05:15:00"><n u="Girls">Girls III (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Beach House
The girls take off for a weekend in Long Island, but when they bump into Elijah it puts a hitch in Marnie's plans</k>  </p>
</a>
