<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2019-08-13 02:25:41"><p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 05:00:00" d="2019-08-20 06:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Arctic Radar
As Sam leaves, he recommends Will Bailey to be Toby's new speechwriter. Elsewhere, Donna asks Josh for some help on the romance front</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 06:00:00" d="2019-08-20 07:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Holy Night
It's two days before Christmas and the White House is inundated with visitors, including Toby's father and Zoey Bartlet and her new boyfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 07:00:00" d="2019-08-20 08:00:00"><n u="Storm City">Storm City (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>From flash floods and storm surges to the relentless power of a tsunami, Ben Fogle finds out how people survive the raging torrent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 08:00:00" d="2019-08-20 09:00:00"><n u="The Guest Wing">The Guest Wing (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>At Chillingham Castle, the staff manage their relationship with eccentric baronet Sir Humphry Wakefield, while Carlton Towers welcomes the Afghan Hound Dog Show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 09:00:00" d="2019-08-20 10:00:00"><n u="Fish Town">Fish Town (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Brixham plunders Devon's colourful piracy past, playing host to the annual Pirate Festival. Elsewhere, back at sea, fisherman Nathan sets off in search of 'Black Gold'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 10:00:00" d="2019-08-20 11:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Maureen O'Hara">Discovering: Maureen O'Hara IV (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the life and career of actress Maureen O'Hara. Born in Ranelagh, Ireland, in 1920, she starred in Hollywood classics Miracle on 34th Street and The Parent Trap</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 11:00:00" d="2019-08-20 12:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Arctic Radar
As Sam leaves, he recommends Will Bailey to be Toby's new speechwriter. Elsewhere, Donna asks Josh for some help on the romance front</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 12:00:00" d="2019-08-20 13:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Holy Night
It's two days before Christmas and the White House is inundated with visitors, including Toby's father and Zoey Bartlet and her new boyfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 13:00:00" d="2019-08-20 14:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Malone v Malone
As the team celebrates the holidays with an office party, Jack endures a traumatic deposition in his custody battle for his daughters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 14:00:00" d="2019-08-20 15:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>4.0
When an academically gifted student vanishes, the team uncovers a secret that may have a connection with her disappearance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 15:00:00" d="2019-08-20 16:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods V (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Bad Company
While Eddie goes on her first undercover assignment, Frank helps an old friend meet the person who killed her family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 16:00:00" d="2019-08-20 17:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Guns Not Butter
While Danny Concannon comes close to the truth in the Sharif affair, Charlie wants to help a female soldier who needs financial assistance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 17:00:00" d="2019-08-20 18:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% The Long Goodbye
When CJ returns home to Dayton, Ohio, to give a talk at her high school reunion, she makes a sad discovery about her father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 18:00:00" d="2019-08-20 19:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Penitence
The team is called in to search for a prisoner who is thought to have escaped two weeks before he was up for parole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 19:00:00" d="2019-08-20 20:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Volcano
An autistic boy vanishes during a school trip to a museum, leaving behind his wrist locator, which is found cut and discarded</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 20:00:00" d="2019-08-20 21:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation IX (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>78% If I Had A Hammer
Catherine challenges the conviction of a man jailed 18 years ago based on shoddy evidence. The team re-open the case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 21:00:00" d="2019-08-20 22:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods V (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Through the Looking Glass
Frank clashes with a journalist who refuses to reveal a source who has admitted to murder. Plus, Danny works with troubled teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-20 22:00:00" d="2019-08-21 01:00:00"><n u="Active Shooter: America. Under Fire">Active Shooter: America. Under Fire I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Oak Creek, Wisconsin
A white supremacist's attack on a Sikh temple and the first responders' acts of heroism transform a community</k>  </p>
</a>
