<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2021-07-09 07:15:01"><p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 05:00:00" d="2021-07-15 06:00:00"><n u="The British">The British (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% Treasure Island
This factual series tells the story of our nation through CGI, re-enactments &amp; interviews with famous faces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 06:00:00" d="2021-07-15 07:00:00"><n>The British</n>    <k>People Power: Stars including Tim Roth and Tracey Emin explore the rampage and rebellion of medieval Britain during the Black Death and Peasants' Revolt. (Ep 2 of 7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 07:00:00" d="2021-07-15 08:00:00"><n u="Fish Town">Fish Town (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Brixham plunders Devon's colourful piracy past, playing host to the annual Pirate Festival. Elsewhere, back at sea, fisherman Nathan sets off in search of 'Black Gold'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 08:00:00" d="2021-07-15 09:00:00"><n u="Elementary">Elementary II (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>79% The Grand Experiment
In the season two finale, Holmes and Watson join forces to disprove the murder and treason charges levied at Sherlock's brother Mycroft</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 09:00:00" d="2021-07-15 10:00:00"><n u="Elementary">Elementary III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>79% Enough Nemesis To Go Around
The slick crime drama returns. Sherlock tries to build bridges with Watson as he returns to New York with a new apprentice in tow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 10:00:00" d="2021-07-15 11:05:00"><n u="Six Feet Under">Six Feet Under II (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% It's the Most Wonderful Time of the Year
Christmas, and a year on from Nathaniel's death, the Fishers recall their final moments with him. Also, Brenda's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 11:05:00" d="2021-07-15 12:10:00"><n u="Six Feet Under">Six Feet Under II (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Someone Else's Eyes
As Lisa contacts Nate, and Brenda continues her hands-on research, their engagement becomes more uncertain than ever. Plus, Nikolai</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 12:10:00" d="2021-07-15 13:20:00"><n u="Boardwalk Empire">Boardwalk Empire I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% Home
A visit to his family home brings back bad memories for Nucky, while Jimmy makes a new ally when visiting a veterans' hospital</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 13:20:00" d="2021-07-15 14:30:00"><n u="Boardwalk Empire">Boardwalk Empire I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% Hold me in Paradise
Trouble looms when Nucky Thompson heads to Chicago, leaving his brother Eli in charge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 14:30:00" d="2021-07-15 15:30:00"><n u="Elementary">Elementary III (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>79% The Five Orange Pipz
Kitty, Sherlock's new apprentice, lets jealousy get the better of her when Holmes and Watson investigate a double homicide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 15:30:00" d="2021-07-15 16:30:00"><n u="Elementary">Elementary III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>79% Just a Regular Irregular
A maths genius turns to Sherlock for help when he discovers a body and Joan attempts to build bridges with the detective and Kitty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 16:30:00" d="2021-07-15 17:35:00"><n u="Dexter">Dexter IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Slack Tide
Dexter seems to have finally balanced his work, family and murderous lives, but will it last?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 17:35:00" d="2021-07-15 18:40:00"><n u="Dexter">Dexter IV (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Road Kill
Dexter goes on an excursion with Trinity, but will he take the opportunity to kill him?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 18:40:00" d="2021-07-15 19:45:00"><n u="The Sopranos">The Sopranos VI (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% Join The Club
A comatose Tony dreams of what could have been if he were a normal, law-abiding civilian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 19:45:00" d="2021-07-15 20:50:00"><n u="The Sopranos">The Sopranos VI (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% Mayham
As Tony's comatose dream continues, the stress of Silvio's added workload affects his health</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 20:50:00" d="2021-07-15 22:00:00"><n u="Game Of Thrones">Game Of Thrones VI (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Battle of the B_____ds
While Daenerys returns to Meereen, Jon Snow's army advances as the battle for Winterfell begins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 22:00:00" d="2021-07-15 23:00:00"><n u="Little Birds">Little Birds I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>61% Hugo struggles with unfinished business that Lucy's father asked him to take care of. Adham finds his royal bearing is of little help in the Interzone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-15 23:00:00" d="2021-07-16 00:10:00"><n u="City On A Hill">City On A Hill II (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Pax Bostonia
As Boston mourns another loss, Decourcy pursues justice in and out of the courtroom. Season finale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 00:10:00" d="2021-07-16 01:20:00"><n u="Oz">Oz I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Capital P
Governor Devlin has reinstated the death penalty and Jefferson Keene will be the first to be put to death in 34 years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 01:20:00" d="2021-07-16 02:35:00"><n u="Oz">Oz I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Straight Life
Said is diagnosed with hypertension but refuses medication and Beecher spirals further into addiction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 02:35:00" d="2021-07-16 03:50:00"><n u="True Blood">True Blood III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>It Hurts Me Too
Sookie searches for Bill, accompanied by werewolf bodyguard Alcide. Meanwhile, Bill is haunted by his past</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 03:50:00" d="2021-07-16 04:25:00"><n u="Californication">Californication VII (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>82% Like Father Like Son
Hank is assigned to write his first Santa Monica Cop episode, much to the chagrin of his co-workers. Elsewhere, Levon tries to bond with Melanie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 04:25:00" d="2021-07-16 05:00:00"><n u="Californication">Californication VII (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>82% D__ks
Julia celebrates her new role with Hank and Levon, while money troubles add to Charlie and Marcy's marital unrest</k>  </p>
</a>
