<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2021-07-09 07:15:09"><p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 05:00:00" d="2021-07-16 06:00:00"><n u="The British">The British (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% Revolution
The factual series charges forwards to the Tudor and Stuart dynasties. CGI and guest stars give fresh insights on Henry VIII and the English Civil War</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 06:00:00" d="2021-07-16 07:00:00"><n u="The British">The British (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% Dirty Money
The factual series proves money does create power. CGI, action-packed drama and guest stars chart how slavery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 07:00:00" d="2021-07-16 08:00:00"><n u="Fish Town">Fish Town (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Dreams become a reality when 17-year-old Logan takes to the high seas as an apprentice deck hand. Plus, landlady Pat enjoys a trip down memory lane</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 08:00:00" d="2021-07-16 09:00:00"><n u="Elementary">Elementary III (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>79% The Five Orange Pipz
Kitty, Sherlock's new apprentice, lets jealousy get the better of her when Holmes and Watson investigate a double homicide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 09:00:00" d="2021-07-16 10:00:00"><n u="Elementary">Elementary III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>79% Just a Regular Irregular
A maths genius turns to Sherlock for help when he discovers a body and Joan attempts to build bridges with the detective and Kitty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 10:00:00" d="2021-07-16 11:05:00"><n u="Six Feet Under">Six Feet Under II (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% The Secret
With Nate still reeling from Lisa's revelation, Melissa leads Brenda further astray. Claire ponders her future, and Karla causes more strife</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 11:05:00" d="2021-07-16 12:10:00"><n u="Six Feet Under">Six Feet Under II (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% The Liar and the W___e
Truths emerge when Nate and Brenda get relationship counselling from Rabbi Ari. Ruth has a run-in with loan shark Yuri, and Keith</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 12:10:00" d="2021-07-16 13:20:00"><n u="Boardwalk Empire">Boardwalk Empire I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% Belle Femme
As Jimmy hunts the gang that shot Eli, criminal mastermind Arnold Rothstein plots to have Nucky Thompson killed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 13:20:00" d="2021-07-16 14:30:00"><n u="Boardwalk Empire">Boardwalk Empire I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% Emerald City
Having survived an assassination attempt, Nucky plots revenge on the D'Alessio brothers with the help of Chalky White</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 14:30:00" d="2021-07-16 15:30:00"><n u="Elementary">Elementary III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>79% Bella
Sherlock is recruited to investigate the theft of a groundbreaking super computer but becomes distracted by disproving its abilities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 15:30:00" d="2021-07-16 16:30:00"><n u="Elementary">Elementary III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>79% Rip Off
Sherlock and Kitty's investigation into the murder of a small shop owner becomes more complicated when they uncover links to the illegal diamond trade</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 16:30:00" d="2021-07-16 17:35:00"><n u="Dexter">Dexter IV (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Hungry Man
The forensic expert spends Thanksgiving with his rival, Arthur, but the holiday takes a twisted turn at the Mitchell residence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 17:35:00" d="2021-07-16 18:40:00"><n u="Dexter">Dexter IV (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lost Boys
A 10-year-old boy goes missing, and Dexter considers putting his 'dark passenger' to bed - but first tries to ensure The Trinity Killer is dead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 18:40:00" d="2021-07-16 19:45:00"><n u="The Sopranos">The Sopranos VI (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% The Fleshy Part Of The Thigh
The sale of Barone Sanitation is complicated by a son who doesn't get how it works</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 19:45:00" d="2021-07-16 20:50:00"><n u="The Sopranos">The Sopranos VI (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% Mr. &amp; Mrs John Sacrimoni Request
Johnny Sack wants to be released from prison to attend his daughter's wedding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 20:50:00" d="2021-07-16 22:00:00"><n u="Game Of Thrones">Game Of Thrones VI (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Winds of Winter
Cersei awaits judgement, Walder Frey and Jaime celebrate and winter finally arrives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 22:00:00" d="2021-07-16 23:00:00"><n u="Totti: One Captain">Totti: One Captain I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Former inmate Marco watches Totti playing his last match. Little does he know he will be back to play in the 2026 Championship. Italian with subtitles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-16 23:00:00" d="2021-07-17 00:15:00"><n u="Oz">Oz I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>To Your Health
Alvarez reunites with his father and grandfather who are also in OZ, meanwhile Beecher attacks Schillinger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-17 00:15:00" d="2021-07-17 01:30:00"><n u="Oz">Oz I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Plan B
Groves decides to kill Warden Glynn to impress Said, and Beecher shows his bad side</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-17 01:30:00" d="2021-07-17 02:40:00"><n u="True Blood">True Blood III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>9 Crimes
Sookie joins Alcide at a party for his ex-fiancee and Jason senses an opportunity after Andy gets promoted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-17 02:40:00" d="2021-07-17 03:50:00"><n u="True Blood">True Blood III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Trouble
Alcide and Sookie turn to a wolf packmaster for help holding off Russell's minions. Meanwhile, Tara considers a proposal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-17 03:50:00" d="2021-07-17 04:25:00"><n u="Californication">Californication VII (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>82% Getting The Poison Out
While Julia is off with Rath, Hank and Levon have a night out with Karen and Marcy. Meanwhile, Charlie may be in</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2021-07-17 04:25:00" d="2021-07-17 05:00:00"><n u="Californication">Californication VII (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>82% Kickoff
It's the Santa Monica Cop kickoff party at Rath's and Hank has an intimate notes session with the show's female lead, Amy Taylor Walsh</k>  </p>
</a>
