<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2019-08-09 01:41:24"><p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-15 05:00:00" d="2019-08-15 06:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% The Red Mass
While a third-party candidate becomes a thorn in Bartlet's side, the team learn that the Ritchie camp wants as few debates as possible</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-15 06:00:00" d="2019-08-15 07:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Debate Camp
While prepping for the debates, flashbacks reveal the administration's first weeks in office. Joey Lucas, meanwhile, has distressing news</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-15 07:00:00" d="2019-08-15 08:00:00"><n u="Urban Secrets">Urban Secrets (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The series concludes as Alan visits Glasgow. Starting at the Necropolis, the actor's journey takes him from the world's oldest music hall to tea with a movie star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-15 08:00:00" d="2019-08-15 09:00:00"><n u="The British">The British (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% War and Peace
The factual series closes with the turbulent and triumphant 20th century. CGI and drama re-create World War I and Queen Elizabeth II's coronation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-15 09:00:00" d="2019-08-15 10:00:00"><n u="Richard E Grant's Hotel Secrets">Richard E Grant's Hotel Secrets II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Venice
In the final episode of the series, Richard travels to Italy to explore the most exclusive and exciting hotels in the Floating City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-15 10:00:00" d="2019-08-15 11:00:00"><n u="Discovering: Errol Flynn">Discovering: Errol Flynn IV (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Film critics discuss the remarkable life and swashbuckling career of Errol Flynn, who became a Hollywood star with films such as The Adventures of Robin Hood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-15 11:00:00" d="2019-08-15 12:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% The Red Mass
While a third-party candidate becomes a thorn in Bartlet's side, the team learn that the Ritchie camp wants as few debates as possible</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-15 12:00:00" d="2019-08-15 13:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Debate Camp
While prepping for the debates, flashbacks reveal the administration's first weeks in office. Joey Lucas, meanwhile, has distressing news</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-15 13:00:00" d="2019-08-15 14:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Upstairs, Downstairs
The team investigate when a wealthy couple's nanny vanishes on the night she was fired after being accused of stealing from the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-15 14:00:00" d="2019-08-15 15:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>American Goddess
The team are called in when the winner of an extreme-makeover reality contest vanishes at the height of her fame. Saved by the Bell's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-15 15:00:00" d="2019-08-15 16:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods V (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Power Players
When a star witness in a double murder trial drops out, Erin must bring a protected mob informant back to New York and keep him safe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-15 16:00:00" d="2019-08-15 17:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Game On
As Bartlet and Ritchie go head to head in a debate, Sam's mission leads to a career-altering decision</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-15 17:00:00" d="2019-08-15 18:00:00"><n u="The West Wing">The West Wing IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Election Night
It's election day, but Charlie has more concerns about the president's physical health than his political well-being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-15 18:00:00" d="2019-08-15 19:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Nickel And Dimed, Part 1
When a single mother leaves her three-year-old son with a babysitter and vanishes, the investigation personally affects Samantha</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-15 19:00:00" d="2019-08-15 20:00:00"><n u="Without A Trace">Without A Trace III (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Nickel And Dimed, Part 2
Conclusion of a two-part story. Samantha goes undercover in a bid to find a missing mother who is involved with drug traffickers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-15 20:00:00" d="2019-08-15 21:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation IX (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>78% Mascara
Ray takes a personal interest when one of his former students turns up dead. The trail leads him to the world of 'Luchadores', Mexican semi-pro wrestling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-15 21:00:00" d="2019-08-15 22:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods V (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% In the Box
When Baez is held at gunpoint in an interrogation room, Danny must try to meet the hostage taker's demands before it's too late</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-15 22:00:00" d="2019-08-15 23:45:00"><n>Bright Lights: Starring Carrie Fisher and Debbie Reynolds</n>    <k>An intimate, Emmy-nominated portrait of the late Hollywood mother and daughter, as they share a compound in what would be their final years together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-15 23:45:00" d="2019-08-16 00:50:00"><n u="The Sopranos">The Sopranos V (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% Irregular Around The Margins
Already at breaking point, Adriana's woes are compounded by rumours about her and Tony</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 00:50:00" d="2019-08-16 02:00:00"><n u="The Sopranos">The Sopranos V (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>91% Sentimental Education
Tony B is intent on staying straight but, as Carmela learns, escaping your past isn't easy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 02:00:00" d="2019-08-16 02:35:00"><n u="Last Week Tonight With John Oliver">Last Week Tonight With John Oliver VI (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>90% New &amp; Exclusive. British comedian John Oliver takes a tongue-in-cheek look at breaking news and current affairs stories in his Emmy Award-winning series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 02:35:00" d="2019-08-16 03:40:00"><n u="Six Feet Under">Six Feet Under V (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% Ecotone
Following Nate's seizure the family race to his bedside. As Nate is rushed into emergency surgery, he has a series of dreams that cause</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 03:40:00" d="2019-08-16 04:55:00"><n u="Six Feet Under">Six Feet Under V (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>88% All Alone
Following a death in the family, David deals with his grief by planning the funeral, while the rest of the family struggle to cope with their loss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1060" o="2019-08-16 04:55:00" d="2019-08-16 05:10:00"><n>Life Itself: Special</n>    <k>A special look at the latest Sky Cinema Original Film - a multi-generational tale of life, loss and love starring Oscar Isaac, Olivia Wilde, Olivia Cooke</k>  </p>
</a>
