<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="30" t="2019-08-15 22:51:12"><p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 05:00:00" d="2019-08-22 06:00:00"><n u="Paramedics">Paramedics III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Onwards
Cork paramedic crew Denise and Imelda respond to a cardiac arrest in Cork city centre</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 06:00:00" d="2019-08-22 06:30:00"><n u="The Real A &amp; E">The Real A &amp; E I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Series exposing the reality of life and death in the UK's biggest A&amp;E department. The helicopter team rushes to a road accident. Contains strong images</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 06:30:00" d="2019-08-22 07:00:00"><n u="The Real A &amp; E">The Real A &amp; E I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Fly on the wall series which follows the work of the medical team at Coventry University Hospital's A&amp;E. The team rushes to help a woman who is impaled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 07:00:00" d="2019-08-22 07:30:00"><n u="Motorway Patrol">Motorway Patrol XV (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series from New Zealand following the madness and mayhem faced by intrepid officers as they pull over motorists for a variety of suspected offences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 07:30:00" d="2019-08-22 08:00:00"><n u="Motorway Patrol">Motorway Patrol XV (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series from New Zealand following the madness and mayhem faced by intrepid officers as they pull over motorists for a variety of suspected offences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 08:00:00" d="2019-08-22 09:00:00"><n u="Stop Search Seize">Stop Search Seize I (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Ireland's Customs teams as they, with the help of the Irish police, try to stop organised smugglers from bringing drugs, cars and even exotic animals into the country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 09:00:00" d="2019-08-22 09:30:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare VI (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Fly-on-the-wall documentary following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, smugglers and terrorists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 09:30:00" d="2019-08-22 10:00:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare VI (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Fly-on-the-wall documentary following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, smugglers and terrorists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 10:00:00" d="2019-08-22 11:00:00"><n u="Brit Cops: Rapid Response">Brit Cops: Rapid Response III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Action-packed documentary following rapid response officers, the fastest cops in Britain, as they crack down on crime. Time is of the essence!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 11:00:00" d="2019-08-22 12:00:00"><n u="Brit Cops: Rapid Response">Brit Cops: Rapid Response III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Action-packed documentary following rapid response officers, the fastest cops in Britain, as they crack down on crime. Time is of the essence!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 12:00:00" d="2019-08-22 13:00:00"><n u="Brit Cops: Rapid Response">Brit Cops: Rapid Response III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Action-packed documentary following rapid response officers, the fastest cops in Britain, as they crack down on crime. Time is of the essence!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 13:00:00" d="2019-08-22 14:00:00"><n u="Paramedics">Paramedics I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series following Australia's ambulance crews. Taz and Amanda treat a swimmer who collapses after leaving a sauna. Matt helps a two-year-old</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 14:00:00" d="2019-08-22 15:00:00"><n u="Paramedics">Paramedics I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series following Australia's ambulance crews. Mark and Carina race to help a critically injured paraglider who's crashed into a cliff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 15:00:00" d="2019-08-22 16:00:00"><n u="Paramedics">Paramedics I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series following Australia's ambulance crews. Mark and Carina race to save a young woman struggling to breathe from a severe asthma attack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 16:00:00" d="2019-08-22 16:30:00"><n u="Border Security: Canada's Front Line">Border Security: Canada's Front Line III (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cameras follow the tireless work of agents as they intercept suspicious characters and contraband on Canada's borders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 16:30:00" d="2019-08-22 17:00:00"><n u="Border Security: Canada's Front Line">Border Security: Canada's Front Line III (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join dedicated teams of agents at Canada's airports and seaports as they intercept visitors smuggling illegal contraband and tourists with tall stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 17:00:00" d="2019-08-22 17:30:00"><n u="Border Security: Canada's Front Line">Border Security: Canada's Front Line III (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join agents at Canada's airports, seaports and borders in a revealing look at life on the front lines of national security</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 17:30:00" d="2019-08-22 18:00:00"><n u="Border Security: Canada's Front Line">Border Security: Canada's Front Line III (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cameras follow the tireless work of agents as they intercept suspicious characters and contraband on Canada borders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 18:00:00" d="2019-08-22 18:30:00"><n u="Border Security: Canada's Front Line">Border Security: Canada's Front Line III (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Go behind the scenes at Canada's Border Services Agency, where suspicious stories, smugglers and strange contraband make every day different for its staff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 18:30:00" d="2019-08-22 19:00:00"><n u="Border Security: Canada's Front Line">Border Security: Canada's Front Line III (26)</n><t>S</t>    <k>There's never a dull moment for agents policing Canada's borders. Join them as they intercept suspicious characters and strange contraband</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 19:00:00" d="2019-08-22 19:30:00"><n u="Border Security: Canada's Front Line">Border Security: Canada's Front Line III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Follow Canadian border services agents on the frontlines of national security. A traveller who's spent a long time abroad gets busted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 19:30:00" d="2019-08-22 21:00:00"><n u="New: My Kitchen Rules Australia">New: My Kitchen Rules Australia X (39)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Victor and G hope to stay in the kitchen and out of the drama, but when dinner is served, a revelation at the table leaves Piper heartbroken</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 21:00:00" d="2019-08-22 22:00:00"><n u="Criminal Minds">Criminal Minds IV (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Big Wheel
A videotape from a serial killer detailing one of his crimes carries a hidden message asking for help to stop his murderous ways</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 22:00:00" d="2019-08-22 23:00:00"><n u="New: FBI">New: FBI I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Crossfire
The team hunts for an active sniper with an elusive motive, but as the body count continues to rise, it's a race against time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-22 23:00:00" d="2019-08-23 00:00:00"><n u="Criminal Minds: Serial Killers">Criminal Minds: Serial Killers II (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% No Way Out, Part II
The Evilution Of Frank: Gideon tries to convince a murderer to reveal the whereabouts of a woman he abducted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-23 00:00:00" d="2019-08-23 01:00:00"><n u="Criminal Minds">Criminal Minds VII (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Divining Rod
The BAU must act quickly when a serial killer is executed and a copycat begins killing in the same fashion in the same Oklahoma town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-23 01:00:00" d="2019-08-23 02:00:00"><n u="The Killer Clown: World's Most Evil Killers">The Killer Clown: World's Most Evil Killers I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>One of the most prolific serial killers in US history, John Wayne Gacy was a well liked member of his community who secretly killed 33 boys and young men</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-23 02:00:00" d="2019-08-23 03:00:00"><n u="World's Most Evil Killers">World's Most Evil Killers I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>. vil Killers. Fritz Honka
An account of German serial killer Fritz Honka, whose insecurities over his height and peculiar sexual habits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-23 03:00:00" d="2019-08-23 04:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Astonishing footage including a man who takes his frustrations out on the camera when the police corner him, and a dramatic cross country police pursuit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2019-08-23 04:00:00" d="2019-08-23 05:00:00"><n u="Brit Cops: War On Crime">Brit Cops: War On Crime V (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Explosive documentary following Lincolnshire cops as they fight crime across one of the UK's largest counties</k>  </p>
</a>
