<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2020-05-30 04:39:30"><p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 05:00:00" d="2020-06-06 06:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars V (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Thames Valley Police provide a fascinating insight into car crime and its prevention. Plus, shocking video footage captures dangerous drivers in action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 06:00:00" d="2020-06-06 07:00:00"><n u="Brit Cops: Law &amp; Disorder">Brit Cops: Law &amp; Disorder IV (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series charting the exploits of the City of London police, charged with safeguarding the Square Mile at the heart of the crime-ridden capital</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 07:00:00" d="2020-06-06 08:00:00"><n u="UK Border Force">UK Border Force (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The series going behind the scenes of immigration continues with rush hour at Calais. Officers search UK-bound lorries for illegal immigrants, with today's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 08:00:00" d="2020-06-06 09:00:00"><n u="UK Border Force">UK Border Force (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A routine passport control check at Heathrow's Terminal 3 turns into a marathon investigation. And a cleaning company is raided during a search for illegal immigrants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 09:00:00" d="2020-06-06 09:30:00"><n u="The Real A &amp; E">The Real A &amp; E II (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>When a heart attack victim collapses on the top of Warwick Castle, he finds himself at the centre of a complicated and troublesome airlift rescue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 09:30:00" d="2020-06-06 10:00:00"><n u="The Real A &amp; E">The Real A &amp; E II (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A keen horsewoman has to be airlifted to hospital after being kicked by a friend's steed. Back at the hospital it takes an operation and 25 stitches</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 10:00:00" d="2020-06-06 10:30:00"><n u="Children's Hospital">Children's Hospital I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary shining a light on the brave young patients and dedicated staff of the Royal Manchester Children's Hospital</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 10:30:00" d="2020-06-06 11:00:00"><n u="Children's Hospital">Children's Hospital I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary shining a light on the brave young patients and dedicated staff of the Royal Manchester Children's Hospital</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 11:00:00" d="2020-06-06 12:00:00"><n u="Air Ambulance ER">Air Ambulance ER I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The team are called to a building site to treat a roofer who has suffered a fall. Plus, alternative transport is required to reach a teenage asthmatic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 12:00:00" d="2020-06-06 13:00:00"><n u="Air Ambulance ER">Air Ambulance ER I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The team take to the skies to treat a boy knocked over by a car in the Isle of Wight, before helping a hard-as-nails granny with an ankle injury. Last in series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 13:00:00" d="2020-06-06 14:00:00"><n u="Sun, Sea And A&amp;E">Sun, Sea And A&amp;E II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bomb
Documentary series following the misfortunes of British holidaymakers who find themselves recuperating in hospital rather than soaking up the sun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 14:00:00" d="2020-06-06 15:00:00"><n u="Caught On Dashcam">Caught On Dashcam II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Outrageous road disasters and highway hijinks, captured on video via people's in-vehicle dashboard cameras</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 15:00:00" d="2020-06-06 15:30:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare VII (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% The observational documentary series goes to the frontline of Australia's defence against customs, quarantine and immigration violations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 15:30:00" d="2020-06-06 16:00:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare VII (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Cameras join officers from Australia's airports, harbours and mail services as they protect the nation from drug smugglers, illegal products and unusual creepy-crawlies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 16:00:00" d="2020-06-06 16:30:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare VII (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% The officers protecting Australia's borders see some very unusual things. Cameras capture first-hand how they deal with drug-runners, smugglers and strange creepy-crawlies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 16:30:00" d="2020-06-06 17:00:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare VII (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% The fly-on-the-wall documentary joins the men and women who enforce Australia's customs, quarantine and immigration laws at the nation's airports and harbours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 17:00:00" d="2020-06-06 17:30:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare VII (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Cameras join officers from Australia's airports, harbours and mail services as they protect the nation from drug-smugglers, illegal products and unusual creepy-crawlies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 17:30:00" d="2020-06-06 18:00:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare VII (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% The fly-on-the-wall documentary joins the men and women who enforce Australia's customs, quarantine and immigration laws at the nation's airports and harbours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 18:00:00" d="2020-06-06 18:30:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare VII (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% The fly-on-the-wall documentary joins the men and women who enforce Australia's customs, quarantine and immigration laws at the nation's airports and harbours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 18:30:00" d="2020-06-06 19:00:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare VII (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Cameras join officers from Australia's airports, harbours and mail services as they protect the nation from drug-smugglers, illegal products and unusual creepy-crawlies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 19:00:00" d="2020-06-06 19:30:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare VII (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% The observational documentary series goes to the frontline of Australia's defence against customs, quarantine and immigration violations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 19:30:00" d="2020-06-06 20:00:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare VII (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% The officers protecting Australia's borders see some very unusual things. Cameras capture how they deal with drug-runners, smugglers and strange creepy-crawlies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 20:00:00" d="2020-06-06 21:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods V (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Power Of The Press
The New York cop drama returns as Frank faces a backlash after an officer's body camera malfunctions during an altercation with a civilian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 21:00:00" d="2020-06-06 22:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods V (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Under The Gun
Danny and Baez investigate the murders of three prominent community leaders. At home, Danny and Linda disagree about her carrying a gun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 22:00:00" d="2020-06-06 23:00:00"><n u="9-1-1">9-1-1 III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. The Searchers
The first responders race to save lives following the devastating tsunami, while Buck worries as Christopher goes missing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2020-06-06 23:00:00" d="2020-06-07 02:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods X (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% New &amp; Exclusive. Fog of War
Danny and Baez enlist the help of Texas Ranger Waylon Gates as they search for the Lone Star Killer</k>  </p>
</a>
