<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="30" t="2021-07-09 07:15:56"><p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 05:00:00" d="2021-07-16 06:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars V (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Elite cops Rosie and Darren are at the centre of a dramatic manhunt through the back gardens of a posh estate while Chris and Simon face a notorious</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 06:00:00" d="2021-07-16 07:00:00"><n u="Brit Cops: Law &amp; Disorder">Brit Cops: Law &amp; Disorder IV (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series charting the exploits of the City of London police, charged with safeguarding the Square Mile at the heart of the crime-ridden capital</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 07:00:00" d="2021-07-16 07:30:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare I (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 07:30:00" d="2021-07-16 08:00:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare I (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 08:00:00" d="2021-07-16 08:30:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare I (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 08:30:00" d="2021-07-16 09:00:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare I (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 09:00:00" d="2021-07-16 09:30:00"><n u="Border Patrol">Border Patrol IX (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New Zealand reality series following the work of customs officers as they prevent drug smuggling, illegal immigrants and more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 09:30:00" d="2021-07-16 10:00:00"><n u="Border Patrol">Border Patrol IX (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New Zealand reality series following the work of customs officers as they prevent drug smuggling, illegal immigrants and more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 10:00:00" d="2021-07-16 11:00:00"><n u="The Real A &amp; E">The Real A &amp; E II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>When a teenager is admitted after suffering nosebleeds, doctors fear the return of a disfiguring disease. Meanwhile, a woman is left injured after being kicked by a horse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 11:00:00" d="2021-07-16 12:00:00"><n u="Sun, Sea And A&amp;E">Sun, Sea And A&amp;E II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Drowning
Documentary series following the misfortunes of British holidaymakers who find themselves recuperating in hospital rather than soaking up the sun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 12:00:00" d="2021-07-16 13:00:00"><n u="Law &amp; Order">Law &amp; Order XII (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>77% Missing
A love affair is exposed when the distraught parents of a 24-year-old missing woman urge the detectives to find her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 13:00:00" d="2021-07-16 14:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation IX (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>77% Woulda, Shoulda, Coulda
Las Vegas based forensic drama. The CSIs investigate a murder in which the prime suspect was also implicated in a homicide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 14:00:00" d="2021-07-16 15:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods II (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Leap Of Faith
Danny investigates when a wealthy woman dies of an apparent heart attack and her daughter claims she received a message from God saying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 15:00:00" d="2021-07-16 16:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods II (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Parenthood
A shooting causes the Reagans to debate how far they would go to protect their family, while Frank faces a dilemma following arrests at a student protest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 16:00:00" d="2021-07-16 17:00:00"><n u="The Real A &amp; E">The Real A &amp; E II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A father of five almost loses his manhood when the motorcycle he is sitting on bursts into flames. Meanwhile, a 12-year-old champion gymnast fears</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 17:00:00" d="2021-07-16 18:00:00"><n u="Stop Search Seize">Stop Search Seize I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Ireland's Customs teams as they, with the help of the Irish police, try to stop organised smugglers from bringing drugs, cars and even exotic animals into the country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 18:00:00" d="2021-07-16 18:30:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare XV (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% When a Chinese bulk carrier docks in Newcastle it appears there's been a major security breach and what the Border Force officers find is shocking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 18:30:00" d="2021-07-16 19:00:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare XV (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Border Force investigate the claims of two people who claim to be on their honeymoon when their travel itinerary raises alarm bells</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 19:00:00" d="2021-07-16 19:30:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare XV (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% A man struggles to explain what his plans are for a three-month trip to Australia, and suspicion heightens when a drug dog takes an interest in his bag</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 19:30:00" d="2021-07-16 20:00:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare XV (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Officers stop a Vietnamese man wearing very unusual jewellery. Another man claims he has nothing to declare but an inspection proves he is lying. a lot!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 20:00:00" d="2021-07-16 20:30:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare XV (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% An alarming X-ray of a package at the mail centre leaves the Wildlife team rushing to get it open before it's too late. A young man is caught out by the drug detector dog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 20:30:00" d="2021-07-16 21:00:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare XV (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Officers investigate the suspicious luggage of a man returning from China and Vietnam. Drug detector dog Vulcan makes an amazing find</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 21:00:00" d="2021-07-16 22:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% A Night On The Town
Danny attempts to juggle an investigation with trying to enjoy a romantic weekend with Linda, while Jamie goes deep undercover into a crime family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 22:00:00" d="2021-07-16 23:00:00"><n u="New: Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit">New: Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit XXII (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Hunt, Trap, Rape and Release
The SVU team up with Lt Barek and the Bronx SVU to investigate a complex serial rape case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 23:00:00" d="2021-07-17 00:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods VIII (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Common Ground
A case turns personal for Danny when he works to protect a nurse from her violent ex-boyfriend. Jamie and Eddy help to deliver a baby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-17 00:00:00" d="2021-07-17 01:00:00"><n u="Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit XXI (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>80% Can't Be Held Accountable
The SVU team spring into action to help a detective who suspects his daughters are being groomed by a predator</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-17 01:00:00" d="2021-07-17 02:00:00"><n u="Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit XXI (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>80% Must Be Held Accountable
Rollins finds herself in danger as a distraught father takes desperate measures to avenge his daughters' rapist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-17 02:00:00" d="2021-07-17 03:00:00"><n u="9-1-1">9-1-1 IV (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>77% New &amp; Exclusive. Buck Begins
The 118 races to save the lives of workers trapped in a factory fire. A painful family secret pushes Buck to confront his childhood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-17 03:00:00" d="2021-07-17 04:00:00"><n u="9-1-1: Lone Star">9-1-1: Lone Star II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% New &amp; Exclusive. Difficult Conversations
Owen and Gwyn discuss their future, while Grace and Carlos must save a woman in a dangerous domestic abuse situation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-17 04:00:00" d="2021-07-17 05:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars V (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Officers raid a huge cannabis plantation with over 650 plants, enough to harvest ?25,000 of weed a week, while cops hunt down two burglars on the run in Ascot</k>  </p>
</a>
