<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="30" t="2021-07-09 07:15:45"><p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 05:00:00" d="2021-07-15 06:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars V (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Officers Chris Piggott and Simon Hills are on the receiving end of a load of grief from a violent suspect they think has been trying to break into a car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 06:00:00" d="2021-07-15 07:00:00"><n u="Brit Cops: Law &amp; Disorder">Brit Cops: Law &amp; Disorder IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series charting the exploits of the City of London police, charged with safeguarding the Square Mile at the heart of the crime-ridden capital</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 07:00:00" d="2021-07-15 07:30:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 07:30:00" d="2021-07-15 08:00:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 08:00:00" d="2021-07-15 08:30:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare I (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 08:30:00" d="2021-07-15 09:00:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Fly-on-the-wall documentary series following the men and women who defend Australia from drug runners, illegal immigrants and terrorists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 09:00:00" d="2021-07-15 09:30:00"><n u="Border Patrol">Border Patrol IX (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New Zealand reality series following the work of customs officers as they prevent drug smuggling, illegal immigrants and more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 09:30:00" d="2021-07-15 10:00:00"><n u="Border Patrol">Border Patrol IX (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New Zealand reality series following the work of customs officers as they prevent drug smuggling, illegal immigrants and more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 10:00:00" d="2021-07-15 11:00:00"><n u="The Real A &amp; E">The Real A &amp; E II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>More real-life medical drama as an ambulance crew come to the aid of a motorcyclist trapped under a truck, and doctors tend to an injured bodybuilder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 11:00:00" d="2021-07-15 12:00:00"><n u="Sun, Sea And A&amp;E">Sun, Sea And A&amp;E II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Swine Flu
Documentary series following the misfortunes of British holidaymakers who find themselves recuperating in hospital rather than soaking up the sun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 12:00:00" d="2021-07-15 13:00:00"><n u="Law &amp; Order">Law &amp; Order XII (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>77% Dr 1-102
The detectives track down a double-homicide suspect and find they have taken a hostage, compelling Southerlyn to risk both her life and career in a heroic move</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 13:00:00" d="2021-07-15 14:00:00"><n u="CSI: Crime Scene Investigation">CSI: Crime Scene Investigation IX (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>77% Say Uncle
Las Vegas-based forensic drama. A gangster-style shooting in Koreatown leaves a man and woman dead, and no witnesses will come forward</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 14:00:00" d="2021-07-15 15:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods II (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% The Uniform
Danny and Jackie investigate a murder at a diner where a witness claims a uniformed officer fled the scene after shots were fired</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 15:00:00" d="2021-07-15 16:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods II (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% The Job
Danny's family are caught in the crossfire when he confronts an armed man, while Frank is haunted by memories of 9/11. Oscar winner F Murray Abraham guest stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 16:00:00" d="2021-07-15 17:00:00"><n u="The Real A &amp; E">The Real A &amp; E II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>When a teenager is admitted after suffering nosebleeds, doctors fear the return of a disfiguring disease. Meanwhile, a woman is left injured after being kicked by a horse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 17:00:00" d="2021-07-15 18:00:00"><n u="Stop Search Seize">Stop Search Seize I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Join Ireland's Customs teams as they, with the help of the Irish police, try to stop organised smugglers from bringing drugs, cars and even exotic animals into the country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 18:00:00" d="2021-07-15 18:30:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare XV (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Things go from bad to worse for a young man when drugs are found in his bag and his fiancee is left further unimpressed by what is revealed next</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 18:30:00" d="2021-07-15 19:00:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare XV (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% A woman shocks the team with an incredible revelation as her bags are searched when a drug detector dog raises the alarm. A nervous passenger attracts attention</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 19:00:00" d="2021-07-15 19:30:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare XV (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% The contents of a young woman from China's suitcase could have catastrophic results for an entire industry. Two brothers claiming to be tourists are caught out in a lie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 19:30:00" d="2021-07-15 20:00:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare XV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% A nervous man claims he has arrived to visit his wife for their wedding anniversary but what's in his luggage may spell the end of his trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 20:00:00" d="2021-07-15 20:30:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare XV (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% A man from Amsterdam says he's here for a holiday, but his suspicious travel itinerary through China and an empty suitcase seem to tell a very different story</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 20:30:00" d="2021-07-15 21:00:00"><n u="Nothing To Declare">Nothing To Declare XV (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Three visitors from Malaysia raise alarms when it emerges that they've cancelled their accommodation just before their flight and their lies begin to unravel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 21:00:00" d="2021-07-15 22:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Innocence
Erin reopens an 18-year-old rape case, in which Frank was the original arresting officer, while Danny and Jackie investigate the murder of three teenagers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 22:00:00" d="2021-07-15 23:00:00"><n u="New: The Rookie">New: The Rookie III (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New &amp; Exclusive. Brave Heart
Nolan and his ex-wife must come together to help their son when he collapses and is rushed to hospital</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-15 23:00:00" d="2021-07-16 00:00:00"><n u="Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit VIII (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>80% Cage
Detective Beck is in over her head when an accident involving two foster children leads to a serious investigation and the death of another child</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 00:00:00" d="2021-07-16 01:00:00"><n u="Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit XXI (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>80% Counselor, It's Chinatown
The SVU joins forces with an undercover task force to take down a human trafficking ring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 01:00:00" d="2021-07-16 02:00:00"><n u="Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit XXI (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>80% We Dream of Machine Elves
Benson helps the victims of drugging and assault separate their hallucinations from their memories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 02:00:00" d="2021-07-16 03:00:00"><n u="Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit">Law &amp; Order: Special Victims Unit XXII (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>80% New &amp; Exclusive. The Long Arm of the Witness
When a powerful judge dismisses a rape case, Carisi investigates the judge's own history of sexual assault</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 03:00:00" d="2021-07-16 04:00:00"><n u="Blue Bloods">Blue Bloods VIII (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% New &amp; Exclusive. Brushed Off
When a famous basketball player is found dead of an apparent overdose, Danny looks into his possible ties to a local drug gang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1065" o="2021-07-16 04:00:00" d="2021-07-16 05:00:00"><n u="Road Wars">Road Wars V (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>This observational documentary returns for a fifth series following the Thames Valley Police. Officers hit the jackpot in Slough's biggest ever drugs raid</k>  </p>
</a>
