<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2020-04-10 04:30:53"><p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-17 05:00:00" d="2020-04-17 06:00:00"><n u="Homicide: Hours To Kill">Homicide: Hours To Kill II (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Blood Money
True crime documentary series following determined investigators as they piece together events during the critical 24-hour window after a crime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-17 06:00:00" d="2020-04-17 07:00:00"><n u="Fear Thy Neighbour">Fear Thy Neighbour III (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Bonfire of Blood
A neighbourly feud over road access ends in a murder that rocked a Californian town to its core</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-17 07:00:00" d="2020-04-17 08:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter VI (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Rearview Mirror
When a retired military man runs over a pedestrian, it's up to lieutenant Joe Kenda to determine if it was an accident or cold-blooded murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-17 08:00:00" d="2020-04-17 09:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>My, My, Merry Christmas
Joe Kenda solves the baffling murder of a popular man in Colorado Springs when his enquiries lead him to a relative with a long criminal history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-17 09:00:00" d="2020-04-17 10:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XVIII (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% Bloody Valentine/Storm Warning
A young father is shot dead in Tulsa, and a home invasion leaves one teenager killed and two wounded in Atlanta</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-17 10:00:00" d="2020-04-17 11:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XVII (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% Shattered Glass
Detective Greg Johnson fights to prove he has enough evidence to convict a man he believes beat a young mother to death in her New Orleans home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-17 11:00:00" d="2020-04-17 12:00:00"><n u="Unusual Suspects">Unusual Suspects VII (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Last Dance
A look at how Virginia detectives used science and cunning to catch the killer of 16-year-old ballet dancer Meghan Landowski in 2008</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-17 12:00:00" d="2020-04-17 13:00:00"><n u="Homicide: Hours To Kill">Homicide: Hours To Kill II (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Blood Money
True crime documentary series following determined investigators as they piece together events during the critical 24-hour window after a crime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-17 13:00:00" d="2020-04-17 14:00:00"><n u="Suzy Lamplugh: Crimes That Shook Britain">Suzy Lamplugh: Crimes That Shook Britain VI (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A look at the case of estate agent Suzy Lamplugh, who showed a client round a house in Fulham in July 1986 and was never seen again. Dermot Murnaghan hosts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-17 14:00:00" d="2020-04-17 15:00:00"><n u="Nightmare In Suburbia">Nightmare In Suburbia II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Walk In The Dark
The tragic story of Rachel Moran, who went missing on New Year's Day, 2004, sparking a mass police search in Hull which would</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-17 15:00:00" d="2020-04-17 16:00:00"><n>Murder For Hire</n>    <k>The Other Woman: The police send a salesman undercover when the girlfriend of their colleague goes shopping for a hit man - but the operation quickly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-17 16:00:00" d="2020-04-17 17:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter VI (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Jekyll &amp; Hyde
Lieutenant Joe Kenda looks for answers in the death of a young man stabbed and left for dead on the roadside. Meanwhile, a woman is shot in the face</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-17 17:00:00" d="2020-04-17 18:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Preying On The Innocent
When the son of a prominent politician is murdered in his basement, Lt Joe Kenda feels pressure from City Hall to solve the case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-17 18:00:00" d="2020-04-17 19:00:00"><n u="On The Case...">On The Case... VIII (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Predator in Deerfield
A young mum and her six-month baby vanish in a quiet neighbourhood. For investigators and locals, it's the start of a terrifying murder mystery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-17 19:00:00" d="2020-04-17 19:30:00"><n u="Motive To Murder">Motive To Murder I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Speed Freak Killers
A drug-fuelled killing spree terrorises a small California town. Police believe they are dealing with a serial killer who lives quietly among them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-17 19:30:00" d="2020-04-17 20:00:00"><n u="Motive To Murder">Motive To Murder I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mysogynist Murderer
Detectives in a small Australian town attempt to track down a sadistic killer when residents start finding bodies of dead women in rural locations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-17 20:00:00" d="2020-04-17 20:30:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series exposing murderers who have brazenly shown their faces on TV and in the media while secretly knowing they had blood on their hands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-17 20:30:00" d="2020-04-17 21:00:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series exposing murderers who have brazenly shown their faces on TV and in the media while secretly knowing they had blood on their hands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-17 21:00:00" d="2020-04-18 00:00:00"><n u="Fear Thy Neighbour">Fear Thy Neighbour I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lies, Lawns &amp; Murder
An almighty neighbourhood feud ignites in North Carolina when a retired Vietnam veteran sells off a piece of his land to a young family</k>  </p>
</a>
