<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-05-12 04:32:09"><p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-19 05:00:00" d="2020-05-19 05:30:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (49)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Vicious Vixen
When mum-to-be Cindy is killed in a horrifying night-time attack, police discover that not everyone was excited about her and boyfriend Mark's new arrival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-19 05:30:00" d="2020-05-19 06:00:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (50)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Killer Swingers
Police untangle a web of secret passions and lies when surveillance footage captures two mysterious figures leaving the scene of a man's murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-19 06:00:00" d="2020-05-19 07:00:00"><n u="On The Case With Paula Zahn">On The Case With Paula Zahn IX (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% New. Good Morning, Goodnight And Goodbye
When a 16-year-old girl vanishes, police consider the terrifying possibility that she may have been kidnapped</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-19 07:00:00" d="2020-05-19 08:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter IV (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Eye Of The Beholder
Lieutenant Joe Kenda encounters a horrendous crime scene, but his hunt leads him to the most unexpected of killers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-19 08:00:00" d="2020-05-19 09:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter III (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Limbrick
Detectives uncover a cold-blooded conspiracy as they investigate the murder of a church-going mother found dead on the floor by her young son</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-19 09:00:00" d="2020-05-19 10:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XXI (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% The Lost Boys
Detective John Brown races the clock when an innocent grandma is gunned down in Tulsa. Could teenagers be behind her tragic death?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-19 10:00:00" d="2020-05-19 11:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XVIII (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% Bad Love
In Tulsa, a young woman is brutally gunned down in broad daylight. Detective Justin Ritter suspects the witnesses know more than they are saying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-19 11:00:00" d="2020-05-19 12:00:00"><n u="Unusual Suspects">Unusual Suspects VIII (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Kill Now, Pay Later
When an arrest is made in the contract killing of a California businessman, police discover that's just the beginning of the story</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-19 12:00:00" d="2020-05-19 13:00:00"><n u="Homicide: Hours To Kill">Homicide: Hours To Kill II (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mayhem on His Mind
True crime documentary series following determined investigators as they piece together events during the critical 24-hour window after a crime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-19 13:00:00" d="2020-05-19 14:00:00"><n u="Sutcliffe: Crimes That Shook Britain">Sutcliffe: Crimes That Shook Britain III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The story of Yorkshire Ripper Peter Sutcliffe, who murdered 13 women during a five-year killing spree that began in 1975</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-19 14:00:00" d="2020-05-19 15:00:00"><n u="When Missing Turns To Murder">When Missing Turns To Murder I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lorraine Benson
The parents of Lorraine Benson revisit the moment their missing daughter's body was found. Meanwhile, Met police investigators</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-19 15:00:00" d="2020-05-19 16:00:00"><n u="Killing Spree">Killing Spree I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Michael Ryan
A closer look at the 1987 Hungerford massacre, in which 27-year-old unemployed labourer Michael Ryan fatally shot 16 people, before dying by suicide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-19 16:00:00" d="2020-05-19 17:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mr LA
When a young man is shot dead at a house party, Lt Joe Kenda must interview countless suspects until a weird clue leads him to a self-styled gangster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-19 17:00:00" d="2020-05-19 18:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Six Feet Under
Detectives encounter endless suspicious characters as they investigate the murder of a young woman found dead in the back of her car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-19 18:00:00" d="2020-05-19 19:00:00"><n u="On The Case With Paula Zahn">On The Case With Paula Zahn IX (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% New. Good Morning, Goodnight And Goodbye
When a 16-year-old girl vanishes, police consider the terrifying possibility that she may have been kidnapped</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-19 19:00:00" d="2020-05-19 19:30:00"><n u="Motive To Murder">Motive To Murder I (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A psychological look into some of the real-life murder cases that have made headlines around the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-19 19:30:00" d="2020-05-19 20:00:00"><n u="Motive To Murder">Motive To Murder I (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Makeover Murder
The story of former beauty queen Michele MacNeill, who was found dead in her bathtub amid rumours her doctor husband was having an affair</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-19 20:00:00" d="2020-05-19 20:30:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (51)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Calculated
A happy couple are found murdered with a baby cradled in their arms. Could a bitter online feud be to blame? Police investigate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-19 20:30:00" d="2020-05-19 21:00:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (52)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Deadly Homecoming
It looked like a typical robbery, but things were far from what they seemed when Navy officer Cory Voss was shot at a cash machine after months at sea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-19 21:00:00" d="2020-05-19 22:00:00"><n u="New: On The Case With Paula Zahn">New: On The Case With Paula Zahn IX (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Smoke And Lies
Police discover the savage and sinister truth about a 'residential house fire' that killed 67-year-old Gwen Bewley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-19 22:00:00" d="2020-05-19 23:00:00"><n u="New: Buried In The Backyard">New: Buried In The Backyard II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Living in Fear
A story of identity theft takes an even darker turn, as detectives make a chilling discovery and must retrace the final steps of a terrified man</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-19 23:00:00" d="2020-05-20 02:00:00"><n u="Shallow Grave">Shallow Grave I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Blood Brothers
The shocking story of two men who brutally murdered their half-brother before burying his mutilated body in dense woodland near Aldershot</k>  </p>
</a>
