<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-05-13 04:32:13"><p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-20 05:00:00" d="2020-05-20 05:30:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (51)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Calculated
A happy couple are found murdered with a baby cradled in their arms. Could a bitter online feud be to blame? Police investigate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-20 05:30:00" d="2020-05-20 06:00:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (52)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Deadly Homecoming
It looked like a typical robbery, but things were far from what they seemed when Navy officer Cory Voss was shot at a cash machine after months at sea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-20 06:00:00" d="2020-05-20 07:00:00"><n u="On The Case With Paula Zahn">On The Case With Paula Zahn IX (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% New. Smoke And Lies
Police discover the savage and sinister truth about a 'residential house fire' that killed 67-year-old Gwen Bewley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-20 07:00:00" d="2020-05-20 08:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mr LA
When a young man is shot dead at a house party, Lt Joe Kenda must interview countless suspects until a weird clue leads him to a self-styled gangster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-20 08:00:00" d="2020-05-20 09:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Six Feet Under
Detectives encounter endless suspicious characters as they investigate the murder of a young woman found dead in the back of her car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-20 09:00:00" d="2020-05-20 10:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XXI (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% The Predator
Every hour is crucial for sergeant James Dousay when the discovery of a woman's body suggests a depraved serial killer has struck Harris County</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-20 10:00:00" d="2020-05-20 11:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XVIII (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% Broken Home
New Orleans detectives race to find the perpetrator after a young mother is ambushed in her own home and shot at close range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-20 11:00:00" d="2020-05-20 12:00:00"><n u="Unusual Suspects">Unusual Suspects VIII (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Silent Night
When a young woman is found murdered in her Oregon apartment on Christmas Day, investigators soon learn the terrifying truth about her killer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-20 12:00:00" d="2020-05-20 13:00:00"><n u="Homicide: Hours To Kill">Homicide: Hours To Kill II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. A Family Affair
A businessman's last 24 hours alive prove critical as detectives hunt for the killer who shot him dead in his bed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-20 13:00:00" d="2020-05-20 14:00:00"><n u="Crimes That Shook Britain">Crimes That Shook Britain I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>77% Beverley Allitt was thought to be a 'model' nurse. Very astute, caring and always willing to help, why did she murder four children and attempt to kill 11 others?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-20 14:00:00" d="2020-05-20 15:00:00"><n u="When Missing Turns To Murder">When Missing Turns To Murder I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Natalie Hemming
The tragic story of the murder of Milton Keynes mum Natalie Hemming whose body was found three weeks after she went missing in 2016</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-20 15:00:00" d="2020-05-20 16:00:00"><n u="Killing Spree">Killing Spree I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Andrew Cunanan
A profile of the American serial killer who murdered at least five people, including fashion designer Gianni Versace and Chicago tycoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-20 16:00:00" d="2020-05-20 17:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter IV (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Dead Weight
A seemingly random attack that left a woman dead is investigated. New evidence and a cryptic note, however, reveal more to the case than initially suspected</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-20 17:00:00" d="2020-05-20 18:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Devoy
Lieutenant Joe Kenda makes a controversial decision during a murder investigation. His choice riles his team, but will his instincts prove right?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-20 18:00:00" d="2020-05-20 19:00:00"><n u="On The Case With Paula Zahn">On The Case With Paula Zahn IX (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% New. Smoke And Lies
Police discover the savage and sinister truth about a 'residential house fire' that killed 67-year-old Gwen Bewley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-20 19:00:00" d="2020-05-20 19:30:00"><n u="Motive To Murder">Motive To Murder I (27)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A psychological look into some of the real-life murder cases that have made headlines around the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-20 19:30:00" d="2020-05-20 20:00:00"><n u="Motive To Murder">Motive To Murder I (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A psychological look into some of the real-life murder cases that have made headlines around the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-20 20:00:00" d="2020-05-20 20:30:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series exposing murderers who have brazenly shown their faces on TV and in the media while secretly knowing they had blood on their hands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-20 20:30:00" d="2020-05-20 21:00:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series exposing murderers who have brazenly shown their faces on TV and in the media while secretly knowing they had blood on their hands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-20 21:00:00" d="2020-05-20 22:00:00"><n u="New: On The Case With Paula Zahn">New: On The Case With Paula Zahn IX (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. A Handful of Coins
The brutal murder of a loving mother leaves detectives baffled and a community outraged, until an unlikely eyewitness provides a vital clue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-20 22:00:00" d="2020-05-20 23:00:00"><n u="New: A Killer's Mistake">New: A Killer's Mistake II (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Sheila LaBarre
A vulnerable man thinks he's found true love when he shacks up with a wealthy, charismatic older woman. until things take a deadly turn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-05-20 23:00:00" d="2020-05-21 02:00:00"><n u="I Killed My BFF">I Killed My BFF III (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Deadly Waters
When a DJ inherits his father's fortune, he and his best friend have a falling out, resulting in a violent showdown, a grisly murder and a frantic manhunt</k>  </p>
</a>
