<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-05-29 04:33:16"><p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 05:00:00" d="2020-06-05 05:30:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series exposing murderers who have brazenly shown their faces on TV and in the media while secretly knowing they had blood on their hands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 05:30:00" d="2020-06-05 06:00:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (26)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series exposing murderers who have brazenly shown their faces on TV and in the media while secretly knowing they had blood on their hands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 06:00:00" d="2020-06-05 07:00:00"><n u="On The Case With Paula Zahn">On The Case With Paula Zahn IX (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% Taken from her Bed
A terrified mother wakes to discover that her eight-year-old daughter has disappeared from her bedroom in the middle of the night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 07:00:00" d="2020-06-05 08:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter IV (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Colorado Springs police detective Joseph Kenda investigates another brutal homicide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 08:00:00" d="2020-06-05 09:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter III (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Master Key
When a pregnant mother and her young sons are brutally murdered, pressure mounts on Lt Joe Kenda and the CSPD to catch the monster who did it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 09:00:00" d="2020-06-05 10:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XVII (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% Shattered Glass
Detective Greg Johnson fights to prove he has enough evidence to convict a man he believes beat a young mother to death in her New Orleans home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 10:00:00" d="2020-06-05 11:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XVIII (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% MIA
Detective Matt Frazier and the rest of the team suspect foul play when an Oklahoma welder vanishes under very suspicious circumstances</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 11:00:00" d="2020-06-05 12:00:00"><n u="Unusual Suspects">Unusual Suspects V (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mother's Day Murders
When a military wife and her two girls are found dead, police uncover many suspects, including a babysitter and an eyewitness who can't be trusted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 12:00:00" d="2020-06-05 13:00:00"><n u="Homicide: Hours To Kill">Homicide: Hours To Kill II (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Three's a Crowd
If he'd kept his mouth shut, teacher Desiree Sunford's killer would have got away with murder. A look into how her shooter was brought to justice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 13:00:00" d="2020-06-05 14:00:00"><n u="Murdertown">Murdertown II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Darlington
Katherine Kelly explores cannibal killer David Harker. One of the UK's most disturbed psychopaths, his crime rocked Darlington, causing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 14:00:00" d="2020-06-05 15:00:00"><n u="What The Killer Did Next">What The Killer Did Next I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Helen Bailey
Philip Glenister delves into the mindset of a murderer and explores their actions, starting with the disappearance of children's author Helen Bailey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 15:00:00" d="2020-06-05 16:00:00"><n u="Buried In The Backyard">Buried In The Backyard I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Murder House
A California couple's dream garden makeover turns into a nightmare when landscapers find a body. It's the start of a shocking murder case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 16:00:00" d="2020-06-05 17:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter IV (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Colorado Springs police detective Joseph Kenda investigates another brutal homicide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 17:00:00" d="2020-06-05 18:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter III (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bump In The Night
While working on a grisly case, Lt Joe Kenda finds a connection between the slain pilot and her killer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 18:00:00" d="2020-06-05 19:00:00"><n u="On The Case with Paula Zahn">On The Case with Paula Zahn VIII (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% Murder in Store
In San Antonio, a video game store manager is murdered in an apparent robbery gone wrong. But detectives are troubled by the evidence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 19:00:00" d="2020-06-05 19:30:00"><n u="Motive To Murder">Motive To Murder I (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Killer Nurse
At hospitals in New Jersey and Pennsylvania, patients are mysteriously dying. Then a rumour spreads that a serial killer is at work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 19:30:00" d="2020-06-05 20:00:00"><n u="Motive To Murder">Motive To Murder I (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A psychological look into some of the real-life murder cases that have made headlines around the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 20:00:00" d="2020-06-05 20:30:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (28)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Friends with Killer Benefits
Derrick Dorsey screams suicide when his wife is found dead. But police find bullet holes in the wall. and zip ties around her wrists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 20:30:00" d="2020-06-05 21:00:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (27)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Secrets Can Kill
When police informant Susan Smith vanishes, her sister points the finger at her mystery boyfriend. As time goes by, it starts to look like she was right</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 21:00:00" d="2020-06-05 22:00:00"><n u="On The Case With Paula Zahn">On The Case With Paula Zahn IX (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% A Bridge Too Far
Police must comb through the last few hours that a popular teenager spent alive when her lifeless body is discovered under a bridge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 22:00:00" d="2020-06-05 22:30:00"><n u="New: PD Cam">New: PD Cam III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Ride shotgun with officers across America as the pursuit of suspects throws them into breakneck car chases, crazy stand-offs and heated gunfights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 22:30:00" d="2020-06-05 23:00:00"><n u="New: PD Cam">New: PD Cam III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Ride shotgun with officers across America as the pursuit of suspects throws them into breakneck car chases, crazy stand-offs and heated gunfights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-06-05 23:00:00" d="2020-06-06 02:00:00"><n u="Court Cam">Court Cam I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A judge chases down defendants attempting an escape. Another criminal brandishes an unlikely weapon in the courtroom</k>  </p>
</a>
