<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2019-08-11 01:29:08"><p id_tv="1066" o="2019-08-17 05:00:00" d="2019-08-17 06:00:00"><n u="Unusual Suspects">Unusual Suspects IV (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Blood Trail
A tiny clue leads investigators to the unlikely man behind the murder of 22-year-old Theresa Wesolowski, who was found stabbed 46 times in Germantown in 1999</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2019-08-17 06:00:00" d="2019-08-17 06:30:00"><n u="Motive To Murder">Motive To Murder I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Texas Teen Love Triangle
When the body of a beautiful Texas school girl is discovered, rumours buzz around the high school that a killer is walking the halls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2019-08-17 06:30:00" d="2019-08-17 07:00:00"><n u="Motive To Murder">Motive To Murder I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>South African Strangler
Detectives get to work on a shocking case when a mass grave of women is discovered just outside of Johannesburg, South Africa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2019-08-17 07:00:00" d="2019-08-17 08:00:00"><n u="On The Case With Paula Zahn">On The Case With Paula Zahn VII (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% New. A Killer Among Friends
When a teenager is found savagely murdered, police must retrace her last steps alive to identify her killer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2019-08-17 08:00:00" d="2019-08-17 09:00:00"><n u="On The Case With Paula Zahn">On The Case With Paula Zahn VII (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% Gone in an Instant
Police are left baffled as young women continue to disappear out of their Kansas City area apartments. Paula Zahn investigates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2019-08-17 09:00:00" d="2019-08-17 09:30:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (42)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. The Barefoot Killer
Years after Carolyn Krizan-Wilson's husband was shot by a mysterious burglar, her dementia leads her to reveal strange clues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2019-08-17 09:30:00" d="2019-08-17 10:00:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (40)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Intent to Kill
Jack Jessee's battle against cancer is cut short when he's stabbed at home. This was no random robbery, yet all the suspects have cast-iron alibis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2019-08-17 10:00:00" d="2019-08-17 11:00:00"><n u="Motives &amp; Murders">Motives &amp; Murders I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>He Came For Me
Detectives reveal how DNA evidence led them to 15-year-old Nanine Grimes' killer, 25 years after she was stabbed more than 80 times in her home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2019-08-17 11:00:00" d="2019-08-17 11:30:00"><n u="Motive To Murder">Motive To Murder I (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Snuff Film Killer
When the body of 41-year-old Marsha Spicer is discovered in Missouri, police discover her links to an ex-con who had a fantasy to make a snuff film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2019-08-17 11:30:00" d="2019-08-17 12:00:00"><n u="Motive To Murder">Motive To Murder I (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Killer Nurse
At hospitals in New Jersey and Pennsylvania, patients are mysteriously dying. Then a rumour spreads that a serial killer is at work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2019-08-17 12:00:00" d="2019-08-17 13:00:00"><n u="Murdertown">Murdertown I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Watford
Happy Valley actress Katherine Kelly examines the tragic case of Anne Cook, who was stabbed to death by Leon Amos while she was out walking her dog in Watford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2019-08-17 13:00:00" d="2019-08-17 14:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XX (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>82% A Fighting Chance
Tulsa detective Ronnie Leatherman searches for answers, when an argument at a local bar ends with a young social activist shot 16 times</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2019-08-17 14:00:00" d="2019-08-17 15:00:00"><n u="Crimes That Shook Britain">Crimes That Shook Britain VI (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>78% The Moors Murders
A look at the crimes of Myra Hindley and Ian Brady, featuring interviews with the family of Keith Bennett, who are still campaigning to find his body</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2019-08-17 15:00:00" d="2019-08-17 16:00:00"><n u="Crimes That Shook Britain">Crimes That Shook Britain III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>78% A hard-hitting look at the murder of Rachel Nickell, who was sexually assaulted and murdered in front of her two-year-old son on Wimbledon Common in 1992</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2019-08-17 16:00:00" d="2019-08-17 17:00:00"><n u="Nightmare In Suburbia">Nightmare In Suburbia I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Night Of Betrayal
Durham couple George and Christina Button lived a happy life, but Christina was secretly mounting up debts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2019-08-17 17:00:00" d="2019-08-17 18:00:00"><n u="Homicide: Hours To Kill">Homicide: Hours To Kill II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>No Sleep for the Wicked
True crime documentary series following determined investigators as they piece together events during the critical 24-hour window after a crime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2019-08-17 18:00:00" d="2019-08-17 19:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mr LA
When a young man is shot dead at a house party, Lt Joe Kenda must interview countless suspects until a weird clue leads him to a self-styled gangster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2019-08-17 19:00:00" d="2019-08-17 20:00:00"><n u="Murder For Hire">Murder For Hire I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. The Other Woman
The police send a salesman undercover when the girlfriend of their colleague goes shopping for a hit man - but the operation quickly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2019-08-17 20:00:00" d="2019-08-17 21:00:00"><n u="Buried In The Backyard">Buried In The Backyard I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The House on Canyon Road
Detectives uncover a scheming family and a decades-old murder plot when a dismembered skeleton is unearthed in a Seattle backyard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2019-08-17 21:00:00" d="2019-08-17 22:00:00"><n u="Snapped: Women Who Kill">Snapped: Women Who Kill XII (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Constance Clark
The chilling story of an Atlanta woman who masterminded a plot to have her husband killed in an effort to cash in on a life insurance policy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2019-08-17 22:00:00" d="2019-08-18 01:00:00"><n u="New: Sex, Lies &amp; Murder">New: Sex, Lies &amp; Murder I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. The Texas Cadet Murders
When a teenage girl is found beaten and shot to death in Texas, the pressure is on police to figure out who she is, who killed her and why</k>  </p>
</a>
