<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="20" t="2021-07-13 04:57:47"><p id_tv="1066" o="2021-07-20 05:00:00" d="2021-07-20 06:00:00"><n u="On The Case With Paula Zahn">On The Case With Paula Zahn IX (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>72% New. A Face and A Voice
When a school teacher is murdered in her home, police must rely on the testimony of a young eye witness who saw the killer outside her home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2021-07-20 06:00:00" d="2021-07-20 07:00:00"><n u="I Lived With A Killer">I Lived With A Killer I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Donnie Brasco And Lefty Guns
When 'Lefty Guns' Ruggiero's life is made into Hollywood film Donnie Brasco, his granddaughter makes it her mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2021-07-20 07:00:00" d="2021-07-20 08:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter VIII (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Trigger
Kenda thinks he's chasing a promising lead as he investigates a mysterious shooting, but it soon emerges that he's barking up the wrong tree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2021-07-20 08:00:00" d="2021-07-20 09:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter VII (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. With Friends Like This
A gang member, a jealous lover or a complete stranger? Kenda and Anderson hunt for a killer who shot a young man outside his home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2021-07-20 09:00:00" d="2021-07-20 10:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48</n>    <k>New. Soldier Down/Blood Vendetta: In Atlanta, a young father is gunned down in cold blood at an abandoned car wash. Meanwhile, a Gulf War veteran is found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2021-07-20 10:00:00" d="2021-07-20 11:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XXII (26)</n><t>S</t>    <k>82% New. The Invader
A father of three is shot dead in front of his family during a bloodsoaked crime spree. Cops race to catch the killer before he can strike again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2021-07-20 11:00:00" d="2021-07-20 12:00:00"><n u="On The Case With Paula Zahn">On The Case With Paula Zahn IX (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>72% Blood Secrets
When a beloved grandmother is savagely murdered in her own home, investigators draw blanks and the case goes cold. Until a family secret emerges</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2021-07-20 12:00:00" d="2021-07-20 13:00:00"><n u="I Lived With A Killer">I Lived With A Killer I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. The San Francisco Witch Killers
The daughter of Michael Bear Carson speaks out about her childhood at the hands of her witching-killing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2021-07-20 13:00:00" d="2021-07-20 14:00:00"><n u="Buried in the Woods">Buried in the Woods III (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Friend Left Behind
A party in the woods takes a chilling turn when someone goes missing, and with the summer thaw comes a shocking discovery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2021-07-20 14:00:00" d="2021-07-20 15:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter VII (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Who took Heather?
Years after a girl vanished, a shocking discovery reopens her unsolved case. But just as detectives think they've cracked it, a strange letter turns up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2021-07-20 15:00:00" d="2021-07-20 16:00:00"><n u="Homicide: Hours To Kill">Homicide: Hours To Kill II (26)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Follow the Money
When a church-going businessman is shot to death in his home, police discover he had a ruthless side that contradicted his squeaky-clean image</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2021-07-20 16:00:00" d="2021-07-20 17:00:00"><n u="Unusual Suspects">Unusual Suspects VII (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Little Girl Gone
The 1988 case of a missing nine-year-old girl went cold until an encounter at a bus stop breathed new life into the investigation and revealed the truth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2021-07-20 17:00:00" d="2021-07-20 18:00:00"><n u="Killer Britain With Dermot Murnaghan">Killer Britain With Dermot Murnaghan I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lewis Daynes
The case of Lewis Daynes, who, at the age of 18, was sentenced to life in prison for the fatal stabbing of 14-year-old Breck Bednar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2021-07-20 18:00:00" d="2021-07-20 19:00:00"><n u="When Missing Turns To Murder">When Missing Turns To Murder I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Shafilea Ahmed
Years after the disappearance of 17-year-old Shafilea Ahmed in Warrington in 2003, her sister provided testimony that saw her parents convicted of murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2021-07-20 19:00:00" d="2021-07-20 20:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48</n>    <k>Night Run: When a young father is ambushed by a group of brazen shooters, Atlanta detective Summer Benton uncovers the shocking reason for his murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2021-07-20 20:00:00" d="2021-07-20 21:00:00"><n u="Buried in the Woods">Buried in the Woods III (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Deadly Premonition
A college graduate has a bright future ahead of her, until her car is found abandoned and a psychic's vision adds more terror to the tale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2021-07-20 21:00:00" d="2021-07-20 22:00:00"><n>New: Meet, Marry, Murder</n>    <k>New. Angela Taylor: A 69-year-old Hertfordshire millionaire caught up in a bitter feud with his estranged wife pays the ultimate price</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2021-07-20 22:00:00" d="2021-07-20 23:00:00"><n u="New: Buried In The Backyard">New: Buried In The Backyard III (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Saint and Sinner
When a former Catholic priest-turned-realtor vanishes from Florida, detectives uncover a murder-for-hire scheme masterminded</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2021-07-20 23:00:00" d="2021-07-21 00:00:00"><n u="What Happened To Ashley &amp; Lauria">What Happened To Ashley &amp; Lauria (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>. ell in the Heartland. The Fire
A fire rips through the Freeman family home in December 1999. Things take an even darker turn when only two out of four bodies are found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2021-07-21 00:00:00" d="2021-07-21 03:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter VII (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Who took Heather?
Years after a girl vanished, a shocking discovery reopens her unsolved case. But just as detectives think they've cracked it, a strange letter turns up</k>  </p>
</a>
