<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2020-04-09 04:30:23"><p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-16 05:00:00" d="2020-04-16 06:00:00"><n u="Homicide: Hours To Kill">Homicide: Hours To Kill II (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Keep Friends Close, Enemies Closer
Detectives investigate a fatal acid attack, uncovering a deadly neighbourhood feud and a manipulative mastermind with a horrific plan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-16 06:00:00" d="2020-04-16 07:00:00"><n u="Fear Thy Neighbour">Fear Thy Neighbour III (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Night of the Machete
Arguments overs music and pets lead to a violent rampage that kicks off in an apartment building when two young couples come to blows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-16 07:00:00" d="2020-04-16 08:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter VI (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bad Moon Rising
On the night before Halloween, a nightmare unfolds as a young man is found clinging to life. Then lieutenant Joe Kenda learns there's a second victim</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-16 08:00:00" d="2020-04-16 09:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter V (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Settle the Score
The investigation of a man's murder initially indicates that he was shot over a musical instrument, but Kenda digs deeper and determines the actual cause</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-16 09:00:00" d="2020-04-16 10:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XVIII (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% Knock Knock
In Tulsa, a man from out of town is found dead in his motel room and detective Michael Zenoni must wade through a web of secrets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-16 10:00:00" d="2020-04-16 11:00:00"><n u="The First">The First 48 XVII (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% Red Brick/Last Kiss
Detectives in Cleveland investigate the murder of an elderly grandmother, while in Dallas, a man is shot to death in his car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-16 11:00:00" d="2020-04-16 12:00:00"><n u="Unusual Suspects">Unusual Suspects VII (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Absent Teacher
In 1993, a primary school teacher went missing after her first day at a new job. Over the next two months, investigators pieced together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-16 12:00:00" d="2020-04-16 13:00:00"><n u="Homicide: Hours To Kill">Homicide: Hours To Kill II (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Keep Friends Close, Enemies Closer
Detectives investigate a fatal acid attack, uncovering a deadly neighbourhood feud and a manipulative mastermind with a horrific plan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-16 13:00:00" d="2020-04-16 14:00:00"><n u="Shipman: Crimes That Shook Britain">Shipman: Crimes That Shook Britain I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>65% . ritain. Doctor Harold Shipman was convicted of killing 15 patients in 2000, but he is thought to have killed up to 215. Discover how he was eventually</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-16 14:00:00" d="2020-04-16 15:00:00"><n u="Nightmare In Suburbia">Nightmare In Suburbia IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Cruellest Cut
Series revealing the dark side of Britain's quiet suburbs, beginning with Greenford, London, where 28-year-old Geeta Aulakh was murdered in 2009</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-16 15:00:00" d="2020-04-16 16:00:00"><n>Murder For Hire</n>    <k>New. An Ex-Wife's Revenge: A therapist blackmails her patient into finding a hitman to kill her husband, but gets a surprise when they enlist an undercover officer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-16 16:00:00" d="2020-04-16 17:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter VI (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Rearview Mirror
When a retired military man runs over a pedestrian, it's up to lieutenant Joe Kenda to determine if it was an accident or cold-blooded murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-16 17:00:00" d="2020-04-16 18:00:00"><n u="Homicide Hunter">Homicide Hunter II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>My, My, Merry Christmas
Joe Kenda solves the baffling murder of a popular man in Colorado Springs when his enquiries lead him to a relative with a long criminal history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-16 18:00:00" d="2020-04-16 19:00:00"><n u="On The Case with Paula Zahn">On The Case with Paula Zahn VIII (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>72% That's Him
Paula's on the hunt for answers when a hail of gunfire leaves a car salesman dead on his front porch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-16 19:00:00" d="2020-04-16 19:30:00"><n u="Motive To Murder">Motive To Murder I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Pickaxe Murders
Houston, Texas, is rocked by a grisly crime scene - a man whose head is practically hammered off his body and a semi-nude woman riddled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-16 19:30:00" d="2020-04-16 20:00:00"><n u="Motive To Murder">Motive To Murder I (28)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A psychological look into some of the real-life murder cases that have made headlines around the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-16 20:00:00" d="2020-04-16 20:30:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series exposing murderers who have brazenly shown their faces on TV and in the media while secretly knowing they had blood on their hands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-16 20:30:00" d="2020-04-16 21:00:00"><n u="Killer In Plain Sight">Killer In Plain Sight I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Documentary series exposing murderers who have brazenly shown their faces on TV and in the media while secretly knowing they had blood on their hands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1066" o="2020-04-16 21:00:00" d="2020-04-17 00:00:00"><n u="New: Fear Thy Neighbour">New: Fear Thy Neighbour III (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New. Bonfire of Blood
A neighbourly feud over road access ends in a murder that rocked a Californian town to its core</k>  </p>
</a>
