<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2019-08-15 22:53:58"><p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-21 05:00:00" d="2019-08-21 07:00:00"><n>Mind Blown</n>    <k>A secret government programme in psychotronic warfare goes wrong, and the Department of Defence attempts to kill everyone involved. Fleeing for his life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-21 07:00:00" d="2019-08-21 08:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: Voyager">Star Trek: Voyager IV (13/26)</n>    <k>Waking Moments
Marauding aliens put the crew to sleep, but Chakotay's knowledge of dreams helps him keep his eyes open long enough to save the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-21 08:00:00" d="2019-08-21 09:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: Voyager">Star Trek: Voyager IV (14/26)</n>    <k>Message in a Bottle
Seven stumbles across a deserted Starfleet vessel on the edge of the Alpha Quadrant, so the crew tries to send a message</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-21 09:00:00" d="2019-08-21 12:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n>    <k>A chance for viewers to buy bargains galore at home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-21 12:00:00" d="2019-08-21 13:00:00"><n u="Merlin">Merlin III (1/13)</n>    <k>The Tears of Uther Pendragon - Part One
A year after her disappearance, Morgana returns to Camelot, where a delighted Uther immediately announces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-21 13:00:00" d="2019-08-21 15:00:00"><n>Highlander III: The Final Dimension</n>    <k>Immortal Connor MacLeod has hung up his sword and settled down to family life, but the sudden reappearance of his arch-enemy Kane compels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-21 15:00:00" d="2019-08-21 16:00:00"><n u="Merlin">Merlin III (2/13)</n>    <k>The Tears of Uther Pendragon - Part Two
Part two of two. Following continued manipulation from Morgause, Cenred launches an attack on the citadel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-21 16:00:00" d="2019-08-21 17:00:00"><n u="Stargate Atlantis">Stargate Atlantis II (17/20)</n>    <k>Coup d'Etat
Sheppard and the team investigate the disappearance of an expedition from Atlantis, but soon become embroiled in a Genii coup</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-21 17:00:00" d="2019-08-21 18:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: Voyager">Star Trek: Voyager II (19/26)</n>    <k>Lifesigns
Romance blossoms in Voyager's sick bay as the Doctor creates a holographic clone to house the consciousness of an ailing Vidiian female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-21 18:00:00" d="2019-08-21 19:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: Voyager">Star Trek: Voyager II (20/26)</n>    <k>Investigations
Disillusioned by the inflexibility of Starfleet's regime, Tom Paris plans to leave Voyager and join a Talaxian convoy. When Neelix finds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-21 19:00:00" d="2019-08-21 20:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: The Next Generation">Star Trek: The Next Generation IV (9/26)</n>    <k>Final Mission
Wesley is accepted for Star Fleet Academy, but he must first join Picard on a final mission to sort out a mining dispute on Pentarus Five</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-21 20:00:00" d="2019-08-21 21:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: The Next Generation">Star Trek: The Next Generation IV (10/26)</n>    <k>The Loss
Counsellor Troi despairs at her inability to communicate with an alien force which proceeds to override the ship's controls, threatening</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-21 21:00:00" d="2019-08-21 22:00:00"><n u="Stargate Atlantis">Stargate Atlantis II (18/20)</n>    <k>Michael
A lieutenant awakes in Atlantis with no memory of his past or identity, but suffering from horrific nightmares. Dr Beckett explains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-21 22:00:00" d="2019-08-21 23:00:00"><n u="Killjoys">Killjoys V (5/10)</n>    <k>A Bout, A Girl
Dutch enters the deadly Supermax prison and fights her way to the top as she seeks a chance to take over the entire ship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-21 23:00:00" d="2019-08-22 02:00:00"><n>The Fountain</n>    <k>A scientist strives to find a cure for his dying wife's illness, while in the 16th-century a conquistador battles to locate the fountain of youth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-22 02:00:00" d="2019-08-22 03:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: The Next Generation">Star Trek: The Next Generation III (16/26)</n>    <k>The Offspring
Data creates a daughter in the form of an android named Lal. However, when she starts showing signs of a more evolved consciousness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-22 03:00:00" d="2019-08-22 04:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: The Next Generation">Star Trek: The Next Generation III (17/26)</n>    <k>Sins of the Father
Worf is pleased when his brother Kurn arrives on the Enterprise as part of an exchange programme - but his happiness is soon shattered</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-22 04:00:00" d="2019-08-22 07:00:00"><n u="Siren">Siren II (11/15)</n>    <k>Mixed Signals
A mermaid-obsessed town is turned upside down when a mysterious girl appears and begins wreaking havoc. Drama, starring Alex Roe and Eline Powell</k>  </p>
</a>
