<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="17" t="2019-07-11 00:21:08"><p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-16 05:00:00" d="2019-07-16 07:00:00"><n>Tornado Warning</n>    <k>An amateur storm chaser and a meteorologist discover strange tornados across the world are a cover for an alien invasion. Sci-fi thriller, starring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-16 07:00:00" d="2019-07-16 08:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: Voyager">Star Trek: Voyager I (9/16)</n>    <k>Emanations
An away team searching for a new atomic power source discovers a number of bodies covered in what look like cobwebs, and Kim mysteriously disappears</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-16 08:00:00" d="2019-07-16 09:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: Voyager">Star Trek: Voyager I (10/16)</n>    <k>Prime Factors
The crew encounters an alien race that offers hope of a return home, but a friendly meeting between the two sides soon becomes a war of words</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-16 09:00:00" d="2019-07-16 12:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n>    <k>Generic NBC CHANNELS ONLY 
A chance for viewers to buy bargains galore at home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-16 12:00:00" d="2019-07-16 13:00:00"><n u="Merlin">Merlin I (1/13)</n>    <k>The Dragon's Call
Drama series charting the legendary wizard's formative years. Merlin's mother sends him to start a new life in Camelot, where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-16 13:00:00" d="2019-07-16 15:00:00"><n>Alien Convergence</n>    <k>When flying reptilian creatures wreak havoc across the globe, the only hope of stopping them is a new, state-of-the-art fighter jet. Thriller, starring Stephen Brown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-16 15:00:00" d="2019-07-16 16:00:00"><n u="Merlin">Merlin I (2/13)</n>    <k>Valiant
Knight Valiant arrives in Camelot to compete in the annual sword-fighting tournament, and Merlin realises the combatant has a ruse that could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-16 16:00:00" d="2019-07-16 17:00:00"><n u="Stargate Atlantis">Stargate Atlantis I (11/20)</n>    <k>The Eye
Part two of two. Major Sheppard does all he can to secure the crew's return home, as well as embarking upon a bold effort to rescue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-16 17:00:00" d="2019-07-16 18:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: Voyager">Star Trek: Voyager VII (10/26)</n>    <k>Flesh and Blood - Part Two
Part two of two. The Doctor reconsiders his decision to betray the ship. Sci-fi adventure, starring Robert Picardo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-16 18:00:00" d="2019-07-16 19:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: Voyager">Star Trek: Voyager VII (11/26)</n>    <k>Shattered
The ship is split into different time-frames leaving Chakotay to convince Janeway of what happened and save Voyager</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-16 19:00:00" d="2019-07-16 20:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: The Next Generation">Star Trek: The Next Generation II (6/22)</n>    <k>Loud as a Whisper
The crew transports a renowned negotiator to mediate in an interplanetary conflict</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-16 20:00:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: The Next Generation">Star Trek: The Next Generation II (5/22)</n>    <k>The Schizoid Man
Data's personality undergoes a transformation on his return from a remote planet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 22:00:00"><n u="Stargate Atlantis">Stargate Atlantis I (12/20)</n>    <k>The Defiant One
The crew investigates a mysterious satellite and discovers the wreckage of a Wraith ship on the planet below, prompting Sheppard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-16 22:00:00" d="2019-07-17 00:10:00"><n>Immortals</n>    <k>A man is chosen by the Greek gods to prevent a power-mad king from conquering the human and immortal worlds. Mythological adventure, with Henry Cavill and Mickey Rourke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-17 00:10:00" d="2019-07-17 03:40:00"><n>Heat</n>    <k>A detective becomes obsessed with capturing a highly intelligent career criminal who is planning one last robbery before his retirement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-17 03:40:00" d="2019-07-17 04:40:00"><n u="Star Trek: The Next Generation">Star Trek: The Next Generation I (1/26)</n>    <k>Encounter at Farpoint - Part One
Part one of two. Captain Jean-Luc Picard of the USS Enterprise-D and his crew go on their first mission, a quest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-17 04:40:00" d="2019-07-17 07:40:00"><n u="The Captains Close Up">The Captains Close Up I (1/5)</n>    <k>William Shatner
Chris Pine is joined by William Shatner, who chats about his role as Captain James T Kirk in the original Star Trek TV series and movies</k>  </p>
</a>
