<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="14" t="2019-08-13 02:28:43"><p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-18 05:00:00" d="2019-08-18 07:00:00"><n>Cold Zone</n>    <k>After finding frozen animals in the woods, a scientist must try to stop an apocalyptic bout of global freezing. Sci-fi, starring Martin Cummins, Kirsten</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-18 07:00:00" d="2019-08-18 08:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: Voyager">Star Trek: Voyager IV (7/26)</n>    <k>Scientific Method
The crew members begin to suffer from a perplexing array of illnesses, which Seven of Nine discovers are the result of cloaked aliens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-18 08:00:00" d="2019-08-18 09:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: Voyager">Star Trek: Voyager IV (8/26)</n>    <k>Year of Hell - Part One
Part one of two. Annorax, the Krenim's desperate leader, vows to manipulate time to alter the course of history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-18 09:00:00" d="2019-08-18 12:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n>    <k>A chance for viewers to buy bargains galore at home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-18 12:00:00" d="2019-08-18 14:00:00"><n>Monster Island</n>    <k>Gigantic monsters threaten to destroy everything in their path as mankind remains defenceless. Sci-fi thriller, starring Eric Roberts and Toshi Toda</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-18 14:00:00" d="2019-08-18 16:00:00"><n>Earthstorm</n>    <k>A comet smashes into the moon, causing devastating changes to tidal movements across the world. However, scientists discover this is only the beginning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-18 16:00:00" d="2019-08-18 18:00:00"><n>Sinbad: Legend of the Seven Seas</n>    <k>A swashbuckling hero has 10 days to recover a priceless book from a deceitful sea goddess or his friend will be executed. As he sets out on his quest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-18 18:00:00" d="2019-08-18 20:00:00"><n>Bedazzled</n>    <k>The Devil appears as a beautiful woman to a lovelorn computer buff and grants him seven wishes in exchange for his soul. However, he quickly discovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-18 20:00:00" d="2019-08-18 22:00:00"><n>Highlander III: The Final Dimension</n>    <k>Immortal Connor MacLeod has hung up his sword and settled down to family life, but the sudden reappearance of his arch-enemy Kane compels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-18 22:00:00" d="2019-08-19 00:10:00"><n>The Butterfly Effect</n>    <k>A college student discovers he can travel back in time to his troubled childhood and change future events for himself and his friends - but his meddling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-19 00:10:00" d="2019-08-19 02:20:00"><n>The Faculty</n>    <k>Six high-school students notice their teachers behaving strangely, and realise they have been replaced by shape-changing aliens who are planning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-19 02:20:00" d="2019-08-19 03:20:00"><n u="The Outpost">The Outpost II (5/13)</n>    <k>The Blade Of The Three
Talon, the lone survivor of a race called Blackbloods, seeks vengeance for her clan's slaughter. Fantasy adventure, starring Jessica Green</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-19 03:20:00" d="2019-08-19 04:30:00"><n u="Star Trek: The Next Generation">Star Trek: The Next Generation III (11/26)</n>    <k>The Hunted
Picard finds himself embroiled in the hunt for an escaped prisoner at an Angosian penal colony, only to discover a sinister secret involving the inmates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-08-19 04:30:00" d="2019-08-19 07:30:00"><n u="The Captains Close Up">The Captains Close Up I (3/5)</n>    <k>Avery Brooks
William Shatner offers a retrospective exploration of Avery Brooks' Captain Benjamin Sisko in Star Trek: Deep Space Nine</k>  </p>
</a>
