<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2019-07-11 00:21:08"><p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-15 05:00:00" d="2019-07-15 07:00:00"><n>Grimm's Snow White</n>    <k>A princess flees into a forest to escape from her stepmother, who wants to kill her so she can rule the kingdom. Fantasy adventure, starring Eliza Bennett and Jane March</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-15 07:00:00" d="2019-07-15 08:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: Voyager">Star Trek: Voyager I (7/16)</n>    <k>Eye of the Needle
The crew members discover a small wormhole and make contact with the Alpha Quadrant - raising hopes that they have found their path home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-15 08:00:00" d="2019-07-15 09:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: Voyager">Star Trek: Voyager I (8/16)</n>    <k>Ex Post Facto
Tom Paris is found guilty of murder by the courts of an unknown planet, but a mental implant in his brain prevents him remembering what really happened</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-15 09:00:00" d="2019-07-15 12:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n>    <k>Generic NBC CHANNELS ONLY 
A chance for viewers to buy bargains galore at home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-15 12:00:00" d="2019-07-15 13:00:00"><n u="Atlantis">Atlantis II (13/13)</n>    <k>The Queen Must Die - Part Two
Part two of two. Jason and his friends face treachery at every turn, and come to realise that the only hope for the future</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-15 13:00:00" d="2019-07-15 15:00:00"><n>Air Collision</n>    <k>A massive solar storm locks the US president's plane into a head-on collision course with a commercial jetliner. Action drama starring Reginald VelJohnson and Jordan Ladd</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-15 15:00:00" d="2019-07-15 16:00:00"><n u="Merlin">Merlin I (1/13)</n>    <k>The Dragon's Call
Drama series charting the legendary wizard's formative years. Merlin's mother sends him to start a new life in Camelot, where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-15 16:00:00" d="2019-07-15 17:00:00"><n u="Stargate Atlantis">Stargate Atlantis I (10/20)</n>    <k>The Storm
Part one of two. A hurricane bears down on the city, so the inhabitants evacuate - enabling the team's new-found enemy, the Genii, to colonise Atlantis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-15 17:00:00" d="2019-07-15 18:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: Voyager">Star Trek: Voyager VII (8/26)</n>    <k>Nightingale
Kim takes on his first command when he captains a damaged Kraylor ship in a bid to save the species' world. Garrett Wang stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-15 18:00:00" d="2019-07-15 19:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: Voyager">Star Trek: Voyager VII (9/26)</n>    <k>Flesh and Blood - Part One
Part one of two. The Hirogen make dangerous modifications to technology given to them by Janeway</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-15 19:00:00" d="2019-07-15 20:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: The Next Generation">Star Trek: The Next Generation II (3/22)</n>    <k>Elementary, Dear Data
Data uses the holodeck to assume the identity of Sherlock Holmes and travels back to Victorian London</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-15 20:00:00" d="2019-07-15 21:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: The Next Generation">Star Trek: The Next Generation II (4/22)</n>    <k>The Outrageous Okona
The crew comes to the rescue of a stricken cargo ship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-15 21:00:00" d="2019-07-15 22:00:00"><n u="Stargate Atlantis">Stargate Atlantis I (11/20)</n>    <k>The Eye
Part two of two. Major Sheppard does all he can to secure the crew's return home, as well as embarking upon a bold effort to rescue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-15 22:00:00" d="2019-07-15 23:00:00"><n>The Outpost</n>    <k>We Only Kill To Survive 
Season 2 Episode 1/

Talon, the lone survivor of a race called Blackbloods, seeks vengeance for her clan's slaughter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-15 23:00:00" d="2019-07-16 02:00:00"><n>Timecop</n>    <k>A federal agent goes back in time to track down a corrupt politician who has the power to manipulate history. Sci-fi adventure, starring Jean-Claude</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-16 02:00:00" d="2019-07-16 03:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: The Next Generation">Star Trek: The Next Generation VII (24/26)</n>    <k>Pre-emptive Strike
A homecoming celebration is interrupted when Federation ships attack a Cardassian vessel. Sci-fi drama, starring Patrick Stewart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-16 03:00:00" d="2019-07-16 04:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: The Next Generation">Star Trek: The Next Generation VII (25/26)</n>    <k>All Good Things - Part One
Part one of two. Captain Picard finds himself drifting between time warps while trying to save mankind. Futuristic drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1070" o="2019-07-16 04:00:00" d="2019-07-16 05:00:00"><n u="Star Trek: The Next Generation">Star Trek: The Next Generation VII (26/26)</n>    <k>All Good Things - Part Two
The final episode of the sci-fi drama. Picard enlists the help of Data to solve his time-travelling torment, and together</k>  </p>
</a>
