<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="36" t="2019-08-13 02:17:30"><p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 07:00:00" d="2019-08-18 07:10:00"><n u="Dino Dana">Dino Dana I (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>65% Face Your Fearosaurus
Dino Dana is an eight-year-old palaeontologist in training. Dana distracts a young boy stuck up a park slide with a story about a brachiosaurus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 07:10:00" d="2019-08-18 07:25:00"><n u="Super">Super 4 II (36)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Romancing the Opal
Dr X wants to steal a magic stone from the fairies that will give one of his robots unlimited energy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 07:25:00" d="2019-08-18 07:35:00"><n u="Super">Super 4 II (37)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Worlds Apart
When the Sykronians attack everywhere at once, the Super 4 split up and each head to different islands. But this is exactly what Sykronior wanted to happen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 07:35:00" d="2019-08-18 08:00:00"><n u="Thunderbirds Are Go">Thunderbirds Are Go II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Deep Search
Alan makes first contact with an alien lifeform when Thunderbird 3 is called out to a moon of Jupiter to save a pair of documentarians</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 08:00:00" d="2019-08-18 08:05:00"><n u="Mission Employable">Mission Employable I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Circus
A behind-the-scenes look at important jobs. Roll up, roll up, welcome to the circus! Agent Danny's mission is to take to the stage as a circus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 08:05:00" d="2019-08-18 08:15:00"><n u="Mr. Bean: The Animated Series">Mr. Bean: The Animated Series I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>67% Homeless
After a regrettable episode involving his landlady sleepwalking into his room, Mr Bean suddenly finds himself out on his ear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 08:15:00" d="2019-08-18 08:30:00"><n u="Mr. Bean: The Animated Series">Mr. Bean: The Animated Series I (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>67% Camping
An old photo album causes Bean to reminisce about summers at scout camp as a boy, and he plans a night under the stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 08:30:00" d="2019-08-18 08:55:00"><n u="Marvel's Avengers: Secret Wars">Marvel's Avengers: Secret Wars IV (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Westland
Hawkeye, Vision, and Wasp travel to the American Old West of 1872 to find a lost Doctor Strange</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 08:55:00" d="2019-08-18 09:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 II (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Xingo's Back
Left to entertain himself, Ben powers up an old Xingo arcade game. But he uses too much juice, and Xingo leaps out into the real world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 09:10:00" d="2019-08-18 09:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 II (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bounty Ball
While Gwen is listening to a boring lecture on the Transcontinental Railroad, Ben sneaks away to the gift shop looking for fun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 09:25:00" d="2019-08-18 09:30:00"><n>ITV News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world as well as the latest major sports results</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 09:30:00" d="2019-08-18 10:25:00"><n u="New: The Sara Cox Show">New: The Sara Cox Show (36)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sara Cox is here to keep you company on a Sunday morning along with her guests Cerys Matthews, author Joanna Trollope and Iain Broudie, with the Lightning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 10:25:00" d="2019-08-18 11:25:00"><n u="Ninja Warrior UK">Ninja Warrior UK V (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>49% In the first episode, members of the public compete alongside Jake Quickenden, Dom Lever, Katie Walsh and Lee Latchford-Evans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 11:25:00" d="2019-08-18 12:00:00"><n u="Zone of Champions">Zone of Champions (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Zone of Champions is the only place to catch sporting events such as Hamster Athletics and Using an Escalator for the Purposes of Banter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 12:00:00" d="2019-08-18 12:30:00"><n u="Countrywise: Guide to Britain">Countrywise: Guide to Britain VIII (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Fogle tours the Isles of Scilly, Liz Bonnin watches birds arriving on the Jurassic coast, and Victoria Pendleton joins the Household Cavalry on their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 12:30:00" d="2019-08-18 13:00:00"><n u="Best Walks with a View with Julia Bradbury">Best Walks with a View with Julia Bradbury I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The High Cup Walk, Cumbria
Travelogue. Julia sets off from the village of Dufton in search of High Cup Nick, a remarkable natural formation in the Pennines</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 13:00:00" d="2019-08-18 13:15:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 13:15:00" d="2019-08-18 15:15:00"><n u="Midsomer Murders">Midsomer Murders XIV (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>78% A Rare Bird
Barnaby and Jones investigate when a keen birdwatcher is killed. Was his obsession with ornithology to blame - or something more sinister?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 15:15:00" d="2019-08-18 16:00:00"><n u="Catchphrase">Catchphrase II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Richie, Rachael and Craig compete to guess familiar phrases hidden in animated clues, then one will go through to the Super Catchphrase for the chance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 16:00:00" d="2019-08-18 17:00:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable III (52)</n><t>S</t>    <k>We're So Nervous. 
Five members of a ukulele band answer a series of top 10 list questions as they attempt to win a bumper cash prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 17:00:00" d="2019-08-18 18:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point V (83)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 18:00:00" d="2019-08-18 19:00:00"><n u="The Chase: Celebrity Special">The Chase: Celebrity Special VI (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz show hosted by Bradley Walsh. Sarah Willingham, Shaun Ryder, Michelle Dewberry and Eddie Edwards join forces in the hope of beating a Chaser</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 19:00:00" d="2019-08-18 19:15:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world as well as the latest major sports results</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 19:15:00" d="2019-08-18 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 19:30:00" d="2019-08-18 20:30:00"><n u="New: Tipping Point: Lucky Stars">New: Tipping Point: Lucky Stars V (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard finds out if Rory Cowan, Kate Garraway and Gok Wan have what it takes to beat the extraordinary machine and win thousands of pounds for charity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 20:30:00" d="2019-08-18 21:30:00"><n u="The Comedy Years">The Comedy Years (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>2003
Comedy in 2003 saw Tim, Lee and Dawn's love triangle reach a memorable conclusion in The Office, while hidden camera shows such as Trigger Happy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 21:30:00" d="2019-08-18 23:20:00"><n u="Vera">Vera VIII (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Darkwater
DCI Vera Stanhope must scrutinise the fractured relationships of a community when the body of a teenage boy is found in a reservoir in a remote rural town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 23:20:00" d="2019-08-18 23:40:00"><n>ITV News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-18 23:40:00" d="2019-08-19 00:10:00"><n>The Best Little Prison in Britain? George Stores, responsible for running the prison shop, has a challenge; a female inmate has asked him to buy her some 'stretch denim butt enhancing ripped jeans'</n>    <k>Ep3</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 00:10:00" d="2019-08-19 00:40:00"><n u="Yorkshire Airport">Yorkshire Airport (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Every day up to 9,500 items of luggage pass though the baggage hall at Leeds Bradford, and baggage agent Johnny is on a mission to reunite these items with their owners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 00:40:00" d="2019-08-19 01:30:00"><n u="Deep Water">Deep Water I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lisa is delighted when Kate invites her to a dinner party, but the evening takes an unexpected turn when she meets Kate's charming brother-in-law</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 01:30:00" d="2019-08-19 01:55:00"><n u="Rescue - River Deep Mountain High">Rescue - River Deep Mountain High I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>On Croagh Patrick in County Mayo, the Mayo Mountain Rescue Team are gearing up for the annual religious pilgrimage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 01:55:00" d="2019-08-19 03:00:00"><n>Ideal World TV</n>    <k>Join Ideal World on ITV for some of the best offers and products on TV. To see more go to www.idealworld.tv</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 03:00:00" d="2019-08-19 04:00:00"><n>Ideal World With Fabulift</n>    <k>Join Ideal World on ITV for some of the best offers and products on TV. To see more go to www.idealworld.tv</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 04:00:00" d="2019-08-19 04:50:00"><n u="Motorsport UK">Motorsport UK (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Richard John Neil presents the show from Snetterton, with action from Round 9 of the Renault Clio Cup UK and Round 12 of the Michelin Ginetta Juniors</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 04:50:00" d="2019-08-19 06:05:00"><n>ITV Nightscreen</n>    <k>Text-based information service</k>  </p>
</a>
