<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2019-08-09 01:38:48"><p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-15 06:05:00" d="2019-08-15 07:00:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder V (113)</n><t>S</t>    <k>54% Hannah v Nicola
Studio courtroom show in which criminal barrister Robert Rinder rules on real life cases</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-15 07:00:00" d="2019-08-15 09:30:00"><n>Good Morning Britain</n>    <k>Breakfast show featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-15 09:30:00" d="2019-08-15 10:25:00"><n>Lorraine</n>    <k>Lorraine Kelly presents a topical mix of entertainment, discussion and showbiz glamour as well as the latest fashion, food and celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-15 10:25:00" d="2019-08-15 11:30:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder IV (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>54% Glen is claiming 3,400 pounds from his former friend Mark, a former salesman and wannabe writer, to whom he sold his classic Range Rover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-15 11:30:00" d="2019-08-15 13:30:00"><n u="This Morning">This Morning XXXI (162)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Magazine show with news and topical items, celebrity guests, expert advice, real life stories, competitions and a mix of cookery, health, beauty, lifestyle and more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-15 13:30:00" d="2019-08-15 14:30:00"><n>Loose Women</n>    <k>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-15 14:30:00" d="2019-08-15 14:55:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-15 14:55:00" d="2019-08-15 15:00:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-15 15:00:00" d="2019-08-15 16:00:00"><n u="Dickinson's Real Deal">Dickinson's Real Deal XIII (74)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Halesowen 2
Simon Schneider makes a splash with a walrus, Jon O'Marah gets a sinking feeling with some White Star Line plates, and Fay Rutter gets hooked</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-15 16:00:00" d="2019-08-15 17:00:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable III (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Young's Offenders
A team of five friends and family answer Top 10 list questions in a bid to top the Tenable Tower and win a cash prize. Hosted by Warwick Davis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-15 17:00:00" d="2019-08-15 18:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point V (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning its 10,000 pound jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-15 18:00:00" d="2019-08-15 19:00:00"><n u="The Chase">The Chase IX (104)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz show hosted by Bradley Walsh. Four contestants must pit their wits against the Chaser, a ruthless quiz genius. Michael, June, Karen and Elliott take on the Chaser</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-15 19:00:00" d="2019-08-15 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-15 19:30:00" d="2019-08-15 20:00:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-15 20:00:00" d="2019-08-15 20:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>Zak tries to hide his emotions. Marlon covers his troubles. Kerry urges Amy to move forwards</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-15 20:30:00" d="2019-08-15 21:00:00"><n u="New: Ross Kemp: Living With Online Gambling Addiction. Online Gambling Addiction">New: Ross Kemp: Living With Online Gambling Addiction. Online Gambling Addiction (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ross Kemp meets some of Britain's problem online gamblers, including Alex who has cut technology from his life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-15 21:00:00" d="2019-08-15 21:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>Faith reveals Bear's secret. Nate confronts Amy and Kerry. Cain is surprised by Matty's attitude</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-15 21:30:00" d="2019-08-15 22:00:00"><n u="New: Eat, Shop, Save">New: Eat, Shop, Save III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Presenter Ranvir Singh and her team of experts are in Bolton with the Vasta family, where new dad Vik urgently needs to get his health back under control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-15 22:00:00" d="2019-08-15 23:00:00"><n>David Walliams Presents Return of Alright on The Night</n>    <k>David Walliams presents Revenge of Alright on the Night - featuring a selection of classic outtakes and previously unseen bloopers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-15 23:00:00" d="2019-08-15 23:30:00"><n>ITV News at Ten</n>    <k>ITV News at Ten provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-15 23:30:00" d="2019-08-15 23:45:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-15 23:45:00" d="2019-08-16 00:45:00"><n u="Long Lost Family: What Happened Next">Long Lost Family: What Happened Next IV (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>This episode follows three stories of siblings brought together after decades apart, catching up with a man united with his siblings after 68 years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 00:45:00" d="2019-08-16 01:35:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable II (37)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Five dads from Watford answer Top 10 list questions on subjects including toys and games, Formula One, and the human body. Warwick Davis hosts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 01:35:00" d="2019-08-16 04:00:00"><n>Ideal World</n>    <k>Join Ideal World on ITV for some of the best offers and products on TV. To see more go to www.idealworld.tv</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 04:00:00" d="2019-08-16 04:25:00"><n u="Eat, Shop, Save">Eat, Shop, Save III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Presenter Ranvir Singh and her team of experts are in Bolton with the Vasta family, where new dad Vik urgently needs to get his health back under control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 04:25:00" d="2019-08-16 06:05:00"><n>ITV Nightscreen</n>    <k>Text-based information service</k>  </p>
</a>
