<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2019-08-10 01:40:32"><p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 06:05:00" d="2019-08-16 07:00:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder VI (48)</n><t>S</t>    <k>54% Narissa v Carl
Featuring a woman who hopes to reclaim a loan she made to a friend to help set up a business and a dispute between a landlord and his former tenant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 07:00:00" d="2019-08-16 09:30:00"><n>Good Morning Britain</n>    <k>Breakfast show featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 09:30:00" d="2019-08-16 10:25:00"><n>Lorraine</n>    <k>Lorraine Kelly presents a topical mix of entertainment, discussion and showbiz glamour as well as the latest fashion, food and celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 10:25:00" d="2019-08-16 11:30:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder III (69)</n><t>S</t>    <k>54% Judge Rinder presides over a case concerning the theft of a business idea and subsequent loss of earnings and another involving a dispute over money</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 11:30:00" d="2019-08-16 13:30:00"><n u="This Morning">This Morning XXXI (163)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Magazine show with news and topical items, celebrity guests, expert advice, real life stories, competitions and a mix of cookery, health, beauty, lifestyle and more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 13:30:00" d="2019-08-16 14:30:00"><n>Loose Women</n>    <k>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 14:30:00" d="2019-08-16 14:55:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 14:55:00" d="2019-08-16 15:00:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 15:00:00" d="2019-08-16 16:00:00"><n u="Dickinson's Real Deal">Dickinson's Real Deal XIII (77)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Newport 1
A huge teapot causes a stir with Jan Keyne, a famous rhinoceros stomps onto Tony Geering's table, and an amber necklace puts Mark Stevens's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 16:00:00" d="2019-08-16 17:00:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable III (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sweet Little Mistrys
A team of five old school friends take on the Tenable Tower as they tackle a series of Top 10 list questions for chance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 17:00:00" d="2019-08-16 18:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point V (42)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning its 10,000 pound jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 18:00:00" d="2019-08-16 19:00:00"><n u="The Chase">The Chase IX (103)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz show hosted by Bradley Walsh. Four contestants must pit their wits against the Chaser, a ruthless quiz genius. Phil, Beckie, Kathy and Af take on the Chaser</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 19:00:00" d="2019-08-16 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 19:30:00" d="2019-08-16 20:00:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 20:00:00" d="2019-08-16 20:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>Matty is determined to get revenge. Moira fears she's been caught out. Faith is grateful for Charity's offer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 20:30:00" d="2019-08-16 21:00:00"><n>Coronation Street</n>    <k>Steve offers support to a grieving Emma. Geoff gives Yasmeen news of her insurance payout. Ken hosts a bridge game in the Rovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 21:00:00" d="2019-08-16 21:30:00"><n u="New: Rescue - River Deep Mountain High">New: Rescue - River Deep Mountain High I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>On Croagh Patrick in County Mayo, the Mayo Mountain Rescue Team are gearing up for the annual religious pilgrimage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 21:30:00" d="2019-08-16 22:00:00"><n>Coronation Street</n>    <k>Steve keeps Tracy and Emma in the dark. Yasmeen comes under fire as the bridge game ends in chaos. Bernie and Michael team up to profit from Gemma's pregnancy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 22:00:00" d="2019-08-16 23:00:00"><n u="New: Lethal Weapon">New: Lethal Weapon III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Leo Getz Justice
Cole reflects upon his time working for the CIA as a person from the past makes a startling reappearance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 23:00:00" d="2019-08-16 23:30:00"><n>ITV News at Ten</n>    <k>ITV News at Ten provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 23:30:00" d="2019-08-16 23:45:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-16 23:45:00" d="2019-08-17 01:30:00"><n>Rambo: First Blood</n>    <k>Action adventure starring Sylvester Stallone and Richard Crenna, 1982. An ex-Green Beret does battle in the US wilds with a sadistic sheriff and his deputies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 01:30:00" d="2019-08-17 03:00:00"><n>Ideal World</n>    <k>Join Ideal World on ITV for some of the best offers and products on TV. To see more go to www.idealworld.tv</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 03:00:00" d="2019-08-17 04:00:00"><n>Ideal World</n>    <k>Join Ideal World on ITV for some of the best offers and products on TV. To see more go to www.idealworld.tv</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 04:00:00" d="2019-08-17 04:50:00"><n u="Saved">Saved (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Incredible stories of survival combined with dramatic reconstructions. A parachute jump goes drastically wrong and an elderly couple's holiday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 04:50:00" d="2019-08-17 07:00:00"><n>ITV Nightscreen</n>    <k>Text-based information service</k>  </p>
</a>
