<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2021-07-09 07:03:59"><p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-14 05:05:00" d="2021-07-14 06:05:00"><n>ITV Nightscreen</n>    <k>Text-based information service</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-14 06:05:00" d="2021-07-14 07:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point IX (58)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-14 07:00:00" d="2021-07-14 10:00:00"><n>Good Morning Britain</n>    <k>News, current affairs and lively debate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-14 10:00:00" d="2021-07-14 11:00:00"><n>Lorraine</n>    <k>Lorraine Kelly presents a topical mix of entertainment, discussion and showbiz glamour as well as the latest fashion, food and celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-14 11:00:00" d="2021-07-14 13:30:00"><n>This Morning</n>    <k>The This Morning team bring you top celebrity guests, lifestyle advice, stunning competitions and award-winning features, all topped off with a sprinkle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-14 13:30:00" d="2021-07-14 14:30:00"><n>Loose Women</n>    <k>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-14 14:30:00" d="2021-07-14 14:55:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-14 14:55:00" d="2021-07-14 15:00:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-14 15:00:00" d="2021-07-14 16:00:00"><n u="Dickinson's Real Deal">Dickinson's Real Deal XV (33)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Leeds 2
David's at Leeds United football club, James gets a red car over some footy caricature, Alison get revved up over some toys, and antiques</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-14 16:00:00" d="2021-07-14 17:00:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable III (57)</n><t>S</t>    <k>For What It's Butterworth
A family of five from Manchester answer a series of top 10 list questions as they attempt to top the Tenable Tower and win a cash prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-14 17:00:00" d="2021-07-14 18:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point VIII (143)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-14 18:00:00" d="2021-07-14 19:00:00"><n u="The Chase">The Chase XI (61)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bradley Walsh hosts the quiz show. All that stands between John, Andrea, Carol and Harry is the small matter of one of the country's finest quiz brains - the Chaser</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-14 19:00:00" d="2021-07-14 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-14 19:30:00" d="2021-07-14 20:00:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-14 20:00:00" d="2021-07-14 20:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>Mandy reads Jimmy the speech she's prepared. Jimmy is in turmoil. Cain's left thoughtful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-14 20:30:00" d="2021-07-14 21:00:00"><n>Coronation Street</n>    <k>Will turns up the heat on Todd. Eileen volunteers to help George after causing him an injury. Maria urges Fiz to go public in the local press</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-14 21:00:00" d="2021-07-14 21:30:00"><n u="New: Craig and Bruno's Great British Road Trips">New: Craig and Bruno's Great British Road Trips I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cornwall
In this episode, Craig and Bruno are on a Cornish adventure on one of the most scenic stretches of coastline in the UK</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-14 21:30:00" d="2021-07-14 22:00:00"><n>Coronation Street</n>    <k>Paul falls under suspicion for Todd's crime. Daisy invites herself along to Ryan's DJ gig. Emma and Curtis recruit models for the charity calendar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-14 22:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:00:00"><n>New: The Two Ronnies: Ronnie Corbett's Lost Tapes</n>    <k>A look back at the life and work of one of Britain's favourite comedians, Ronnie Corbett, one half of The Two Ronnies, with access to his family's archives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-14 23:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:30:00"><n>ITV News at Ten</n>    <k>ITV News provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-14 23:30:00" d="2021-07-14 23:45:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-14 23:45:00" d="2021-07-15 00:45:00"><n u="Diana's Decades">Diana's Decades I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The 1970s
Princess Diana was an icon who both captured and transformed the spirt of the times. Here we see how this thoroughly modern princess emerged in the 1970s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-15 00:45:00" d="2021-07-15 01:35:00"><n u="Tour De France Highlights">Tour De France Highlights (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Stage 17, Muret - Saint-Lary-Soulan Col du Portet
All of France will be hoping for a home winner as the Tour offers a mountain top finish in the Pyrenees</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-15 01:35:00" d="2021-07-15 04:00:00"><n>Shop: Ideal World</n>    <k>Join Ideal World on ITV for some of the best offers and products on TV. To see more go to www.idealworld.tv</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-15 04:00:00" d="2021-07-15 04:15:00"><n>FYI Extra</n>    <k>A short bulletin rounding up the day's stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-15 04:15:00" d="2021-07-15 06:05:00"><n>ITV Nightscreen</n>    <k>Text-based information service</k>  </p>
</a>
