<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2020-05-13 04:35:50"><p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-20 06:05:00" d="2020-05-20 07:00:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder VII (68)</n><t>S</t>    <k>53% Jan v Glenn
Jan is in court to claim 500 pounds for a refund on a sculpture he had commissioned for his wedding which he says did not fit the brief</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-20 07:00:00" d="2020-05-20 10:00:00"><n>Good Morning Britain</n>    <k>Breakfast show featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-20 10:00:00" d="2020-05-20 11:00:00"><n>Good Morning Britain with Lorraine</n>    <k>Lorraine Kelly joins the GMB team for an extra hour of Good Morning Britain, featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-20 11:00:00" d="2020-05-20 13:30:00"><n>This Morning</n>    <k>The This Morning team bring you top celebrity guests, lifestyle advice, stunning competitions and award-winning features, all topped off with a sprinkle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-20 13:30:00" d="2020-05-20 14:30:00"><n>Loose Women</n>    <k>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-20 14:30:00" d="2020-05-20 14:55:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-20 14:55:00" d="2020-05-20 15:00:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-20 15:00:00" d="2020-05-20 16:00:00"><n u="New: Judge Rinder">New: Judge Rinder VII (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Arbitration show in which real small-claims cases are adjudicated over within a studio courtroom by Judge Robert Rinder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-20 16:00:00" d="2020-05-20 17:00:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz show hosted by Warwick Davis. A team of five friends from Southampton answer more questions about Top 10 lists for the chance to win a big cash prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-20 17:00:00" d="2020-05-20 18:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point VI (43)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-20 18:00:00" d="2020-05-20 19:00:00"><n u="The Chase">The Chase X (103)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz show hosted by Bradley Walsh. Four contestants must pit their wits against the Chaser, a ruthless quiz genius determined to stop them winning the cash prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-20 19:00:00" d="2020-05-20 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-20 19:30:00" d="2020-05-20 20:00:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-20 20:00:00" d="2020-05-20 20:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>Harriet feels guilty. Leyla fears she's ruined things with Liam. Vinny tells Mandy that she will like his new friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-20 20:30:00" d="2020-05-20 21:00:00"><n>Coronation Street</n>    <k>Steve searches for a positive spin on Oliver's illness. Aggie insists on attending the bistro's re-opening. Sean encourages Gemma to share her story</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-20 21:00:00" d="2020-05-20 21:30:00"><n u="New: Absolutely India: Mancs in Mumbai">New: Absolutely India: Mancs in Mumbai (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Thomas's are on tour as they trade Mumbai for the sun, sea and sand of beautiful Goa. While there they track down another branch of their growing family tree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-20 21:30:00" d="2020-05-20 22:00:00"><n u="Paul O'Grady: For the Love of Dogs">Paul O'Grady: For the Love of Dogs VIII (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% Paul O'Grady meets some special dogs who need to go to unconventional homes, including a dog with star potential and a pointer cross who may have been shot at in the past</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-20 22:00:00" d="2020-05-21 01:00:00"><n u="New: Harry's Heroes: Euro Having a Laugh">New: Harry's Heroes: Euro Having a Laugh II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>It's the final leg of the Tour in Germany. And there's only a few days for Harry and John to get the team ready to take on our arch rivals in their own back yard</k>  </p>
</a>
