<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2021-07-13 05:01:37"><p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-20 05:05:00" d="2021-07-20 06:05:00"><n>ITV Nightscreen</n>    <k>Text-based information service</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-20 06:05:00" d="2021-07-20 07:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point IX (141)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-20 07:00:00" d="2021-07-20 10:00:00"><n>Good Morning Britain</n>    <k>News, current affairs and lively debate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-20 10:00:00" d="2021-07-20 11:00:00"><n>Lorraine</n>    <k>Lorraine Kelly presents a topical mix of entertainment, discussion and showbiz glamour as well as the latest fashion, food and celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-20 11:00:00" d="2021-07-20 13:30:00"><n>This Morning</n>    <k>The This Morning team bring you top celebrity guests, lifestyle advice, stunning competitions and award-winning features, all topped off with a sprinkle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-20 13:30:00" d="2021-07-20 14:30:00"><n>Loose Women</n>    <k>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-20 14:30:00" d="2021-07-20 14:55:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-20 14:55:00" d="2021-07-20 15:00:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-20 15:00:00" d="2021-07-20 16:00:00"><n u="Dickinson's Real Deal">Dickinson's Real Deal XV (26)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Blackpool 2
The dealers den pitches up in Blackpool, where Fay Rutter gets a piece of possessed wood. A knight on horseback fails to woo Jo Brayshaw</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-20 16:00:00" d="2021-07-20 17:00:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz show hosted by Warwick Davis. In this episode, a team made up of five account managers from Harrogate attempt to walk away with a big cash prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-20 17:00:00" d="2021-07-20 18:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point IX (142)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-20 18:00:00" d="2021-07-20 19:00:00"><n u="The Chase">The Chase XI (65)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bradley Walsh hosts the quiz show. All that stands between David, Alex, Lisa and Jack is the small matter of one of the country's finest quiz brains - the Chaser</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-20 19:00:00" d="2021-07-20 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-20 19:30:00" d="2021-07-20 20:00:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-20 20:00:00" d="2021-07-20 20:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>Drama set in the Yorkshire Dales with one of Britain's longest running and most beloved soaps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-20 20:30:00" d="2021-07-20 21:00:00"><n u="New: Wild China with Ray Mears">New: Wild China with Ray Mears I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Walking with Elephants
Ray explores wildlife in China's tropical rainforest. He meets elephant conservationist Dr Bao Mingwei and goes in search</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-20 21:00:00" d="2021-07-20 22:00:00"><n u="New: Love Your Garden">New: Love Your Garden X (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Chippenham
Alan and his team create a traditional formal garden for inspirational couple, Richard and Lynette Warren. Plus, the team reveal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-20 22:00:00" d="2021-07-20 23:00:00"><n u="New: Cooking with the Stars">New: Cooking with the Stars I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The next four celebrities - Griff Rhys Jones, Catherine Tyldesley, Denise Van Outen and AJ Odudu - take to the kitchen in a series of head-to-head cooking battles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-20 23:00:00" d="2021-07-20 23:30:00"><n>ITV News at Ten</n>    <k>ITV News provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-20 23:30:00" d="2021-07-20 23:45:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-20 23:45:00" d="2021-07-21 02:45:00"><n u="Goodwood Future Lab">Goodwood Future Lab (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Future Lab is the Festival of Speed's celebration of the most aspirational, inspirational, ground-breaking, cutting-edge technology and inventions in the world</k>  </p>
</a>
