<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="32" t="2020-05-16 04:53:18"><p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 07:00:00" d="2020-05-23 07:10:00"><n u="Dino Dana">Dino Dana II (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>65% Game of Bones Part 1
It's a two part special, and Dana has made her own board game so that the whole family can learn about what ended the Dinosaurs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 07:10:00" d="2020-05-23 07:25:00"><n u="Super">Super 4 II (48)</n><t>S</t>    <k>70% Chasing the Chameleon
Animated adventure series. The Super 4 watch powerlessly as Sharkbeard steals the Chameleon by surprise and escapes with it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 07:25:00" d="2020-05-23 07:35:00"><n u="Super">Super 4 II (49)</n><t>S</t>    <k>70% Super Rock
The Furios have allied with the giant apes to take control of the Lost World, and only Alien and Rock Brock can save it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 07:35:00" d="2020-05-23 08:00:00"><n u="Robozuna">Robozuna II (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Finding Proto
Ariston, Mangle and the Freebot Fighters return to Feronia's old lab and uncover the secret of Mangle's connection to Ariston</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 08:00:00" d="2020-05-23 08:05:00"><n u="Mission Employable">Mission Employable II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Become a Pilot
Join Agent Danny from the Mission Employable Agency as he takes to the skies as a pilot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 08:05:00" d="2020-05-23 08:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Wallpapering Magoo
Magoo thinks that he is peeling off old wallpaper on Linda's walls, but he is actually destroying Fizz' hypnotic posters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 08:15:00" d="2020-05-23 08:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lend Me Your Earpiece
Magoo finds himself shrunk and then dragged inside the President's head, along with Fizz. He thinks the hamster is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 08:25:00" d="2020-05-23 08:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Honey Bear
Magoo thinks that he is on a camping trip, but he is actually just in the city park. He mistakes Weasel for a wounded bear and tries to help him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 08:35:00" d="2020-05-23 08:45:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (41)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Show Must Go On!
The turtles turn to Mike for help when Aramis gets fed up and runs away. Can they convince her to come back?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 08:45:00" d="2020-05-23 08:55:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (42)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Main E-Vent
Things are mysteriously disappearing from the Mikkelsen's house and Mike can't seem to get to the bottom of it. Could the raccoons have a new trick?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 08:55:00" d="2020-05-23 09:10:00"><n u="Mr. Bean: The Animated Series">Mr. Bean: The Animated Series I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>67% Homeless
After a regrettable episode involving his landlady sleepwalking into his room, Mr Bean suddenly finds himself out on his ear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 09:10:00" d="2020-05-23 09:20:00"><n u="Mr. Bean: The Animated Series">Mr. Bean: The Animated Series I (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>67% Camping
An old photo album causes Bean to reminisce about summers at scout camp as a boy, and he plans a night under the stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 09:20:00" d="2020-05-23 09:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 III (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Which Watch
After a battle with Kevin gets cut short, Ben turns his attention to one upping Gwen at Space Camp. But it turns out Kevin isn't done yet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 09:30:00" d="2020-05-23 09:55:00"><n u="The Epic Tales of Captain Underpants">The Epic Tales of Captain Underpants I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Captain Underpants and the Flustering Mindless Woe of the Flushable Memory Wipes: Animated comedy. A chocolate pudding incident forces George and Harold into hiding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 09:55:00" d="2020-05-23 10:10:00"><n u="The Rubbish World of Dave Spud">The Rubbish World of Dave Spud I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Whaley Good Time
Fuzzypeg eats the Spuds' fish supper and Dave has to catch another. Things look up when he hooks something, but it turns out to be a whale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 10:10:00" d="2020-05-23 10:25:00"><n u="The Rubbish World of Dave Spud">The Rubbish World of Dave Spud I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Born Free
George takes Dave on an adventure camping, but Dave isn't sure it's a great idea. He's proved right when they both wake up in a bear's cave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 10:25:00" d="2020-05-23 12:30:00"><n u="New: James Martin's Saturday Morning">New: James Martin's Saturday Morning III (29)</n><t>S</t>    <k>James shares more of his favourite moments from past series and introduces dishes from chefs Nick Nairn, Clare Smyth and Lenny Carr Roberts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 12:30:00" d="2020-05-23 13:25:00"><n u="James Martin's Islands to Highlands">James Martin's Islands to Highlands I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Oxford
James is joined by top TV chef Monica Galetti. They're in Oxford, where Monica discovers the delights of an organic local distiller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 13:25:00" d="2020-05-23 14:20:00"><n u="Ainsley's Mediterranean Cookbook">Ainsley's Mediterranean Cookbook I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Jordan - Amman
Ainsley is pushing the boundaries with a visit to Jordan, a country in the region of the eastern Mediterranean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 14:20:00" d="2020-05-23 14:30:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 14:30:00" d="2020-05-23 15:00:00"><n u="How To Keep Your Dog Happy at Home">How To Keep Your Dog Happy at Home I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In this episode, we look at how you can tap into their basic breeding instincts to keep your dog happy and help you out in the process too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 15:00:00" d="2020-05-23 16:00:00"><n u="Dickinson's Real Deal">Dickinson's Real Deal XIII (32)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Oswestry 1
In Oswestry, Helen Gardiner finds a caddy that is just her cup of tea, a family of six run rings around Tim Hogarth, and a cameo bracelet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 16:00:00" d="2020-05-23 17:00:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable IV (57)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Disco Dave &amp; His Disco Balls
Five friends join forces to take on the Tenable tower. Have they got what it takes to score a Perfect 10 and win 125,000 pounds? Hosted by Warwick Davis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 17:00:00" d="2020-05-23 18:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point X (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 18:00:00" d="2020-05-23 19:00:00"><n>1989 Liverpool v Arsenal Title Decider - ITV Football Classics</n>    <k>Extended highlights of the 1988-89 Division One title decider between Liverpool and Arsenal, one of the most dramatic and memorable endings to a season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 19:00:00" d="2020-05-23 19:20:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world as well as the latest major sports results</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 19:20:00" d="2020-05-23 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 19:30:00" d="2020-05-23 20:30:00"><n u="Ninja Warrior UK">Ninja Warrior UK V (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>55% It's The Eliminator. Only the toughest competitors who complete the course against the clock will survive. Who will go through to the Grand Final?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 20:30:00" d="2020-05-23 21:00:00"><n u="In For A Penny">In For A Penny I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Leeds
Stephen Mulhern travels the UK with his feel-good, on the street game show. Stephen hits the streets of Leeds to find someone to play for a thousand pounds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 21:00:00" d="2020-05-23 22:20:00"><n u="New: Britain's Got Talent">New: Britain's Got Talent XIV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Auditions 7
The nation's favourite TV talent show, Britain's Got Talent, returns to our screens for a fun-filled 14th series packed full of variety</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 22:20:00" d="2020-05-23 23:15:00"><n u="Through the Keyhole">Through the Keyhole VI (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>54% Guessing 'who habitates in a house like this' are comedian Jimmy Carr, presenter Carol Vorderman and sporting legend Kriss Akabusi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-23 23:15:00" d="2020-05-24 02:15:00"><n>ITV News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world</k>  </p>
</a>
