<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2021-07-09 07:04:21"><p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-16 05:05:00" d="2021-07-16 06:05:00"><n>ITV Nightscreen</n>    <k>Text-based information service</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-16 06:05:00" d="2021-07-16 07:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point VIII (124)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-16 07:00:00" d="2021-07-16 10:00:00"><n>Good Morning Britain</n>    <k>News, current affairs and lively debate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-16 10:00:00" d="2021-07-16 11:00:00"><n>Lorraine</n>    <k>Lorraine Kelly presents a topical mix of entertainment, discussion and showbiz glamour as well as the latest fashion, food and celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-16 11:00:00" d="2021-07-16 13:30:00"><n>This Morning</n>    <k>The This Morning team bring you top celebrity guests, lifestyle advice, stunning competitions and award-winning features, all topped off with a sprinkle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-16 13:30:00" d="2021-07-16 14:30:00"><n>Loose Women</n>    <k>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-16 14:30:00" d="2021-07-16 14:55:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-16 14:55:00" d="2021-07-16 15:00:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-16 15:00:00" d="2021-07-16 16:00:00"><n u="Dickinson's Real Deal">Dickinson's Real Deal XV (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Milton Keynes 4
David and the team are in Milton Keynes. Mark Stevens gets his hands on a dazzling diamond ring and Stewart Hofgartner gets some postcards</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-16 16:00:00" d="2021-07-16 17:00:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable III (59)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Frizbee Quizbees
A team of five ultimate frisbee players from London get their chance to take on the Tower in a bid to fly off with a big cash prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-16 17:00:00" d="2021-07-16 18:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point VIII (145)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-16 18:00:00" d="2021-07-16 19:00:00"><n u="The Chase">The Chase XI (63)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bradley Walsh hosts the quiz show. All that stands between Shelagh, Holly, Daniel and Norman is the small matter of one of the country's finest quiz brains - the Chaser</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-16 19:00:00" d="2021-07-16 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-16 19:30:00" d="2021-07-16 20:00:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-16 20:00:00" d="2021-07-16 20:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>Will Jimmy admit the truth? Meena's fuming. Tracy pours out her feelings to Nate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-16 20:30:00" d="2021-07-16 21:30:00"><n>Coronation Street</n>    <k>Paul faces questions from the police. Fiz's newspaper interview angers Tyrone and Alina. Nick is excited by the prospect of having Sam to stay</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-16 21:30:00" d="2021-07-16 23:20:00"><n u="Endeavour">Endeavour V (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Passenger
The case of a missing woman leads Endeavour to an investigation on Oxford's railways. Meanwhile, a lorry hijack exposes a new criminal threat in Oxford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-16 23:20:00" d="2021-07-16 23:50:00"><n>ITV News at Ten</n>    <k>ITV News provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-16 23:50:00" d="2021-07-17 00:05:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 00:05:00" d="2021-07-17 00:35:00"><n u="The Jonathan Ross Show: Special Guests">The Jonathan Ross Show: Special Guests I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>60% Amongst the very special guests featured in this show are Madonna, Dave Bautista, Mel Giedroyc, Peter Kay, Spice Girls, Harrison Ford, Glenn Close, Mo Gilligan, and more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 00:35:00" d="2021-07-17 01:30:00"><n u="Who Wants To Be A Millionaire? Jeremy Clarkson is back">Who Wants To Be A Millionaire? Jeremy Clarkson is back XXXIV (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Six new contestants, four lifelines and just 15 questions stand between them and one million pounds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 01:30:00" d="2021-07-17 02:20:00"><n u="Tour De France Highlights">Tour De France Highlights (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Stage 19, Mourenx - Libourne
This should be a chance for the sprinters to test their legs after the rigours of the mountains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 02:20:00" d="2021-07-17 04:00:00"><n>Shop: Ideal World</n>    <k>Join Ideal World on ITV for some of the best offers and products on TV. To see more go to www.idealworld.tv</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 04:00:00" d="2021-07-17 04:15:00"><n>FYI Extra</n>    <k>A short bulletin rounding up the day's stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 04:15:00" d="2021-07-17 05:05:00"><n u="Martin and Roman's Weekend Best! Father and son duo, Martin and Roman Kemp are joined by Tom Kerridge, Nina Wadia and Dominic Monaghan">Martin and Roman's Weekend Best! Father and son duo, Martin and Roman Kemp are joined by Tom Kerridge, Nina Wadia and Dominic Monaghan II (26)</n><t>S</t>    <k>[SL]</k>  </p>
</a>
