<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="17" t="2020-04-15 04:33:48"><p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-22 06:05:00" d="2020-04-22 07:00:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder VII (120)</n><t>S</t>    <k>53% Arbitration show in which real small-claims cases are adjudicated over within a studio courtroom by Judge Robert Rinder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-22 07:00:00" d="2020-04-22 10:00:00"><n>Good Morning Britain</n>    <k>Breakfast show featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-22 10:00:00" d="2020-04-22 11:00:00"><n>Good Morning Britain with Lorraine</n>    <k>Lorraine Kelly joins the GMB team for an extra hour of Good Morning Britain, featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-22 11:00:00" d="2020-04-22 13:30:00"><n>This Morning</n>    <k>The This Morning team bring you top celebrity guests, lifestyle advice, stunning competitions and award-winning features, all topped off with a sprinkle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-22 13:30:00" d="2020-04-22 14:30:00"><n>Loose Women</n>    <k>Special guests Karren Brady and Craig Revel Horwood join a jam-packed Loose Women panel to talk about everything they've been getting up to recently</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-22 14:30:00" d="2020-04-22 14:55:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-22 14:55:00" d="2020-04-22 15:00:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-22 15:00:00" d="2020-04-22 16:00:00"><n u="New: James Martin's Islands to Highlands">New: James Martin's Islands to Highlands I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Northumberland
James is joined by Michelin-starred chef Kenny Atkinson and they set out to sample the delights of Northumberland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-22 16:00:00" d="2020-04-22 17:00:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable IV (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Leach for the Stars
A team of family members answer a series of Top 10 list questions as they attempt to win a big cash prize. Quiz show hosted by Warwick Davis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-22 17:00:00" d="2020-04-22 18:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point IX (48)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-22 18:00:00" d="2020-04-22 19:00:00"><n u="The Chase">The Chase X (68)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz show hosted by Bradley Walsh. Four contestants must pit their wits against the Chaser, a ruthless quiz genius determined to stop them winning the cash prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-22 19:00:00" d="2020-04-22 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-22 19:30:00" d="2020-04-22 20:00:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-22 20:00:00" d="2020-04-22 20:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>Vanessa remains angry at Charity. Dawn gets advice from Carol. Moira becomes suspicious of Cain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-22 20:30:00" d="2020-04-22 21:00:00"><n>Coronation Street</n>    <k>Gary intervenes in Amy and Kelly's fight. Ken tells Claudia that Stillwaters will never be his home. Johnny feels uneasy leaving Scott at the Rovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-22 21:00:00" d="2020-04-22 21:30:00"><n u="New: Kate &amp; Koji">New: Kate &amp; Koji I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Not for the first time, Kate is being sued, but this time by Councillor Bone. Koji discovers he is under investigation for working illegally</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-22 21:30:00" d="2020-04-23 00:30:00"><n u="Paul O'Grady: For the Love of Dogs">Paul O'Grady: For the Love of Dogs VII (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% Paul O'Grady meets Florence, a pug-terrier cross who's been badly injured in a car accident, and talks to Jennifer Saunders, one of the volunteers at Battersea</k>  </p>
</a>
