<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="28" t="2019-07-11 00:18:50"><p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-16 06:05:00" d="2019-07-16 07:00:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder V (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>54% Cheryl v Luke
Cheryl is in court to claim back the money owed on loans she made to her niece's former partner. Lynne hopes to claim back money</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-16 07:00:00" d="2019-07-16 09:30:00"><n>Good Morning Britain</n>    <k>Breakfast show featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-16 09:30:00" d="2019-07-16 10:25:00"><n>Lorraine</n>    <k>Lorraine Kelly presents a topical mix of entertainment, discussion and showbiz glamour as well as the latest fashion, food and celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-16 10:25:00" d="2019-07-16 11:30:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder V (118)</n><t>S</t>    <k>54% Bob v Lyndsey and Steve
Bob claims for loss of earnings due to defamation of character while James hopes to claim for a lost deposit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-16 11:30:00" d="2019-07-16 13:30:00"><n u="This Morning">This Morning XXXI (140)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Magazine show with news and topical items, celebrity guests, expert advice, real life stories, competitions and a mix of cookery, health, beauty, lifestyle and more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-16 13:30:00" d="2019-07-16 14:30:00"><n>Loose Women</n>    <k>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-16 14:30:00" d="2019-07-16 14:55:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-16 14:55:00" d="2019-07-16 15:00:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-16 15:00:00" d="2019-07-16 16:00:00"><n u="Dickinson's Real Deal">Dickinson's Real Deal XIII (28)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Southport 5
David and his Dealers' Den pitches up in Southport. James Layte is alarmed by a clock, Alys Dobbie struts her stuff in some funky boots</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-16 16:00:00" d="2019-07-16 17:00:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable II (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Warwick Davis hosts the quiz show based on Top 10 lists. A bridal party made up of five university friends attempt to walk away with a big cash prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-16 17:00:00" d="2019-07-16 18:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point VI (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-16 18:00:00" d="2019-07-16 19:00:00"><n u="The Chase">The Chase IX (162)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz show hosted by Bradley Walsh. Scott, Marie, Richard and Joanne must pit their wits against the Chaser</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-16 19:00:00" d="2019-07-16 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-16 19:30:00" d="2019-07-16 20:00:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-16 20:00:00" d="2019-07-16 20:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>Aaron is shocked by Robert's plan. Brenda gives Vanessa an idea. Debbie has a confession</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-16 20:30:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00"><n u="New: Save Money: Good Diet">New: Save Money: Good Diet II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Phil takes on one of our takeaway favourites - which delicious dish will claim number four in our countdown? And can triplets from Stourbridge follow their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 21:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>Robert and Aaron are on a mission. Rhona feigns happiness. Lydia confronts Nicola</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-16 21:30:00" d="2019-07-16 22:00:00"><n u="New: Yorkshire Airport">New: Yorkshire Airport (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Operations Manager Jamie deals with a plane making an emergency landing and Terminal Manager Nathan handles a potential disaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-16 22:00:00" d="2019-07-16 23:00:00"><n>New: The Day We Walked on the Moon</n>    <k>On July 20th, 1969, astronaut Neil Armstrong became the first man to walk on the moon. This is the story of how he got there, with interviews</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-16 23:00:00" d="2019-07-16 23:30:00"><n>ITV News at Ten</n>    <k>ITV News at Ten provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-16 23:30:00" d="2019-07-16 23:45:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-16 23:45:00" d="2019-07-17 00:45:00"><n u="Holiday Horrors: Caught on Camera">Holiday Horrors: Caught on Camera (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Find out exactly what happens when airline passengers prepare for an emergency landing, when a parachute fails to open and what's so funny about a hot-air balloon crash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 00:45:00" d="2019-07-17 01:40:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable II (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Warwick Davis hosts the quiz show based on top ten lists. A team of five friends from Taunton attempt to walk away with a big cash prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 01:40:00" d="2019-07-17 02:30:00"><n u="Cycling: Tour de France Highlights">Cycling: Tour de France Highlights 2019 (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Rest Day
It's the first rest day of the race. Gary Imlach reports from Albi with a look back at the opening 10 days</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 02:30:00" d="2019-07-17 03:20:00"><n u="James Martin's French Adventure">James Martin's French Adventure I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Camargue
James's culinary tour takes him to the Camargue, where he learns all about the Camargue bull and the delicate hand-harvested salty crust fleur de sel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 03:20:00" d="2019-07-17 03:50:00"><n>Teleshopping</n>    <k>Shopping from home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 03:50:00" d="2019-07-17 04:15:00"><n u="River Monsters">River Monsters IX (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% Malaysian Lake Monster
When two men mysteriously vanish on a remote lake in Malaysia, monster hunter Jeremy Wade sets out to track down the possible killer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 04:15:00" d="2019-07-17 06:05:00"><n>ITV Nightscreen</n>    <k>Text-based information service</k>  </p>
</a>
