<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2019-08-13 02:17:47"><p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 06:05:00" d="2019-08-20 07:00:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder VI (36)</n><t>S</t>    <k>54% Billy v Students
A landlord hopes to claim the court maximum of 5,000 pounds for the cost of repairing a property that he says was damaged by his former tenants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 07:00:00" d="2019-08-20 09:30:00"><n>Good Morning Britain</n>    <k>Breakfast show featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 09:30:00" d="2019-08-20 10:25:00"><n>Lorraine</n>    <k>Lorraine Kelly presents a topical mix of entertainment, discussion and showbiz glamour as well as the latest fashion, food and celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 10:25:00" d="2019-08-20 11:30:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder IV (31)</n><t>S</t>    <k>54% Kebbie is in court to claim for non-payment of wages. Bridget is in court to claim back an investment she made to her former friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 11:30:00" d="2019-08-20 13:30:00"><n u="This Morning">This Morning XXXI (165)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Magazine show with news and topical items, celebrity guests, expert advice, real life stories, competitions and a mix of cookery, health, beauty, lifestyle and more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 13:30:00" d="2019-08-20 14:30:00"><n>Loose Women</n>    <k>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 14:30:00" d="2019-08-20 14:55:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 14:55:00" d="2019-08-20 15:00:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 15:00:00" d="2019-08-20 16:00:00"><n u="Dickinson's Real Deal">Dickinson's Real Deal XIII (84)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Best Of 4
The best bits of David's Dealers' Den. Michael Hogben gets tied up by some Pelham puppets and Jon O'Marah is cut to the quick by an old sword!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 16:00:00" d="2019-08-20 17:00:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable III (32)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Good Squad Almighty
Five family members get their chance to take on the Tower as they attempt to take home a big cash prize. Daytime quiz show hosted by Warwick Davis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 17:00:00" d="2019-08-20 18:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point V (44)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 18:00:00" d="2019-08-20 19:00:00"><n u="The Chase">The Chase IX (95)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz show hosted by Bradley Walsh. All that stands between Dav, Manoj, Susan and Louise and thousands of pounds is one of the country's finest quiz brains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 19:00:00" d="2019-08-20 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 19:30:00" d="2019-08-20 20:00:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 20:00:00" d="2019-08-20 20:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>Moira is determined to prove a point. Dawn has a plan. Paddy tells Bear the truth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 20:30:00" d="2019-08-20 21:00:00"><n u="New: Save Money: Good Health">New: Save Money: Good Health III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>This episode is all about sleep. Dr Ranj Singh meets pharmacist Harsha Parmar to look at everything from natural remedies to sleeping tablets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 21:00:00" d="2019-08-20 21:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>Moira has a close call. David and Leyla are stunned by a discovery. Harriet pleads Will's case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 21:30:00" d="2019-08-20 22:00:00"><n u="New: Yorkshire Airport">New: Yorkshire Airport (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The airport is preparing for the grand opening of its multi-million-pound facelift and Phil is under pressure to impress Transport secretary Chris Grayling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 22:00:00" d="2019-08-21 01:00:00"><n u="New: Fighter Pilot: The Real Top Gun">New: Fighter Pilot: The Real Top Gun (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>This new three-part documentary series spends a year inside Britain's elite Fighter Pilot School, following three young recruits as they compete to become</k>  </p>
</a>
