<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2019-08-11 01:37:10"><p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 07:00:00" d="2019-08-17 07:10:00"><n u="Dino Dana">Dino Dana I (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>67% Dinomite
Dino Dana is an eight-year-old palaeontologist in training. Dad tries to get Dana up for school, but she is busy dreaming about discovering</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 07:10:00" d="2019-08-17 07:25:00"><n u="Super">Super 4 II (34)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Princess Ruby
With King Kenric absent and his successor Alex ill and unable to uphold his role, the responsibility of temporarily ruling Kingsland falls to Ruby the pirate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 07:25:00" d="2019-08-17 07:35:00"><n u="Super">Super 4 II (35)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Pied Piper of Kingsland
Animated comedy adventure series. Fourchesac helps the Super 4 team, but when they refuse to let him join them, he feels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 07:35:00" d="2019-08-17 08:00:00"><n u="Thunderbirds Are Go">Thunderbirds Are Go II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Ghost Ship
GDF Captain Ridley O'Bannon sends out a distress call during a routine inspection of a derelict generation ship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 08:00:00" d="2019-08-17 08:05:00"><n u="Mission Employable">Mission Employable I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Firefighter
A behind-the-scenes look at everyday jobs. Agent Kym's next mission takes her to a fire station, where she walks in the shoes of the brave firefighters there</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 08:05:00" d="2019-08-17 08:15:00"><n u="Mr. Bean: The Animated Series">Mr. Bean: The Animated Series I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>67% The Sofa
The sofa's springs explode under Mr Bean. Can he afford to buy a new sofa? Will he never relax in front of the telly again?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 08:15:00" d="2019-08-17 08:30:00"><n u="Mr. Bean: The Animated Series">Mr. Bean: The Animated Series I (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>67% Treasure!
In a dark corner of his attic, Mr Bean finds a treasure map. But tricky clues lead him nearly all the way to Australia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 08:30:00" d="2019-08-17 08:55:00"><n u="Marvel's Avengers: Secret Wars">Marvel's Avengers: Secret Wars IV (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Weirdworld
Black Widow and Captain Marvel must work together to stop the separated Bruce Banner and the Hulk from harming each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 08:55:00" d="2019-08-17 09:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 II (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>That's the Stuff
Ben visits an exciting space museum, and learns that new areas of space are being investigated by the team in the laboratory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 09:10:00" d="2019-08-17 09:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 II (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Charm Offensive
The evil Charmcaster interrupts Ben and Gwen's visit to Fort Knox, and demands revenge for Michael Morningstar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 09:25:00" d="2019-08-17 09:30:00"><n>ITV News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world as well as the latest major sports results</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 09:30:00" d="2019-08-17 10:25:00"><n u="New: The Sara Cox Show">New: The Sara Cox Show (35)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Joining Sara Cox on the show are author Jack Monroe and stars of Poldark, Ellise Chappell and Harry Richardson. Plus, music from Lucy Rose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 10:25:00" d="2019-08-17 12:25:00"><n u="James Martin's Saturday Morning">James Martin's Saturday Morning II (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>James is joined by singer Rebecca Ferguson and chef Claude Bosi. On the menu are chocolate cherry roulade, garlic soup and chicken in a mustard and wine sauce</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 12:25:00" d="2019-08-17 13:25:00"><n u="John and Lisa's Weekend Kitchen">John and Lisa's Weekend Kitchen II (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>There's a chilled vibe in John and Lisa's Kitchen this time with a menu best served cold. Lisa makes her wonderful gazpacho and an ingenious quiche</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 13:25:00" d="2019-08-17 13:55:00"><n u="Ainsley's Caribbean Kitchen">Ainsley's Caribbean Kitchen I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Grenada
Ainsley Harriott stops off in Grenada, also known as the spice island, for the next leg of his Caribbean tour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 13:55:00" d="2019-08-17 14:25:00"><n u="Save Money: Good Health">Save Money: Good Health III (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sian Williams reviews some of the latest health products and gadgets set to hit the shelves from cannabis oil to algae as well as wearable tech to reduce stress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 14:25:00" d="2019-08-17 14:35:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 14:35:00" d="2019-08-17 16:30:00"><n u="Midsomer Murders">Midsomer Murders XIV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>78% A Sacred Trust
When a nun is killed at Midsomer Priory, teenage liaisons, missing antique silver, African art and holy orders make it a complex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 16:30:00" d="2019-08-17 17:30:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable III (51)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Dial Tones
Five workmates from Manchester all working in the telecoms industry take on the Tenable Tower. Can they dial in 10 answers and take home a big cash prize?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 17:30:00" d="2019-08-17 18:30:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point V (82)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 18:30:00" d="2019-08-17 19:25:00"><n u="The Chase">The Chase IX (130)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz show hosted by Bradley Walsh. All that stands between Oliver, Hannah, Mike, Tiana, and thousands of pounds, is the small matter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 19:25:00" d="2019-08-17 19:35:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world as well as the latest major sports results</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 19:35:00" d="2019-08-17 19:45:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 19:45:00" d="2019-08-17 20:15:00"><n u="New: Zone of Champions">New: Zone of Champions (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Zone of Champions is the only place to catch sporting events such as Hamster Athletics and Using an Escalator for the Purposes of Banter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 20:15:00" d="2019-08-17 22:00:00"><n>Minions</n>    <k>Animation featuring the voices of Sandra Bullock and Jon Hamm, 2015. Minions Stuart, Kevin and Bob are recruited by super-villain Scarlet Overkill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-17 22:00:00" d="2019-08-18 01:00:00"><n u="Fast and Furious">Fast and Furious 8</n>    <k>Action thriller sequel starring Vin Diesel and Charlize Theron, 2017. When Dom Toretto is lured back into the world of crime by a mysterious woman</k>  </p>
</a>
