<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2020-05-14 04:54:31"><p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-21 06:05:00" d="2020-05-21 07:00:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder VII (114)</n><t>S</t>    <k>53% Arbitration show in which real small-claims cases are adjudicated over within a studio courtroom by Judge Robert Rinder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-21 07:00:00" d="2020-05-21 10:00:00"><n>Good Morning Britain</n>    <k>Breakfast show featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-21 10:00:00" d="2020-05-21 11:00:00"><n>Good Morning Britain with Lorraine</n>    <k>Lorraine Kelly joins the GMB team for an extra hour of Good Morning Britain, featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-21 11:00:00" d="2020-05-21 13:30:00"><n>This Morning</n>    <k>The This Morning team bring you top celebrity guests, lifestyle advice, stunning competitions and award-winning features, all topped off with a sprinkle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-21 13:30:00" d="2020-05-21 14:30:00"><n>Loose Women</n>    <k>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-21 14:30:00" d="2020-05-21 14:55:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-21 14:55:00" d="2020-05-21 15:00:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-21 15:00:00" d="2020-05-21 16:00:00"><n u="New: Judge Rinder">New: Judge Rinder VII (30)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Arbitration show in which real small-claims cases are adjudicated over within a studio courtroom by Judge Robert Rinder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-21 16:00:00" d="2020-05-21 17:00:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz show hosted by Warwick Davis. Will a team of tram workers from Sheffield top the tower and get the elusive Perfect 10, or will they prove to be untenable?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-21 17:00:00" d="2020-05-21 18:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point VI (44)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-21 18:00:00" d="2020-05-21 19:00:00"><n u="The Chase">The Chase X (104)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz show hosted by Bradley Walsh. Four contestants must pit their wits against the Chaser, a ruthless quiz genius determined to stop them winning the cash prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-21 19:00:00" d="2020-05-21 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-21 19:30:00" d="2020-05-21 20:00:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-21 20:00:00" d="2020-05-21 20:30:00"><n u="You've Been Framed!">You've Been Framed! XXXIII (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A motorbike gets stuck up a tree, a woman is electrocuted by a fly zapper, and a pensioner is crushed by a falling TV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-21 20:30:00" d="2020-05-21 21:00:00"><n>The Race for a Cure: Making Britain Safe - Tonight</n>    <k>Dr Ranj Singh looks at the urgent race to find a cure for Covid 19. He gains first-hand access to drug trials and reports on the scientific effort going</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-21 21:00:00" d="2020-05-21 21:30:00"><n>New: The Martin Lewis Money Show - A Coronavirus Special</n>    <k>Martin will be taking your questions on how the economic crisis affects family finances, jobs and consumer rights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-21 21:30:00" d="2020-05-21 22:00:00"><n u="New: Secrets of the Driving Test">New: Secrets of the Driving Test I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cocksure 17-year-old Bethany is barely out of the test centre before getting into a game of chicken. Meanwhile, Drew and Julie are eager to improve on their first tests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-21 22:00:00" d="2020-05-21 23:00:00"><n>New: Inside the Crown: Secrets of the Royals</n>    <k>The Queen - Inside the Crown: This film follows the Royal family's own frightening experience of the Corona Virus crisis - Charles caught</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-05-21 23:00:00" d="2020-05-22 02:00:00"><n>ITV News at Ten</n>    <k>ITV News at Ten provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents</k>  </p>
</a>
