<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2020-05-29 04:36:00"><p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-05 06:05:00" d="2020-06-05 07:00:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder VIII (37)</n><t>S</t>    <k>53% Arbitration show in which real small-claims cases are adjudicated over within a studio courtroom by Judge Robert Rinder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-05 07:00:00" d="2020-06-05 10:00:00"><n>Good Morning Britain</n>    <k>Breakfast show featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-05 10:00:00" d="2020-06-05 11:00:00"><n>Good Morning Britain with Lorraine</n>    <k>Lorraine Kelly joins the GMB team for an extra hour of Good Morning Britain, featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-05 11:00:00" d="2020-06-05 13:30:00"><n>This Morning</n>    <k>The This Morning team bring you top celebrity guests, lifestyle advice, stunning competitions and award-winning features, all topped off with a sprinkle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-05 13:30:00" d="2020-06-05 14:30:00"><n>Loose Women</n>    <k>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-05 14:30:00" d="2020-06-05 14:55:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-05 14:55:00" d="2020-06-05 15:00:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-05 15:00:00" d="2020-06-05 16:00:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder V (39)</n><t>S</t>    <k>53% Mark v Ian
Mark is in court to claim for dog training and kennel fees, but defendant Ian says he can no longer afford the payments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-05 16:00:00" d="2020-06-05 17:00:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable I (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Warwick Davis presents the Top 10-themed quiz show. Five friends from Surrey answer Top 10 list questions in a bid to win a big cash prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-05 17:00:00" d="2020-06-05 18:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point VI (65)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-05 18:00:00" d="2020-06-05 19:00:00"><n u="The Chase">The Chase X (121)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz show hosted by Bradley Walsh. Four contestants must pit their wits against the Chaser, a ruthless quiz genius determined to stop them winning the cash prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-05 19:00:00" d="2020-06-05 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-05 19:30:00" d="2020-06-05 20:00:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-05 20:00:00" d="2020-06-05 20:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>More worry for Jamie. Kerry overhears a confession. The guilt builds for Rhona</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-05 20:30:00" d="2020-06-05 21:00:00"><n>Coronation Street</n>    <k>Geoff is forced to come clean about hiring escorts. Asha finds a renewed confidence. Shona agrees to live with Roy rather than David</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-05 21:00:00" d="2020-06-05 21:30:00"><n u="Birds of a Feather">Birds of a Feather III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Tonight I'll Be Staying Here with You
Sitcom. Auntie Vera has got hip problems and defective lifts and tells the girls that she is moving in, so Dorien</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-05 21:30:00" d="2020-06-05 23:25:00"><n u="Vera">Vera IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>On Harbour Street
Detective drama series. DCI Vera Stanhope investigates a mysterious death in a quiet coastal town with clues that keep revolving around one street</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-05 23:25:00" d="2020-06-06 02:25:00"><n>ITV News</n>    <k>ITV News at Ten provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents</k>  </p>
</a>
