<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="28" t="2019-07-11 00:18:51"><p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 06:05:00" d="2019-07-17 07:00:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder V (36)</n><t>S</t>    <k>54% Lewis v Scott
Lewis is in court to claim for the outstanding amount owed for two snakes that he sold to his friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 07:00:00" d="2019-07-17 09:30:00"><n>Good Morning Britain</n>    <k>Breakfast show featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 09:30:00" d="2019-07-17 10:25:00"><n>Lorraine</n>    <k>Lorraine Kelly presents a topical mix of entertainment, discussion and showbiz glamour as well as the latest fashion, food and celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 10:25:00" d="2019-07-17 11:30:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder VI (36)</n><t>S</t>    <k>54% Billy v Students
A landlord hopes to claim the court maximum of 5,000 pounds for the cost of repairing a property that he says was damaged by his former tenants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 11:30:00" d="2019-07-17 13:30:00"><n u="This Morning">This Morning XXXI (141)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Magazine show with news and topical items, celebrity guests, expert advice, real life stories, competitions and a mix of cookery, health, beauty, lifestyle and more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 13:30:00" d="2019-07-17 14:30:00"><n>Loose Women</n>    <k>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 14:30:00" d="2019-07-17 14:55:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 14:55:00" d="2019-07-17 15:00:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 15:00:00" d="2019-07-17 16:00:00"><n u="Dickinson's Real Deal">Dickinson's Real Deal XIII (58)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Dunstable 2
Dunstable hosts David and his dealers. Cheryl Hakeney unmasks some amazing Troika and Helen Gardiner gets ganged up on when she tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 16:00:00" d="2019-07-17 17:00:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable II (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Warwick Davis hosts the quiz show based on top ten lists. A team from Cumbria get their chance to take on the Tower of 10 in an attempt to walk away with a big cash prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 17:00:00" d="2019-07-17 18:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point VI (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 18:00:00" d="2019-07-17 19:00:00"><n u="The Chase">The Chase IX (163)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz show hosted by Bradley Walsh. Kim, Mark, Brian and Gwyneth must pit their wits against the Chaser, a ruthless quiz genius determined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 19:00:00" d="2019-07-17 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 19:30:00" d="2019-07-17 20:00:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 20:00:00" d="2019-07-17 20:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>Pete has a romantic surprise. Doug is determined to stay in control. Bernice is suspicious of Liam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 20:30:00" d="2019-07-17 21:00:00"><n>Coronation Street</n>    <k>Gary sweats when Sharon turns up asking questions about Rick. Sarah proposes a strategy to the factory staff. Evelyn dislikes sharing her home with Roy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 21:00:00" d="2019-07-17 21:30:00"><n u="New: Inside the Ritz Hotel">New: Inside the Ritz Hotel I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>We peek further inside The Ritz Hotel as it hosts a dinner dance and John Williams launches a new home grown ingredient onto the menu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 21:30:00" d="2019-07-17 22:00:00"><n>Coronation Street</n>    <k>Gary feels the net closing in on him. Jan contrives to keep Seb and Alina apart. Beth sulks at her colleagues' decision to forfeit their bonuses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 22:00:00" d="2019-07-17 23:00:00"><n u="New: Wild Bill">New: Wild Bill (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A spate of gruesome nail-gun murders puts Bill on the hunt for an old hitman-turned-Crown witness but is he doing the real villains' dirty work for them?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 23:00:00" d="2019-07-17 23:30:00"><n>ITV News at Ten</n>    <k>ITV News at Ten provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 23:30:00" d="2019-07-17 23:45:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-17 23:45:00" d="2019-07-18 00:45:00"><n u="New: Peston">New: Peston V (26)</n><t>S</t>    <k>As the political temperature rises, join Robert Peston for a late night political magazine show, featuring big interviews with the country's leading politicians</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-18 00:45:00" d="2019-07-18 01:35:00"><n>The Day We Walked on the Moon</n>    <k>On July 20th, 1969, astronaut Neil Armstrong became the first man to walk on the moon. This is the story of how he got there, with interviews</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-18 01:35:00" d="2019-07-18 02:25:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable II (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Warwick Davis hosts the quiz show based on top ten lists. A team of five NHS medical staff from Teesside attempt to walk away with a big cash prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-18 02:25:00" d="2019-07-18 03:15:00"><n u="Cycling: Tour de France Highlights">Cycling: Tour de France Highlights 2019 (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Stage 11
The race resumes after the rest day with a 167km route from Albi to Toulouse. The sprinters will have their targeted systems locked on this one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-18 03:15:00" d="2019-07-18 03:45:00"><n>Teleshopping</n>    <k>Shopping from home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-18 03:45:00" d="2019-07-18 04:35:00"><n u="Surprise Surprise">Surprise Surprise III (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Holly Willoughby presents the show where ordinary people are rewarded for doing extraordinary things. McBusted surprise a fan with a performance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-07-18 04:35:00" d="2019-07-18 06:05:00"><n>ITV Nightscreen</n>    <k>Text-based information service</k>  </p>
</a>
