<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2020-05-30 04:37:18"><p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 07:00:00" d="2020-06-06 07:10:00"><n u="Dino Dana">Dino Dana I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% A Game of Microraptor and Mouse
Edutainment series. Dana studies the hunting techniques of microraptors when she finds a mouse in the apartment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 07:10:00" d="2020-06-06 07:25:00"><n u="Super">Super 4 II (29)</n><t>S</t>    <k>70% Poetry Party
Animated comedy adventure series. Leonora organises the first poetry contest in Kingsland. Then our heroes quickly see that something strange is going on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 07:25:00" d="2020-06-06 07:35:00"><n u="Super">Super 4 II (30)</n><t>S</t>    <k>70% Jurassic Safari
Agent Franz invites Doctor X for a guided tour of The Lost World - The Jurassic Ride. Tyrannosauruses, velociraptors, pterosauruses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 07:35:00" d="2020-06-06 08:00:00"><n u="Robozuna">Robozuna II (27)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Coach Mangle
Gizi and Zeve steal some valuable strategy chips to give them an unfair advantage against Team Veredus in the arena</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 08:00:00" d="2020-06-06 08:05:00"><n u="Mission Employable">Mission Employable II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Become a Marine Biologist
Agent Danny gets up close and personal with sharks and even gets into the water to feed stingrays as he becomes a marine biologist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 08:05:00" d="2020-06-06 08:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Nice Little Doggy
Magoo is handing out food to the neighbourhood animals when he stumbles on a gigantic hamster that Fizz has released from some parallel dimension</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 08:15:00" d="2020-06-06 08:20:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Home Havoc
Magoo can't find the book that Linda lent him and he's ready to turn the house upside down to find it. The problem is that he's actually in Fizz's loft</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 08:20:00" d="2020-06-06 08:30:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Whiter Than White
Magoo, thinking he's at the laundromat, wanders into a candy factory, where Fizz and Weasel are creating a bubblegum that makes Fizz-shaped bubbles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 08:30:00" d="2020-06-06 08:40:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (49)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ditzy Home
Stephan upgrades the house's security system, and Mike may be able to take a break from playing guard dog. Maybe. Possibly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 08:40:00" d="2020-06-06 08:50:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (50)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Well Trained
The raccoons stumble upon an old whistle and discover that it has strange powers over Mike. Can Mike combat their new power over him?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 08:50:00" d="2020-06-06 09:05:00"><n u="Mr. Bean: The Animated Series">Mr. Bean: The Animated Series I (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>67% Toothache
Bean is tormented by the toothache from hell, but his DIY attempts to pull it out fail and he has to visit the dentist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 09:05:00" d="2020-06-06 09:20:00"><n u="Mr. Bean: The Animated Series">Mr. Bean: The Animated Series I (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>67% Haircut
The animated antics of the hapless bumbler Mr Bean. After accidentally rescuing a kitten from a tree, Mr Bean is about to get his picture in the newspaper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 09:20:00" d="2020-06-06 09:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 III (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mutiny for the Bounty
While Phil and Grandpa Max tune-up the Omni-Copter, a restless Ben takes the Rustbuggy off road, leaving him exposed to danger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 09:30:00" d="2020-06-06 09:55:00"><n>LEGO Marvel Super Heroes: Avengers Reassembled</n>    <k>Ultron gains control of Iron Man's armour and uses it to wreak havoc on the world. Can the Avengers stop him and save Iron Man in the process?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 09:55:00" d="2020-06-06 10:10:00"><n u="The Rubbish World of Dave Spud">The Rubbish World of Dave Spud I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Culture
George takes the Spuds to the museum of mouldy cheese. Anna dares Dave to lick the cheeses on display, and Dave's bad breath wakes one of the exhibits up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 10:10:00" d="2020-06-06 10:25:00"><n u="The Rubbish World of Dave Spud">The Rubbish World of Dave Spud I (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Dig
When Betty insists Dave finds a hobby, he takes up treasure hunting, and rocks the very foundations of his tower block home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 10:25:00" d="2020-06-06 12:35:00"><n u="New: James Martin's Saturday Morning">New: James Martin's Saturday Morning III (31)</n><t>S</t>    <k>James is back in the kitchen on a Saturday morning with a brand new episode. He'll be joined by his guests Roman Kemp and Vick Hope</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 12:35:00" d="2020-06-06 13:35:00"><n u="New: John and Lisa's Weekend Kitchen">New: John and Lisa's Weekend Kitchen IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>John and Lisa invite us into their kitchen for a morning of feel good food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 13:35:00" d="2020-06-06 14:35:00"><n u="James Martin's Islands to Highlands">James Martin's Islands to Highlands I (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Northern Ireland 1
James is joined in Northern Ireland by his good pal and local boy Paul Rankin. They brave the Carrick-a-Rede rope bridge together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 14:35:00" d="2020-06-06 15:00:00"><n u="Countrywise: Guide to Britain">Countrywise: Guide to Britain VIII (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Fogle tries his hand at free diving in Cornwall. Liz Bonnin volunteers at Cuan Wildlife Rescue centre in Shropshire, and Lesley Joseph indulges</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 15:00:00" d="2020-06-06 15:10:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 15:10:00" d="2020-06-06 16:10:00"><n u="Dickinson's Real Deal">Dickinson's Real Deal XIII (28)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Coventry 3
Coventry is our host as Henry Nicholls turns detective with some Minton. Will Fay Rutter bag a Breitling? And Alison Chapman is in a fluster with some coins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 16:10:00" d="2020-06-06 17:10:00"><n>Euro 96 England v Netherlands - ITV Football Classics</n>    <k>ITV Football Classics continues with extended highlights of England's Euro 96 meeting with the Netherlands at Wembley Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 17:10:00" d="2020-06-06 17:30:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world as well as the latest major sports results</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 17:30:00" d="2020-06-06 17:40:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 17:40:00" d="2020-06-06 19:30:00"><n u="The Masked Singer US">The Masked Singer US II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Nick Cannon introduces the first four contestants - Butterfly, Egg, Thingamajig and Skeleton. With panelists Robin Thicke, Jenny McCarthy, Ken Jeong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 19:30:00" d="2020-06-06 20:30:00"><n u="Ninja Warrior UK">Ninja Warrior UK IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>55% Action-packed game show. Ben Shephard, Rochelle Humes and Chris Kamara host the first episode of the fourth series, and this time the competitors include some famous faces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 20:30:00" d="2020-06-06 21:30:00"><n u="New: Alan Carr's Epic Gameshow">New: Alan Carr's Epic Gameshow I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Price Is Right
Alan Carr's Epic Gameshow returns with a true classic - The Price Is Right. Eight players from the audience are invited to 'come</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-06 21:30:00" d="2020-06-07 00:30:00"><n>Casino Royale</n>    <k>Bond movie starring Daniel Craig and Eva Green, 2006. Newly-qualified James Bond is sent on his first mission to investigate a banker suspected of aiding</k>  </p>
</a>
