<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2019-08-15 22:44:41"><p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-21 06:05:00" d="2019-08-21 07:00:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder VI (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>54% Alyson v Adrian
Featuring a dispute over a loan given to a former partner, and a performance artist who says another man copied his act</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-21 07:00:00" d="2019-08-21 09:30:00"><n>Good Morning Britain</n>    <k>Breakfast show featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-21 09:30:00" d="2019-08-21 10:25:00"><n>Lorraine</n>    <k>Lorraine Kelly presents a topical mix of entertainment, discussion and showbiz glamour as well as the latest fashion, food and celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-21 10:25:00" d="2019-08-21 11:30:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder V (67)</n><t>S</t>    <k>54% Jema (Levi) v Richard
Levi is in court to claim for loss of earnings while Jeff and Alex are pursuing 650 pounds owed on loans they made to their former neighbour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-21 11:30:00" d="2019-08-21 13:30:00"><n u="This Morning">This Morning XXXI (166)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Magazine show with news and topical items, celebrity guests, expert advice, real life stories, competitions and a mix of cookery, health, beauty, lifestyle and more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-21 13:30:00" d="2019-08-21 14:00:00"><n>Loose Women</n>    <k>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-21 14:00:00" d="2019-08-21 14:20:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-21 14:20:00" d="2019-08-21 14:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-21 14:30:00" d="2019-08-21 17:00:00"><n>ITV Racing: Live from York</n>    <k>It's day one of the prestigious York Ebor Meeting, with the feature race being the Juddmonte International Stakes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-21 17:00:00" d="2019-08-21 18:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point V (45)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-21 18:00:00" d="2019-08-21 19:00:00"><n u="The Chase">The Chase IX (97)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz show hosted by Bradley Walsh. Four people who have never met before - Andy, Karryn, Chris and Tom - take on the Chaser in the hope of winning thousands of pounds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-21 19:00:00" d="2019-08-21 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-21 19:30:00" d="2019-08-21 20:00:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-21 20:00:00" d="2019-08-21 20:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>Moira gives in to temptation. Kim offers to help Jamie. Leyla and David confront Jacob</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-21 20:30:00" d="2019-08-21 21:00:00"><n>Coronation Street</n>    <k>Emma feels betrayed by her entire family. Aggie reacts angrily to Michael's latest business venture. Geoff give Yasmeen cause for concern about his health</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-21 21:00:00" d="2019-08-21 21:30:00"><n u="New: The Best Little Prison in Britain? We meet Ross Senior and Ross Junior, a father and son serving time on the same wing">New: The Best Little Prison in Britain? We meet Ross Senior and Ross Junior, a father and son serving time on the same wing I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Will seeing his own son doing time be a wakeup call for Ross Senior?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-21 21:30:00" d="2019-08-21 22:00:00"><n>Coronation Street</n>    <k>Steve's paternity bombshell astounds Emma. Ed's brush with temptation prompts an overdue confession. Geoff invents symptoms to gain Yasmeen's sympathy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-21 22:00:00" d="2019-08-21 23:00:00"><n u="New: Deep Water">New: Deep Water I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lisa tries to make amends for Lucinda's disappearance but is starting to see a different side to Kate and Guy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-21 23:00:00" d="2019-08-21 23:30:00"><n>ITV News at Ten</n>    <k>ITV News at Ten provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-21 23:30:00" d="2019-08-21 23:45:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-21 23:45:00" d="2019-08-22 00:40:00"><n u="Killer Women with Piers Morgan">Killer Women with Piers Morgan II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Piers travels to Gadsden Correctional Facility near Tallahassee in Florida to meet Ashley Humphrey, who shot eight bullets into a woman that she had never met</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 00:40:00" d="2019-08-22 01:35:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable II (40)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Popcorn Sweepers
Quiz show hosted by Warwick Davis. The Popcorn Sweepers - five cinema workers from East Anglia - answer Top 10 list questions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 01:35:00" d="2019-08-22 04:00:00"><n>Ideal World With Create and Craft</n>    <k>Join Ideal World on ITV for some of the best offers and products on TV. To see more go to www.idealworld.tv</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 04:00:00" d="2019-08-22 04:50:00"><n u="Go for It">Go for It (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Stephen Mulhern sees challengers attempting to wow the nation by putting their unusual skills and implausible party tricks to the test</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 04:50:00" d="2019-08-22 06:05:00"><n>ITV Nightscreen</n>    <k>Text-based information service</k>  </p>
</a>
