<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2020-05-27 04:35:41"><p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-03 06:05:00" d="2020-06-03 07:00:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder VIII (45)</n><t>S</t>    <k>53% Arbitration show in which real small-claims cases are adjudicated over within a studio courtroom by Judge Robert Rinder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-03 07:00:00" d="2020-06-03 10:00:00"><n>Good Morning Britain</n>    <k>Breakfast show featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-03 10:00:00" d="2020-06-03 11:00:00"><n>Good Morning Britain with Lorraine</n>    <k>Lorraine Kelly joins the GMB team for an extra hour of Good Morning Britain, featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-03 11:00:00" d="2020-06-03 13:30:00"><n>This Morning</n>    <k>The This Morning team bring you top celebrity guests, lifestyle advice, stunning competitions and award-winning features, all topped off with a sprinkle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-03 13:30:00" d="2020-06-03 14:30:00"><n>Loose Women</n>    <k>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-03 14:30:00" d="2020-06-03 14:55:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-03 14:55:00" d="2020-06-03 15:00:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-03 15:00:00" d="2020-06-03 16:00:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder V (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>53% Sen v Mel
Sen is in court to claim what he is owed on loans he made to his friend. Julie is in court to claim what she is owed on a loan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-03 16:00:00" d="2020-06-03 17:00:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz show presented by Warwick Davis. The Gandhi family from Middlesex answer Top 10 list questions on subjects including EastEnders, the Jungle Book, and Formula One</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-03 17:00:00" d="2020-06-03 18:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point VI (63)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-03 18:00:00" d="2020-06-03 19:00:00"><n u="The Chase">The Chase X (116)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz show hosted by Bradley Walsh. Four contestants must pit their wits against the Chaser, a ruthless quiz genius determined to stop them winning the cash prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-03 19:00:00" d="2020-06-03 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-03 19:30:00" d="2020-06-03 20:00:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-03 20:00:00" d="2020-06-03 20:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>Jamie is worried for Andrea and Millie. Rhona is uneasy by her betrayal. Brenda wants an apology</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-03 20:30:00" d="2020-06-03 21:00:00"><n>Coronation Street</n>    <k>Alya makes a shocking discovery regarding Geoff. Asha's problems follow her to her new school. Roy invites Shona to move into his flat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-03 21:00:00" d="2020-06-03 21:30:00"><n u="New: Absolutely India: Mancs in Mumbai">New: Absolutely India: Mancs in Mumbai (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The lads meet their match when they take on a junior girl's hockey team, and they make tracks out of Mumbai for the last time on one of India's iconic trains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-03 21:30:00" d="2020-06-03 22:00:00"><n u="Paul O'Grady: For the Love of Dogs">Paul O'Grady: For the Love of Dogs VIII (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% Paul meets a nine-month-old terrier called Roo who is far too young to have puppies, but was found roaming the streets, heavily pregnant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-03 22:00:00" d="2020-06-03 23:00:00"><n>New: Bradley Walsh: Happy 60th Birthday</n>    <k>Bradley Walsh is one of the nation's favourite performers and, in honour of his 60th birthday, ITV is celebrating with a one-off special looking back at his career</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-03 23:00:00" d="2020-06-04 02:00:00"><n>ITV News at Ten</n>    <k>ITV News at Ten provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents</k>  </p>
</a>
