<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2019-08-13 02:17:40"><p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 06:05:00" d="2019-08-19 07:00:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder VI (30)</n><t>S</t>    <k>54% Mark S v Mark F
Featuring two friends in a dispute over a car sale and a tenant who hopes to claim from her landlord for the costs incurred after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 07:00:00" d="2019-08-19 09:30:00"><n>Good Morning Britain</n>    <k>Breakfast show featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 09:30:00" d="2019-08-19 10:25:00"><n>Lorraine</n>    <k>Lorraine Kelly presents a topical mix of entertainment, discussion and showbiz glamour as well as the latest fashion, food and celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 10:25:00" d="2019-08-19 11:30:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder V (59)</n><t>S</t>    <k>54% Sarah v Juliet
Sarah is in court to claim 2,625 pounds and 10 pence for a refund on a horse while Nadine is pursuing 400 pounds owed on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 11:30:00" d="2019-08-19 13:30:00"><n u="This Morning">This Morning XXXI (164)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Magazine show with news and topical items, celebrity guests, expert advice, real life stories, competitions and a mix of cookery, health, beauty, lifestyle and more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 13:30:00" d="2019-08-19 14:30:00"><n>Loose Women</n>    <k>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 14:30:00" d="2019-08-19 14:55:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 14:55:00" d="2019-08-19 15:00:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 15:00:00" d="2019-08-19 16:00:00"><n u="Dickinson's Real Deal">Dickinson's Real Deal XIII (83)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Best Of 3
David Dickinson is all aboard for the Real Deal! Tim Hogarth has double trouble over some railway tickets and Tony Geering has some saucy ladies in his sights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 16:00:00" d="2019-08-19 17:00:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable III (31)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Neo-It-Alls
Five more contestants take on the Tenable Tower and attempt to win a big cash prize. Warwick Davis hosts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 17:00:00" d="2019-08-19 18:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point V (43)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 18:00:00" d="2019-08-19 19:00:00"><n u="The Chase">The Chase IX (96)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz show hosted by Bradley Walsh. Can Gaynor, Richard, Tony and Jenny beat the Chaser and leave with thousands of pounds in prize money?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 19:00:00" d="2019-08-19 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 19:30:00" d="2019-08-19 20:00:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 20:00:00" d="2019-08-19 20:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>Charity relays some bad news. Moira's resistance weakens. Harriet is glad when Will returns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 20:30:00" d="2019-08-19 21:00:00"><n>Coronation Street</n>    <k>Bethany turns to Daniel when faced with a reminder of her past. Geoff installs security cameras in Yasmeen's house. Steve seeks a sample of Emma's DNA</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 21:00:00" d="2019-08-19 21:30:00"><n u="Ainsley's Caribbean Kitchen">Ainsley's Caribbean Kitchen I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Barbados
Barbados is the next stop on Ainsley's trip around the Caribbean, where he meets a local chef who cooks a dish of roast breadfruit with swordfish and lobster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 21:30:00" d="2019-08-19 22:00:00"><n>Coronation Street</n>    <k>Craig gets caught in the crossfire of Bethany's drama. Geoff walks out on a heartbroken Yasmeen. Aggie tackles Ed about their finances</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 22:00:00" d="2019-08-19 23:00:00"><n u="New: Long Lost Family">New: Long Lost Family IX (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In a first for Long Lost Family, this final episode includes an appeal for information on behalf of families whose loved ones have been reported missing to the police</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 23:00:00" d="2019-08-19 23:30:00"><n>ITV News at Ten</n>    <k>ITV News at Ten provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 23:30:00" d="2019-08-19 23:45:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-19 23:45:00" d="2019-08-20 00:45:00"><n>Neighbours from Hell: Caught on Camera</n>    <k>Most of us live in peace and harmony. But what's it like when the people next door become neighbours from Hell?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 00:45:00" d="2019-08-20 01:35:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable II (38)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Hashtag Lads - five friends from Hertfordshire - answer Top 10 list questions on subjects including watch brands, the Rugby World Cup, Dr Who and US Presidents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 01:35:00" d="2019-08-20 03:00:00"><n>Ideal World With Steepletone</n>    <k>Join Ideal World on ITV for some of the best offers and products on TV. To see more go to www.idealworld.tv</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 03:00:00" d="2019-08-20 04:00:00"><n>Ideal World TV</n>    <k>Join Ideal World on ITV for some of the best offers and products on TV. To see more go to www.idealworld.tv</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 04:00:00" d="2019-08-20 04:50:00"><n u="Masterpiece with Alan Titchmarsh">Masterpiece with Alan Titchmarsh I (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Series hosted by Alan Titchmarsh in which teams try to uncover the most rare and valuable pieces in a stately home. This episode's stately home is Firle Place in Sussex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-20 04:50:00" d="2019-08-20 06:05:00"><n>ITV Nightscreen</n>    <k>Text-based information service</k>  </p>
</a>
