<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="30" t="2021-07-10 05:01:06"><p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 05:05:00" d="2021-07-17 07:00:00"><n>ITV Nightscreen</n>    <k>Text-based information service</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 07:00:00" d="2021-07-17 07:10:00"><n u="Dino Dana">Dino Dana I (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% Dino Dodgeball
Series following the adventures of Dino Dana, an eight-year-old palaeontologist in training. Saara fails to pick Dana for her dodgeball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 07:10:00" d="2021-07-17 07:20:00"><n u="The Rubbish World of Dave Spud">The Rubbish World of Dave Spud I (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bog Roll Roll
It's the biggest sporting event in Grimsby - the bog roll roll. All Dave has to do is chase the bog roll down the hill and catch it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 07:20:00" d="2021-07-17 07:35:00"><n u="The Rubbish World of Dave Spud">The Rubbish World of Dave Spud I (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Spud-Ageddon
The Spuds don't care about a carbon footprint, since George has come home with a haul of free electronics that they all want to test out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 07:35:00" d="2021-07-17 07:55:00"><n u="Robozuna">Robozuna II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Off Sides
Mangle discovers that his new teammates moonlight as thieves. When Vermis hires the team to steal a crystal chip from Illex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 07:55:00" d="2021-07-17 08:00:00"><n u="LEGO Hidden Side">LEGO Hidden Side I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Carnival of Doom
Our heroes investigate a carnival after hours, but the ghost finds Jack and Parker first, knocking them out in a spooky hall of mirrors</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 08:00:00" d="2021-07-17 08:10:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (74)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% Fluffy the Fugitive
Animated comedy series following Mike the pug, as he tries to date his neighbour's dog. Mike rescues Fluffy from the raccoon's lair</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 08:10:00" d="2021-07-17 08:15:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (75)</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% And Then There Were None
Mike is forced to act when the raccoons steal the turtles. Can he be the hero needed to save the day?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 08:15:00" d="2021-07-17 08:30:00"><n u="Mr. Bean: The Animated Series">Mr. Bean: The Animated Series II (46)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% In the Garden
The animated antics of the hapless bumbler Mr Bean. Mr Bean digs a hole in his garden - and finds a bomb</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 08:30:00" d="2021-07-17 08:40:00"><n u="Mr. Bean: The Animated Series">Mr. Bean: The Animated Series II (47)</n><t>S</t>    <k>68% A Magic Day Out
Mr Bean and Irma are off for a day at the seaside, where his trunk gets accidentally swapped with that of a stage magician</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 08:40:00" d="2021-07-17 08:55:00"><n u="Hotel Transylvania">Hotel Transylvania II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>71% For Whom the Smell Tolls
Animated series based on and serving as a prequel to the popular film series. Mavis gets 'The Vapours', a next-level event</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 08:55:00" d="2021-07-17 09:25:00"><n u="Don't Unleash the Beast">Don't Unleash the Beast I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Game show set in the mythological underground world of Halian. A team of three intrepid treasure seekers face a series of obstacles in their quest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 09:25:00" d="2021-07-17 09:30:00"><n>ITV News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world as well as the latest major sports results</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 09:30:00" d="2021-07-17 10:25:00"><n u="New: Martin and Roman's Weekend Best! Martin and Roman Kemp will be filling your weekend mornings with fun chat, celebrity guests and light-hearted challenges">New: Martin and Roman's Weekend Best! Martin and Roman Kemp will be filling your weekend mornings with fun chat, celebrity guests and light-hearted challenges (27)</n><t>S</t>    <k>S2</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 10:25:00" d="2021-07-17 12:35:00"><n u="James Martin's Saturday Morning">James Martin's Saturday Morning IV (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>James is back in the kitchen on a Saturday morning, where he's serving up a feast of delicious food for former Saturdays singer and Radio One star Mollie King</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 12:35:00" d="2021-07-17 13:40:00"><n u="Cooking with the Stars">Cooking with the Stars I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The first four celebrities - Johnny Vegas, McFly's Harry Judd, Shirley Ballas and Naughty Boy - will battle it out in the kitchen as they compete</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 13:40:00" d="2021-07-17 14:10:00"><n u="James Martin's Islands to Highlands">James Martin's Islands to Highlands I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Jersey
James is joined by pal and Michelin-starred chef Mark Jordan, and together they set out to explore the delights of Jersey aboard mini motor bikes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 14:10:00" d="2021-07-17 14:25:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 14:25:00" d="2021-07-17 17:00:00"><n>ITV Racing: Live from Newbury</n>    <k>Ed Chamberlin presents action from Newbury, Market Rasen and The Curragh, including four top races from Newbury and the 2021 Irish Oaks from The Curragh</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 17:00:00" d="2021-07-17 17:30:00"><n u="You've Been Framed! Gold">You've Been Framed! Gold XXXI (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A girl squirts glue in her eyes, a man is hit by a falling sofa and a toddler fires a rocket into his sister's face</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 17:30:00" d="2021-07-17 18:30:00"><n u="Tipping Point: Lucky Stars">Tipping Point: Lucky Stars VII (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Funny man Tom Allen, Radio DJ Melvin Odoom and Corrie star Patti Clare put their wits to the test to discover if any of them have what it takes to master the machine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 18:30:00" d="2021-07-17 18:50:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world as well as the latest major sports results</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 18:50:00" d="2021-07-17 19:00:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 19:00:00" d="2021-07-17 20:00:00"><n u="The Chase: Celebrity Special">The Chase: Celebrity Special VIII (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Broadcaster Giles Coren, journalist Rachel Johnson, TV presenter Chris Packham and comedian Josie Long take on the Chaser, hoping to win thousands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 20:00:00" d="2021-07-17 21:00:00"><n u="New: Rolling In It">New: Rolling In It II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Stephen Mulhern is joined by Martine McCutcheon, Jason Manford and AJ Odudu for the game show in which everything can change on the roll of a coin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 21:00:00" d="2021-07-17 22:00:00"><n u="New: The Void">New: The Void I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ashley Banjo and Fleur East host the physical game show. Amongst those trying to win the jackpot are a circus performer, a dodgeball world champion and an amateur boxer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 22:00:00" d="2021-07-17 23:00:00"><n u="New: Who Wants To Be A Millionaire? Jeremy Clarkson welcomes six more contestants who are given the opportunity to take their place in the hot seat">New: Who Wants To Be A Millionaire? Jeremy Clarkson welcomes six more contestants who are given the opportunity to take their place in the hot seat XXXIV (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Can any of them take home the one million-pound prize?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 23:00:00" d="2021-07-17 23:35:00"><n>New: It's Clarkson on TV</n>    <k>Jeremy judges shouty Americans, manufactured jeopardy and Tony Robinson. In the studio, Jeremy wins a staring match with a dog and is very brave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 23:35:00" d="2021-07-17 23:55:00"><n>ITV News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2021-07-17 23:55:00" d="2021-07-18 02:55:00"><n>Bridget Jones's Baby</n>    <k>Comedy sequel with Renee Zellweger and Colin Firth, 2016. Single again, Bridget decides to focus on her job, but in a twist of fate finds herself pregnant</k>  </p>
</a>
