<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2020-05-28 04:38:52"><p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-04 06:05:00" d="2020-06-04 07:00:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder VIII (68)</n><t>S</t>    <k>53% Arbitration show in which real small-claims cases are adjudicated over within a studio courtroom by Judge Robert Rinder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-04 07:00:00" d="2020-06-04 10:00:00"><n>Good Morning Britain</n>    <k>Breakfast show featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-04 10:00:00" d="2020-06-04 11:00:00"><n>Good Morning Britain with Lorraine</n>    <k>Lorraine Kelly joins the GMB team for an extra hour of Good Morning Britain, featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-04 11:00:00" d="2020-06-04 13:30:00"><n>This Morning</n>    <k>The This Morning team bring you top celebrity guests, lifestyle advice, stunning competitions and award-winning features, all topped off with a sprinkle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-04 13:30:00" d="2020-06-04 14:30:00"><n>Loose Women</n>    <k>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-04 14:30:00" d="2020-06-04 14:55:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-04 14:55:00" d="2020-06-04 15:00:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-04 15:00:00" d="2020-06-04 16:00:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder V (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>53% Jonathan v Patrick
Johnny is in court to claim for non-payment of wages after he was booked to perform at a charity event, while Daniella makes a claim</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-04 16:00:00" d="2020-06-04 17:00:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Warwick Davis presents the Top 10-themed quiz show. A team of firefighters from London answer Top 10 list questions for the chance to win a big cash prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-04 17:00:00" d="2020-06-04 18:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point VI (64)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-04 18:00:00" d="2020-06-04 19:00:00"><n u="The Chase">The Chase X (118)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz show hosted by Bradley Walsh. Four contestants must pit their wits against the Chaser, a ruthless quiz genius determined to stop them winning the cash prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-04 19:00:00" d="2020-06-04 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-04 19:30:00" d="2020-06-04 20:00:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-04 20:00:00" d="2020-06-04 20:30:00"><n u="New: You've Been Framed!">New: You've Been Framed! XXXIII (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A birthday cake sets a house on fire, a toddler puts an iPad in a washing machine and a cow breaks into a home to use the swimming pool</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-04 20:30:00" d="2020-06-04 21:00:00"><n>Car Crime: Is My Car Safe? Tonight</n>    <k>Alex Beresford reports on the alarming rise in car crime over recent years. As more motorists are targeted by organised gangs, we look at what we can all do to prevent it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-04 21:00:00" d="2020-06-04 21:30:00"><n u="New: Britain's Brightest Celebrity Family">New: Britain's Brightest Celebrity Family I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Knockout tournament hosted by Anne Hegerty. This edition is a football special, featuring John Barnes and his family against Matt Le Tissier and his clan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-04 21:30:00" d="2020-06-04 22:00:00"><n u="New: The Martin Lewis Money Show Live">New: The Martin Lewis Money Show Live (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>As life in lockdown continues, Martin Lewis has up-to-the-minute advice for these financially uncertain times</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-04 22:00:00" d="2020-06-04 23:00:00"><n u="New: Unbelievable Moments: Caught On Camera">New: Unbelievable Moments: Caught On Camera V (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Clip show hosted by Alastair Stewart, featuring incredible clips of astonishing eyewitness footage, shot by members of the public on mobile devices</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-06-04 23:00:00" d="2020-06-05 02:00:00"><n>ITV News at Ten</n>    <k>ITV News at Ten provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents</k>  </p>
</a>
