<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="17" t="2020-04-16 04:34:11"><p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-23 06:05:00" d="2020-04-23 07:00:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder VIII (34)</n><t>S</t>    <k>53% Arbitration show in which real small-claims cases are adjudicated over within a studio courtroom by Judge Robert Rinder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-23 07:00:00" d="2020-04-23 10:00:00"><n>Good Morning Britain</n>    <k>Breakfast show featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-23 10:00:00" d="2020-04-23 11:00:00"><n>Good Morning Britain with Lorraine</n>    <k>Lorraine Kelly joins the GMB team for an extra hour of Good Morning Britain, featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-23 11:00:00" d="2020-04-23 13:30:00"><n>This Morning</n>    <k>The This Morning team bring you top celebrity guests, lifestyle advice, stunning competitions and award-winning features, all topped off with a sprinkle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-23 13:30:00" d="2020-04-23 14:30:00"><n>Loose Women</n>    <k>Burlesque performer and model Dita Von Teese joins the Loose Women panel to talk about her appearance at Jean Paul Gaultier's final fashion show before his retirement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-23 14:30:00" d="2020-04-23 14:55:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-23 14:55:00" d="2020-04-23 15:00:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-23 15:00:00" d="2020-04-23 16:00:00"><n u="New: James Martin's Islands to Highlands">New: James Martin's Islands to Highlands I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Isle of Man
James is joined by Michelin-starred chef Lisa Goodwin-Allen, and they pay a visit to the Isle of Man during the famous TT race warm-up week</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-23 16:00:00" d="2020-04-23 17:00:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable IV (26)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Truly Scrum-Tious
A touch rugby team from the South West play to take home a big cash prize by answering a series of Top 10 list questions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-23 17:00:00" d="2020-04-23 18:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point IX (49)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning a cash jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-23 18:00:00" d="2020-04-23 19:00:00"><n u="The Chase">The Chase X (69)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz show hosted by Bradley Walsh. Four contestants must pit their wits against the Chaser, a ruthless quiz genius determined to stop them winning the cash prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-23 19:00:00" d="2020-04-23 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-23 19:30:00" d="2020-04-23 20:00:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-23 20:00:00" d="2020-04-23 20:30:00"><n u="New: You've Been Framed!">New: You've Been Framed! XXX (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A selection of hilarious home videos sent in by members of the public and presented in a much-loved format to entertain people of all ages</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-23 20:30:00" d="2020-04-23 21:00:00"><n>Keeping Britain Fed? Tonight</n>    <k>As Britain and Europe remain locked down in the fight against Coronavirus, Tonight asks how seriously our food supply chain is being affected</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-23 21:00:00" d="2020-04-23 21:30:00"><n>New: The Martin Lewis Money Show - A Coronavirus Special</n>    <k>As everyday life in lockdown continues Martin Lewis has up to the minute advice for those who have found themselves in financial uncertainty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2020-04-23 21:30:00" d="2020-04-24 00:30:00"><n u="Secrets of the Driving Test">Secrets of the Driving Test I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Grandma Wendy's confident she's going to pass but is barely in the driving seat before nerves take over. Meanwhile, Shaunna's back with a new secret weapon</k>  </p>
</a>
