<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2019-08-15 22:44:48"><p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 06:05:00" d="2019-08-22 07:00:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder VI (34)</n><t>S</t>    <k>54% Lyndsey v Stevie
Criminal barrister Robert Rinder presides over two cases, featuring two women who are taking on a bespoke bed company and a car dispute</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 07:00:00" d="2019-08-22 09:30:00"><n>Good Morning Britain</n>    <k>Breakfast show featuring the latest news, sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 09:30:00" d="2019-08-22 10:25:00"><n>Lorraine</n>    <k>Lorraine Kelly presents a topical mix of entertainment, discussion and showbiz glamour as well as the latest fashion, food and celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 10:25:00" d="2019-08-22 11:30:00"><n u="Judge Rinder">Judge Rinder III (66)</n><t>S</t>    <k>54% Judge Rinder presides over a case concerning outstanding rent, another involving an unpaid Christmas loan and another involving a dispute over property after a separation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 11:30:00" d="2019-08-22 13:30:00"><n u="This Morning">This Morning XXXI (167)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Magazine show with news and topical items, celebrity guests, expert advice, real life stories, competitions and a mix of cookery, health, beauty, lifestyle and more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 13:30:00" d="2019-08-22 14:00:00"><n>Loose Women</n>    <k>Join the Loose Women panellists as they interview celebrity guests and discuss the day's most topical issues, from current affairs to celebrity gossip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 14:00:00" d="2019-08-22 14:20:00"><n>ITV Lunchtime News</n>    <k>The latest headlines from around the world at lunchtime with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents, all of which are followed by a national weather forecast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 14:20:00" d="2019-08-22 14:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 14:30:00" d="2019-08-22 17:00:00"><n>ITV Racing: Live from York</n>    <k>Francesca Cumani and Ed Chamberlin present coverage of day two of the Ebor festival, headlined by the Yorkshire Oaks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 17:00:00" d="2019-08-22 18:00:00"><n u="Tipping Point">Tipping Point V (61)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben Shephard hosts the quiz show in which four players take on an extraordinary machine in the hope of winning the 10,000 pound jackpot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 18:00:00" d="2019-08-22 19:00:00"><n u="The Chase">The Chase IX (132)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz show hosted by Bradley Walsh. Four people who have never met before, Kris, Paschal, Michelle and Gaynor join forces in an attempt to take home thousands of pounds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 19:00:00" d="2019-08-22 19:30:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 19:30:00" d="2019-08-22 20:00:00"><n>ITV Evening News</n>    <k>National and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents in the UK and around the world, plus a focus on the stories that matter to you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 20:00:00" d="2019-08-22 20:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>Jacob prepares to receive his exam results. Kim makes secret plans. Jai takes his frustrations out on Laurel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 20:30:00" d="2019-08-22 21:00:00"><n>The Trouble with Garden Centres? Tonight</n>    <k>Britain is blooming and garden centres are booming. But are we truly aware of how green our garden centres really are? This programme digs up some surprising stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 21:00:00" d="2019-08-22 21:30:00"><n>Emmerdale</n>    <k>Priya is shocked by an accusation. Tracy is in denial. Moira hides her rising panic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 21:30:00" d="2019-08-22 22:00:00"><n u="New: Eat, Shop, Save">New: Eat, Shop, Save III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Presenter Ranvir Singh and her team of experts are in Northamptonshire with the Thomas family, helping spark new ideas for healthy, cheap meals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 22:00:00" d="2019-08-22 23:00:00"><n>David Walliams Presents Revenge of Alright on the Night</n>    <k>David Walliams presents Revenge of Alright on the Night - featuring a selection of classic outtakes and previously unseen bloopers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 23:00:00" d="2019-08-22 23:30:00"><n>ITV News at Ten</n>    <k>ITV News at Ten provides a fresh perspective on the major stories of the day with national and international news with reports and analysis from ITV's Correspondents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 23:30:00" d="2019-08-22 23:45:00"><n>ITV News London</n>    <k>The latest news and weather from London and the South East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-22 23:45:00" d="2019-08-23 00:40:00"><n u="Long Lost Family">Long Lost Family IX (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In a first for Long Lost Family, this final episode includes an appeal for information on behalf of families whose loved ones have been reported missing to the police</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-23 00:40:00" d="2019-08-23 01:35:00"><n u="Tenable">Tenable II (41)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz show hosted by Warwick Davis. A team of five neighbours from Lancashire take on the Tenable Tower and answer Top 10 list questions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-23 01:35:00" d="2019-08-23 03:00:00"><n>Ideal World With Tefal</n>    <k>Join Ideal World on ITV for some of the best offers and products on TV. To see more go to www.idealworld.tv</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-23 03:00:00" d="2019-08-23 04:00:00"><n>Ideal World With Rug Doctor</n>    <k>Join Ideal World on ITV for some of the best offers and products on TV. To see more go to www.idealworld.tv</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-23 04:00:00" d="2019-08-23 04:25:00"><n u="Eat, Shop, Save">Eat, Shop, Save III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Presenter Ranvir Singh and her team of experts are in Northamptonshire with the Thomas family, helping spark new ideas for healthy, cheap meals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1076" o="2019-08-23 04:25:00" d="2019-08-23 06:05:00"><n>ITV Nightscreen</n>    <k>Text-based information service</k>  </p>
</a>
