<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="35" t="2020-04-12 04:29:22"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 05:30:00" d="2020-04-19 05:55:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>R</e>    <k>Time Share: Adam and Jennifer agree to go away with Jeff and Audrey, even though they must sit through a timeshare sales pitch in order to get a deal on the trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 05:55:00" d="2020-04-19 06:15:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>R</e>    <k>Jen at Work: Adam and Jennifer realise that living and working together is harder than they anticipated when he hires her to do some freelance work for his company</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 06:15:00" d="2020-04-19 07:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>R</e>    <k>Optimal Male: Jeff struggles to lose enough weight to be eligible for the 'optimal male' fitness category in his life insurance exam. Jennifer frets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 07:00:00" d="2020-04-19 08:25:00"><n>Hollyoaks: Omnibus</n><t>S</t>    <k>49% Hollyoaks Omnibus
Jordan sends Sid and Juliet to the seaside to make a delivery. Nancy decides to tell Kyle's parents about their engagement. Scott urges</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 08:25:00" d="2020-04-19 09:25:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n>    <k>Gordon Ramsay heads to Sushi Ko in California, where owners Akira and Lisa are losing up to $20,000 a month. Can Gordon piece the family back together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 09:25:00" d="2020-04-19 10:30:00"><n>Don't Tell the Bride</n><e>R</e>    <k>Harry wants a royal wedding and to be King for the day. But bride-to-be Charlotte wants something low key. Will this be Harry's crowning moment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 10:30:00" d="2020-04-19 11:00:00"><n u="Man with a Plan">Man with a Plan II</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Brand new series - We Hate Money: Adam and Don realise they need to bring in more business, so film a commercial for their firm. And Andi works</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 11:00:00" d="2020-04-19 11:30:00"><n u="Man with a Plan">Man with a Plan II</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Brand new series - We Got a Girl: Adam and Andi set up Adam's boss on a date to boost her spirits hoping she'll then be in the mood to have Adam resume</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 11:30:00" d="2020-04-19 12:00:00"><n u="Man with a Plan">Man with a Plan II</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Brand new series - Family Business: Andi proposes an exciting idea for Adam and her to go into business together when she isn't able to find work. Ep21)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 12:00:00" d="2020-04-19 12:30:00"><n u="Man with a Plan">Man with a Plan III</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Brand new series - Wife-Proof: Adam attempts to make the office more inviting since Andi will be joining him at work every day. And Lowell has been hiding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 12:30:00" d="2020-04-19 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (7)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Lucky: Barry badgers Murray into getting him a puppy. Beverly wants to join in with Erica and Lainey's pyjama party, but the girls exclude her from the event</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 13:00:00" d="2020-04-19 13:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (8)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>In Conclusion, Thanksgiving: Adam exploits his father's soft spot for a popular song. Beverly wants Murray to invite his grouchy dad to Thanksgiving dinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 13:30:00" d="2020-04-19 14:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (9)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Wingmom: Murray agrees to let Barry join the junior Reserve Officers Training Corps, but when the going gets tough Barry begs Beverly to get him out of it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 14:00:00" d="2020-04-19 14:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (10)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>A Christmas Story: Beverly begins to worry that the family's holiday traditions have grown stale, so she launches a new celebration called 'Super Hanukkah'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 14:30:00" d="2020-04-19 16:30:00"><n>Eragon</n><e>R</e>    <k>Action-packed fantasy. Despotic ruler Galbatorix (John Malkovich) thinks he has exterminated all the Dragon Riders, but one survives to challenge his reign</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 16:30:00" d="2020-04-19 17:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VII</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Brand new series - The Beverly Goldberg Cookbook: Part 2: When a publisher shows interest in her recipes, Beverly prepares to finally realise her dream</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 17:00:00" d="2020-04-19 17:30:00"><n u="Schooled">Schooled II</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Brand new series - The Pokemon Society: Learning he's not into baseball cards, Coach Mellor encourages Toby to be competitive in CB's Pokemon club. Ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 17:30:00" d="2020-04-19 18:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine III (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% New Captain: After Holt is transferred to the NYPD Department of Public Relations, the arrival of a new captain causes the precinct to dissolve into chaos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 18:00:00" d="2020-04-19 18:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine III (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% The Funeral: The precinct gets another personnel change, putting Peralta and Santiago's budding relationship at risk. Boyle is attracted to a fellow officer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 18:30:00" d="2020-04-19 19:00:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon III</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Brand new series - An Academic Crime and a More Romantic Taco Bell: Dr Sturgis is mad when Sheldon accuses him of plagiarism. Mary finds a girl trophy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 19:00:00" d="2020-04-19 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (14)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Troll Manifestation: Leonard and Sheldon co-publish a physics paper but are forced to defend themselves against negative comments from an online critic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 19:30:00" d="2020-04-19 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (15)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Comic Book Store Regeneration: The gang prepare for the reopening of Stuart's comic book shop. Penny teaches Sheldon to 'let it go' when he is irritated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 20:00:00" d="2020-04-19 20:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (16)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Intimacy Acceleration: When the gang hear about an experiment designed to make participants fall in love, Sheldon and Penny put it to the test as a joke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 20:30:00" d="2020-04-19 21:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (17)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Colonization Application: Amy learns that Sheldon has applied to take part in a one-way mission to colonise Mars. Leonard surprises Penny with a gift</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 21:00:00" d="2020-04-19 21:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (18)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Leftover Thermalization: A power cut at Mrs Wolowitz's house defrosts the last meal she prepared before her death, so the gang consume it in her honour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 21:30:00" d="2020-04-19 22:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (19)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Skywalker Incursion: When Leonard and Sheldon are invited to speak at Berkeley, they take a detour during the journey to try to meet one of their idols</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 22:00:00" d="2020-04-19 23:00:00"><n>Batwoman</n><t>S</t>    <k>41% New: Batwoman
Brand new series - Who Are You?: A new villain drops in on the city. Kate attempts to find a balance between her personal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 23:00:00" d="2020-04-20 00:00:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction I</n><e>R</e>    <k>DJ Darryl is used to seeing women all dressed up in clubs. Will stripping everything back help? And Ania is looking for a mate who won't disappoint</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-20 00:00:00" d="2020-04-20 01:05:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction I</n><e>R</e>    <k>Tracy's been single for three years and hopes the revealing dating show will find her a man. Phone salesman Matthew is bored of dating apps and wants girls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-20 01:05:00" d="2020-04-20 02:05:00"><n u="Supernatural">Supernatural XIV</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Supernatural
Brand new series - Mint Condition: Sam must think fast when action figures come to life and our heroes find themselves in a real-life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-20 02:05:00" d="2020-04-20 02:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (20)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Fortification Implementation: When Sheldon and Amy build a blanket fort, they come to a major crossroads in their relationship. Howard meets his half-brother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-20 02:35:00" d="2020-04-20 03:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (21)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Communication Deterioration: Raj is asked to create a message for Nasa to use if one of their missions finds alien life. Penny considers taking up acting again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-20 03:00:00" d="2020-04-20 03:50:00"><n>Batwoman</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>41% Brand new series - Who Are You?: A new villain drops in on the city. Kate attempts to find a balance between her personal life and her new role as Gotham's guardian. (Ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-20 03:50:00" d="2020-04-20 04:45:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction I</n><e>R</e>    <k>DJ Darryl is used to seeing women all dressed up in clubs. Will stripping everything back help? And Ania is looking for a mate who won't disappoint</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-20 04:45:00" d="2020-04-20 07:45:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>R</e>    <k>Russell's Secret: Audrey discovers that Russell is a closet Broadway musical fan, and uses this knowledge to blackmail him for tickets. Adam and Jennifer</k>  </p>
</a>
