<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="39" t="2019-08-13 02:07:32"><p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 07:00:00" d="2019-08-19 07:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Stuart and Jonny have an alarming secret plan, which is discovered by an intruder. Goldie is burning all of her clothes from her exes, and Mercedes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 07:30:00" d="2019-08-19 08:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>It's Jack and Breda's secret wedding day, but Breda has pressing matters to attend to. She tells Joel in the confession box that someone in her family has sinned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 08:00:00" d="2019-08-19 08:30:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Jeff Day: When Jeff proclaims that it's 'Jeff Day', everything goes swimmingly until the cleaning lady arrives. Adam is baffled when his eye keeps twitching</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 08:30:00" d="2019-08-19 09:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Zygote: Jeff and Audrey go to a surrogacy seminar with their surrogate, Brenda, but Jeff is sceptical about the new age advice given to help the implantation process</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 09:00:00" d="2019-08-19 09:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother IX (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% The End of the Aisle: With only 30 minutes before the wedding, both Robin and Barney are having panic attacks, and Lily and Marshall think about their own wedding vows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 09:30:00" d="2019-08-19 10:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother IX (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Last Forever (Part 1/2): With Barney and Robin's wedding day over, Ted says goodbye to the gang and prepares to leave for a new life in Chicago, but fate has other plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 10:00:00" d="2019-08-19 10:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Toledo's Next Top Model: Lennox seeks Mel's permission when she is asked to become a model. Mel isn't keen on the idea until she finds out how much Lennox could earn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 10:30:00" d="2019-08-19 11:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% The Mel Word: When Mel's cousin Emily gets engaged to her girlfriend Bianca, Mel plans their wedding, but it seems one of the brides-to-be has her eye on somebody else</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 11:00:00" d="2019-08-19 11:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% I'm Not That Guy: Riley asks Ben to be her date at a work party but Ben's efforts to prove he is dependable fall short. Tucker schemes to go out with a model</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 11:30:00" d="2019-08-19 12:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% There's Something Fitchy Going On: Ben discovers a shocking secret about Riley's new beau Fitch. Things heat up between Danny and his new girlfriend Milena</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 12:00:00" d="2019-08-19 12:30:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless I (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>P-r--Prom: It's prom night, and all three DiMeo kids are going, leaving Maya and Jimmy with a rare night to themselves, in which they analyse past arguments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 12:30:00" d="2019-08-19 13:00:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless I (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>M-a--May-Jay: Maya is excited to spend the school summer holidays with JJ, but he and Kenneth have other plans. Dylan's identity in the family is threatened</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 13:00:00" d="2019-08-19 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Christmas: When Captain Holt gets death threats, Peralta must run his security. Santiago tries to take a precinct Christmas photo for Holt, but Diaz won't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 13:30:00" d="2019-08-19 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Pontiac Bandit: In order to catch the Pontiac Bandit, a car thief he has been tracking for years, Peralta tries to make a deal with a suspect Diaz has just arrested</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 14:00:00" d="2019-08-19 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory V (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Countdown Reflection: Bernadette decides that she wants to get married to Howard before his Nasa space mission takes place, but can they get organised in time?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 14:30:00" d="2019-08-19 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Date Night Variable: Howard gets caught in a row between his mum and Bernadette while he's at the International Space Station. Sheldon invites</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 15:00:00" d="2019-08-19 15:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (27)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Play Ball: Mel recruits Joe to play for her office's softball team when their star player is injured. Ryder asks Lennox to post Holly's story on the school blog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 15:30:00" d="2019-08-19 16:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (28)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% A House Divided: Mel and Joe get into an unexpected property dispute with their neighbour. Ryder makes a short film about not texting while driving, starring Lennox</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 16:00:00" d="2019-08-19 16:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Whatever Lola Wants: Ben offers to dog-sit for his girlfriend Megan but the dog doesn't seem to like him much. Danny hires two cute girls to clean the apartment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 16:30:00" d="2019-08-19 17:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% The Christening: Ben convinces Bonnie and Ray to invite conservative Aunt Betty to Emma's baptism in the hopes she'll write a nice fat cheque for Emma</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 17:00:00" d="2019-08-19 17:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Unsolvable: Peralta and Jeffords tackle a cold case that everyone thinks is unsolvable, while Santiago plans a romantic weekend away with her new boyfriend Teddy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 17:30:00" d="2019-08-19 18:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Charges and Specs: Peralta suspects a civic leader of money laundering but his investigation is shut down by the police commissioner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 18:00:00" d="2019-08-19 18:30:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>S-t--Star W--Wars W--Wars: Two tickets to a film premiere promise a glorious night for JJ and Ray, until JJ is drawn to the dark side by a pretty classmate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 18:30:00" d="2019-08-19 19:00:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>S-i--Silent N-i--Night: After putting JJ under pressure to get a new dog, Dylan takes a vow of silence to better understand what it's like to be her brother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 19:00:00" d="2019-08-19 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Fish Guts Displacement: Sheldon begrudgingly takes care of Amy when she is sick. Bernadette arranges for Howard to go on a fishing trip with her macho father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 19:30:00" d="2019-08-19 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Santa Simulation: Sheldon unwillingly reveals painful memories of Christmas past when Leonard persuades him to join in with a seasonal game of Dungeons &amp; Dragons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 20:00:00" d="2019-08-19 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>The village is shaken by the disturbing discovery. The walls are closing in on Breda, but she will manage to talk her way out of it? Damon has a big idea to show Maxine how special she is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 20:30:00" d="2019-08-19 21:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>There Can Be Only One Highlander Club: Adam and Johnny Atkins compete to become head of the Highlander Club at school, though Beverly would prefer them to bond. Ep16)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 21:00:00" d="2019-08-19 21:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Tattler: Peralta and Gina attend their 20-year high school reunion. Boyle helps Diaz with a decision. A radio show mystery sound contest baffles the guys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 21:30:00" d="2019-08-19 22:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Four Movements: Gina plays a game of chess with Captain Holt, goes out for lunch with Diaz and Santiago and infiltrates an expensive social club with Peralta</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 22:00:00" d="2019-08-19 23:00:00"><n u="Celebs Go Dating">Celebs Go Dating VII (12)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>54% New: Celebs Go Dating
Brand new series: It's speed dating time for Megan, Demi, Chloe and Lauren, but two of the girls fancy the same guy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 23:00:00" d="2019-08-20 00:10:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates X</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Tall, handsome J wants to prove there's more to him than meets the eye. Stuart and his ex-wife Mandy come to the First Dates restaurant together for a date each. Ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 00:10:00" d="2019-08-20 00:40:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Fuzzyboots Corollary: Leonard is depressed when he discovers that Penny is seeing someone, so he summons up the courage to ask a woman out on a date</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 00:40:00" d="2019-08-20 01:10:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Luminous Fish Effect: Getting fired forces Sheldon to ponder life outside physics, leaving Leonard to take drastic action to snap his friend out of his reverie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 01:10:00" d="2019-08-20 01:35:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Golden Child: Peralta helps Santiago to navigate the complicated relationship she has with her brother. Boyle introduces drama into an undercover mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 01:35:00" d="2019-08-20 02:10:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Gintars: Boyle and Peralta investigate Nikolaj's family. Holt and Santiago bring in forensic scientist Dr Yee to help close a difficult murder case for Diaz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 02:10:00" d="2019-08-20 03:10:00"><n u="Celebs Go Dating">Celebs Go Dating VII (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>54% Brand new series: It's speed dating time for Megan, Demi, Chloe and Lauren, but two of the girls fancy the same guy. Jack heads off on his second date with Tilly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 03:10:00" d="2019-08-20 04:05:00"><n u="First Dates Hotel">First Dates Hotel III</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Are Spurs fan Ryland and West Ham-supporting Amanda a match made in heaven? Meanwhile, First Dates waitress Laura gives an unhappy couple a shoulder to cry on. Ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 04:05:00" d="2019-08-20 05:00:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox VI</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Britain's favourite viewers on: Doctor Foster, The X Factor, Last Night of the Proms, This Is England '90, Britain's Biggest Adventure with Bear Grylls</k>  </p>
</a>
