<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="42" t="2020-05-27 04:34:06"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 05:00:00" d="2020-06-03 05:25:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Love Spell Potential: When the girls' trip to Las Vegas falls through, the guys invite them to a Dungeons &amp; Dragons night that changes Sheldon and Amy's relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 05:25:00" d="2020-06-03 05:50:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Bon Voyage Reaction: Leonard is offered an exciting job opportunity that will keep him out of the country for several months. Raj pushes the boundaries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 05:50:00" d="2020-06-03 06:15:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch VI (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Cloud Ten: After having her story about a refuse collection strike rejected by the newspaper and then being ignored by her roommates, Sabrina takes a wild, escapist trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 06:15:00" d="2020-06-03 07:00:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch VI (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Sabrina and the Candidate: Sabrina writes a scathing article exposing the shady dealings of a local politician, only to discover he has been anonymously</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 07:00:00" d="2020-06-03 07:30:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>The Home Stretch: Audrey has private Pilates sessions at home and Jeff is thrilled when the workouts increase her sex drive, but less pleased when he sees her instructor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 07:30:00" d="2020-06-03 08:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Uh-Oh It's Magic: Russell takes his date Jessica to a magic show, only to see the magician make her disappear and not return. Illusionist Criss Angel guest stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 08:00:00" d="2020-06-03 08:30:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch VI (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>I Think I Love You: Josh tells Sabrina he loves her and she attempts to reciprocate, but every time she tries to profess her affection the words</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 08:30:00" d="2020-06-03 09:00:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch VI (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Arrangement: Great Aunt Irma turns up with a witch named Peter and claims that Sabrina must marry him immediately. But things get more complex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 09:00:00" d="2020-06-03 09:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% The Honeymooners: Mel is disappointed when her honeymoon to Tahiti is cancelled because she has broken her leg, so Joe surprises her with a romantic getaway</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 09:30:00" d="2020-06-03 10:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% The Day After: When Dani wants to go on a date with a boy from school, Joe tells her that she's not allowed, so she tricks Mel into taking her along instead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 10:00:00" d="2020-06-03 10:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Go Brit or Go Home: Riley asks a reluctant Ben to hang out with her new British boyfriend Philip. Tucker fakes a British accent while trying to attract dates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 10:30:00" d="2020-06-03 11:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% An Affair Not to Remember: A horrified Ben realises he once dated Tucker's new girlfriend. Riley is excited when she is invited to a spa day with her boss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 11:00:00" d="2020-06-03 11:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Hofstadter Insufficiency: Sheldon and Penny bond while Leonard is away. Raj finds someone to share his heartache. Bernadette and Amy attract</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 11:30:00" d="2020-06-03 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Deception Verification: Leonard returns early from his research expedition as a surprise for Penny, but Sheldon becomes upset that he wasn't in on the secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 12:00:00" d="2020-06-03 12:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>I Heart Video Dating: Erica and Lainey try to set Bill up with a 'woman of interest' by using new video dating technology. Barry decides to become a gym teacher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 12:30:00" d="2020-06-03 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>George! George Glass!: Adam risks bodily harm during a game of paintball to impress his latest crush, and Erica pretends she has a college-aged boyfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 13:00:00" d="2020-06-03 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Charges and Specs: Peralta suspects a civic leader of money laundering but his investigation is shut down by the police commissioner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 13:30:00" d="2020-06-03 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Undercover: Peralta enlists Boyle's help to track down a missing mobster, Holt tests the squad's patience with practice drills, and Gina pleads with Boyle to keep a secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 14:00:00" d="2020-06-03 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Retraction Reaction: Leonard angers the university during an embarrassing interview. Amy and Bernadette must hide their success from Sheldon and Howard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 14:30:00" d="2020-06-03 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Relaxation Integration: Amy tries to convince Sheldon that he has a more laid-back side. Raj and Stuart compete to woo Bernadette's new colleague Ruchi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 15:00:00" d="2020-06-03 15:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% You Little Devil: Joe loses his swagger in the bedroom when he learns about the romantic significance of a little devil tattoo that Mel has on her rear end</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 15:30:00" d="2020-06-03 16:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% The Early Shift: Joe gets a new job as the lifestyle correspondent on a local morning television show but he is required to get up very early every day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 16:00:00" d="2020-06-03 16:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Foos It or Lose It: Bonnie baby-proofs the flat and sells the table football game to a student fraternity. Riley is not happy that Danny is dating Georgie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 16:30:00" d="2020-06-03 17:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% All Aboard the Love Train: Riley plans to attend her family reunion in Florida, so Ben volunteers to tag along. Tucker gets the chance to co-host a TV show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 17:00:00" d="2020-06-03 17:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Pontiac Bandit Returns: Doug Judy is back in custody after scamming Peralta and Diaz when they last met, but Captain Holt offers him a plea deal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 17:30:00" d="2020-06-03 18:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Stakeout: Peralta and Boyle go on an eight-day stakeout, putting a strain on their friendship. Holt's nephew visits and makes an instant impression on Diaz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 18:00:00" d="2020-06-03 18:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Snow Day: Adam and Barry take advantage of Murray when they discover that he has a fear of snow. Erica isn't pleased when Beverly finds her college application</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 18:30:00" d="2020-06-03 19:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Agassi: Adam tries to join the school tennis team to stay close to his best friend Chad, while Beverly helps Erica to get through her post-break-up depression</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 19:00:00" d="2020-06-03 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Matrimonial Metric: Sheldon and Amy secretly test their friends to see who is the most qualified to act as best man and maid of honour at their wedding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 19:30:00" d="2020-06-03 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Solo Oscillation: Amy and Leonard bond over some experiments. Bert replaces Howard in his band. Penny gives Sheldon unexpected scientific inspiration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 20:00:00" d="2020-06-03 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks Favourites</n><e>F</e>    <k>A look back at a classic Hollyoaks villain. It's Halloween in the village, and serial killer Silas Blissett strikes again as he decides that 'Catwoman'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 20:30:00" d="2020-06-03 21:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Slump: Peralta has a growing number of crime cases that he can't seem to solve. Holt asks Santiago to take charge of a community outreach programme for at-risk youth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 21:00:00" d="2020-06-03 22:00:00"><n u="Gogglesprogs">Gogglesprogs II (2)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>The Gogglesprogs share their honest and hilarious reactions to our top TV, including, in this episode, the election, Come Dine with Me, and Mrs Doubtfire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 22:00:00" d="2020-06-03 23:00:00"><n>Celebrity Gogglebox USA</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Celebrity Gogglebox USA
Brand new series: Gogglebox heads across the pond and steps into the homes of a selection of celebrity faces, including</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 23:00:00" d="2020-06-04 00:00:00"><n u="Celebrity Gogglebox">Celebrity Gogglebox I</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>From First Dates to Serengeti what do Jessie J, Jamal Edwards, Chris Eubank Sr, Chris Eubank Jr, Martin and Roman Kemp, Nick Grimshaw and other famous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 00:00:00" d="2020-06-04 01:00:00"><n u="Buffy the Vampire Slayer">Buffy the Vampire Slayer I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Witch: A witch attempts to eliminate Buffy from a cheerleading competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 01:00:00" d="2020-06-04 01:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The White Asparagus Triangulation: Sheldon is delighted that Leonard has finally found a girlfriend who matches up to his high standards. perhaps a little too delighted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 01:30:00" d="2020-06-04 02:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Vartabedian Conundrum: Leonard goes to Penny for help when his relationship with Stephanie takes off faster than he'd like, but will he choose to act on her advice?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 02:00:00" d="2020-06-04 03:05:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Cathy wants to settle down and have kids. Adam, who's 24, hates online dating. Will baring all help them find their perfect partner?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 03:05:00" d="2020-06-04 04:00:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates V</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Will hairdresser Lauren fall for party boy Danny's perma-tan chutzpah, or will his Dutch courage put her off? And Paolo returns; can Mario handle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 04:00:00" d="2020-06-04 04:55:00"><n u="Celebrity Gogglebox">Celebrity Gogglebox I</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>From First Dates to Serengeti what do Jessie J, Jamal Edwards, Chris Eubank Sr, Chris Eubank Jr, Martin and Roman Kemp, Nick Grimshaw and other famous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 04:55:00" d="2020-06-04 05:20:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Hofstadter Insufficiency: Sheldon and Penny bond while Leonard is away. Raj finds someone to share his heartache. Bernadette and Amy attract</k>  </p>
</a>
