<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="39" t="2020-05-25 04:47:08"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 05:45:00" d="2020-06-01 07:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks: Omnibus</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>49% Hollyoaks Omnibus
Nancy gives Kyle some tough love: can Darren help him to prove himself? Tony starts his new medication. Tom makes a bold move</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 07:00:00" d="2020-06-01 07:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Kyle makes a shocking discovery. Tony starts his new medication, prescribed by manipulative Edward. Tom makes a move that doesn't go down well with Yazz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 07:30:00" d="2020-06-01 08:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nancy struggles to trust a spiralling Kyle to look after Oscar: can Darren help Kyle prove himself? Mercedes has had enough of Sylver's behaviour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 08:00:00" d="2020-06-01 08:30:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch VI (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>A Birthday Witch: Sabrina's birthday plans are interrupted when Great Aunt Irma pays a visit. She has come to test Harvey's trustworthiness because</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 08:30:00" d="2020-06-01 09:00:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch VI (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Deliver Us from E-mail: Sabrina gets the chance to have her own newspaper column, but things go awry when her evil twin Katrina gives her a virus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 09:00:00" d="2020-06-01 09:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Maybe I'm Amazed: After Mel drops a bombshell on Joe during their wedding ceremony, he is forced to make a decision in a hurry that could affect their marriage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 09:30:00" d="2020-06-01 10:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% At Last: Still reeling from the unexpected news at the wedding, Joe issues an impulsive invitation without consulting Mel first, putting their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 10:00:00" d="2020-06-01 10:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Life's a Beach: When Ben's rooftop beach gets shut down by Sondra, the president of the board of the apartment building, the boys campaign to overthrow her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 10:30:00" d="2020-06-01 11:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Romancing the Phone: Ben finds a mobile phone belonging to an attractive young woman and arranges to meet her. Bonnie tries to create a new business slogan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 11:00:00" d="2020-06-01 11:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Closure Alternative: Amy employs a series of exercises to cure Sheldon of his compulsion to complete every task without fail and seek closure for every incident</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 11:30:00" d="2020-06-01 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Proton Resurgence: Leonard and Sheldon hire Professor Proton, the host of a TV science show they watched as children, to come to their flat and entertain them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 12:00:00" d="2020-06-01 12:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Smother's Day: Barry and Erica forget to buy Beverly a Mother's Day present and make some last-minute 'Mom Coupons' instead, hurting her feelings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 12:30:00" d="2020-06-01 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Big Orange: Beverly and Lainey hatch a plan to destroy Barry's favourite shirt. Murray decides to tear down the family tree house, leaving Adam distraught</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 13:00:00" d="2020-06-01 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Apartment: Peralta is in danger of losing his flat but has no money to buy his own place, so Gina tries to help him find a new home. The officers do self-evaluations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 13:30:00" d="2020-06-01 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Tactical Village: The officers attend mandatory training exercises in which all regional precincts compete. Captain Holt becomes addicted to a game on his smartphone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 14:00:00" d="2020-06-01 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Cognition Regeneration: Leonard isn't thrilled when he finds out Penny is considering taking a new job that has been offered by her ex-boyfriend Zack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 14:30:00" d="2020-06-01 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Gyroscopic Collapse: Amy is offered a fellowship at Princeton, Raj makes new living arrangements, and the guys' gyroscope project spins out of control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 15:00:00" d="2020-06-01 15:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Being There: Hoping to improve face-to-face communication within the family, Joe puts a ban on the use of all mobile phones and computers over the weekend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 15:30:00" d="2020-06-01 16:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Parental Guidance: Joe is furious when he finds out that Dani invited some older friends over to the house and they drank his expensive bottle of wine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 16:00:00" d="2020-06-01 16:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% From Here to Paternity: Riley tries to find her biological father, using her parents' high school yearbook as a guide, and locates two possible candidates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 16:30:00" d="2020-06-01 17:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Curious Georgie: Riley is thrilled when Philip's sister Georgie visits from England. Danny's new contract negotiations with the Rangers are put in jeopardy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 17:00:00" d="2020-06-01 17:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Jake and Sophia: Peralta hits it off with a woman in a bar, only to find out she is the defence attorney representing a perpetrator he wants to put in jail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 17:30:00" d="2020-06-01 18:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Lockdown: Peralta is left in charge of the precinct at Thanksgiving because Holt and Jeffords are away, but chaos ensues when a strange package is delivered</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 18:00:00" d="2020-06-01 18:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Greatest Musical Ever Written: Barry makes fun of Adam for taking part in a school musical. Beverly's job as a substitute teacher causes problems for Erica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 18:30:00" d="2020-06-01 19:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Globetrotters: When Adam creates a video that makes it look as though he and his friends beat Barry in a game of basketball, Barry demands a rematch in the gym</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 19:00:00" d="2020-06-01 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Tesla Recoil: Leonard and Howard learn that Sheldon went to work with the military behind their backs. Bernadette thinks Ruchi's trying to steal her job</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 19:30:00" d="2020-06-01 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Bitcoin Entanglement: Sheldon seeks revenge when the guys cut him out of a potentially valuable investment. A secret about Leonard and Penny is revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 20:00:00" d="2020-06-01 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Mercedes and Sylver renew their vows, but there's a shock when an uninvited guest makes a big announcement. Kyle urges Darren to help him fix things with Nancy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 20:30:00" d="2020-06-01 21:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Pilot: US comedy about a group of New York City police detectives. A talented but carefree detective is taken aback when a strict new captain takes over at his precinct</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 21:00:00" d="2020-06-01 22:00:00"><n>Don't Tell the Bride</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Billy believes the sty's the limit as he plans a pig-themed wedding involving a world record parade of porkers. But will prim Steph kick up a stink at Billy's plans?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 22:00:00" d="2020-06-01 23:00:00"><n u="Celebrity SAS: Who Dares Wins">Celebrity SAS: Who Dares Wins I (1)</n><t>S</t><e>TF</e>    <k>Celebrity SAS: Who Dares Wins. 
. or Stand Up To Cancer: Twelve famous faces embark on one of the toughest tests of their lives, starting with a terrifying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-01 23:00:00" d="2020-06-02 00:00:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction VI</n><e>R</e>    <k>In the dating show that dares to bare all, Emmy-Lou from Brighton hopes it's third time lucky and forensics student Charlie strips as he seeks his ideal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 00:00:00" d="2020-06-02 01:00:00"><n u="Buffy the Vampire Slayer">Buffy the Vampire Slayer I (1)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Welcome to the Hellmouth: The very first episode following the legendary Buffy Summers - a high school sophomore who faces her destiny as a slayer of the undead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 01:00:00" d="2020-06-02 01:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Euclid Alternative: When Leonard can't drive Sheldon to and from work, the friends stage an intervention to overcome Sheldon's fear of getting behind the wheel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 01:30:00" d="2020-06-02 02:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Cooper-Nowitzki Theorem: Sheldon's friends are mystified when a younger student is attracted to him, but her intense devotion soon becomes too much to bear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 02:00:00" d="2020-06-02 03:05:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox VII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>What do Britain's favourite viewers think of Flowers, Fierce, Louis Theroux: Drinking to Oblivion, Horizon: How to Find Love Online, Caravanner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 03:05:00" d="2020-06-02 04:00:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction VI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In the dating show that dares to bare all, Emmy-Lou from Brighton hopes it's third time lucky and forensics student Charlie strips as he seeks his ideal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 04:00:00" d="2020-06-02 04:55:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates V</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>More hopeful singletons visit the First Dates restaurant. Will vet Simon see past lawyer Arunima's wheelchair? And can Londoners Suzie and Gareth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 04:55:00" d="2020-06-02 07:55:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Closure Alternative: Amy employs a series of exercises to cure Sheldon of his compulsion to complete every task without fail and seek closure for every incident</k>  </p>
</a>
