<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="46" t="2019-07-11 00:18:51"><p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 05:15:00" d="2019-07-17 05:40:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Holiday Summation: After spending Christmas apart, the gang gather at Penny and Leonard's flat and hear about Sheldon and Amy's terrible trip to Texas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 05:40:00" d="2019-07-17 06:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine IV (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Halloween IV: On Halloween night, the squad members follow precinct tradition and compete for the title of Ultimate Detective Slash Genius</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 06:00:00" d="2019-07-17 06:25:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine IV (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Monster in the Closet: When Pimento and Diaz decide to tie the knot, the squad members try to prepare the perfect wedding under Santiago's careful direction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 06:25:00" d="2019-07-17 07:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother VII (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Ducky Tie: Ted tries to make amends with an ex because he cheated on her during their relationship. Marshall and Lily make a bet with Barney</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 07:00:00" d="2019-07-17 07:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Liam and Mercedes know the identity of their blackmailer, so Liam comes to a drastic decision. Sparks continue to fly between Goldie and Joel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 07:30:00" d="2019-07-17 08:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Damon and Maxine go to view their wedding venue, but after some upsetting news, Maxine shocks everyone. Meanwhile, Liam goes on a date with Cindy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 08:00:00" d="2019-07-17 08:30:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Guy Code: A puzzled Audrey learns all about the mysterious 'guy code' when Jeff decides it's time to share a juicy secret about a new friend with her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 08:30:00" d="2019-07-17 09:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Old School Jeff: Audrey and Jen go to a wedding but Jeff is not willing to attend and takes the opportunity to have a night out with his male friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 09:00:00" d="2019-07-17 09:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother VII (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Mystery vs History: Ted shocks his friends by going on a date without researching the woman on the internet beforehand. Lily and Marshall find out the sex of their baby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 09:30:00" d="2019-07-17 10:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother VII (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Noretta: The gang realise that their partners bear some resemblance to their parents. Barney and Nora's romantic evening is ruined by a string of disasters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 10:00:00" d="2019-07-17 10:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Catch &amp; Release: Against Mel's wishes, Joe agrees to act as wingman to his recently divorced friend Charlie when they go out to a bar. Zander gets two new roommates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 10:30:00" d="2019-07-17 11:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Born to Run: Mel's father comes to town to help Mel announce her candidacy for the State Senate. Ryder tries to find a winning idea for his Entrepreneur's Club project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 11:00:00" d="2019-07-17 11:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Romance Recalibration: Penny thinks Leonard has stopped making an effort in their relationship so she decides to go away for a spa weekend with Amy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 11:30:00" d="2019-07-17 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Emotion Detection Automation: Sheldon tests a newly invented device after hearing it could help him to read people's emotions. Raj seeks dating advice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 12:00:00" d="2019-07-17 12:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Venue: The Vulture makes an unwelcome return to Peralta and Santiago's lives. Boyle and Diaz must track down kidnapped NYPD horse Sergeant Peanut Butter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 12:30:00" d="2019-07-17 13:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Two Turkeys: Peralta and Santiago aim to get their parents to bond over Thanksgiving dinner. Captain Holt and Kevin's special pie is stolen from Holt's office</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 13:00:00" d="2019-07-17 13:30:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon I (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>74% Summer Sausage, a Pocket Poncho, and Tony Danza: Sheldon is busy obsessing over the status of Meemaw's budding relationship with his mentor Dr John Sturgis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 13:30:00" d="2019-07-17 14:00:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon I (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>74% Vanilla Ice Cream, Gentlemen Callers, and a Dinette Set: When Meemaw is pursued by two gentlemen callers and decides to date them both, Sheldon interferes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 14:00:00" d="2019-07-17 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Cruciferous Vegetable Amplification: Sheldon realises he won't live long enough to download his consciousness into a robot body, so he tries to extend his lifespan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 14:30:00" d="2019-07-17 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Zazzy Substitution: The guys are concerned when a heartbroken Sheldon starts bulk-buying cats after he breaks up with Amy, so Leonard tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 15:00:00" d="2019-07-17 15:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Witch Came First: Mel gets a strange visit from her doctor, who calls at the house at Halloween to convince her that she was once a powerful teenage witch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 15:30:00" d="2019-07-17 16:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% A Melanie &amp; Josiah Christmas: Competition grows between Mel and Joe over whose treasured ornament should take the prestigious top spot on the Christmas tree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 16:00:00" d="2019-07-17 16:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Nutriboom: Peralta and Boyle realise that they have been fooled into joining a cult-like pyramid scheme and they struggle to terminate their contracts with it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 16:30:00" d="2019-07-17 17:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% DFW: Peralta invites his newly discovered half-sister Kate to come and stay with him in New York, but he and Santiago soon realise she's a bit of a nightmare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 17:00:00" d="2019-07-17 17:30:00"><n u="Black-ish">Black-ish II (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>72% Daddy Dre-Care: When influenza goes around the Johnson household, Dre steps up to nurse the whole family while trying to avoid catching the bug at all costs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 17:30:00" d="2019-07-17 18:00:00"><n u="Black-ish">Black-ish II (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>72% Good-ish Times: Dre drifts off to sleep in front of the TV and dreams that the Johnson family go back in time to the 1970s to appear in a classic sitcom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 18:00:00" d="2019-07-17 18:30:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon II (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>74% Family Dynamics and a Red Fiero: Sheldon must study the dynamics of his family for his school psychology project. George Sr is offered a new job in Oklahoma</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 18:30:00" d="2019-07-17 19:00:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon II (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>74% A Stunted Childhood and a Can of Fancy Mixed Nuts: Sheldon experiments with practical jokes. Meemaw teaches Dr Sturgis to drive, testing their relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 19:00:00" d="2019-07-17 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Bus Pants Utilization: Leonard's idea for a smartphone application derails his friendship with Sheldon as they fight for control of the project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 19:30:00" d="2019-07-17 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Love Car Displacement: Tensions are high when Bernadette runs into her hulk of an ex-boyfriend at a science conference, leaving Howard feeling threatened</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 20:00:00" d="2019-07-17 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Maxine feels like no one is on her side after discovering what Grace said behind her back. Harry begs Sadie to stay. And Tony makes a shocking discovery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 20:30:00" d="2019-07-17 21:00:00"><n u="School of Rock">School of Rock I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: School of Rock
Brand new series - The Story of Us (But More About Me): Summer sets out to be the band's songwriter, but she has difficulty finding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 21:00:00" d="2019-07-17 21:30:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon II (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>74% A Nuclear Reactor and a Boy Called Lovey: Sheldon attempts to build a nuclear reactor. Georgie is heartbroken when he learns that Veronica has a boyfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 21:30:00" d="2019-07-17 22:00:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon II (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>74% David, Goliath and a Yoo-Hoo from the Back: Sheldon uses his new friendship with the school bully to boss Georgie around. Missy steals Meemaw's make-up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 22:00:00" d="2019-07-17 22:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Donation Oscillation: Penny attempts to sabotage Leonard's efforts to help her ex-boyfriend Zack and his wife Marissa have a family of their own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 22:30:00" d="2019-07-17 23:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The D &amp; D Vortex: When the gang find out that Wil Wheaton is hosting a celebrity game of Dungeons &amp; Dragons at his home, deception and betrayal take hold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 23:00:00" d="2019-07-18 00:00:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats">8 Out of 10 Cats XXI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Rob Beckett and Josh Widdicombe are joined by Joe Swash, Harriet Kemsley, Dotty, and Suzi Ruffell to compete in the popular panel show. Ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-18 00:00:00" d="2019-07-18 00:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Solder Excursion Diversion: Sheldon makes a surprise revelation when Amy buys him a new laptop. Leonard and Howard lie to their wives to avoid an errand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-18 00:30:00" d="2019-07-18 00:55:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Big Bear Precipitation: Sheldon shares a secret about Leonard when the two of them go on a weekend trip to a cabin in the country with Amy and Penny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-18 00:55:00" d="2019-07-18 01:25:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine IV (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Mr Santiago: Peralta goes to extremes to impress Santiago's dad at Thanksgiving dinner. Holt helps Pimento deal with no longer being able to work for the NYPD</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-18 01:25:00" d="2019-07-18 01:55:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine IV (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Skyfire Cycle: When a famous author receives death threats, Peralta and Jeffords take the case so that Jeffords can meet his lifelong literary hero</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-18 01:55:00" d="2019-07-18 02:30:00"><n u="The Inbetweeners">The Inbetweeners III (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Gig and the Girlfriend: To impress a girl in the year below, Simon attends his first concert since seeing Take That with his mum. But Will, Jay and Neil tag along too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-18 02:30:00" d="2019-07-18 03:05:00"><n u="The Inbetweeners">The Inbetweeners III (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Will's Dilemma: Simon and his new girlfriend Tara double date with Will and Tara's friend Kerry, but Will wonders if it's worth spending</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-18 03:05:00" d="2019-07-18 03:45:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats">8 Out of 10 Cats XX</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Aisling Bea, Rizzle Kicks' Jordan Stephens and Desiree Burch face Rob Beckett, Ayda Field and Dane Baptiste in the comedy panel show. Ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-18 03:45:00" d="2019-07-18 04:40:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates X</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Will James from Hertfordshire get the royal seal of approval from Kate Middleton lookalike Jodie? Abbie, who's a descendant of Henry VIII, meets former</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-18 04:40:00" d="2019-07-18 05:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Romance Recalibration: Penny thinks Leonard has stopped making an effort in their relationship so she decides to go away for a spa weekend with Amy</k>  </p>
</a>
