<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="47" t="2020-05-12 04:33:02"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 05:00:00" d="2020-05-19 05:25:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Date Night Variable: Howard gets caught in a row between his mum and Bernadette while he's at the International Space Station. Sheldon invites</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 05:25:00" d="2020-05-19 05:50:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Decoupling Fluctuation: Sheldon intervenes when he learns that Penny is thinking about breaking up with Leonard, but he is hampered by his inability to keep a secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 05:50:00" d="2020-05-19 06:15:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch V (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>My Best Shot: When Sabrina gives Josh a confidence boost to help him follow his dream of becoming a photographer, he gets too full of himself and quits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 06:15:00" d="2020-05-19 07:00:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch V (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Tick Tock Hilda's Clock: Hilda feels her biological clock is ticking so she sends it away to have it slowed down. But when Sabrina goes to retrieve</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 07:00:00" d="2020-05-19 07:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Tony has a life-changing decision to make. James plans to win back John Paul. Charlie needs cash but starts looking in the wrong places. Ollie and Brooke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 07:30:00" d="2020-05-19 08:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Verity makes a shocking discovery about Edward: will she jeopardise his plan? Drug-dealer Jordan sets his sights on Charlie. Sami can't hide his feelings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 08:00:00" d="2020-05-19 08:30:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch V (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Sabrina's New Roommate: Sabrina and her roommates try to get Zelda to relax and have a bit of fun, but it works too well and Zelda becomes something of a party animal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 08:30:00" d="2020-05-19 09:00:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch V (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Making the Grade: Sabrina writes an article for the student paper about how the school athletes get special treatment, and Roxie worries about her grades</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 09:00:00" d="2020-05-19 09:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Independence Day: Mel feels it's a good idea for her and Joe to explore their new relationship slowly, but he takes things too far when he gets another job and moves out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 09:30:00" d="2020-05-19 10:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% The New Deal: Mel becomes frustrated when Joe's demanding new job prevents him from spending any quality time with her, so she sneaks over to see him at work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 10:00:00" d="2020-05-19 10:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% New Bonnie vs Old Ben: Bonnie sets up her new apartment right across the hall from the boys but Ben and Tucker are keen to force her out as soon as possible</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 10:30:00" d="2020-05-19 11:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% The Wheeler and the Dealer: Ben persuades Danny to sign a sponsorship deal with a brand of Japanese energy drink, but things go haywire at the photo shoot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 11:00:00" d="2020-05-19 11:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Higgs Boson Observation: Amy is jealous when Sheldon hires an attractive female assistant, and Howard's return from space is delayed by a week</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 11:30:00" d="2020-05-19 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Re-entry Minimization: Howard is disappointed when he doesn't receive a hero's welcome on his return from space. Will he ever get the recognition he deserves?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 12:00:00" d="2020-05-19 12:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>I Caddyshacked the Pool: Adam goes to great lengths to dodge school swimming classes, but his plan to avoid the sport could affect his friendship with Dave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 12:30:00" d="2020-05-19 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Boy Barry: When Murray grows a moustache, it ignites a feud between his wife and his best friend. Barry becomes convinced that he's lost Lainey's affections</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 13:00:00" d="2020-05-19 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Suicide Squad: Desperate circumstances call for desperate measures as Peralta, Captain Holt and the team are forced to ally themselves with some old enemies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 13:30:00" d="2020-05-19 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Pilot: US comedy about a group of New York City police detectives. A talented but carefree detective is taken aback when a strict new captain takes over at his precinct</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 14:00:00" d="2020-05-19 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Cohabitation Experimentation: When Amy's flat is flooded, she has to move out while it is repaired and proposes a 'cohabitation experiment' with Sheldon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 14:30:00" d="2020-05-19 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Hot Tub Contamination: Leonard and Penny intervene when Sheldon and Amy have an argument. Howard and Bernadette are disturbed by unexpected guests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 15:00:00" d="2020-05-19 15:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Catch &amp; Release: Against Mel's wishes, Joe agrees to act as wingman to his recently divorced friend Charlie when they go out to a bar. Zander gets two new roommates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 15:30:00" d="2020-05-19 16:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Born to Run: Mel's father comes to town to help Mel announce her candidacy for the State Senate. Ryder tries to find a winning idea for his Entrepreneur's Club project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 16:00:00" d="2020-05-19 16:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% All Riled Up: When Tucker and Danny bail on movie night, Riley and Ben are left alone for the evening and Ben gets it into his head that Riley fancies him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 16:30:00" d="2020-05-19 17:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% The Emma Dilemma: Ben finds out that his neighbour is hosting a playgroup for all of the kids in the local area except Emma because she thinks Ben is a horrible dad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 17:00:00" d="2020-05-19 17:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Thanksgiving: Santiago hosts a Thanksgiving dinner at her apartment for all of her colleagues at the precinct, but the celebration risks turning into a holiday disaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 17:30:00" d="2020-05-19 18:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Christmas: When Captain Holt gets death threats, Peralta must run his security. Santiago tries to take a precinct Christmas photo for Holt, but Diaz won't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 18:00:00" d="2020-05-19 18:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Lainey Loves Lionel: Barry takes inspiration from Lionel Richie and sets about creating a sculpture of Lainey as the ultimate Valentine's Day gift</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 18:30:00" d="2020-05-19 19:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Weird Al: Adam plans to reignite his fading relationship with Dana by taking her to a concert. Barry and Erica worry that Murray may be feeling depressed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 19:00:00" d="2020-05-19 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Emotion Detection Automation: Sheldon tests a newly invented device after hearing it could help him to read people's emotions. Raj seeks dating advice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 19:30:00" d="2020-05-19 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Locomotion Reverberation: Leonard and Howard distract Sheldon with a trip to a historic railway when he slows their progress on the guidance system</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 20:00:00" d="2020-05-19 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Kyle makes a shocking discovery. Tony starts his new medication, prescribed by manipulative Edward. Tom makes a move that doesn't go down well with Yazz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 20:30:00" d="2020-05-19 21:00:00"><n>Celebrity Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Second to host is ex-Coronation Street actor and dinner party virgin Steven Arnold. Can his hearty northern grub match his impeccable hosting? (Ep2/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 21:00:00" d="2020-05-19 21:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Cinco de Mayo: When Jeffords becomes anxious about his upcoming lieutenant's exam, the squad hold the precinct's annual Halloween Heist on a new date</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 21:30:00" d="2020-05-19 22:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VII</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series - Dillman: When a prank goes disastrously wrong, things at the Nine-Nine take a distinctly Agatha Christie turn. Ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 22:00:00" d="2020-05-19 22:35:00"><n u="The Inbetweeners">The Inbetweeners II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Duke of Edinburgh Awards: Will is asked to coordinate the school's Duke of Edinburgh Awards scheme, and immediately turns the situation to his own advantage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 22:35:00" d="2020-05-19 23:05:00"><n u="The Inbetweeners">The Inbetweeners II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>End of Term: Will is stressed about exams, Jay has other things on his mind, Simon finally seems to be making headway with Carli, and Neil forgets his kit for his PE exam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 23:05:00" d="2020-05-19 23:35:00"><n u="Derry Girls">Derry Girls II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Prom: Jenny Joyce organises a 50s-style prom, Erin, Clare and Michelle are looking for prom dates, but Orla has already got someone special in mind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-19 23:35:00" d="2020-05-20 00:05:00"><n u="Derry Girls">Derry Girls II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The President: As Christmas nears, excitement in Derry is at fever pitch for President Bill Clinton's visit. James gets a surprise, and Granda Joe embarks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 00:05:00" d="2020-05-20 00:40:00"><n u="The IT Crowd">The IT Crowd II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>66% Smoke and Mirrors: When a bad bra makes Jen lose concentration in a board meeting, Moss overcomes his fear of ladies' underwear and invents a bra that will never fail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 00:40:00" d="2020-05-20 01:10:00"><n u="The IT Crowd">The IT Crowd II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>66% Men without Women: Douglas hires Jen as his new PA, giving Moss and Roy freedom in the office. How will they cope without her, and how</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 01:10:00" d="2020-05-20 02:15:00"><n u="Made in Chelsea">Made in Chelsea IV (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>While Binky mends her broken heart, Jamie texts Lucy for another date, but Lucy juggles invites from Jamie and Andy to attend Rosie's dinner party. Arguments unfold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 02:15:00" d="2020-05-20 02:45:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Long Distance Dissonance: The gang worry when Sheldon's former admirer, Dr Ramona Nowitzki, turns up while Amy is away working at Princeton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 02:45:00" d="2020-05-20 03:10:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Pilot: The first ever episode of the hit sitcom. Leonard and Sheldon's ignorance of women seems set to change when the beautiful Penny moves in next door</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 03:10:00" d="2020-05-20 03:40:00"><n u="The Inbetweeners">The Inbetweeners II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Duke of Edinburgh Awards: Will is asked to coordinate the school's Duke of Edinburgh Awards scheme, and immediately turns the situation to his own advantage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 03:40:00" d="2020-05-20 04:10:00"><n u="The Inbetweeners">The Inbetweeners II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>End of Term: Will is stressed about exams, Jay has other things on his mind, Simon finally seems to be making headway with Carli, and Neil forgets his kit for his PE exam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 04:10:00" d="2020-05-20 04:35:00"><n u="Derry Girls">Derry Girls II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Prom: Jenny Joyce organises a 50s-style prom, Erin, Clare and Michelle are looking for prom dates, but Orla has already got someone special in mind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 04:35:00" d="2020-05-20 05:05:00"><n u="Derry Girls">Derry Girls II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The President: As Christmas nears, excitement in Derry is at fever pitch for President Bill Clinton's visit. James gets a surprise, and Granda Joe embarks</k>  </p>
</a>
