<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2019-08-13 02:07:23"><p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 05:10:00" d="2019-08-18 05:35:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Baked: Audrey hopes to start her own cookie business after leaving her previous employment, while Timmy does his best to fit in with the guys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 05:35:00" d="2019-08-18 06:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Les-bro: Audrey is upset when Jeff is too distracted to help find a surrogate, but a conversation with one of his softball team-mates leads to an unexpected resolution</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 06:00:00" d="2019-08-18 07:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Fun Run: Jeff tells his colleagues that he can't give any more money to their charity fundraising efforts, but then Audrey signs up for a 10km race for a good cause</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 07:00:00" d="2019-08-18 09:25:00"><n>Hollyoaks: Omnibus</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>50% Hollyoaks Omnibus
The Maalik family's Eid celebration turns nasty and Ste is very shocked by the level of intimidation that Stuart and Jonny inflict upon the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 09:25:00" d="2019-08-18 10:30:00"><n u="The Crystal Maze">The Crystal Maze V</n><e>TF</e>    <k>The Science Nerds prove that putting the words 'science' and 'nerds' in the name of your team isn't necessarily a guarantee of competence. Richard Ayoade</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 10:30:00" d="2019-08-18 11:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Wedding Singer: Barry and Lainey's wedding date is right around the corner and Beverly is in her element, but is the groom starting to have second thoughts? Ep11)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 11:00:00" d="2019-08-18 11:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Pina Colada Episode: Murray and Geoff try to pull Beverly, Barry and Erica out of their shared misery after Lainey's departure. Coach Nick returns to town. Ep12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 11:30:00" d="2019-08-18 12:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>I Coulda Been a Lawyer: Beverly decides the street where the family lives needs another stop sign, and Barry realises he's neglected his college applications. Ep13)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 12:00:00" d="2019-08-18 12:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Major League'd: Adam is terrified when he and his friends are recruited to the school baseball team. Geoff's father interferes in his relationship with Erica. Ep14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 12:30:00" d="2019-08-18 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>My Valentine Boy: Erica and Valley Erica find a new band member to replace Lainey. Adam and Murray plot to escape from Valentine's Day dinner with Beverly. Ep15)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 13:00:00" d="2019-08-18 13:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Indecision Amalgamation: Raj faces a dating dilemma, Penny can't decide whether to accept a role in a terrible film, and Sheldon chooses between two gaming systems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 13:30:00" d="2019-08-18 14:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Relationship Diremption: Sheldon wonders whether he's wasting his time with his study of String Theory. Raj and Emily go on a double date with Howard and Bernadette</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 14:00:00" d="2019-08-18 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Solo Oscillation: Amy and Leonard bond over some experiments. Bert replaces Howard in his band. Penny gives Sheldon unexpected scientific inspiration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 14:30:00" d="2019-08-18 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Separation Triangulation: Raj gets into a domestic drama with his new date Nell and her estranged husband. Sheldon rents his old room back from Leonard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 15:00:00" d="2019-08-18 15:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Novelization Correlation: Amy appears on the Professor Proton show. Penny hates the idea that the female protagonist in Leonard's novel is based on her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 15:30:00" d="2019-08-18 16:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Neonatal Nomenclature: When Bernadette is unable to go into labour, her friends employ a number of different tactics to get the process started</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 16:00:00" d="2019-08-18 16:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Athenaeum Allocation: Leonard jumps through hoops to secure the perfect wedding venue for Sheldon and Amy. Howard and Bernadette face a big decision</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 16:30:00" d="2019-08-18 17:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Gates Excitation: The guys do everything in their power to meet Bill Gates when his firm has dealings with the pharmaceutical company Penny works for</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 17:00:00" d="2019-08-18 17:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Tenant Disassociation: Leonard competes with Sheldon to become president of the tenants' association. Howard and Raj find a drone in the back garden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 17:30:00" d="2019-08-18 18:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Reclusive Potential: A brilliant scientist invites Sheldon to his cabin in the middle of nowhere, so Leonard, Raj and Howard go along for the trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 18:00:00" d="2019-08-18 18:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Comet Polarization: Sheldon isn't pleased by the comic book shop's new-found popularity. Raj tries to take the credit for Penny's astronomical discovery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 18:30:00" d="2019-08-18 19:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Monetary Insufficiency: Sheldon goes to Las Vegas in an attempt to win money for science. Penny and Bernadette take Amy shopping for a wedding dress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 19:00:00" d="2019-08-18 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Sibling Realignment: When Sheldon learns that his mother won't attend his wedding unless he invites his brother Georgie, he and Leonard travel to Texas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 19:30:00" d="2019-08-18 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Bow Tie Asymmetry: Everyone focuses on making sure all the arrangements for Amy and Sheldon's big day go according to plan - except the bride and groom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 20:00:00" d="2019-08-18 22:00:00"><n>102 Dalmatians</n><e>F</e>    <k>Disney family comedy starring Glenn Close. Cruella de Vil is back, having served three years in prison for trying to turn Dalmatian puppies into a fur coat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 22:00:00" d="2019-08-18 23:05:00"><n u="Celebs Go Dating">Celebs Go Dating VII (11)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>54% New: Celebs Go Dating
Brand new series: Charlotte Crosby and Josh Ritchie come to the agency for advice on their stormy relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 23:05:00" d="2019-08-19 00:05:00"><n u="Marvel's Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D.">Marvel's Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D. VI (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Marvel's Agents of. 
.H.I.E.L.D: Brand new series - New Life: In the last episode of the sixth series, the agents battle problems, conflicts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 00:05:00" d="2019-08-19 01:10:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Edinburgh musician Jamie is tired of the life of groupies and flings and seeks a deeper connection. Jasmin from Bognor has ME and needs acceptance from a new lover. Ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 01:10:00" d="2019-08-19 01:40:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Pilot: The first ever episode of the hit sitcom. Leonard and Sheldon's ignorance of women seems set to change when the beautiful Penny moves in next door</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 01:40:00" d="2019-08-19 02:10:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Big Bran Hypothesis: Bothered by how messy Penny's flat is, Sheldon sneaks in to clean and organise it, but Penny isn't best pleased when she finds out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 02:10:00" d="2019-08-19 03:15:00"><n u="Celebs Go Dating">Celebs Go Dating VII (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>54% Brand new series: Charlotte Crosby and Josh Ritchie come to the agency for advice on their stormy relationship. Lee dates a Blue fan, and Nathan takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 03:15:00" d="2019-08-19 04:10:00"><n u="First Dates Hotel">First Dates Hotel III (3)</n><t>S</t><e>TF</e>    <k>The Lauren and Pat drama continues as Lauren tries to win Pat's heart. And dapper Essex farmer George seeks a lady - will agricultural surveyor Louise be his muddy match?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 04:10:00" d="2019-08-19 04:50:00"><n u="Marvel's Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D.">Marvel's Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D. VI (13)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Brand new series - New Life: In the last episode of the sixth series, the agents battle problems, conflicts and the threat of invasion. Who will survive?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-19 04:50:00" d="2019-08-19 07:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks: Omnibus</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>50% Hollyoaks Omnibus
The Maalik family's Eid celebration turns nasty and Ste is very shocked by the level of intimidation that Stuart and Jonny inflict upon the family</k>  </p>
</a>
