<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="46" t="2019-08-09 01:35:06"><p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 05:10:00" d="2019-08-15 05:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Four Movements: Gina plays a game of chess with Captain Holt, goes out for lunch with Diaz and Santiago and infiltrates an expensive social club with Peralta</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 05:30:00" d="2019-08-15 05:55:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother IX (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% How Your Mother Met Me: In flashback for the 200th episode, it is revealed how Ted has a history of missed connections with his future wife</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 05:55:00" d="2019-08-15 06:15:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother IX (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Sunrise: On the eve of the wedding, Ted and Robin take a walk on the beach and have a heart-to-heart conversation. Marshall finds out that his hotel room is haunted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 06:15:00" d="2019-08-15 07:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>The Big Picture: Russell's mother cuts off his trust fund and he is forced to move in with Timmy. Audrey volunteers to help Jeff impress his boss to get a year-end bonus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 07:00:00" d="2019-08-15 07:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Ste is very shocked by how far Jonny and Stuart went in frightening the Maalik family. Misbah wants to protect her children, but does she have any fight left?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 07:30:00" d="2019-08-15 08:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>The tension mounts as Ste is offered a way out of the far right group. Mercedes fools around with Liam while her husband is away, but she doesn't realise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 08:00:00" d="2019-08-15 08:30:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Refusing to Budget: When the utilities are turned off in Russell's flat, Timmy convinces him that he needs to budget sensibly and pay his bills on time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 08:30:00" d="2019-08-15 09:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Little Bummer Boy: Timmy thinks it's a total bummer that he and Alison have split up at Christmas, but he cheers himself up by dressing as an elf to greet party guests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 09:00:00" d="2019-08-15 09:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother IX (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Rally: Barney can't get out of bed on the morning of his wedding because he had too much to drink the night before, so the gang try to make him a famous hangover cure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 09:30:00" d="2019-08-15 10:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother IX (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Vesuvius: On the morning of the wedding, Ted helps a stressed Barney decide which suit to wear. Lily thinks Robin isn't treating her big day with the gravity it deserves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 10:00:00" d="2019-08-15 10:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Enemies with Benefits: Joe rekindles a romantic spark with his ex-wife Tiffany, but when Tiffany meets Mel, she reveals that she has been keeping a big secret from Joe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 10:30:00" d="2019-08-15 11:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Don't Train on My Parade: Joe takes an interest in Mel's personal trainer as soon as they meet. Lennox develops a crush on Beckett but does her best to stay just friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 11:00:00" d="2019-08-15 11:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy I (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% May the Best Friend Win: While out clubbing, Ben and Tucker meet a girl called Ava. They both return with her phone number and argue over who should call her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 11:30:00" d="2019-08-15 12:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy I (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% The Daddy Whisperer: When Ben begs to join super-mum Izzy's parenting class, she meets him for a one-on-one tutorial. Tucker and Danny set up a 'man cave'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 12:00:00" d="2019-08-15 12:30:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless I (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>S-u-r--Surprise!: Dylan asks Maya not to give her a birthday party but Maya throws a surprise bash anyway. Jimmy and Kenneth try to find something in common</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 12:30:00" d="2019-08-15 13:00:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless I (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>D-i--Ding: When Maya dents a nearby car, Ray leaves a note to the other driver behind his mother's back. Kenneth hides the fact that he's been moonlighting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 13:00:00" d="2019-08-15 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% 48 Hours: Peralta jumps the gun and makes an arrest without enough evidence, leaving himself only 48 hours to collect the proof he needs before the suspect is released</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 13:30:00" d="2019-08-15 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Old School: Peralta is overjoyed when his hero, crime reporter Jimmy Brogan, visits the precinct, but things soon go awry. Jeffords and Boyle prepare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 14:00:00" d="2019-08-15 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory V (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Transporter Malfunction: Penny buys Leonard and Sheldon some Star Trek memorabilia but she is irked when they refuse to remove the toys from their packaging</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 14:30:00" d="2019-08-15 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory V (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Hawking Excitation: When Stephen Hawking comes to lecture at the university, Howard is given the task of maintaining his wheelchair, making Sheldon envious</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 15:00:00" d="2019-08-15 15:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Going the Distance?: As Mel's relationship with George grows more serious, he is offered a new job abroad and she is forced to contemplate the future of their romance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 15:30:00" d="2019-08-15 16:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% All Politics Is Local: Mel's father returns to town to lobby for a political bill that Mel is opposed to. Lennox's poems catch the attention of a popular classmate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 16:00:00" d="2019-08-15 16:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% On the Lamb-Y: Ben, Danny and Tucker band together to rescue Emma's missing stuffed animal. Riley hosts a book club in an effort to make friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 16:30:00" d="2019-08-15 17:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Never Ben in Love: Riley plans to break up with Fitch, but then receives the news that Fitch is dead. Ben realises he might be in love with Megan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 17:00:00" d="2019-08-15 17:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Full Boyle: Boyle's new romance increases his self-confidence, Diaz and Santiago can't take a costumed crime-fighter seriously, and Holt faces a leadership challenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 17:30:00" d="2019-08-15 18:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Apartment: Peralta is in danger of losing his flat but has no money to buy his own place, so Gina tries to help him find a new home. The officers do self-evaluations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 18:00:00" d="2019-08-15 18:30:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>T-r--Training D-a--Day: Jimmy takes JJ camping to give him 'the talk'. Maya attempts to train a ragtag group of aides for some new students at the school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 18:30:00" d="2019-08-15 19:00:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>S-h--Shipping: JJ is under pressure to date a new student. Maya and Jimmy want Ray and Taylor to be more carefree. Dylan rebels against a no-prank initiative</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 19:00:00" d="2019-08-15 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Extract Obliteration: Sheldon is thrilled when Stephen Hawking agrees to play against him in an online game. Penny signs up for a class at community college</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 19:30:00" d="2019-08-15 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Habitation Configuration: Amy is upset when Sheldon fails to defend her in an argument with Wil Wheaton during the filming of a new episode of Fun with Flags</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 20:00:00" d="2019-08-15 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>It's Jack and Breda's secret wedding day, but Breda has pressing matters to attend to. She tells Joel in the confession box that someone in her family has sinned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 20:30:00" d="2019-08-15 21:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Major League'd: Adam is terrified when he and his friends are recruited to the school baseball team. Geoff's father interferes in his relationship with Erica. Ep14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 21:00:00" d="2019-08-15 21:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Indecision Amalgamation: Raj faces a dating dilemma, Penny can't decide whether to accept a role in a terrible film, and Sheldon chooses between two gaming systems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 21:30:00" d="2019-08-15 22:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Relationship Diremption: Sheldon wonders whether he's wasting his time with his study of String Theory. Raj and Emily go on a double date with Howard and Bernadette</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 22:00:00" d="2019-08-15 23:00:00"><n u="Celebs Go Dating">Celebs Go Dating VII (10)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>54% New: Celebs Go Dating
Brand new series: Nathan Henry is on a second date and things are looking up. Lee Ryan goes on a date with a blast from the past</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 23:00:00" d="2019-08-15 23:35:00"><n u="The Good Place">The Good Place II (12)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: The Good Place
Brand new series - The Burrito: The friends consider how much they have (or have not) improved over time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-15 23:35:00" d="2019-08-16 00:10:00"><n u="The Inbetweeners">The Inbetweeners I (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Will Gets a Girlfriend: Will sees that going to a mixed-sex school isn't so bad when he pulls the most popular girl in the year above, but he alienates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 00:10:00" d="2019-08-16 00:40:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Comet Polarization: Sheldon isn't pleased by the comic book shop's new-found popularity. Raj tries to take the credit for Penny's astronomical discovery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 00:40:00" d="2019-08-16 01:10:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Monetary Insufficiency: Sheldon goes to Las Vegas in an attempt to win money for science. Penny and Bernadette take Amy shopping for a wedding dress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 01:10:00" d="2019-08-16 01:40:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% A Tale of Two Bandits: Jeffords thinks the Pontiac Bandit's up to his old tricks again. The team battle some firefighters to keep Shaw's bar a police hangout</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 01:40:00" d="2019-08-16 02:10:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Crime Scene: Peralta and Diaz doggedly work and rework a crime scene in an effort to solve a difficult murder case that is clouded by confusing evidence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 02:10:00" d="2019-08-16 03:15:00"><n u="Celebs Go Dating">Celebs Go Dating VII (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>54% Brand new series: Nathan Henry is on a second date and things are looking up. Lee Ryan goes on a date with a blast from the past</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 03:15:00" d="2019-08-16 04:10:00"><n u="First Dates Hotel">First Dates Hotel III (2)</n><t>S</t><e>TF</e>    <k>A new batch of the young and beautiful eye each other up in the Italian sunshine. Is London ladette Lauren the right match for 6' 4&quot; bearded market trader Patrick?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 04:10:00" d="2019-08-16 04:35:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty III (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>92% Rick and Morty [adult swim]
Brand new series - Rest and Ricklaxation: After a stressful and exhausting adventure, Rick and Morty take a break</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 04:35:00" d="2019-08-16 04:50:00"><n u="Robot Chicken">Robot Chicken IX</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Robot Chicken [adult swim]
Shall I Visit the Dinosaurs?: Robot Chicken demands the slaughter of Furbies be remembered. The Sound of Music gets a reboot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 04:50:00" d="2019-08-16 05:05:00"><n u="Robot Chicken">Robot Chicken IX</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Robot Chicken [adult swim]
What Can You Tell Me About Butt Rashes?: The Wicked Witch has last-minute confessions it may not be enjoyable to hear</k>  </p>
</a>
