<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="43" t="2020-05-13 04:33:04"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 05:05:00" d="2020-05-20 05:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Higgs Boson Observation: Amy is jealous when Sheldon hires an attractive female assistant, and Howard's return from space is delayed by a week</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 05:30:00" d="2020-05-20 05:55:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Re-entry Minimization: Howard is disappointed when he doesn't receive a hero's welcome on his return from space. Will he ever get the recognition he deserves?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 05:55:00" d="2020-05-20 06:20:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch V (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Sabrina's New Roommate: Sabrina and her roommates try to get Zelda to relax and have a bit of fun, but it works too well and Zelda becomes something of a party animal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 06:20:00" d="2020-05-20 07:00:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch V (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Making the Grade: Sabrina writes an article for the student paper about how the school athletes get special treatment, and Roxie worries about her grades</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 07:00:00" d="2020-05-20 07:30:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Harassment: A new employee who takes exception to Audrey files a sexual harassment claim against her. Timmy challenges Jeff to a game of cricket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 07:30:00" d="2020-05-20 08:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>They Do?: Adam and Jennifer decide to organise a secret wedding ceremony, but a series of unfortunate events soon puts their romantic plans in jeopardy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 08:00:00" d="2020-05-20 08:30:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch V (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Love Is a Many Complicated Thing: Morgan fixes Sabrina up with fellow student Kevin so that she and Josh can double-date with them on Valentine's Day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 08:30:00" d="2020-05-20 09:00:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch V (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Sabrina, the Muse: When Kevin tells Sabrina that she is the inspiration for his songs, Sabrina is forced to step in when he gets a bad case of writer's block</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 09:00:00" d="2020-05-20 09:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Feel the Burn: After winning a 10-course dining experience in a raffle, Mel decides to join an exercise boot camp to lose weight before gorging on the gourmet meal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 09:30:00" d="2020-05-20 10:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Plus One: When Mel takes Joe to a social event connected with her work, he reveals too much about both their opinions to the press and gains her some bad publicity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 10:00:00" d="2020-05-20 10:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% The Slump: Dr Shaw decides that Riley's the cause of Danny's inability to focus during ice hockey matches. Riley thinks things are moving too fast with Fitch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 10:30:00" d="2020-05-20 11:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Ben's Big Gaycare Adventure: Ben tries to get Emma into daycare by flirting with cute assistant manager Megan, who jumps to the wrong conclusion about Ben and Tucker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 11:00:00" d="2020-05-20 11:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Holographic Excitation: The gang celebrate Halloween with a fancy dress party at Stuart's comic book shop, but Sheldon and Amy can't agree on which costumes to wear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 11:30:00" d="2020-05-20 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Extract Obliteration: Sheldon is thrilled when Stephen Hawking agrees to play against him in an online game. Penny signs up for a class at the community college</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 12:00:00" d="2020-05-20 12:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Couples Costume: Barry and Erica persuade Adam not to go trick-or-treating at Halloween, but to take his girlfriend Dana to visit a haunted house instead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 12:30:00" d="2020-05-20 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Lucky: Barry badgers Murray into getting him a puppy. Beverly wants to join in with Erica and Lainey's pyjama party, but the girls exclude her from the event</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 13:00:00" d="2020-05-20 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Tagger: When Peralta turns up late for morning roll call, Captain Holt responds by assigning him to a minor graffiti case and then closely monitoring his every move</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 13:30:00" d="2020-05-20 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Slump: Peralta has a growing number of crime cases that he can't seem to solve. Holt asks Santiago to take charge of a community outreach programme for at-risk youth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 14:00:00" d="2020-05-20 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Fetal Kick Catalyst: Penny meets her fans at a comic book convention. Sheldon and Amy host a brunch at Penny's flat. Howard makes an impulsive purchase</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 14:30:00" d="2020-05-20 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Veracity Elasticity: Leonard is upset when he finds out Penny has been moving his collectables out of Sheldon's old room and into storage behind his back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 15:00:00" d="2020-05-20 15:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% More Than Roommates: Joe inherits an ugly chair from his grandma and is pleased to be able to bring a piece of his life into Mel's home at last, but Mel doesn't agree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 15:30:00" d="2020-05-20 16:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Accidents Will Happen: Mel thinks she might be pregnant but is unsure about whether to share the tidings with Joe because he's busy preparing for a major business pitch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 16:00:00" d="2020-05-20 16:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Surprise!: Ben learns why Riley doesn't like celebrating her birthday. Bonnie reveals she forgot to complete some paperwork and that Ben isn't Emma's sole custodian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 16:30:00" d="2020-05-20 17:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Emma's First Christmas: Ben and Danny end up wearing elf suits when they go out of their way to find a particular toy as a Christmas gift for baby Emma</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 17:00:00" d="2020-05-20 17:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Pontiac Bandit: In order to catch the Pontiac Bandit, a car thief he has been tracking for years, Peralta tries to make a deal with a suspect Diaz has just arrested</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 17:30:00" d="2020-05-20 18:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Bet: Peralta and Santiago's ongoing bet about who can make the most arrests comes to an awkward conclusion. Boyle gets a medal after he's shot in the line of duty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 18:00:00" d="2020-05-20 18:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Edward 'Eddie the Eagle' Edwards: Barry seeks fresh inspiration when he loses his standing as a champion athlete at school. Sales at Murray's shop nosedive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 18:30:00" d="2020-05-20 19:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Dirty Dancing Dance: Erica suggests the film Dirty Dancing as the theme for the upcoming school dance, but Principal Ball refuses to sanction her idea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 19:00:00" d="2020-05-20 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Allowance Evaporation: Amy is furious when she learns that Sheldon has chosen to share intimate details of their relationship with his colleagues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 19:30:00" d="2020-05-20 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Comic-Con Conundrum: Cut off from his father's fortune, Raj appoints Sheldon to organise his finances. Penny considers joining the guys at Comic-Con</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 20:00:00" d="2020-05-20 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks Favourites</n><e>F</e>    <k>Hollyoaks stars Ellis Hollins and Matt Littler relive a classic episode of the soap. It's Christmas Day, and a seriously ill Max makes a shocking discovery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 20:30:00" d="2020-05-20 21:00:00"><n>Celebrity Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Real Housewives of Cheshire star Dawn Ward goes all out to throw the perfect dinner party with drag maids, a personal barman and a 'glamorous' dress code. (Ep3/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 21:00:00" d="2020-05-20 21:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VII</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: The Goldbergs
Brand new series - The Preventa Mode: As Valentine's Day approaches, Barry is shocked when an attractive teaching assistant agrees</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 21:30:00" d="2020-05-20 22:00:00"><n>Schooled</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>48% New: Schooled
Brand new series - Singled Out: Lainey works out her feelings in time for Valentine's Day. Felicia has body image issues and Coach Mellor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 22:00:00" d="2020-05-20 23:00:00"><n>Celebrity Gogglebox USA</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Celebrity Gogglebox USA
Brand new series: Gogglebox heads across the pond and steps into the homes of a selection of celebrity faces, including</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-20 23:00:00" d="2020-05-21 00:00:00"><n>Celebrity Gogglebox</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>From Love Island to The Family Brain Game, what do Oti Mabuse, Rachel Riley, Rylan Clark-Neal, Denise van Outen, Emily Atack, Nick Grimshaw and other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-21 00:00:00" d="2020-05-21 01:00:00"><n>Zoey's Extraordinary Playlist</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Zoey's Extraordinary Playlist
Brand new series - Zoey's Extraordinary Dad: After hearing an ominous song, Zoey does everything in her power</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-21 01:00:00" d="2020-05-21 01:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Big Bran Hypothesis: Bothered by how messy Penny's flat is, Sheldon sneaks in to clean and organise it, but Penny isn't best pleased when she finds out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-21 01:30:00" d="2020-05-21 02:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Fuzzyboots Corollary: Leonard is depressed when he discovers that Penny is seeing someone, so he summons up the courage to ask a woman out on a date</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-21 02:00:00" d="2020-05-21 03:05:00"><n u="Made in Chelsea">Made in Chelsea IV (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Sophia wonders whether she might have feelings for Francis, while Andy is keen to patch up his friendship with Jamie after the fallout at Rosie's dinner party over Lucy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-21 03:05:00" d="2020-05-21 04:00:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox VII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Britain's favourite TV viewers share their sharp, insightful and emotional critiques of the top shows, including Secret Life of the Zoo, Happy Valley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-21 04:00:00" d="2020-05-21 04:55:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates IV</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Self-confessed nerd and Star Wars fan Lachlan returns. Is his date with Becca out of this world? Young professionals Louisa and Cameron</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-21 04:55:00" d="2020-05-21 05:20:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VII</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series - The Preventa Mode: As Valentine's Day approaches, Barry is shocked when an attractive teaching assistant agrees to go out with him. Ep14)</k>  </p>
</a>
