<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="41" t="2021-07-09 06:48:27"><p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 05:15:00" d="2021-07-14 05:40:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Sweet Taste of Liberty: Ted agrees that Barney should spice up his love life, as a result of which he ends up flying to Philadelphia for a crazy adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 05:40:00" d="2021-07-14 06:05:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother I (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Return of the Shirt: Ted's views about life and love change when he discovers an old shirt that he previously disliked and suddenly loves the look of it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 06:05:00" d="2021-07-14 06:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Good to Go: Mel and Joe are shocked to discover that Lennox's boyfriend Aidan spent the night in her bedroom. Holly declares that it's time for Ryder to start shaving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 06:30:00" d="2021-07-14 07:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% All Up in My Business: When Joe starts to run Mel's finances he becomes convinced that her credit card statements reveal she is having an affair with a married man</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 07:00:00" d="2021-07-14 07:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>After a shock intimate moment, one Hollyoaks resident is in hot water. A break-in leads Juliet to make a decision. Ste reflects on second chances</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 07:30:00" d="2021-07-14 08:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Sami is on a mission to get rid of an unwelcome house guest. James faces a difficult ultimatum. Martine takes matters into her own hands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 08:00:00" d="2021-07-14 09:00:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay visits Casa Roma, the oldest restaurant in Lancaster, California. Although the bar is a success, the restaurant struggles to make money</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 09:00:00" d="2021-07-14 09:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother I (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Okay Awesome: Ted investigates the club scene with Barney and Robin, while Marshall and Lily try to be more 'grown up' as their wedding day approaches</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 09:30:00" d="2021-07-14 10:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother I (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Slutty Pumpkin: Ted goes to a boring Halloween party hoping to find a girl he lost touch with who dresses as a 'slutty pumpkin'. Robin goes on a double date</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 10:00:00" d="2021-07-14 10:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% The Knockout: When Mel punches a man who picks on Ryder at the cinema, a clip of the event is soon posted online and she becomes known as 'Battling Burke'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 10:30:00" d="2021-07-14 11:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Breaking Up Is Hard to Do: Mel wants to break up with her boyfriend Donald, but feels guilty because he's just been fired from his job. Holly confides a secret to Lennox</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 11:00:00" d="2021-07-14 11:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Go Brit or Go Home: Riley asks a reluctant Ben to hang out with her new British boyfriend Philip. Tucker fakes a British accent while trying to attract dates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 11:30:00" d="2021-07-14 12:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% An Affair Not to Remember: A horrified Ben realises he once dated Tucker's new girlfriend. Riley is excited when she is invited to a spa day with her boss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 12:00:00" d="2021-07-14 12:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Edward 'Eddie the Eagle' Edwards: Barry seeks fresh inspiration when he loses his standing as a champion athlete at school. Sales at Murray's shop nosedive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 12:30:00" d="2021-07-14 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Dirty Dancing Dance: Erica suggests the film Dirty Dancing as the theme for the upcoming school dance, but Principal Ball refuses to sanction her idea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 13:00:00" d="2021-07-14 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% USPIS: While trying to catch a drug-dealer, Peralta and Boyle join forces with Agent Jack Danger, a pompous investigator at the US Postal Inspection Service</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 13:30:00" d="2021-07-14 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Road Trip: In an attempt to add a touch of romance to his work trip with Santiago, Peralta invites his girlfriend and Santiago's boyfriend to join them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 14:00:00" d="2021-07-14 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Procreation Calculation: Stuart starts bringing his new girlfriend home to Howard and Bernadette's house. Penny and Leonard talk about starting a family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 14:30:00" d="2021-07-14 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Tam Turbulence: When Sheldon won't tell anyone why he's never mentioned Tam, his childhood best friend, Leonard tries to find out more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 15:00:00" d="2021-07-14 15:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Friendship Algorithm: Sheldon develops a scientific procedure for making friends when he discovers that Kripke has control of a new supercomputer at the university</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 15:30:00" d="2021-07-14 16:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Financial Permeability: When Sheldon lends Penny some money, it brings her ex-boyfriend Kurt back into her life, with negative consequences for the gang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 16:00:00" d="2021-07-14 16:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>I Heart Video Dating: Erica and Lainey try to set Bill up with a 'woman of interest' by using new video-dating technology. Barry decides to become a gym teacher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 16:30:00" d="2021-07-14 17:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>George! George Glass!: Adam risks bodily harm during a game of paintball to impress his latest crush, and Erica pretends that she has a college-aged boyfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 17:00:00" d="2021-07-14 17:30:00"><n u="Black-ish">Black-ish VI</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: black-ish
Brand new series - Boss Daddy: Dre's torn at the office between looking out for Junior and letting him make his own mistakes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 17:30:00" d="2021-07-14 18:00:00"><n u="Black-ish">Black-ish VI</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: black-ish
Brand new series - Kid Life Crisis: The Johnsons go on vacation, where Dre and Bow meet a couple without kids and live a childless fantasy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 18:00:00" d="2021-07-14 18:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Captain Peralta: Peralta's father, an airline pilot who hasn't played a big part in his life, comes to town. Holt sets the squad an impossible brain teaser</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 18:30:00" d="2021-07-14 19:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Sabotage: Peralta thinks someone's trying to sabotage his professional life, but Santiago and Diaz aren't convinced. Boyle joins Hitchcock and Scully to solve a case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 19:00:00" d="2021-07-14 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Confirmation Polarization: Sheldon and Amy are thrilled when their super-asymmetry theory is proved correct. Bernadette enjoys some big success at work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 19:30:00" d="2021-07-14 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Meteorite Manifestation: Sheldon is thrilled to help Howard and Bernadette with some bureaucratic paperwork until he realises they are breaking the law</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 20:00:00" d="2021-07-14 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>The Maalik family are rattled by a shock confession, but there's another twist. Martine and Felix are drawn together. A minor slip-up allows captive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 20:30:00" d="2021-07-14 21:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>A stag do leads to a confession from the husband-to-be. Elsewhere, a startling secret is uncovered, there's a heartfelt conversation in the Maalik</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 21:00:00" d="2021-07-14 22:00:00"><n u="Below Deck Mediterranean">Below Deck Mediterranean IV</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Below Deck Mediterranean
Brand new series - Cannes You Cook?: The crew come to terms with Mila's views. Dr Jennifer Berman returns and Hannah's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 22:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:00:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction V (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Thirty-year-old Pablo is HIV positive and wants to break the stigma about his condition. Rapper Leon has been attracting the wrong sort of lady. Can Naked Attraction help?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 23:00:00" d="2021-07-15 00:05:00"><n>Naked Attraction</n><e>TF</e>    <k>A celebration of Naked Attraction's very best naughty bits, as we revisit some of the most outrageous OMG moments, including Judith who</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 00:05:00" d="2021-07-15 01:05:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats">8 Out of 10 Cats XXII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts the comedy panel show and he's joined by Rob Beckett, Katherine Ryan, Richard Osman, Tom Allen, Sophie Hermann and Sophie Duker. Ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 01:05:00" d="2021-07-15 02:05:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox IX</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Britain's favourite viewers on: Mary Berry Everyday, The Nightly Show, The Secret Life of the Zoo, Little Big Shots, the Oscars and squirrels on the News - and more. Ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 02:05:00" d="2021-07-15 03:10:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates XI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Glamorous former reality TV star Aisleyne is looking for a man with 'the heart of the Dalai Lama, the personality of Russell Brand and the body of Rocky Balboa'. Ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 03:10:00" d="2021-07-15 03:35:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty I (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>91% Rick and Morty [adult swim]
Meeseeks and Destroy: Rick allows Morty to lead their next expedition, and provides an inventive solution to the family's trivial problems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 03:35:00" d="2021-07-15 04:00:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty I (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>91% Rick and Morty [adult swim]
Rick Potion #9: Rick gives Morty a potion that will make Jessica, the girl of his dreams, attracted to him at the school dance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 04:00:00" d="2021-07-15 04:55:00"><n>Naked Attraction</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>A celebration of Naked Attraction's very best naughty bits, as we revisit some of the most outrageous OMG moments, including Judith who</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 04:55:00" d="2021-07-15 05:20:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother I (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Okay Awesome: Ted investigates the club scene with Barney and Robin, while Marshall and Lily try to be more 'grown up' as their wedding day approaches</k>  </p>
</a>
