<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="44" t="2019-07-11 00:18:50"><p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 05:10:00" d="2019-07-16 05:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Property Division Collision: Sheldon, Amy, Leonard and Penny attempt to divide up all their possessions into two separate households but tension ensues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 05:30:00" d="2019-07-16 05:50:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine IV (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Coral Palms (Part 3/3): The team go on a road trip to help Peralta and Holt take down crime boss Jimmy Figgis but their plan is hindered by an unforeseen injury</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 05:50:00" d="2019-07-16 06:15:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine IV (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Night Shift: Holt looks for ways to improve the team's morale, while Santiago is filled with curiosity when Diaz starts to take long breaks from her desk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 06:15:00" d="2019-07-16 06:35:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother VII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Best Man: While Barney prepares for his wedding to a mystery bride, he and Ted reminisce about Punchy's wedding. Robin considers telling Barney</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 06:35:00" d="2019-07-16 07:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother VII (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Naked Truth: Marshall lands his dream job but worries that his past indiscretions will cost him the role. Ted can't decide who to bring to the Architects' Ball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 07:00:00" d="2019-07-16 07:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Goldie jumps at the chance of helping Joel with his new project. Marnie urges James to stop his suspicious behaviour. Maxine's dream wedding may be further</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 07:30:00" d="2019-07-16 08:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Liam and Mercedes know the identity of their blackmailer, so Liam comes to a drastic decision. Sparks continue to fly between Goldie and Joel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 08:00:00" d="2019-07-16 08:30:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Flirting with Disaster: When Jeff's snoring finally becomes unbearable, Audrey decides that they should sleep in separate bedrooms, but Jeff soon takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 08:30:00" d="2019-07-16 09:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Audrey's Sister: Audrey's sister Barbara has problems in her marriage and turns to her sibling for help, but while she is around, Russell tries his hardest to woo her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 09:00:00" d="2019-07-16 09:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother VII (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Ducky Tie: Ted tries to make amends with an ex because he cheated on her during their relationship. Marshall and Lily make a bet with Barney</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 09:30:00" d="2019-07-16 10:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother VII (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Field Trip: When Marshall witnesses his manager's soft approach in settling with a powerful company, he takes matters into his own hands. Ted takes his class on a trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 10:00:00" d="2019-07-16 10:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% The Chaperones: Mel and Joe volunteer to chaperone Ryder's school dance, but get themselves kicked out for bad behaviour. Ryder contemplates breaking up with Stella</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 10:30:00" d="2019-07-16 11:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% I'll Cut You: Mel takes Joe's side when he's involved in a hit-and-run accident, until she discovers the other driver is her hairdresser. Ryder tries to win Stella back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 11:00:00" d="2019-07-16 11:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Birthday Synchronicity: Sheldon and Amy try to celebrate her birthday with an intimate night at home but are interrupted as Bernadette goes into labour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 11:30:00" d="2019-07-16 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Holiday Summation: After spending Christmas apart, the gang gather at Penny and Leonard's flat and hear about Sheldon and Amy's terrible trip to Texas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 12:00:00" d="2019-07-16 12:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% HalloVeen: The precinct embarks on its fifth annual Halloween Heist. Everybody has a plan, no one is safe, and relationships and friendships are sorely tested</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 12:30:00" d="2019-07-16 13:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Bad Beat: To track down an arms dealer, Peralta and Jeffords go undercover at an illegal gambling club. Hitchcock and Scully have an unusual challenge for Diaz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 13:00:00" d="2019-07-16 13:30:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon I (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>74% Gluons, Guacamole, and the Color Purple: No longer academically challenged at school, Sheldon audits a college class taught by his pen pal Dr John Sturgis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 13:30:00" d="2019-07-16 14:00:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon I (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>74% A Dog, a Squirrel, and a Fish Named Fish: A neighbourhood feud erupts between the Coopers and the Sparks family when the Sparks' new dog terrorizes Sheldon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 14:00:00" d="2019-07-16 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory III (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Lunar Excitation: Raj registers Sheldon for online dating and finds the perfect match: the female version of Sheldon. Penny seduces Leonard while she's drunk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 14:30:00" d="2019-07-16 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Robotic Manipulation: Penny tags along to Sheldon's first date with a woman he's been texting for months. Howard finds a new use for a robotic arm</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 15:00:00" d="2019-07-16 15:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Maybe I'm Amazed: After Mel drops a bombshell on Joe during their wedding ceremony, he is forced to make a decision in a hurry that could affect their marriage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 15:30:00" d="2019-07-16 16:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% At Last: Still reeling from the unexpected news at the wedding, Joe issues an impulsive invitation without consulting Mel first, putting their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 16:00:00" d="2019-07-16 16:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Box: Captain Holt sacrifices an evening at the opera to help Peralta carry out an interrogation in the hope of getting a confession from a stubborn suspect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 16:30:00" d="2019-07-16 17:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Puzzle Master: Peralta and Santiago investigate arson attacks connected to a crossword puzzle author. Gina helps Holt with his Commissioner presentation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 17:00:00" d="2019-07-16 17:30:00"><n u="Black-ish">Black-ish II (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>72% The Johnson Show: When news spreads of lay-offs at Stevens &amp; Lido, Dre panics that his family's reputation will be tarnished if he loses his job</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 17:30:00" d="2019-07-16 18:00:00"><n u="Black-ish">Black-ish II (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>72% Super Rich Kids: Dre has always felt that Andre Jr is nothing like him, but when he meets his son's friends, he's pleased he enjoys a good social life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 18:00:00" d="2019-07-16 18:30:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon II (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>74% Carbon Dating and a Stuffed Raccoon: Sheldon gets into trouble with fellow child genius Paige at the Science Museum. Meemaw has a jumble sale in her garage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 18:30:00" d="2019-07-16 19:00:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon II (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>74% An 8-Bit Princess and a Flat Tire Genius: Meemaw gives Sheldon his first video game. George Sr gets jealous when Georgie bonds with Herschel from the garage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 19:00:00" d="2019-07-16 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Alien Parasite Hypothesis: Amy finds that she has romantic feelings for Zack, while Raj and Howard compete to prove who would make the better superhero</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 19:30:00" d="2019-07-16 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Justice League Recombination: The guys slowly warm to Zack and find an enjoyable way to bond with him when they enter a New Year's Eve fancy dress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 20:00:00" d="2019-07-16 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Sienna is on a mission to get what is hers. Cindy realises Liam's true intentions. And Sadie returns with a demand for Liam. Also, Dr Levi wants Maxine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 20:30:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00"><n u="School of Rock">School of Rock I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: School of Rock
Brand new series - Cover Me: When Summer asks Tomika for help becoming the band's lead singer, Tomika must choose between helping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 21:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Hofstadter Insufficiency: Sheldon and Penny bond while Leonard is away. Raj finds someone to share his heartache. Bernadette and Amy attract</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 21:30:00" d="2019-07-16 22:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Long Distance Dissonance: The gang worry when Sheldon's former admirer, Dr Ramona Nowitzki, turns up while Amy is away working at Princeton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 22:00:00" d="2019-07-17 00:10:00"><n>The World's End</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Sci-fi comedy with Simon Pegg, Nick Frost and Martin Freeman. During a pub crawl, a group of old school friends discover a scary threat to humankind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 00:10:00" d="2019-07-17 00:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Celebration Experimentation: The gang persuade Sheldon to celebrate his birthday and invite a few special guests along to his party in the 200th episode</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 00:35:00" d="2019-07-17 01:05:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Application Deterioration: Leonard, Sheldon and Howard run into problems when they file for a patent. Emily reaches out to Raj after their break-up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 01:05:00" d="2019-07-17 01:35:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine IV (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Halloween IV: On Halloween night, the squad members follow precinct tradition and compete for the title of Ultimate Detective Slash Genius</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 01:35:00" d="2019-07-17 02:05:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine IV (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Monster in the Closet: When Pimento and Diaz decide to tie the knot, the squad members try to prepare the perfect wedding under Santiago's careful direction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 02:05:00" d="2019-07-17 03:00:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats">8 Out of 10 Cats XX</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Aisling Bea, Alex Brooker and Katherine Ryan face Rob Beckett, Natalie Cassidy and Tom Allen in the comedy panel show. Ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 03:00:00" d="2019-07-17 04:00:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox III (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>72% Britain's opinionated viewers pass judgement on the week's biggest and best TV including Britain's Got Talent, The Cube Celebrity Special, Dogging Tales</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 04:00:00" d="2019-07-17 04:55:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates X</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Emily - Miss Essex 2016/17 - is looking for a man who won't just see her as a trophy girlfriend. Ketan, who has autism, meets Brodie, who's looking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-17 04:55:00" d="2019-07-17 05:15:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Birthday Synchronicity: Sheldon and Amy try to celebrate her birthday with an intimate night at home but are interrupted as Bernadette goes into labour</k>  </p>
</a>
