<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="41" t="2020-05-29 04:34:09"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 05:10:00" d="2020-06-05 05:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Scavenger Vortex: Raj organises an epic and demanding scavenger hunt for the group of friends, designed to test their scientific knowledge and common sense</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 05:35:00" d="2020-06-05 06:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Raiders Minimization: Amy ruins one of Sheldon's favourite films by pointing out a flaw in the storyline. Raj and Stuart decide to create online dating profiles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 06:00:00" d="2020-06-05 06:25:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch VI (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Time After Time: Sabrina uses magic to erase Zelda's broken heart after she breaks up with Professor Carlin, but changing the course of history leaves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 06:25:00" d="2020-06-05 07:00:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch VI (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Sabrina and the Kiss: Sabrina kisses her old boyfriend Derek, but when she tells Josh about it, he says he doesn't mind, leaving her troubled. Hilda hosts a charity auction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 07:00:00" d="2020-06-05 07:30:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Zygote: Jeff and Audrey go to a surrogacy seminar with their surrogate, Brenda, but Jeff is sceptical about the new age advice given to help the implantation process</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 07:30:00" d="2020-06-05 08:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Anniversary Chicken: Jeff is convinced that he has remembered his wedding anniversary and that Audrey has forgotten. Russell pays Timmy to be his translator on a date</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 08:00:00" d="2020-06-05 08:30:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch VI (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Competition: Sabrina is annoyed when Josh says that women can't play tennis as well as men, so she gets magical help. Zelda and Hilda coach Amanda</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 08:30:00" d="2020-06-05 09:00:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch VI (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>I, Busybody: Sabrina tries to give friends, family and colleagues advice but it seems to backfire, so she aims to be less of a busybody</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 09:00:00" d="2020-06-05 09:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Thanks But No Thanks: Mel and Joe write thank you cards to everyone who sent them wedding gifts, and pretend to be delighted with a huge, ugly coffee maker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 09:30:00" d="2020-06-05 10:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Face the Music: Mel discovers that Joe used to be a member of a boy band in his youth, so she buys Dani a piano to foster her dreams of a musical career</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 10:00:00" d="2020-06-05 10:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Play It Again, Bonnie: A lovesick Bonnie realises how much she misses her ex-boyfriend Brad, so she turns to Tucker for help in arranging a reunion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 10:30:00" d="2020-06-05 11:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Livin' on a Prom: When Bonnie goes on strike because she feels unappreciated, Ben tries to get back into her good books by taking her to a Bon Jovi concert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 11:00:00" d="2020-06-05 11:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Workplace Proximity: Amy tells Sheldon she's been asked to work on a project at his university, but the guys insist that this will be bad for their relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 11:30:00" d="2020-06-05 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Romance Resonance: Sheldon is mortified when he stumbles upon an important scientific breakthrough by accident. Howard makes a romantic gesture to Bernadette</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 12:00:00" d="2020-06-05 12:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Recipe for Death II: Kiss the Cook: Adam asks his father for money to film his own action movie, while Erica and Beverly go on a clothes shopping expedition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 12:30:00" d="2020-06-05 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Ho-ly K.I.T.T: A shared love of the TV show Knight Rider brings Murray and his brother Marvin together. Beverly invites Lainey and Bill to Thanksgiving dinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 13:00:00" d="2020-06-05 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Halloween II: Peralta and Holt repeat their Halloween wager of the previous year as Peralta bets the Captain that he can steal his watch before midnight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 13:30:00" d="2020-06-05 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Mole: When an Internal Affairs investigator reveals there's a mole in the precinct, Peralta and Holt must find out who it is before Wuntch catches on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 14:00:00" d="2020-06-05 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Proton Regeneration: Sheldon goes head-to-head with Wil Wheaton as they compete for the role of the new Professor Proton when the TV series has a reboot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 14:30:00" d="2020-06-05 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Geology Methodology: Sheldon and Bert collaborate on a research project, although Sheldon feels embarrassed to be associated with the study of geology</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 15:00:00" d="2020-06-05 15:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Put a Ring on It: Joe buys Mel a fake birthday gift to distract her from his big surprise: a unique wedding ring that he has had created especially for her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 15:30:00" d="2020-06-05 16:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Game Night: With Ryder home on leave from the Navy, Mel decides to organise a fun family game night, pitting herself and Joe against Lennox and Zander</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 16:00:00" d="2020-06-05 16:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy IV (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% It's a Wonderful Emma: Feeling grumpy about all the fuss and upheaval surrounding the yuletide season, Ben makes a wish that Christmas had never existed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 16:30:00" d="2020-06-05 17:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy IV (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% She Loves Me, She Loves Me Note: Ben becomes suspicious that Riley might secretly be in love with Danny and plants a fake love note to find out the truth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 17:00:00" d="2020-06-05 17:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Defense Rests: Sophia's job gets in the way of her relationship with Peralta. Deputy Chief Wuntch needs Captain Holt's help with a job recommendation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 17:30:00" d="2020-06-05 18:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Windbreaker City: The team is invited to a Homeland Security counter-terrorism training exercise where the agent in charge assigns them the role of hostages</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 18:00:00" d="2020-06-05 18:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Kara-te Kid: Inspired by the Karate Kid films, Adam and the other Adam Goldberg face off in a karate match to settle their long-running feud for good</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 18:30:00" d="2020-06-05 19:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Baré: When Lainey reveals that she has won a scholarship to a top art college, Barry considers modifying his dream of becoming a doctor to go with her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 19:00:00" d="2020-06-05 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Neonatal Nomenclature: When Bernadette is unable to go into labour, her friends employ a number of different tactics to get the process started</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 19:30:00" d="2020-06-05 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Athenaeum Allocation: Leonard jumps through hoops to secure the perfect wedding venue for Sheldon and Amy. Howard and Bernadette face a big decision</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 20:00:00" d="2020-06-05 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks Favourites</n><e>F</e>    <k>A look back at a classic Hollyoaks villain. Silas is arrested as the village grieves for Heidi. But it doesn't end there when the McQueens receive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 20:30:00" d="2020-06-05 21:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Vulture: Peralta is irked when a detective from Major Crimes takes over a murder case that he is close to solving. Can he prevent the officer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 21:00:00" d="2020-06-05 21:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Santa Simulation: Sheldon unwillingly reveals painful memories of Christmas past when Leonard persuades him to join in with a seasonal game of Dungeons &amp; Dragons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 21:30:00" d="2020-06-05 22:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Egg Salad Equivalency: Sheldon is accused of sexual harassment and sent to Human Resources, where he ends up dragging Leonard, Raj and Howard into trouble too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 22:00:00" d="2020-06-06 00:20:00"><n>Anchorman 2: The Legend Continues</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Comedy sequel starring Will Ferrell. TV presenter Ron attempts to re-establish his career by joining the world's first 24-hour news channel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 00:20:00" d="2020-06-06 01:20:00"><n u="Buffy the Vampire Slayer">Buffy the Vampire Slayer I (5)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Never Kill a Boy on the First Date: While Buffy awaits the arrival of a warrior vampire, she dates a boy who is attracted to her exciting lifestyle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 01:20:00" d="2020-06-06 01:50:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Friendship Algorithm: Sheldon develops a scientific procedure for making friends when he discovers that Kripke has control of a new supercomputer at the university</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 01:50:00" d="2020-06-06 02:20:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Financial Permeability: When Sheldon lends Penny some money, it brings her ex-boyfriend Kurt back into her life, with negative consequences for the gang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 02:20:00" d="2020-06-06 03:25:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction V (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Mum Michelle goes naked in the hope of finding her leading man. And gym bunny Adam from Essex hopes his body confidence will help him meet a partner who's fit like him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 03:25:00" d="2020-06-06 04:20:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox VII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>What do Britain's favourite viewers think of Britain's Got Talent, Natural World: Kangaroo Dundee, The Secret, Jaws, Paul Merton's Secret Stations and the News? Ep12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 04:20:00" d="2020-06-06 05:15:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats">8 Out of 10 Cats XXI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Rob Beckett, Kerry Godliman, Nish Kumar, Natasia Demetriou, Fred Sirieix and Judi Love compete in this edition of the comedy panel show. Ep3)</k>  </p>
</a>
