<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="40" t="2020-06-01 04:32:30"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 05:40:00" d="2020-06-08 07:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks: Omnibus</n><t>S</t>    <k>49% Hollyoaks Omnibus
Nancy debates whether she can ever trust Kyle again. Jordan and Leela have a heart-to-heart. An uninvited guest makes a shock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 07:00:00" d="2020-06-08 07:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>R</e>    <k>Can Nancy ever trust Kyle again? Jordan and Leela have a heart-to-heart about their upbringings. Mercedes and Sylver are loved-up but unaware that someone is watching them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 07:30:00" d="2020-06-08 08:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>R</e>    <k>Mercedes and Sylver renew their vows, but there's a shock when an uninvited guest makes a big announcement. Kyle urges Darren to help him fix things with Nancy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 08:00:00" d="2020-06-08 08:30:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch VI (19)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Guilty!: Sabrina's plan to have Zelda nominated for Professor of the Year goes awry when the committee discover she attended college in</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 08:30:00" d="2020-06-08 09:00:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch VI (20)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Whole Ball of Wax: Thinking that somebody has been following her, Sabrina corners her stalker in a classroom at school and is happy to see that it's her mother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 09:00:00" d="2020-06-08 09:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (9)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>68% Being There: Hoping to improve face-to-face communication within the family, Joe puts a ban on the use of all mobile phones and computers over the weekend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 09:30:00" d="2020-06-08 10:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (10)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>68% Parental Guidance: Joe is furious when he finds out that Dani invited some older friends over to the house and they drank his expensive bottle of wine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 10:00:00" d="2020-06-08 10:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (15)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>71% From Here to Paternity: Riley tries to find her biological father, using her parents' high school yearbook as a guide, and locates two possible candidates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 10:30:00" d="2020-06-08 11:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (16)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>71% Curious Georgie: Riley is thrilled when Philip's sister Georgie visits from England. Danny's new contract negotiations with the Rangers are put in jeopardy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 11:00:00" d="2020-06-08 11:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (7)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Proton Displacement: Sheldon is jealous when Professor Proton asks Leonard to read his latest publication, so he befriends a TV personality from a rival science show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 11:30:00" d="2020-06-08 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (8)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Itchy Brain Simulation: A worried Leonard thinks that Sheldon will overreact when he confesses that he failed to return a DVD to the rental shop seven years earlier</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 12:00:00" d="2020-06-08 12:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (8)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Greatest Musical Ever Written: Barry makes fun of Adam for taking part in a school musical. Beverly's job as a substitute teacher causes problems for Erica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 12:30:00" d="2020-06-08 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (9)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Globetrotters: When Adam creates a video that makes it look as though he and his friends beat Barry in a game of basketball, Barry demands a rematch in the gym</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 13:00:00" d="2020-06-08 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% Jake and Sophia: Peralta hits it off with a woman in a bar, only to find out she is the defence attorney representing a perpetrator he wants to put in jail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 13:30:00" d="2020-06-08 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (7)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% Lockdown: Peralta is left in charge of the precinct at Thanksgiving because Holt and Jeffords are away, but chaos ensues when a strange package is delivered</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 14:00:00" d="2020-06-08 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (8)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Tesla Recoil: Leonard and Howard learn that Sheldon went to work with the military behind their backs. Bernadette thinks Ruchi's trying to steal her job</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 14:30:00" d="2020-06-08 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (9)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Bitcoin Entanglement: Sheldon seeks revenge when the guys cut him out of a potentially valuable investment. A secret about Leonard and Penny is revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 15:00:00" d="2020-06-08 15:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (21)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>68% Be the Bigger Person: Mel launches a healthy diet campaign while running for a Senate seat, but a voter soon catches her out eating some unhealthy fast food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 15:30:00" d="2020-06-08 16:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (22)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>68% Double Happiness: Mel receives unexpected news that could directly affect her run for a Senate seat. Lennox and Zander are involved in a serious car crash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 16:00:00" d="2020-06-08 16:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy IV (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>71% I See Crazy People: Riley doubts her future with Ben when a psychic reading says the relationship is doomed, so he tries to convince her that they are soulmates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 16:30:00" d="2020-06-08 17:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy IV (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>71% Mugging for the Camera: When Ben and Riley are attacked by a mugger, Danny saves the day but can't take the credit as he's still pretending he lives in Paris</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 17:00:00" d="2020-06-08 17:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (16)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% The Wednesday Incident: When Peralta notices that Captain Holt is in a bad mood, he teams up with Holt's husband Kevin to find out what has gone wrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 17:30:00" d="2020-06-08 18:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (17)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% Boyle-Linetti Wedding: As the wedding day of Gina's mother and Boyle's father dawns, each member of the squad is given a task to complete for the nuptials</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 18:00:00" d="2020-06-08 18:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (19)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>A Night to Remember: Barry plans romantic gestures for Lainey on prom night, Erica and Geoff try to attend the event together and a nerdy girl asks Adam out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 18:30:00" d="2020-06-08 19:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (20)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Dynamic Duo: Barry tries to drive a wedge between Adam and Pops when they discuss a recently released Batman movie. Erica messes up her college interview</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 19:00:00" d="2020-06-08 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (18)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Gates Excitation: The guys do everything in their power to meet Bill Gates when his firm has dealings with the pharmaceutical company Penny works for</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 19:30:00" d="2020-06-08 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (19)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Tenant Disassociation: Leonard competes with Sheldon to become president of the tenants' association. Howard and Raj find a drone in the back garden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 20:00:00" d="2020-06-08 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n>    <k>Kyle gives Nancy, Oscar and Charlie the perfect day. Darren tells Luke that he's depressed. Mercedes catches Cher stealing from her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 20:30:00" d="2020-06-08 21:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (6)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% Halloween: On a very busy Halloween night, Santiago - who detests the holiday - is forced to put on a fancy dress costume and go undercover on a street patrol with Boyle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 21:00:00" d="2020-06-08 22:00:00"><n>Don't Tell the Bride</n><e>R</e>    <k>The hit series where grooms plan every detail of their weddings. Carl hopes to make a splash in Spain as he organises his big day with Rebecca</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 22:00:00" d="2020-06-08 23:00:00"><n u="Celebrity SAS: Who Dares Wins">Celebrity SAS: Who Dares Wins I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>T</e>    <k>Celebrity SAS: Who Dares Wins. 
. or Stand Up To Cancer: One celebrity recruit collapses on a mountain and another is badly affected by the extreme cold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 23:00:00" d="2020-06-09 00:05:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction VI</n><e>RT</e>    <k>In the studio this time are 27-year old flight attendant Alex, who has never had a serious relationship, and horse loving Laura, who hopes to find herself a sexy stallion. Ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-09 00:05:00" d="2020-06-09 01:05:00"><n u="Buffy the Vampire Slayer">Buffy the Vampire Slayer I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Pack: Xander and several other students are possessed by the spirit of a demonic breed of hyenas that wreak havoc at the high school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-09 01:05:00" d="2020-06-09 01:35:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty I (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>92% Rick and Morty [adult swim]
Pilot: Acclaimed animation following drunken scientist Rick and his easily influenced grandson Morty as they split their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-09 01:35:00" d="2020-06-09 02:05:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>92% Rick and Morty [adult swim]
Lawnmower Dog: Rick builds a device to make the family dog Snuffles more intelligent but things go awry. Rick and Morty invade</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-09 02:05:00" d="2020-06-09 02:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (17)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Terminator Decoupling: Leonard, Sheldon, Howard and Raj discover that beautiful sci-fi actress Summer Glau is on board their train to San Francisco</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-09 02:35:00" d="2020-06-09 03:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (18)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Work Song Nanocluster: Penny's home-based business selling hair accessories gets out of hand when an overexcited Sheldon takes charge of production</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-09 03:00:00" d="2020-06-09 03:55:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox VIII</n><e>R</e>    <k>What do Britain's favourite opinionated viewers think of Strictly Come Dancing, The Lie Detective, Victoria, Celebrity Island with Bear Grylls, National</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-09 03:55:00" d="2020-06-09 04:50:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates VI</n><e>R</e>    <k>Is there chemistry between hunky scientist Ashley and single parent Sonia? Burlesque dancer Becky meets budding comedian Lewis. Do Queen fans Gemma</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-09 04:50:00" d="2020-06-09 07:50:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (7)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Proton Displacement: Sheldon is jealous when Professor Proton asks Leonard to read his latest publication, so he befriends a TV personality from a rival science show</k>  </p>
</a>
