<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="45" t="2019-08-15 22:31:45"><p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 05:00:00" d="2019-08-21 05:20:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Therapist: Boyle brings Peralta into a case when a psychiatrist reports one of his patients missing. Captain Holt wants to meet Diaz's new girlfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 05:20:00" d="2019-08-21 05:45:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Casecation: Peralta and Santiago celebrate their wedding anniversary while standing guard over a comatose drugs baron who was shot and rushed into hospital</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 05:45:00" d="2019-08-21 06:10:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother IX (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Last Forever (Part 2/2): The gang are seeing less of each other, but reunite one more time for Ted's wedding. A huge event in his personal life leads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 06:10:00" d="2019-08-21 06:35:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother I (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Pilot: Ted realises he wants to find true love when his best friend Marshall proposes to his girlfriend Lily. Soon, Ted becomes smitten when he meets Robin in a nearby bar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 06:35:00" d="2019-08-21 07:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Anniversary Chicken: Jeff is convinced that he has remembered his wedding anniversary and that Audrey has forgotten. Russell pays Timmy to be his translator on a date</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 07:00:00" d="2019-08-21 07:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Goldie is forced to lie to her mum about Joel. Maxine has some distressing news for Damon, and Liam tries to fix things with Bobby. There's a shocking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 07:30:00" d="2019-08-21 08:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>The village is shaken by the disturbing discovery. The walls are closing in on Breda, but will she manage to talk her way out of it? Damon has a big idea to show Maxine how special she is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 08:00:00" d="2019-08-21 08:30:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>The Jeff Photo: While at a gallery, Audrey finds an old photo of Jeff looking very fit, which motivates him to try to get fit again. Russell is having no luck with women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 08:30:00" d="2019-08-21 09:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Double Down: Jeff and Audrey are thrown into a panic when their surrogate, Brenda, has an ultrasound scan that reveals they might be having twins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 09:00:00" d="2019-08-21 09:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Purple Giraffe: Ted feels desperate when Robin doesn't turn up to a party he invited her to as a second date and he vows to continue throwing parties until she does</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 09:30:00" d="2019-08-21 10:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Sweet Taste of Liberty: Ted agrees that Barney should spice up his love life, as a result of which he ends up flying to Philadelphia for a crazy adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 10:00:00" d="2019-08-21 10:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Young Love: Mel embarks upon a romantic relationship with a younger man. Lennox faces a challenge when she aims to take up the post of editor of the school blog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 10:30:00" d="2019-08-21 11:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Mel and Joe's Anniversary: Joe confronts his ex-wife for going on a date with a new man to their special place on what would have been their wedding anniversary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 11:00:00" d="2019-08-21 11:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% The Slump: Dr Shaw decides that Riley's the cause of Danny's inability to focus during ice hockey matches. Riley thinks things are moving too fast with Fitch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 11:30:00" d="2019-08-21 12:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Ben's Big Gaycare Adventure: Ben tries to get Emma into daycare by flirting with cute assistant manager Megan, who jumps to the wrong conclusion about Ben and Tucker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 12:00:00" d="2019-08-21 12:30:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>F-i--First S-e--Second F--First Day: When new students with disabilities start at the school, Maya urges their parents to demand full-time aides like Kenneth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 12:30:00" d="2019-08-21 13:00:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>J-J's D-r--Dream: Ray gets in over his head when he makes up a fake charity to impress his girlfriend. Maya gives newly promoted Jimmy tips on being the boss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 13:00:00" d="2019-08-21 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Operation: Broken Feather: Peralta is upset to hear that Santiago is considering leaving the precinct to work with his nemesis 'the Vulture' in the Special Crimes Unit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 13:30:00" d="2019-08-21 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Party: Captain Holt invites the entire squad over to his house to celebrate his birthday, but Peralta and Santiago make a bad impression on Holt's husband Kevin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 14:00:00" d="2019-08-21 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Re-entry Minimization: Howard is disappointed when he doesn't receive a hero's welcome on his return from space. Will he ever get the recognition he deserves?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 14:30:00" d="2019-08-21 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Holographic Excitation: The gang celebrates Halloween with a fancy dress party at Stuart's comic book shop, but Sheldon and Amy can't agree on which costumes to wear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 15:00:00" d="2019-08-21 15:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% I Can Manage: When Mel feels the pressure of balancing her home renovations with her duties at work, Joe convinces her to put him in charge of construction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 15:30:00" d="2019-08-21 16:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% If You Can't Stand the Heat: Mel is charmed by the good-looking young man who designs her new kitchen cabinets, but Joe's reaction to him leads to an argument</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 16:00:00" d="2019-08-21 16:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Surprise!: Ben learns why Riley doesn't like celebrating her birthday. Bonnie reveals she forgot to complete some paperwork and that Ben isn't Emma's sole custodian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 16:30:00" d="2019-08-21 17:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Emma's First Christmas: Ben and Danny end up wearing elf suits when they go out of their way to find a particular toy as a Christmas gift for baby Emma</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 17:00:00" d="2019-08-21 17:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Jimmy Jab Games: When the squad has time to kill, Peralta launches the seventh annual Jimmy Jab Games, an eccentric series of contests held in the precinct building</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 17:30:00" d="2019-08-21 18:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Halloween II: Peralta and Holt repeat their Halloween wager of the previous year as Peralta bets the Captain that he can steal his watch before midnight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 18:00:00" d="2019-08-21 18:30:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>D-i--DiMeo A-c--Academy: After a dust-up about JJ's graduation with his teachers, Maya comes to her son's rescue and launches her own school from their home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 18:30:00" d="2019-08-21 19:00:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>E-i--Eighteen: JJ struggles with not being treated like an adult on his 18th birthday. Ray tries to make Taylor jealous with some of his father's old moves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 19:00:00" d="2019-08-21 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Cooper/Kripke Inversion: Sheldon is forced to work on the same project as his nemesis Barry Kripke. Howard and Raj spend a fortune on personalised action figures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 19:30:00" d="2019-08-21 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Spoiler Alert Segmentation: After Sheldon and Leonard have a row, Leonard attempts to move in with Penny, even though she isn't ready for this big step</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 20:00:00" d="2019-08-21 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Maxine is over the moon for her big day, but will Sienna manage to convince her to tell the truth? Liam gives Mercedes a big ultimatum, and Jack helps a grieving villager</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 20:30:00" d="2019-08-21 21:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VI (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Beverly Goldberg Cookbook: Beverly and Adam appear on a mother-and-son cookery show on public access TV. Barry ruins his college letter of recommendation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 21:00:00" d="2019-08-21 21:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Locomotion Interruption: Leonard and Amy take an impromptu road trip to Arizona to pick up Sheldon when his epic railway journey ends in chaos. Penny has an interview</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 21:30:00" d="2019-08-21 22:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Junior Professor Solution: When Sheldon has to teach a course at the university, Howard enrols in his class. Tension is brewing between Penny and Bernadette</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 22:00:00" d="2019-08-21 23:00:00"><n u="Celebs Go Dating">Celebs Go Dating VII (14)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>54% New: Celebs Go Dating
Brand new series: Nathan goes on a second date with sexy Spanish Alain, hoping it will be as spicy as the first! Jack Fincham</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 23:00:00" d="2019-08-22 00:00:00"><n u="Wife Swap USA">Wife Swap USA I</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Wife Swap USA
Brand new series: An old-school mother of eight children swaps lives with a gay millennial father of two infants who believes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-22 00:00:00" d="2019-08-22 00:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Dumpling Paradox: When Howard seduces Penny's friend and spends the night with her in Penny's flat, Penny asks if she can sleep on Leonard and Sheldon's sofa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-22 00:30:00" d="2019-08-22 01:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Grasshopper Experiment: Raj panics when his parents arrange a blind date for him, only to discover he actually can talk to a member of the opposite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-22 01:00:00" d="2019-08-22 01:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Bimbo: Holt and Peralta investigate when valuable antique coins are stolen from the university where Kevin works. Jeffords and Santiago get competitive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-22 01:30:00" d="2019-08-22 02:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Ticking Clocks: Peralta and the squad track down a hacker who infiltrates the precinct's servers, compromising protected information on undercover agents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-22 02:00:00" d="2019-08-22 03:05:00"><n u="Celebs Go Dating">Celebs Go Dating VII (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>54% Brand new series: Nathan goes on a second date with sexy Spanish Alain, hoping it will be as spicy as the first! Jack Fincham is sent on a new date with Megan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-22 03:05:00" d="2019-08-22 03:55:00"><n u="Wife Swap USA">Wife Swap USA I</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series: An old-school mother of eight children swaps lives with a gay millennial father of two infants who believes that traditional ways aren't always the best. Ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-22 03:55:00" d="2019-08-22 04:50:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox VI</n><e>RF</e>    <k>What do Britain's favourite TV viewers think of Doctor Foster, Strictly Come Dancing, Sex Diaries: Webcam Couples, Release the Hounds, First Dates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-22 04:50:00" d="2019-08-22 05:15:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Bimbo: Holt and Peralta investigate when valuable antique coins are stolen from the university where Kevin works. Jeffords and Santiago get competitive</k>  </p>
</a>
