<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="44" t="2019-08-13 02:07:42"><p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 05:00:00" d="2019-08-20 05:20:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Golden Child: Peralta helps Santiago to navigate the complicated relationship she has with her brother. Boyle introduces drama into an undercover mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 05:20:00" d="2019-08-20 05:45:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Gintars: Boyle and Peralta investigate Nikolaj's family. Holt and Santiago bring in forensic scientist Dr Yee to help close a difficult murder case for Diaz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 05:45:00" d="2019-08-20 06:05:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother IX (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% The End of the Aisle: With only 30 minutes before the wedding, both Robin and Barney are having panic attacks, and Lily and Marshall think about their own wedding vows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 06:05:00" d="2019-08-20 06:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother IX (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Last Forever (Part 1/2): With Barney and Robin's wedding day over, Ted says goodbye to the gang and prepares to leave for a new life in Chicago, but fate has other plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 06:30:00" d="2019-08-20 07:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Jeff Day: When Jeff proclaims that it's 'Jeff Day', everything goes swimmingly until the cleaning lady arrives. Adam is baffled when his eye keeps twitching</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 07:00:00" d="2019-08-20 07:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>It's Jack and Breda's secret wedding day, but Breda has pressing matters to attend to. She tells Joel in the confession box that someone in her family has sinned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 07:30:00" d="2019-08-20 08:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Goldie is forced to lie to her mum about Joel. Maxine has some distressing news for Damon, and Liam tries to fix things with Bobby. There's a shocking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 08:00:00" d="2019-08-20 08:30:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Anniversary Chicken: Jeff is convinced that he has remembered his wedding anniversary and that Audrey has forgotten. Russell pays Timmy to be his translator on a date</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 08:30:00" d="2019-08-20 09:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Beating the System: When Jeff and Audrey learn that their surrogate is pregnant, Jeff is unprepared for the radical changes that soon begin to affect their lives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 09:00:00" d="2019-08-20 09:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother IX (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Last Forever (Part 2/2): The gang are seeing less of each other, but reunite one more time for Ted's wedding. A huge event in his personal life leads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 09:30:00" d="2019-08-20 10:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother I (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Pilot: Ted realises he wants to find true love when his best friend Marshall proposes to his girlfriend Lily. Soon, Ted becomes smitten when he meets Robin in a nearby bar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 10:00:00" d="2019-08-20 10:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Auction Hero: Mel urges Joe to participate in a school charity auction, but when he does so, it seems that the winner of the event has ulterior motives for taking part</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 10:30:00" d="2019-08-20 11:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Waiting for Mr Right: Joe teases Mel when she brings home a guy who's boring, but she feels the pressure to be in a relationship when her last single friend gets engaged</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 11:00:00" d="2019-08-20 11:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% New Bonnie vs Old Ben: Bonnie sets up her new apartment right across the hall from the boys but Ben and Tucker are keen to force her out as soon as possible</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 11:30:00" d="2019-08-20 12:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% The Wheeler and the Dealer: Ben persuades Danny to sign a sponsorship deal with a brand of Japanese energy drink, but things go haywire at the photo shoot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 12:00:00" d="2019-08-20 12:30:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless I (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>C-a--Camp: As the family prepares for their flight to JJ's summer camp, Maya receives a shock at the airport. Ray spies an opportunity to reinvent himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 12:30:00" d="2019-08-20 13:00:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>W-e--We're B-a--Back!: Maya, Jimmy and Dylan make dramatic changes in their lives. When JJ comes home from summer camp, Dylan finds a love note in his bag</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 13:00:00" d="2019-08-20 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Bet: Peralta and Santiago's ongoing bet about who can make the most arrests comes to an awkward conclusion. Boyle gets a medal after he's shot in the line of duty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 13:30:00" d="2019-08-20 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Ebony Falcon: For his first task back in the field, Sgt Jeffords prepares to join Peralta and Boyle to infiltrate a gymnasium where steroids are being sold illegally</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 14:00:00" d="2019-08-20 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Decoupling Fluctuation: Sheldon intervenes when he learns that Penny is thinking about breaking up with Leonard, but he is hampered by his inability to keep a secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 14:30:00" d="2019-08-20 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Higgs Boson Observation: Amy is jealous when Sheldon hires an attractive female assistant, and Howard's return from space is delayed by a week</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 15:00:00" d="2019-08-20 15:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (29)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Do As I Say, Not As I Did: Lennox plans to go to an all-night party with her boyfriend. Holly grows jealous when she and Ryder allow another girl into their study group</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 15:30:00" d="2019-08-20 16:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (30)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% The Settlement: Mel and Joe face some difficult decisions after Joe comes into some money. A small leak in the ceiling grows into a huge problem for Mel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 16:00:00" d="2019-08-20 16:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% All Riled Up: When Tucker and Danny bail on movie night, Riley and Ben are left alone for the evening and Ben gets it into his head that Riley fancies him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 16:30:00" d="2019-08-20 17:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% The Emma Dilemma: Ben finds out that his neighbour is hosting a playgroup for all of the kids in the local area except Emma because she thinks Ben is a horrible dad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 17:00:00" d="2019-08-20 17:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Undercover: Peralta enlists Boyle's help to track down a missing mobster, Holt tests the squad's patience with practice drills, and Gina pleads with Boyle to keep a secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 17:30:00" d="2019-08-20 18:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Chocolate Milk: Holt's long-time nemesis arrives to carry out an inspection of his precinct. Boyle searches for a 'plus one' to take to his ex-wife's engagement party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 18:00:00" d="2019-08-20 18:30:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>N-e--New Y--Year's E--Eve: Jimmy convinces Maya to go on a night out together on New Year's Eve, but they struggle with Maya's urge to rush home to the kids</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 18:30:00" d="2019-08-20 19:00:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The H-u-s--Hustle: Maya and Jimmy get dragged into a school fundraiser at which Maya makes a new friend. Ray explores his reckless side with JJ and Dylan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 19:00:00" d="2019-08-20 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Egg Salad Equivalency: Sheldon is accused of sexual harassment and sent to Human Resources, where he ends up dragging Leonard, Raj and Howard into trouble too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 19:30:00" d="2019-08-20 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Bakersfield Expedition: The guys take a road trip to a comic book convention in Bakersfield and visit a location where several episodes of Star Trek were filmed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 20:00:00" d="2019-08-20 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Breda is at a crossroads as she begs for God to give her a sign. Jack has gathered everyone at The Dog to try and establish who the serial killer is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 20:30:00" d="2019-08-20 21:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VI (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Our Perfect Strangers: Erica, Barry and Adam are unhappy when their distant relative Gleb visits from Russia, until they realise he can make their lives easier</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 21:00:00" d="2019-08-20 21:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Anything Can Happen Recurrence: Penny and Leonard distract Sheldon from his career problems by reinstating Anything Can Happen Thursday. Raj asks for Howard's advice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 21:30:00" d="2019-08-20 22:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Proton Transmogrification: Sheldon struggles to process his feelings of grief when his idol Professor Proton passes away. The gang gather to celebrate Star Wars Day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 22:00:00" d="2019-08-20 23:00:00"><n u="Celebs Go Dating">Celebs Go Dating VII (13)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>54% New: Celebs Go Dating
Brand new series: An emotional Charlotte gets a mouthful from Josh. Nathan and Lee go punting in Cambridge with first dates Alain and Celina</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-20 23:00:00" d="2019-08-21 00:10:00"><n>Celebrity Gogglebox</n><e>F</e>    <k>From The Chase to Fatal Attraction, what do Westlife, Kelly Osbourne, Laurence and Emilia Fox, Oti Mabuse, Rylan Clark-Neal, Nick Grimshaw and other celebs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 00:10:00" d="2019-08-21 00:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Hamburger Postulate: Leonard fears he's wasting his time on Penny and ends up making a connection with Leslie. Sheldon frets over a change to his hamburger routine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 00:35:00" d="2019-08-21 01:05:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Middle Earth Paradigm: Penny decides to host a big Halloween party, putting Leonard, Sheldon, Howard and Raj through a demanding new test of their social skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 01:05:00" d="2019-08-21 01:35:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Therapist: Boyle brings Peralta into a case when a psychiatrist reports one of his patients missing. Captain Holt wants to meet Diaz's new girlfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 01:35:00" d="2019-08-21 02:05:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Casecation: Peralta and Santiago celebrate their wedding anniversary while standing guard over a comatose drugs baron who was shot and rushed into hospital</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 02:05:00" d="2019-08-21 03:10:00"><n u="Celebs Go Dating">Celebs Go Dating VII (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>54% Brand new series: An emotional Charlotte gets a mouthful from Josh. Nathan and Lee go punting in Cambridge with first dates Alain and Celina</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 03:10:00" d="2019-08-21 04:05:00"><n u="First Dates Hotel">First Dates Hotel III (5)</n><t>S</t><e>TF</e>    <k>Can First Dates Hotel assistant manager Francesca teach plucky mummy's boy Ash to be a Casanova? And Shane, who's been single for 15 years, meets theatre designer Roberto</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-21 04:05:00" d="2019-08-21 05:00:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox VI</n><e>RF</e>    <k>What do Britain's favourite viewers think of Downton Abbey, PigGate on Newsnight, Countdown to Life, Singing in the Rainforest, Antiques Roadshow</k>  </p>
</a>
