<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="45" t="2020-05-26 04:34:09"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 05:20:00" d="2020-06-02 05:45:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Proton Resurgence: Leonard and Sheldon hire Professor Proton, the host of a TV science show they watched as children, to come to their flat and entertain them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 05:45:00" d="2020-06-02 06:10:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch VI (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>A Birthday Witch: Sabrina's birthday plans are interrupted when Great Aunt Irma pays a visit. She has come to test Harvey's trustworthiness because</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 06:10:00" d="2020-06-02 07:00:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch VI (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Deliver Us from E-mail: Sabrina gets the chance to have her own newspaper column, but things go awry when her evil twin Katrina gives her a virus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 07:00:00" d="2020-06-02 07:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nancy struggles to trust a spiralling Kyle to look after Oscar: can Darren help Kyle prove himself? Mercedes has had enough of Sylver's behaviour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 07:30:00" d="2020-06-02 08:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Can Nancy ever trust Kyle again? Jordan and Leela have a heart-to-heart about their upbringings. Mercedes and Sylver are loved-up but unaware that someone is watching them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 08:00:00" d="2020-06-02 08:30:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch VI (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Cloud Ten: After having her story about a refuse collection strike rejected by the newspaper and then being ignored by her roommates, Sabrina takes a wild, escapist trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 08:30:00" d="2020-06-02 09:00:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch VI (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Sabrina and the Candidate: Sabrina writes a scathing article exposing the shady dealings of a local politician, only to discover he has been anonymously</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 09:00:00" d="2020-06-02 09:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Witch Came First: Mel gets a strange visit from her doctor, who calls at the house at Halloween to convince her that she was once a powerful teenage witch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 09:30:00" d="2020-06-02 10:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% A Melanie &amp; Josiah Christmas: Competition grows between Mel and Joe over whose treasured ornament should take the prestigious top spot on the Christmas tree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 10:00:00" d="2020-06-02 10:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% The Bet: Riley wagers Ben that he can't get a second date with Heather. Bonnie meets a handsome stranger and ponders ending her relationship with Brad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 10:30:00" d="2020-06-02 11:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% A Knight to Remember: Ben helps Tucker to pose as a lawyer because Tucker hasn't told his father that he dropped out of law school and is now working in TV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 11:00:00" d="2020-06-02 11:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Love Spell Potential: When the girls' trip to Las Vegas falls through, the guys invite them to a Dungeons &amp; Dragons night that changes Sheldon and Amy's relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 11:30:00" d="2020-06-02 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Bon Voyage Reaction: Leonard is offered an exciting job opportunity that will keep him out of the country for several months. Raj pushes the boundaries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 12:00:00" d="2020-06-02 12:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Have a Summer: Adam worries about being 'hazed' by the older students when he goes to high school, but he soon earns their respect by body-slamming Barry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 12:30:00" d="2020-06-02 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Breakfast Club: Adam works on a new persona that he hopes will make him seem cool on his first day at high school, while Beverly gets her teaching certificate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 13:00:00" d="2020-06-02 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Fancy Brudgom: Boyle asks Peralta to be his best man. Jeffords, Santiago and Gina start a new diet but struggle to stick to it. Holt helps Diaz to make a sincere apology</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 13:30:00" d="2020-06-02 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Unsolvable: Peralta and Jeffords tackle a cold case that everyone thinks is unsolvable, while Santiago plans a romantic weekend away with her new boyfriend Teddy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 14:00:00" d="2020-06-02 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Long Distance Dissonance: The gang worry when Sheldon's former admirer, Dr Ramona Nowitzki, turns up while Amy is away working at Princeton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 14:30:00" d="2020-06-02 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Proposal Proposal: Amy must decide whether or not to marry Sheldon and answers his proposal. Howard and Bernadette struggle with some unexpected news</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 15:00:00" d="2020-06-02 15:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Gone Girl: Mel tries to talk Lennox out of going to Colombia on a research expedition with her college professor. Joe makes Dani call her mother, Felicia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 15:30:00" d="2020-06-02 16:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Call of Duty: Reeling from Ryder's announcement that he wants to join the Navy, Mel and Joe try to discourage him by putting him through a mock boot camp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 16:00:00" d="2020-06-02 16:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Flirty Dancing: Riley gives Ben and Danny the time capsules they made when they were at school. Tucker and Riley turn up uninvited at Bonnie's dance class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 16:30:00" d="2020-06-02 17:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Baby Steps: When a disappointed Ben misses out on seeing Emma's first steps, Bonnie, Tucker, Danny and Riley attempt to recreate the moment for him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 17:00:00" d="2020-06-02 17:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% USPIS: While trying to catch a drug dealer, Peralta and Boyle join forces with Agent Jack Danger, a pompous investigator at the US Postal Inspection Service</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 17:30:00" d="2020-06-02 18:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Road Trip: In an attempt to add a touch of romance to his work trip with Santiago, Peralta invites his girlfriend and her boyfriend to join them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 18:00:00" d="2020-06-02 18:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Han Ukkah Solo: When Beverly talks Erica into writing a Hanukkah song for the school holiday concert, she inspires Barry to prove his own musical prowess</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 18:30:00" d="2020-06-02 19:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>O Captain! My Captain!: Beverly hopes to inspire the students when she takes over as substitute teacher in Barry's chemistry class. Adam embarrasses Emmy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 19:00:00" d="2020-06-02 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Confidence Erosion: Sheldon and Amy try to eliminate stress from their wedding plans by applying mathematics to the process. Raj falls out with Howard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 19:30:00" d="2020-06-02 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Celebration Reverberation: Sheldon and Howard plan birthday celebrations for Amy and Halley. Leonard is stressed by a Christmas letter from his brother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 20:00:00" d="2020-06-02 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>There are more surprises in store for Sylver and Mercedes following the shock announcement at their vow renewal. Mandy tries everything to help Darren</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 20:30:00" d="2020-06-02 21:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Tagger: When Peralta turns up late for morning roll call, Captain Holt responds by assigning him to a minor graffiti case and then closely monitoring his every move</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 21:00:00" d="2020-06-02 21:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Suicide Squad: Desperate circumstances call for desperate measures as Peralta, Captain Holt and the team are forced to ally themselves with some old enemies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 21:30:00" d="2020-06-02 22:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VII</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series - Valloweaster: The squad competes in an effort to determine who is the greatest human/genius. Ep11)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 22:00:00" d="2020-06-02 22:35:00"><n u="The Inbetweeners">The Inbetweeners III (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Will's Dilemma: Simon and his new girlfriend Tara double date with Will and Tara's friend Kerry, but Will wonders if it's worth spending</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 22:35:00" d="2020-06-02 23:05:00"><n u="The Inbetweeners">The Inbetweeners III (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Trip to Warwick: Simon and his new girlfriend Tara are going on a trip to visit her sister at university, but the other boys decide to invite themselves along</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 23:05:00" d="2020-06-02 23:40:00"><n u="Derry Girls">Derry Girls I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The girls are tense about a big exam and naturally jump at a dubious opportunity to get out of it, especially as it involves spending time with the beautiful Father Peter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-02 23:40:00" d="2020-06-03 00:10:00"><n u="Derry Girls">Derry Girls I (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Erin is excited that teenage Katya, 'a child of Chernobyl', is coming to stay, but Katya isn't grateful to be in Derry. And there are developments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 00:10:00" d="2020-06-03 01:10:00"><n u="Buffy the Vampire Slayer">Buffy the Vampire Slayer I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>The Harvest: Buffy and her friends encounter a powerful vampire bent on opening a portal to a dimension inhabited by demons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 01:10:00" d="2020-06-03 01:40:00"><n u="The IT Crowd">The IT Crowd III (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>66% Tramps Like Us: The gang's lives move in different directions after a disappointing settlement to a sexual harassment suit. Jen seeks pastures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 01:40:00" d="2020-06-03 02:15:00"><n u="The IT Crowd">The IT Crowd III (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>66% Speech: As 'Employee of the Month', Jen asserts herself as manager and makes powerful enemies in Moss and Roy. Douglas finds the love of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 02:15:00" d="2020-06-03 02:45:00"><n u="Friday Night Dinner">Friday Night Dinner VI</n><e>TF</e>    <k>The Cage: Jim sets up a giant dog cage for Milson in the Goodmans' living room, and Aunty Val's got a hot date with a 'sex robot'. Ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 02:45:00" d="2020-06-03 03:15:00"><n u="Friday Night Dinner">Friday Night Dinner VI</n><e>TF</e>    <k>The Females: Adam and Jonny bring their 'females' home to meet the parents. Cue an overexcited Mum and an extremely embarrassing Dad. Ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 03:15:00" d="2020-06-03 03:40:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Panty Pinata Polarization: Sheldon bans Penny from the flat for numerous minor infractions, so she retaliates. Howard and Raj search for the America's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 03:40:00" d="2020-06-03 04:05:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Lizard-Spock Expansion: A girl for whom Howard harbours romantic feelings falls for Leonard instead, despite Howard's efforts to woo her, leaving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-03 04:05:00" d="2020-06-03 05:00:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates V</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Singleton Nicole's friends call her Bridget Jones. At first glance, chartered surveyor Gary is no Mr Darcy, but will his karaoke skills impress Nicole? Ep2)</k>  </p>
</a>
