<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="33" t="2020-05-16 04:48:28"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 05:20:00" d="2020-05-23 05:45:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Fish Guts Displacement: Sheldon begrudgingly takes care of Amy when she is sick. Bernadette arranges for Howard to go on a fishing trip with her macho father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 05:45:00" d="2020-05-23 06:10:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch V (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Sabrina, the Activist: Sabrina gets involved in a protest to save a historical building. Josh starts to realise how much he has in common with Sabrina</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 06:10:00" d="2020-05-23 07:00:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch V (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Do You See What I See?: Miles sees Sabrina's flying car and, thinking that he has sighted a UFO, makes a presentation to the class about it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 07:00:00" d="2020-05-23 07:20:00"><n u="Rude Tube Shorts">Rude(ish) Tube Shorts</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Cheeky original clips featuring ducks going up an escalator, animal impressions, a few narrow escapes on a snowboard and rally driving. Plus some interesting food clips</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 07:20:00" d="2020-05-23 07:45:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Harassment: A new employee who takes exception to Audrey files a sexual harassment claim against her. Timmy challenges Jeff to a game of cricket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 07:45:00" d="2020-05-23 08:10:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>They Do?: Adam and Jennifer decide to organise a secret wedding ceremony, but a series of unfortunate events soon puts their romantic plans in jeopardy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 08:10:00" d="2020-05-23 08:40:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Surro-Gate: Jeff and Audrey discover some surprising news about the woman they regard as the perfect candidate to be the surrogate mother for their baby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 08:40:00" d="2020-05-23 09:10:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>The Bank: Jeff reveals he keeps a list of mistakes Audrey has made, which he calls 'the bank'. Russell sends a suggestive email to a colleague on behalf</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 09:10:00" d="2020-05-23 09:40:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Rug-of-War: Jeff is angry when Audrey gives Adam and Jen their old rug, so he tries to discourage them from accepting it by telling them about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 09:40:00" d="2020-05-23 10:40:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>T</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay is in California at Jamaican restaurant Café Kingston. He meets micromanaging owner Dr Una Morris, who's also a radiotherapist in the clinic next door</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 10:40:00" d="2020-05-23 11:40:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>T</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay travels to Eagle Rock, California, to visit Capri - a restaurant in a rut that's owned by identical twins Jim and Jeff and is closed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 11:40:00" d="2020-05-23 12:40:00"><n>Don't Tell the Bride</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Mummy's boy Tiago plans to put his self-conscious bride Karlette on the big screen at his 1950s drive-in wedding, but she wants something intimate and contemporary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 12:40:00" d="2020-05-23 13:40:00"><n>Don't Tell the Bride</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Adrenaline junkie Mark wants to fly high and take to the sky on his big day, but his straight-talking bride-to-be Lynsey wants more personal, no-nonsense nuptials</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 13:40:00" d="2020-05-23 14:10:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>12 Tapes for a Penny: Adam joins a mail-order music club hoping to assemble a huge cassette tape collection. Barry realises Lainey's father doesn't like him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 14:10:00" d="2020-05-23 14:40:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Magic Is Real: Adam tries to use his new magic act to attract girls at school but he's thwarted when Beverly insists on taking to the stage as his assistant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 14:40:00" d="2020-05-23 15:10:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VII</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series - The Preventa Mode: As Valentine's Day approaches, Barry is shocked when an attractive teaching assistant agrees to go out with him. Ep14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 15:10:00" d="2020-05-23 15:40:00"><n u="Schooled">Schooled II</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series - Singled Out: Lainey works out her feelings for Valentine's Day. Felicia has body image issues. Coach Mellor does a workout</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 15:40:00" d="2020-05-23 16:10:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Cinco de Mayo: When Jeffords becomes anxious about his upcoming lieutenant's exam, the squad hold the precinct's annual Halloween Heist on a new date</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 16:10:00" d="2020-05-23 16:40:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VII</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series - Admiral Peralta: Jake and his father deal with unsettled family business. Amy and Rosa work a high-profile case. Terry wants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 16:40:00" d="2020-05-23 17:10:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>75% A High-Pitched Buzz and Training Wheels: Sheldon dismantles the fridge to stop it making an annoying humming noise but must pay for the damage he has done</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 17:10:00" d="2020-05-23 17:40:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Pilot: The first ever episode of the hit sitcom. Leonard and Sheldon's ignorance of women seems set to change when the beautiful Penny moves in next door</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 17:40:00" d="2020-05-23 18:10:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Recollection Dissipation: Sheldon collaborates on two projects - one with Leonard and Howard, plus another with Amy - pushing himself to the limit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 18:10:00" d="2020-05-23 18:40:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Separation Agitation: Howard and Bernadette are upset when they leave Halley at the nursery. Bert the geologist introduces his girlfriend to the gang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 18:40:00" d="2020-05-23 19:10:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Cognition Regeneration: Leonard isn't thrilled when he finds out Penny is considering taking a new job that has been offered by her ex-boyfriend Zack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 19:10:00" d="2020-05-23 19:40:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Gyroscopic Collapse: Amy is offered a fellowship at Princeton, Raj makes new living arrangements, and the guys' gyroscope project spins out of control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 19:40:00" d="2020-05-23 20:10:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Long Distance Dissonance: The gang worry when Sheldon's former admirer, Dr Ramona Nowitzki, turns up while Amy is away working at Princeton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 20:10:00" d="2020-05-23 22:00:00"><n u="Kung Fu Panda">Kung Fu Panda 2</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Animated adventure sequel with the voices of Jack Black and Gary Oldman. Po the panda and his five friends must use all their martial arts skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 22:00:00" d="2020-05-24 00:20:00"><n u="Taken">Taken 3</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Violent action-thriller sequel starring Liam Neeson. The troubled ex-CIA agent is framed for murder. With Famke Janssen, Maggie Grace and Forest Whitaker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 00:20:00" d="2020-05-24 01:20:00"><n>Celebrity Gogglebox USA</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Brand new series: Gogglebox heads across the pond and steps into the homes of a selection of celebrity faces, including Sharon and Kelly Osbourne</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 01:20:00" d="2020-05-24 02:25:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox VII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>What do Britain's favourite viewers think of Take Me Out, Tattoo Fixers, Dunblane: Our Story, Steve Backshall's Extreme Mountain Challenge, Doctor Thorne</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 02:25:00" d="2020-05-24 03:30:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox VII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>What do Britain's favourite opinionated viewers think of Crufts, Horizon: The Immortalist, Big, The Night Manager, Dangerman: The Incredible Mr Goodwin and the News? Ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 03:30:00" d="2020-05-24 04:25:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Can policeman Mark cross the thin line between hate and love on a date with self-confessed 'nightmare' Abi? And will latex-loving Shirlie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 04:25:00" d="2020-05-24 05:20:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Charlotte says she has no 'gender boundaries' but when her date, Charlie, reveals he used to be a girl, Charlotte is uncharacteristically speechless</k>  </p>
</a>
