<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="39" t="2019-07-11 00:18:49"><p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 07:00:00" d="2019-07-15 07:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Jonny and Stuart continue to pull Ste's strings, while James is horrified by his own behaviour. And Mercedes is nearly caught out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 07:30:00" d="2019-07-15 08:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Goldie jumps at the chance of helping Joel with his new project. Marnie urges James to stop his suspicious behaviour. Maxine's dream wedding may be further</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 08:00:00" d="2019-07-15 08:30:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Game On: Audrey is upset when Jeff doesn't react to her recent promotion at work and assumes that he is more interested in the Knicks than in her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 08:30:00" d="2019-07-15 09:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Jeff's Wooby: Russell thinks that he's found the perfect girl when she keeps making sexy comments to him, while Audrey worries about her marriage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 09:00:00" d="2019-07-15 09:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother VII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Best Man: While Barney prepares for his wedding to a mystery bride, he and Ted reminisce about Punchy's wedding. Robin considers telling Barney</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 09:30:00" d="2019-07-15 10:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother VII (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Naked Truth: Marshall lands his dream job but worries that his past indiscretions will cost him the role. Ted can't decide who to bring to the Architects' Ball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 10:00:00" d="2019-07-15 10:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% To Tell the Truth: Mel and Joe's friendship with married couple Nate and Gillian is put in jeopardy when Mel reveals a secret that Nate has told Joe in confidence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 10:30:00" d="2019-07-15 11:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% My Roof, My Rules: When Mel and Joe discover that Lennox is dating Emerson, her teaching assistant, Joe asks Mel to put her foot down and forbid the relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 11:00:00" d="2019-07-15 11:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Geology Elevation: Sheldon can't contain his jealousy when he hears that his university colleague Bert the geologist has won a prestigious fellowship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 11:30:00" d="2019-07-15 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Property Division Collision: Sheldon, Amy, Leonard and Penny attempt to divide up all their possessions into two separate households but tension ensues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 12:00:00" d="2019-07-15 12:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Big House Part 2: Peralta is trapped by divided loyalties after the warden persuades him to investigate prison gang leader Romero's drug smuggling operation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 12:30:00" d="2019-07-15 13:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Kicks: Officially back at the precinct, Peralta looks for a loophole to get out of his temporarily designated desk duty. Diaz thinks Pimento is cheating on her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 13:00:00" d="2019-07-15 13:30:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon I (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>74% Ju-Jitsu, Bubble Wrap, and Yoo-Hoo: When Sheldon is bullied by an unlikely character, Mary and George disagree about how to handle the situation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 13:30:00" d="2019-07-15 14:00:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon I (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>74% A Mother, a Child, and a Blue Man's Backside: When Mary bans Sheldon from reading a comic book, he decides it's time to stop living under his mother's thumb</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 14:00:00" d="2019-07-15 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory III (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Plimpton Stimulation: When Sheldon meets a famous physicist online, he invites her over to the apartment, where she spends her time flirting with Leonard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 14:30:00" d="2019-07-15 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory III (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Staircase Implementation: This episode flashes back to the start of Sheldon and Leonard's friendship seven years earlier and explains the roommate agreement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 15:00:00" d="2019-07-15 15:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Uninvited: Mel is not thrilled when Joe's mother Gloria drops by, but it's Joe who hits the roof when his estranged brother Tony turns up expecting to be able to stay</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 15:30:00" d="2019-07-15 16:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% You're the One That I Want: As Mel and Joe's wedding weekend dawns, Joe is injured at his bachelor party, Mel's father is missing, and a secret is accidentally revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 16:00:00" d="2019-07-15 16:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Safe House: After mobster Seamus Murphy threatens Kevin, Captain Holt devises an elaborate plan to hide his husband in a safe house, with Peralta as his guard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 16:30:00" d="2019-07-15 17:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Negotiation: Peralta negotiates a hostage situation with a jewel thief whose face is familiar. Santiago and Gina aid Boyle with his new food truck business</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 17:00:00" d="2019-07-15 17:30:00"><n u="Black-ish">Black-ish II (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>72% The Leftovers: Dre and Rainbow realise they haven't nominated a legal guardian for their kids, and decide to find replacement parents, just in case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 17:30:00" d="2019-07-15 18:00:00"><n u="Black-ish">Black-ish II (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>72% Johnson &amp; Johnson: As Dre's sister Rhonda prepares to marry her girlfriend Sharon, Rainbow reveals she is against the convention of taking a man's last name</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 18:00:00" d="2019-07-15 18:30:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>74% A Research Study and Czechoslovakian Wedding Pastries: Dr Sturgis recommends Sheldon and Missy for a university research study on twins, but Mary is unhappy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 18:30:00" d="2019-07-15 19:00:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>74% Seven Deadly Sins and a Small Carl Sagan: Mary and Sheldon's drama teacher Mr Lundy clash over plans for a Halloween haunted house fundraiser for the church</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 19:00:00" d="2019-07-15 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The 21-Second Excitation: The gang's plans to attend a film screening are scuppered by Sheldon's nemesis Wil Wheaton. Penny and Bernadette invite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 19:30:00" d="2019-07-15 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Boyfriend Complexity: When Penny's father comes to visit, Leonard discovers her parents still think that he and Penny are a couple, so he takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 20:00:00" d="2019-07-15 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Damon and Maxine go to view their wedding venue, but after some upsetting news, Maxine shocks everyone. Meanwhile, Liam goes on a date with Cindy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 20:30:00" d="2019-07-15 21:00:00"><n u="School of Rock">School of Rock I (1)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: School of Rock
Brand new series - Come Together: Comedy series based on the 2003 film. A down-on-his-luck musician poses as a teacher and inspires</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 21:00:00" d="2019-07-15 21:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Cognition Regeneration: Leonard isn't thrilled when he finds out Penny is considering taking a new job that has been offered by her ex-boyfriend Zack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 21:30:00" d="2019-07-15 22:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Gyroscopic Collapse: Amy is offered a fellowship at Princeton, Raj makes new living arrangements, and the guys' gyroscope project spins out of control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-15 22:00:00" d="2019-07-16 00:10:00"><n u="Conan the Barbarian">Conan the Barbarian (2011)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Conan the Barbarian
(2011) Fantasy action-adventure. Jason Momoa stars as Conan, who sets out to kill the evil warlord who massacred his village</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 00:10:00" d="2019-07-16 00:40:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Valentino Submergence: Sheldon and Amy host a special live Valentine's Day episode of their internet show Fun with Flags. Leonard and Penny grapple with getting older</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 00:40:00" d="2019-07-16 01:05:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Positive Negative Reaction: When Bernadette makes a big announcement, Howard becomes convinced that he needs to start earning more money</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 01:05:00" d="2019-07-16 01:35:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine IV (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Coral Palms (Part 3/3): The team go on a road trip to help Peralta and Holt take down crime boss Jimmy Figgis but their plan is hindered by an unforeseen injury</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 01:35:00" d="2019-07-16 02:05:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine IV (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Night Shift: Holt looks for ways to improve the team's morale, while Santiago is filled with curiosity when Diaz starts to take long breaks from her desk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 02:05:00" d="2019-07-16 03:00:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats">8 Out of 10 Cats XX</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Aisling Bea, Pamela Anderson and Kerry Godliman face Rob Beckett, Ella Eyre and Joe Wilkinson in the comedy panel show. Ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 03:00:00" d="2019-07-16 03:55:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox III (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>72% Britain's favourite opinionated viewers pass judgement on the week's biggest and best TV and films, including The Grand National, Ghost, Fifteen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 03:55:00" d="2019-07-16 04:50:00"><n u="Gogglebox Australia">Gogglebox Australia I (7)</n><t>S</t><e>TF</e>    <k>New: Gogglebox Australia
Brand new series: The viewers react to Keeping Up with the Kardashians, Antiques Roadshow, Titanic, Selling Houses Australia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-07-16 04:50:00" d="2019-07-16 05:10:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Geology Elevation: Sheldon can't contain his jealousy when he hears that his university colleague Bert the geologist has won a prestigious fellowship</k>  </p>
</a>
