<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="40" t="2021-07-09 06:48:41"><p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 05:20:00" d="2021-07-15 05:45:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother I (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Slutty Pumpkin: Ted goes to a boring Halloween party hoping to find a girl he lost touch with who dresses as a 'slutty pumpkin'. Robin goes on a double date</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 05:45:00" d="2021-07-15 06:10:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% The Knockout: When Mel punches a man who picks on Ryder at the cinema, a clip of the event is soon posted online and she becomes known as 'Battling Burke'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 06:10:00" d="2021-07-15 06:35:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Breaking Up Is Hard to Do: Mel wants to break up with her boyfriend Donald, but feels guilty because he's just been fired from his job. Holly confides a secret to Lennox</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 06:35:00" d="2021-07-15 07:00:00"><n u="Black-ish">Black-ish VI</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Brand new series - Boss Daddy: Dre's torn at the office between looking out for Junior and letting him make his own mistakes. Jack loses a friendship after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 07:00:00" d="2021-07-15 07:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Sami is on a mission to get rid of an unwelcome house guest. James faces a difficult ultimatum. Martine takes matters into her own hands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 07:30:00" d="2021-07-15 08:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>An unwelcome visitor causes Shaq to make a shocking confession. Captive Liberty is desperate to return home to her daughter. Martine finds it difficult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 08:00:00" d="2021-07-15 09:00:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>In Fishtown, Philadelphia, Gordon Ramsay visits the Hot Potato Café, which has never made a profit. When the chips are down, can Gordon help save the restaurant?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 09:00:00" d="2021-07-15 09:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother I (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Matchmaker: Ted is coaxed into joining a matchmaking service that Robin has written about and which offers a 100% success rate at finding a soulmate in three days</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 09:30:00" d="2021-07-15 10:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother I (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% The Duel: Ted feels pushed out when Lily and Marshall dominate the household and tells them that he wants to take the flat after they get married</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 10:00:00" d="2021-07-15 10:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Mixed Doubles: Joe sets Mel up on a blind date with his pal, but in exchange for this favour he asks her to arrange a date for him with her attractive friend Ariel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 10:30:00" d="2021-07-15 11:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% The Donor: Mel's friend Jackie decides she wants a baby and settles on Joe as the man most suitable to be the father of her child. Lennox and Haskell buy a rare book</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 11:00:00" d="2021-07-15 11:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% The Wingmom: Bonnie sets Ben up with Bailey, a fast-talking, animated spitfire with plenty of attitude. Riley and Tucker take a cherished car out for a spin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 11:30:00" d="2021-07-15 12:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Send in the Clowns: Ben is determined to give Emma the perfect first birthday party at the ice cream parlour where he and Riley both worked as teenagers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 12:00:00" d="2021-07-15 12:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>12 Tapes for a Penny: Adam joins a mail-order music club, hoping to assemble a huge cassette tape collection. Barry realises that Lainey's father doesn't like him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 12:30:00" d="2021-07-15 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Magic Is Real: Adam tries to use his new magic act to attract girls at school, but he's thwarted when Beverly insists on taking to the stage as his assistant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 13:00:00" d="2021-07-15 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Pontiac Bandit Returns: Doug Judy is back in custody after scamming Peralta and Diaz when they last met, but Captain Holt offers him a plea deal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 13:30:00" d="2021-07-15 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Stakeout: Peralta and Boyle go on an eight-day stakeout, putting a strain on their friendship. Holt's nephew visits and makes an instant impression on Diaz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 14:00:00" d="2021-07-15 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Planetarium Collision: Sheldon accidentally sabotages Amy's career. Raj isn't keen when Howard is invited to join him to host a show at the planetarium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 14:30:00" d="2021-07-15 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Imitation Perturbation: Howard dresses up as Sheldon for Halloween but Sheldon gets revenge. Leonard is shocked that Penny can't recall their first kiss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 15:00:00" d="2021-07-15 15:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Maternal Capacitance: A disastrous visit from Leonard's mother, Beverly, has the unexpected side-effect of bringing Leonard and Penny closer together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 15:30:00" d="2021-07-15 16:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Cushion Saturation: A game of paintball leads to a squabble when Penny accidentally shoots paint at one of Sheldon's cushions. Romance blossoms between Howard and Leslie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 16:00:00" d="2021-07-15 16:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Crazy Calls: After getting telephone answering machines, Murray and Pop-Pop wage a message war on one another. Adam finds a lunchtime home with the school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 16:30:00" d="2021-07-15 17:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Stefan King: Adam gets in trouble with Beverly for portraying her as a monster in a horror story, and Erica forces Barry to attend a Halloween costume dance with her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 17:00:00" d="2021-07-15 17:30:00"><n u="Black-ish">Black-ish VI</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: black-ish
Brand new series - Adventure to Ventura: Dre worries Diane and Jack don't know how to fend for themselves, so he sends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 17:30:00" d="2021-07-15 18:00:00"><n u="Black-ish">Black-ish VI</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: black-ish
Brand new series - The Gauntlet: Dre tries to get Bow a meaningful gift for Valentine's Day. Ruby teaches Jack how to get a girl after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 18:00:00" d="2021-07-15 18:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% AC/DC: Peralta injures himself chasing a suspect but won't take time off to recover. Holt and Diaz have an awkward dinner date with their significant others</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 18:30:00" d="2021-07-15 19:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Det. Dave Majors: Peralta is excited to work on a case with Dave Majors, the best detective in the NYPD, until Majors reveals that he intends to ask Santiago out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 19:00:00" d="2021-07-15 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Donation Oscillation: Penny attempts to sabotage Leonard's efforts to help her ex-boyfriend Zack and his wife Marissa have a family of their own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 19:30:00" d="2021-07-15 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The D &amp; D Vortex: When the gang find out that Wil Wheaton is hosting a celebrity game of Dungeons &amp; Dragons at his home, deception and betrayal take hold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 20:00:00" d="2021-07-15 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Wedding bells are chiming in Hollyoaks, but the bride-to-be has a devilish plan. Elsewhere, Warren is confronted, and Yazz and Tom struggle to get people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 20:30:00" d="2021-07-15 21:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks Favourites</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Former Hollyoaks star Kieron Richardson revisits a classic episode about heartbreak, as Brendan Brady prepares to open up about the childhood abuse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 21:00:00" d="2021-07-15 22:00:00"><n u="Below Deck Mediterranean">Below Deck Mediterranean IV</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Below Deck Mediterranean
Brand new series - Too Many Cooks in the Kitchen: Joao confides in Captain Sandy about his heartbreak. Chef Mila is still</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 22:00:00" d="2021-07-15 23:00:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox XVII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Britain's sharpest armchair critics have been watching Line of Duty, Naked Attraction, I Can See Your Voice, Alan Carr's Epic Gameshow and BBC News (Prince Philip). Ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-15 23:00:00" d="2021-07-16 00:05:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox XVI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Britain's sharpest armchair critics watch Mariah Carey's Magical Christmas Special, Coronation Street, and Good Morning Britain (Matt Hancock and the vaccine). Ep14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 00:05:00" d="2021-07-16 01:10:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>After dating a few love rats, 24-year-old beautician Gemma wants to find her Prince Charming. Fed up with men, 28-year-old tattoo artist Jennafer seeks the perfect woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 01:10:00" d="2021-07-16 02:10:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox IX</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>What do Britain's favourite opinionated TV viewers think of The Voice, Mutiny, Mastermind, The Replacement, Five Gold Rings, Top Gear and the News? Ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 02:10:00" d="2021-07-16 02:45:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty V (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>91% Rick and Morty [adult swim]
Brand new series - Rickdependence Spray: The fifth series of the Emmy-winning animation. A failed Rick experiment creates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 02:45:00" d="2021-07-16 03:15:00"><n>Birdgirl</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series - We Got the Internet: Animation series that's a spin-off from Harvey Birdman, Attorney at Law. Judy discovers her office is alive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 03:15:00" d="2021-07-16 04:05:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates XII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Serial dater Jack, who's looking for a 'naughty sort', thinks his luck's in when he meets glamorous fire-breather Safina. But will his laddish charm impress her? Ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 04:05:00" d="2021-07-16 05:00:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox XVII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Britain's sharpest armchair critics have been watching Line of Duty, Naked Attraction, I Can See Your Voice, Alan Carr's Epic Gameshow and BBC News (Prince Philip). Ep8)</k>  </p>
</a>
