<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="47" t="2020-04-16 04:31:27"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 05:20:00" d="2020-04-23 05:45:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (14)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Thespian Catalyst: Sheldon lectures at the university but worries that the students don't seem to like him. Raj fantasises about his best friend's girlfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 05:45:00" d="2020-04-23 06:10:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother VII (20)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>82% Trilogy Time: When Barney and Quinn start living together, Barney's reluctance to throw out any of his old possessions makes the gang doubt his faith in the relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 06:10:00" d="2020-04-23 07:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother VII (22)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>82% Good Crazy: Despite feigning indifference, Barney is plagued by jealousy as a result of his girlfriend Quinn's job as a stripper and he tries to persuade</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 07:00:00" d="2020-04-23 07:30:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>R</e>    <k>Pimp My Bride: Jeff finally buys the car that he has always wanted. Russell hopes to get a date with a model by allowing Audrey to use his flat for a photo shoot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 07:30:00" d="2020-04-23 08:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>R</e>    <k>Russell's Secret: Audrey discovers that Russell is a closet Broadway musical fan, and uses this knowledge to blackmail him for tickets. Adam and Jennifer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 08:00:00" d="2020-04-23 08:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother VII (23)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>82% The Magician's Code (Part 1/2): Lily goes into labour while Marshall is in Atlantic City with Barney, so Ted and Robin try to distract her from her painful contractions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 08:30:00" d="2020-04-23 09:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother VII (24)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>82% The Magician's Code (Part 2/2): Barney and Quinn take their first holiday together but get in trouble with airport security. Ted gets in touch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 09:00:00" d="2020-04-23 09:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (27)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>68% Play Ball: Mel recruits Joe to play for her office's softball team when their star player is injured. Ryder asks Lennox to post Holly's story on the school blog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 09:30:00" d="2020-04-23 10:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (28)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>68% A House Divided: Mel and Joe get into an unexpected property dispute with their neighbour. Ryder makes a short film about not texting while driving, starring Lennox</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 10:00:00" d="2020-04-23 10:30:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly V</n><e>R</e>    <k>What Ever Happened to Baby Peggy?: Peggy makes Molly do chores in exchange for sharing tantalising stories from her past that Molly wants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 10:30:00" d="2020-04-23 11:00:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly V</n><e>R</e>    <k>Pie Fight: Mike is delighted when he hits a personal best weight-loss goal, but then he makes the risky decision to indulge in a slice of pie. Ep15)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 11:00:00" d="2020-04-23 11:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (15)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Benefactor Factor: A wealthy benefactor at the university makes Leonard consider how far he's willing to go in the name of science</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 11:30:00" d="2020-04-23 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (16)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Cohabitation Formulation: Howard is torn between taking things to the next level with Bernadette and pleasing his mother. Leonard rekindles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 12:00:00" d="2020-04-23 12:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs I (15)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Muscles Mirsky: When Beverly is caught out reading Erica's diary she promises to trust her daughter instead of snooping in future, but Erica takes advantage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 12:30:00" d="2020-04-23 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs I (16)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Goldbergs Never Say Die!: Adam and his friends go on a treasure hunt inspired by comedy adventure film The Goonies when Pops misplaces some family jewels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 13:00:00" d="2020-04-23 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% Kicks: Officially back at the precinct, Peralta looks for a loophole to get out of his temporarily designated desk duty. Diaz thinks Pimento is cheating on her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 13:30:00" d="2020-04-23 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% HalloVeen: The precinct embarks on its fifth annual Halloween Heist. Everybody has a plan, no one is safe, and relationships and friendships are sorely tested</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 14:00:00" d="2020-04-23 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (16)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Intimacy Acceleration: When the gang hear about an experiment designed to make participants fall in love, Sheldon and Penny put it to the test as a joke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 14:30:00" d="2020-04-23 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (17)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Colonization Application: Amy learns that Sheldon has applied to take part in a one-way mission to colonise Mars. Leonard surprises Penny with a gift</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 15:00:00" d="2020-04-23 15:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (7)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>68% Mixed Doubles: Joe sets Mel up on a blind date with his pal, but in exchange for this favour he asks her to arrange a date for him with her attractive friend Ariel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 15:30:00" d="2020-04-23 16:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (8)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>68% The Donor: Mel's friend Jackie decides she wants a baby and settles on Joe as the man most suitable to be the father of her child. Lennox and Haskell buy a rare book</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 16:00:00" d="2020-04-23 16:30:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly VI (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>65% One Small Step for Mike: Molly buys Mike a fitness tracking device, hoping it will encourage him to be more active and take better care of himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 16:30:00" d="2020-04-23 17:00:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly VI (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>65% Peg O' My Heart Attack: Mike blames Molly when his mother Peggy has a heart attack after a heated argument with her, so a remorseful Molly does her best to make amends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 17:00:00" d="2020-04-23 17:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs II (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Mama Drama: Adam is disappointed to be cast in a minor role in the school musical, so Beverly helps him to land a leading part in a competing stage show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 17:30:00" d="2020-04-23 18:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs II (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Facts of Bleeping Life: Barry and Adam put together a garage rock band, and ask Lainey and Erica to get involved - leading to unexpected consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 18:00:00" d="2020-04-23 18:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (13)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% The Negotiation: Peralta negotiates a hostage situation with a jewel thief whose face is familiar. Santiago and Gina aid Boyle with his new food truck business</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 18:30:00" d="2020-04-23 19:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (14)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% The Box: Captain Holt sacrifices an evening at the opera to help Peralta carry out an interrogation in the hope of getting a confession from a stubborn suspect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 19:00:00" d="2020-04-23 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Separation Oscillation: Sheldon films a special post-break-up episode of Fun with Flags. Bernadette feels guilty about withholding a secret from Penny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 19:30:00" d="2020-04-23 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Bachelor Party Corrosion: The guys' science skills are tested when they get a flat tyre during Leonard's surprise bachelor party weekend in Mexico</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 20:00:00" d="2020-04-23 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks Favourites</n>    <k>Kieron Richardson relives the soap's biggest stunts. Celebration turns to tragedy in the aftermath of the McQueens' wedding party train crash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 20:30:00" d="2020-04-23 21:00:00"><n u="Man with a Plan">Man with a Plan III</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Man with a Plan
Brand new series - The New Old School: When Adam catches Kate sneaking back into the house at night, he is determined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 21:00:00" d="2020-04-23 21:30:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon III</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Brand new series - An Academic Crime and a More Romantic Taco Bell: Dr Sturgis is mad when Sheldon accuses him of plagiarism. Mary finds a girl trophy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 21:30:00" d="2020-04-23 22:00:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon III</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Young Sheldon
Brand new series - A Couple Bruised Ribs and a Cereal Box Ghost Detector: When George Sr accidentally lands the school librarian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 22:00:00" d="2020-04-23 22:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VII</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Brooklyn Nine-Nine
Brand new series - Trying: Jake and Amy work an uncrackable case while Holt adjusts to a new beat. Hitchcock looks for the love of his life. Ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 22:30:00" d="2020-04-23 23:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (8)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% He Said, She Said: Captain Holt suspects a cunning escape after discovering that his lifelong criminal arch-nemesis has died in a prison transport accident</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 23:00:00" d="2020-04-23 23:30:00"><n>Duncanville</n>    <k>Fridgy: Animated comedy that revolves around a 15-year-old boy with a rich fantasy life. The family get a new smart fridge that turns out to be too smart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 23:30:00" d="2020-04-24 00:00:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty IV</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Rick and Morty [adult swim]
Claw and Hoarder: Special Ricktim's Morty: Rick promises Morty he can get a new companion: a flying, fire-breathing dragon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-24 00:00:00" d="2020-04-24 00:15:00"><n u="Mr. Pickles">Mr. Pickles II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% New: Mr. Pickles [adult swim]
Brand new series - ADD: Mr Pickles is in outer space with a dolphin and an evil shrimp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-24 00:15:00" d="2020-04-24 00:30:00"><n u="Robot Chicken">Robot Chicken VII (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% New: Robot Chicken [adult swim]
Brand new series - El Skeletorito: The Cryptkeeper brings three tales of terror that will haunt you forever, while Woody</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-24 00:30:00" d="2020-04-24 01:00:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>92% Rick and Morty [adult swim]
A Rickle in Time: Rick unfreezes time hoping that everything will return to normal, but Morty and Summer's feelings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-24 01:00:00" d="2020-04-24 01:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The 2003 Approximation: Sheldon sulks when Penny and Leonard announce they're moving in together. Howard and Raj form a band to play at the comic book shop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-24 01:30:00" d="2020-04-24 02:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (5)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Perspiration Implementation: The guys take fencing lessons from Barry Kripke. Stuart struggles to attract female customers to the comic book shop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-24 02:00:00" d="2020-04-24 02:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VII</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Brand new series - Trying: Jake and Amy work an uncrackable case while Holt adjusts to a new beat. Hitchcock looks for the love of his life. Ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-24 02:30:00" d="2020-04-24 03:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (8)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% He Said, She Said: Captain Holt suspects a cunning escape after discovering that his lifelong criminal arch-nemesis has died in a prison transport accident</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-24 03:00:00" d="2020-04-24 03:55:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox XIV</n><e>R</e>    <k>The armchair critics watch and react to The X Factor: Celebrity, Celebrity Hunted, The Lesbian Guide to Straight Sex, Own the Sky: Jetpack Dreamers, and the News. Ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-24 03:55:00" d="2020-04-24 04:35:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats">8 Out of 10 Cats XX</n><e>R</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Aisling Bea, Pamela Anderson and Kerry Godliman face Rob Beckett, Ella Eyre and Joe Wilkinson in the comedy panel show. Ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-24 04:35:00" d="2020-04-24 05:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (15)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Benefactor Factor: A wealthy benefactor at the university makes Leonard consider how far he's willing to go in the name of science</k>  </p>
</a>
