<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2020-05-30 04:34:02"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 05:15:00" d="2020-06-06 05:40:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Workplace Proximity: Amy tells Sheldon she's been asked to work on a project at his university, but the guys insist that this will be bad for their relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 05:40:00" d="2020-06-06 06:05:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Romance Resonance: Sheldon is mortified when he stumbles upon an important scientific breakthrough by accident. Howard makes a romantic gesture to Bernadette</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 06:05:00" d="2020-06-06 06:30:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch VI (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Competition: Sabrina is annoyed when Josh says that women can't play tennis as well as men, so she gets magical help. Zelda and Hilda coach Amanda</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 06:30:00" d="2020-06-06 07:00:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch VI (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>I, Busybody: Sabrina tries to give friends, family and colleagues advice but it seems to backfire, so she aims to be less of a busybody</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 07:00:00" d="2020-06-06 07:25:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>The Home Stretch: Audrey has private Pilates sessions at home and Jeff is thrilled when the workouts increase her sex drive, but less pleased when he sees her instructor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 07:25:00" d="2020-06-06 07:50:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Uh-Oh It's Magic: Russell takes his date Jessica to a magic show, only to see the magician make her disappear and not return. Illusionist Criss Angel guest stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 07:50:00" d="2020-06-06 09:25:00"><n>The House of Magic</n><e>R</e>    <k>Family animated adventure. A cruelly abandoned ginger kitten is rescued by a kindly elderly magician who lives in a creepy mansion. But the kitten's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 09:25:00" d="2020-06-06 10:25:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n>    <k>In the second half of a two-part Nightmare at The Burger Kitchen in Los Angeles, can Gordon bring together the fragmented Saffron family and save their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 10:25:00" d="2020-06-06 11:25:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>R</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay travels to Orange County in southern California to try to save Italian restaurant Luigi's from a disaster caused by family arguments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 11:25:00" d="2020-06-06 12:25:00"><n>Don't Tell the Bride</n><e>R</e>    <k>Yorkshire groom Lee and his brother take off on a week-long tour of Europe, telling bride-to-be Becky that if she wants to marry Lee, she has to find him first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 12:25:00" d="2020-06-06 13:30:00"><n>Don't Tell the Bride</n><e>R</e>    <k>Nathan loves music and Stoke-on-Trent, so when bride-to-be Beccie gives him free rein to plan their wedding, he honours them with nuptials based on Northern Soul</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 13:30:00" d="2020-06-06 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% Pilot: US comedy about a group of New York City police detectives. A talented but carefree detective is taken aback when a strict new captain takes over at his precinct</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 14:00:00" d="2020-06-06 14:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Tagger: When Peralta turns up late for morning roll call, Captain Holt responds by assigning him to a minor graffiti case and then closely monitoring his every move</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 14:30:00" d="2020-06-06 15:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Slump: Peralta has a growing number of crime cases that he can't seem to solve. Holt asks Santiago to take charge of a community outreach programme for at-risk youth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 15:00:00" d="2020-06-06 15:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% M.E. Time: Peralta meets an attractive medical examiner, but he annoys his colleagues when his attempts to get together with her cause a hold-up with an autopsy report</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 15:30:00" d="2020-06-06 16:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Vulture: Peralta is irked when a detective from Major Crimes takes over a murder case that he is close to solving. Can he prevent the officer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 16:00:00" d="2020-06-06 16:30:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>75% A Financial Secret and Fish Sauce: George Sr asks Sheldon to keep a secret from Mary but the stress of not being honest drives Sheldon to hide at Tam's house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 16:30:00" d="2020-06-06 17:00:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>75% A Research Study and Czechoslovakian Wedding Pastries: Dr Sturgis recommends Sheldon and Missy for a university research study on twins, but Mary is unhappy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 17:00:00" d="2020-06-06 17:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Barbarian Sublimation: Penny becomes addicted to an online game based on the world of Conan the Barbarian and begins to pester Sheldon for advice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 17:30:00" d="2020-06-06 18:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Griffin Equivalency: Full of confidence after being named one of People Magazine's '30 to Watch Under 30', Raj hits on Penny and becomes impossibly arrogant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 18:00:00" d="2020-06-06 18:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Euclid Alternative: When Leonard can't drive Sheldon to and from work, the friends stage an intervention to overcome Sheldon's fear of getting behind the wheel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 18:30:00" d="2020-06-06 19:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Cooper-Nowitzki Theorem: Sheldon's friends are mystified when a younger student is attracted to him, but her intense devotion soon becomes too much to bear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 19:00:00" d="2020-06-06 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (7)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Panty Pinata Polarization: Sheldon bans Penny from the flat for numerous minor infractions, so she retaliates. Howard and Raj search for the America's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 19:30:00" d="2020-06-06 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (8)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Lizard-Spock Expansion: A girl for whom Howard harbours romantic feelings falls for Leonard instead, despite Howard's efforts to woo her, leaving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 20:00:00" d="2020-06-06 20:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Matrimonial Momentum: Penny struggles with Leonard's confession that he kissed another woman. Sheldon doesn't know how to act when Amy breaks up with him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 20:30:00" d="2020-06-06 21:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Separation Oscillation: Sheldon films a special post-break-up episode of Fun with Flags. Bernadette feels guilty about withholding a secret from Penny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 21:00:00" d="2020-06-06 21:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Bachelor Party Corrosion: The guys' science skills are tested when they get a flat tyre during Leonard's surprise bachelor party weekend in Mexico</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 21:30:00" d="2020-06-06 22:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (4)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The 2003 Approximation: Sheldon sulks when Penny and Leonard announce that they're moving in together. Howard and Raj form a band to play at the comic book shop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-06 22:00:00" d="2020-06-07 00:35:00"><n>Mission: Impossible - Ghost...</n><e>R</e>    <k>. rotocol: (2011) Part four of the action-thriller franchise with Tom Cruise. The Impossible Missions Force fight to clear their name and save humankind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 00:35:00" d="2020-06-07 01:35:00"><n>Celebrity Gogglebox USA</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Brand new series: Gogglebox heads across the pond and steps into the homes of a selection of celebrity faces, including Sharon and Kelly Osbourne</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 01:35:00" d="2020-06-07 02:40:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox VIII</n><e>R</e>    <k>What do Britain's favourite opinionated TV viewers think of Victoria, The Great British Bake Off, Hunted, Penelope Keith's Hidden Villages, Body Fixers and the News? Ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 02:40:00" d="2020-06-07 03:40:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates V</n><e>R</e>    <k>Matthew has been to Disneyland 43 times, but hasn't yet met his Prince Charming. Can fellow Disney fanatic Paul give him his happy ever after? Ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 03:40:00" d="2020-06-07 04:35:00"><n>First Dates</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>First Dates: Be My Valentine
In this special Valentine's episode, Mayfair-based Miki is looking for a man to treat her like a princess</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 04:35:00" d="2020-06-07 05:30:00"><n>Don't Tell the Bride</n><e>R</e>    <k>Yorkshire groom Lee and his brother take off on a week-long tour of Europe, telling bride-to-be Becky that if she wants to marry Lee, she has to find him first</k>  </p>
</a>
