<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="42" t="2020-05-15 04:49:47"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 05:10:00" d="2020-05-22 05:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Habitation Configuration: Amy is upset when Sheldon fails to defend her in an argument with Wil Wheaton during the filming of a new episode of Fun with Flags</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 05:35:00" d="2020-05-22 06:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The 43 Peculiarity: The guys notice that Sheldon disappears for 20 minutes after lunch every day. Filled with curiosity, they attempt to work out what he's been doing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 06:00:00" d="2020-05-22 06:25:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch V (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Beach Blanket Bizarro: Sabrina and friends plan to spend Spring Break in Florida, so Sabrina's aunts cast a spell transforming the resort into an innocent 1960s beach movie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 06:25:00" d="2020-05-22 07:00:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch V (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Witchright Hall: Sabrina's cousin Amanda is sent to live for a year in the mortal realm, where Hilda and Zelda make her apply to study at a school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 07:00:00" d="2020-05-22 07:30:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Rug-of-War: Jeff is angry when Audrey gives Adam and Jen their old rug, so he tries to discourage them from accepting it by telling them about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 07:30:00" d="2020-05-22 08:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Baked: Audrey hopes to start her own cookie business after leaving her previous employment, while Timmy does his best to fit in with the guys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 08:00:00" d="2020-05-22 08:30:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch V (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Sabrina, the Activist: Sabrina gets involved in a protest to save a historical building. Josh starts to realise how much he has in common with Sabrina</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 08:30:00" d="2020-05-22 09:00:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch V (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Do You See What I See?: Miles sees Sabrina's flying car and, thinking that he has sighted a UFO, makes a presentation to the class about it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 09:00:00" d="2020-05-22 09:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% To Tell the Truth: Mel and Joe's friendship with married couple Nate and Gillian is put in jeopardy when Mel reveals a secret that Nate has told Joe in confidence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 09:30:00" d="2020-05-22 10:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% My Roof, My Rules: When Mel and Joe discover that Lennox is dating Emerson, her teaching assistant, Joe asks Mel to put her foot down and forbid the relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 10:00:00" d="2020-05-22 10:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% All's Flair in Love and War: Tucker's girlfriend Vanessa gets an assistant manager position at Ben's bar and makes Ben's life miserable with ridiculous hours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 10:30:00" d="2020-05-22 11:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Test Anxiety: Ben's feelings are hurt when Riley wants to talk to Danny and not him about her bar exam woes, but she finally confides in him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 11:00:00" d="2020-05-22 11:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Parking Spot Escalation: When non-driver Sheldon finds out that his unused parking space at the university has been reallocated to Howard, he feels undermined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 11:30:00" d="2020-05-22 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Fish Guts Displacement: Sheldon begrudgingly takes care of Amy when she is sick. Bernadette arranges for Howard to go on a fishing trip with her macho father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 12:00:00" d="2020-05-22 12:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Christmas Story: Beverly begins to worry that the family's holiday traditions have grown stale, so she launches a new celebration called 'Super Hanukkah'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 12:30:00" d="2020-05-22 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Tasty Boys: Adam and Barry team up to form a rap super-group just like the Beastie Boys. Beverly puts pressure on Murray to let her redesign the kitchen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 13:00:00" d="2020-05-22 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Halloween: On a very busy Halloween night, Santiago - who detests the holiday - is forced to put on a fancy dress costume and go undercover on a street patrol with Boyle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 13:30:00" d="2020-05-22 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% 48 Hours: Peralta jumps the gun and makes an arrest without enough evidence, leaving himself only 48 hours to collect the proof he needs before the suspect is released</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 14:00:00" d="2020-05-22 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Property Division Collision: Sheldon, Amy, Leonard and Penny attempt to divide up all their possessions into two separate households but tension ensues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 14:30:00" d="2020-05-22 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Birthday Synchronicity: Sheldon and Amy try to celebrate her birthday with an intimate night at home but are interrupted as Bernadette goes into labour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 15:00:00" d="2020-05-22 15:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Uninvited: Mel is not thrilled when Joe's mother Gloria drops by, but it's Joe who hits the roof when his estranged brother Tony turns up expecting to be able to stay</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 15:30:00" d="2020-05-22 16:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey IV (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% You're the One That I Want: As Mel and Joe's wedding weekend dawns, Joe is injured at his bachelor party, Mel's father is missing, and a secret is accidentally revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 16:00:00" d="2020-05-22 16:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Lights! Camera! No Action!: Tucker arranges for Danny to be interviewed on a television chat show. Ben and Riley have a misunderstanding over Angela</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 16:30:00" d="2020-05-22 17:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Bonnie's Unreal Estate: Riley's company is hired to represent a preacher whose life is tainted by a scandal. Bonnie's new career in real estate hits problems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 17:00:00" d="2020-05-22 17:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Party: Captain Holt invites the entire squad over to his house to celebrate his birthday, but Peralta and Santiago make a bad impression on Holt's husband Kevin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 17:30:00" d="2020-05-22 18:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Full Boyle: Boyle's new romance increases his self-confidence, Diaz and Santiago can't take a costumed crime-fighter seriously, and Holt faces a leadership challenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 18:00:00" d="2020-05-22 18:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Dungeons &amp; Dragons, Anyone?: Adam picks a team of popular athletes over his friends in gym class. Erica decides she wants to leave home to attend college</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 18:30:00" d="2020-05-22 19:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Rush: When Barry insists that Beverly always favours Adam, she tries to make amends. Murray is not happy about Erica's new boyfriend, a fanatical music fan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 19:00:00" d="2020-05-22 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Recollection Dissipation: Sheldon collaborates on two projects - one with Leonard and Howard, plus another with Amy - pushing himself to the limit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 19:30:00" d="2020-05-22 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Separation Agitation: Howard and Bernadette are upset when they leave Halley at the nursery. Bert the geologist introduces his girlfriend to the gang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 20:00:00" d="2020-05-22 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks Favourites</n><e>F</e>    <k>Hollyoaks star Jamie Lomas relives a classic episode of the soap. When Clare kidnaps a terrified Katy, Warren and Max come to the rescue: can they save her?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 20:30:00" d="2020-05-22 21:00:00"><n>Celebrity Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Geordie Shore's Charlotte Crosby hosts the final night with an apres-ski-themed evening. There's fondue and a DIY dessert, but who will win the charity prize? (Ep5/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 21:00:00" d="2020-05-22 21:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Habitation Configuration: Amy is upset when Sheldon fails to defend her in an argument with Wil Wheaton during the filming of a new episode of Fun with Flags</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 21:30:00" d="2020-05-22 22:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The 43 Peculiarity: The guys notice that Sheldon disappears for 20 minutes after lunch every day. Filled with curiosity, they attempt to work out what he's been doing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 22:00:00" d="2020-05-22 23:55:00"><n u="Taken">Taken 2</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Violent thriller sequel starring Liam Neeson, Maggie Grace and Famke Janssen. The Mills family must again fight for survival when an old enemy seeks revenge in Istanbul</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-22 23:55:00" d="2020-05-23 00:25:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Middle Earth Paradigm: Penny decides to host a big Halloween party, putting Leonard, Sheldon, Howard and Raj through a demanding new test of their social skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 00:25:00" d="2020-05-23 00:55:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Dumpling Paradox: When Howard seduces Penny's friend and spends the night with her in Penny's flat, Penny asks if she can sleep on Leonard and Sheldon's sofa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 00:55:00" d="2020-05-23 02:00:00"><n u="Made in Chelsea">Made in Chelsea IV (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Worried that Spencer will revert to his philandering ways under Jamie's influence, Louise turns to Millie and Rosie for advice. Sophia faces a dilemma about Francis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 02:00:00" d="2020-05-23 03:05:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox VII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>What do Britain's favourite opinionated viewers think of The Secret Life of the Zoo, Dogs Might Fly, Do We Really Need the Moon?, Happy Valley, The Getaway</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 03:05:00" d="2020-05-23 04:00:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats">8 Out of 10 Cats XXI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Rob Beckett, Katherine Ryan, Tom Allen, Maya Jama, Richard Osman and Catherine Bohart compete in the comedy panel show. Ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 04:00:00" d="2020-05-23 04:55:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Bisexual Jo embarks on her first ever date with a woman - 4ft 7in personal trainer Naomi. And Dean, still single at 29, meets flame-haired estate agent Kate. Ep11)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-23 04:55:00" d="2020-05-23 07:55:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Parking Spot Escalation: When non-driver Sheldon finds out that his unused parking space at the university has been reallocated to Howard, he feels undermined</k>  </p>
</a>
