<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2020-05-10 04:31:13"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 05:00:00" d="2020-05-17 05:50:00"><n>Don't Tell the Bride</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Former boxing champ Jordan plans a fight-night wedding in front of thousands, while his bride-to-be Danielle has dreams of a girly and intimate day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 05:50:00" d="2020-05-17 07:00:00"><n>Don't Tell the Bride</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Thrill junkie Lee plans an extreme wedding for his unadventurous bride Aimee. Will their wedding have the wow factor, or will it crash to the ground?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 07:00:00" d="2020-05-17 07:55:00"><n>Hollyoaks: Omnibus</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>49% Hollyoaks Omnibus
Tony gets some devastating health news. Scott and Mitchell have big news for Martine. James plans to win back John Paul. Charlie needs cash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 07:55:00" d="2020-05-17 08:10:00"><n u="Rude Tube Shorts">Rude(ish) Tube Shorts</n><e>RF</e>    <k>A short, cheeky clip from Rude Tube's naughty little sister that features a variety of cats doing strange things, some soldiers stuck in the</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 08:10:00" d="2020-05-17 09:05:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>T</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay is in LA to visit La Frite, a family-owned French restaurant that's being run into the ground by Andre, his son and his daughter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 09:05:00" d="2020-05-17 10:05:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>T</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay revisits three restaurants - Lido, Anna Vincenzo's and Le Bistro - to check in with the owners he previously helped. Has his advice been put to good use?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 10:05:00" d="2020-05-17 11:05:00"><n>Don't Tell the Bride</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Laid-back Daniel fancies a Caribbean street parade for his nuptials, while Sabrina dreams of a more traditional event. Will their big day be carnage or carnival?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 11:05:00" d="2020-05-17 12:05:00"><n>Don't Tell the Bride</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Beauty queen and bride-to-be Yasmin has her heart set on a fairytale wedding. Can powerlifter Yiannis deliver her dream nuptials?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 12:05:00" d="2020-05-17 12:40:00"><n>Celebrity Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Love Islander Jack Fincham hosts first, with a menu of bistro favourites, but he's chosen three dishes he's never cooked before! (Ep1/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 12:40:00" d="2020-05-17 13:10:00"><n>Celebrity Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Second to host is former boy bander Abz Love from Five, who lives with his mum. Abz plans to win with his Turkish-inspired grub and even a dance routine or two. (Ep2/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 13:10:00" d="2020-05-17 13:40:00"><n>Celebrity Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Comedy duo Donna and Verona channel their inner child and serve their 'Jamshire' menu. But tensions between Abz Love and Mark Francis explode during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 13:40:00" d="2020-05-17 14:15:00"><n>Celebrity Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Dani Harmer's hosts an inner-diva-themed evening. But she's never chopped an onion before, let alone hosted a dinner party. (Ep4/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 14:15:00" d="2020-05-17 14:45:00"><n>Celebrity Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Made in Chelsea's Mark Francis hosts the final night with a menu inspired by his Italian heritage with unpronounceable courses and the finest high-end ingredients. (Ep5/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 14:45:00" d="2020-05-17 15:15:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>12 Tapes for a Penny: Adam joins a mail-order music club hoping to assemble a huge cassette tape collection. Barry realises Lainey's father doesn't like him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 15:15:00" d="2020-05-17 15:45:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Magic Is Real: Adam tries to use his new magic act to attract girls at school but he's thwarted when Beverly insists on taking to the stage as his assistant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 15:45:00" d="2020-05-17 16:15:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VII</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series - Geoff the Pleaser: Geoff struggles to balance demands from the Jenkintown Posse and Erica. Adam faces a crisis of confidence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 16:15:00" d="2020-05-17 16:45:00"><n u="Schooled">Schooled II</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series - Titanic Love: Principal Glascott uses the season's bad football team to teach coach Mellor how to be both a good winner and a good loser. Ep13)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 16:45:00" d="2020-05-17 17:15:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon III</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series - A Secret Letter and a Lowly Disc of Processed Meat: Sheldon finds out that Mary has a secret about his future. And Meemaw gets angry with Dale. Ep21)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 17:15:00" d="2020-05-17 17:40:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Emotion Detection Automation: Sheldon tests a newly invented device after hearing it could help him to read people's emotions. Raj seeks dating advice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 17:40:00" d="2020-05-17 18:10:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Locomotion Reverberation: Leonard and Howard distract Sheldon with a trip to a historic railway when he slows their progress on the guidance system</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 18:10:00" d="2020-05-17 18:40:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Allowance Evaporation: Amy is furious when she learns that Sheldon has chosen to share intimate details of their relationship with his colleagues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 18:40:00" d="2020-05-17 19:10:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Comic-Con Conundrum: Cut off from his father's fortune, Raj appoints Sheldon to organise his finances. Penny considers joining the guys at Comic-Con</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 19:10:00" d="2020-05-17 19:40:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Escape Hatch Identification: Leonard and Penny offer Sheldon's old room to Raj when he's forced to move out of his flat, leading to unexpected conflict</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 19:40:00" d="2020-05-17 20:10:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Collaboration Fluctuation: Leonard, Penny and Raj settle into their new living arrangement, and Sheldon expresses an interest in Amy's professional life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 20:10:00" d="2020-05-17 22:00:00"><n u="Kung Fu Panda">Kung Fu Panda 2</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Animated adventure sequel with the voices of Jack Black and Gary Oldman. Po the panda and his five friends must use all their martial arts skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 22:00:00" d="2020-05-17 23:00:00"><n>Batwoman</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>42% New: Batwoman
Brand new series - A Mad Tea-Party: Kate and Alice continue their sister/nemesis dance, while Alice and Mouse construct their most evil plan yet. (Ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-17 23:00:00" d="2020-05-18 00:00:00"><n u="Misfits">Misfits I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Alisha is having fun using and abusing her power, but she can't get the man she really wants. Meanwhile, builders are digging a hole exactly where the bodies are buried</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-18 00:00:00" d="2020-05-18 01:05:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Cathy wants to settle down and have kids. Adam, who's 24, hates online dating. Will baring all help them find their perfect partner?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-18 01:05:00" d="2020-05-18 02:10:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Gym addict Sophie from Surrey is looking for a change from the usual body-builder types who lack sparkle, while Dom seeks his perfect man to waltz him down the aisle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-18 02:10:00" d="2020-05-18 03:10:00"><n u="Supernatural">Supernatural XIV</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Supernatural
Brand new - Byzantium: When Sam and Dean join forces with an unexpected ally, the outcome will alter the course of two lives. Ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-18 03:10:00" d="2020-05-18 03:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Recollection Dissipation: Sheldon collaborates on two projects - one with Leonard and Howard, plus another with Amy - pushing himself to the limit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-18 03:35:00" d="2020-05-18 04:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Separation Agitation: Howard and Bernadette are upset when they leave Halley at the nursery. Bert the geologist introduces his girlfriend to the gang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-18 04:00:00" d="2020-05-18 04:45:00"><n>Batwoman</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>42% Brand new series - A Mad Tea-Party: Kate and Alice continue their sister/nemesis dance, while Alice and Mouse construct their most evil plan yet. (Ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-18 04:45:00" d="2020-05-18 07:45:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch V (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>House of Pi's: Sabrina goes undercover at Morgan's sorority house to write a provocative article and land a position on the student newspaper</k>  </p>
</a>
