<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="43" t="2020-04-15 04:31:06"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 05:05:00" d="2020-04-22 05:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (11)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Justice League Recombination: The guys slowly warm to Zack and find an enjoyable way to bond with him when they enter a New Year's Eve fancy dress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 05:30:00" d="2020-04-22 05:55:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (12)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Bus Pants Utilization: Leonard's idea for a smartphone application derails his friendship with Sheldon as they fight for control of the project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 05:55:00" d="2020-04-22 07:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother VII (19)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>82% The Broath: Barney tries to persuade his friends to meet Quinn and get to know her properly. However, Ted is convinced that Quinn is only after Barney's money</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 07:00:00" d="2020-04-22 07:30:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>R</e>    <k>Russell's Father's Son: Adam is worried that Russell will be upset when he discovers that Russell's father asked Adam to pose as his son in a promotional video</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 07:30:00" d="2020-04-22 08:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>R</e>    <k>Buyer's Remorse: Adam and Jennifer consider buying their flat. Jeff and Audrey give them some housing advice, which ends up doing more harm than good</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 08:00:00" d="2020-04-22 08:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother VII (20)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>82% Trilogy Time: When Barney and Quinn start living together, Barney's reluctance to throw out any of his old possessions makes the gang doubt his faith in the relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 08:30:00" d="2020-04-22 09:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother VII (22)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>82% Good Crazy: Despite feigning indifference, Barney is plagued by jealousy as a result of his girlfriend Quinn's job as a stripper and he tries to persuade</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 09:00:00" d="2020-04-22 09:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (25)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>68% The Other Longo: When Joe's photographer brother Tony visits, Mel is impressed by his work and asks him to take some shots of her. Lennox avoids Ryder when he has a cold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 09:30:00" d="2020-04-22 10:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (26)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>68% Teacher/Teacher: Joe gets Ryder into trouble with his teacher when he helps him to complete a homework assignment. Mel sneaks Lennox into an 18-years-and-over concert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 10:00:00" d="2020-04-22 10:30:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly V</n><e>R</e>    <k>The World According to Peggy: Molly plans to throw a big party for Peggy after finding out that she has suddenly decided to retire from her job at the cafeteria. Ep12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 10:30:00" d="2020-04-22 11:00:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly V</n><e>R</e>    <k>Buy the Book: Molly's book is available for purchase, but she worries nobody will buy it and obsessively visits the publisher's website to see if it's selling. Ep13)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 11:00:00" d="2020-04-22 11:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (13)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Love Car Displacement: Tensions are high when Bernadette runs into her hulk of an ex-boyfriend at a science conference, leaving Howard feeling threatened</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 11:30:00" d="2020-04-22 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (14)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Thespian Catalyst: Sheldon lectures at the university but worries that the students don't seem to like him. Raj fantasises about his best friend's girlfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 12:00:00" d="2020-04-22 12:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs I (13)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Other Smother: While attempting to micro-manage Barry and Erica's search for college places, Beverly is pitted against a rival meddling mother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 12:30:00" d="2020-04-22 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs I (14)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>You Opened the Door: Adam reluctantly agrees to take dancing lessons from Beverly because he is planning to attend the school dance with Dana</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 13:00:00" d="2020-04-22 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% The Big House Part 1: Adjusting to life behind bars, Peralta bonds with a cellmate and is forced to join a prison gang, while Diaz puts her visitors to the test</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 13:30:00" d="2020-04-22 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% The Big House Part 2: Peralta is trapped by divided loyalties after the warden persuades him to investigate prison gang leader Romero's drug smuggling operation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 14:00:00" d="2020-04-22 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (14)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Troll Manifestation: Leonard and Sheldon co-publish a physics paper but are forced to defend themselves against negative comments from an online critic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 14:30:00" d="2020-04-22 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (15)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Comic Book Store Regeneration: The gang prepare for the reopening of Stuart's comic book shop. Penny teaches Sheldon to 'let it go' when he is irritated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 15:00:00" d="2020-04-22 15:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>68% The Knockout: When Mel punches a man who picks on Ryder at the cinema, a clip of the event is soon posted online and she becomes known as 'Battling Burke'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 15:30:00" d="2020-04-22 16:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>68% Breaking Up Is Hard to Do: Mel wants to break up with her boyfriend Donald, but feels guilty because he's just been fired from his job. Holly confides a secret to Lennox</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 16:00:00" d="2020-04-22 16:30:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly V</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Bitter Man and the Sea: Mike and Molly are forced to revoke Carl's invitation to their anniversary cruise after his nasty break-up with Victoria. Ep22)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 16:30:00" d="2020-04-22 17:00:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly VI (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>65% Cops on the Rocks: Mike and Carl go to a counselling session to reconcile their professional partnership. Molly does a promotional radio interview alone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 17:00:00" d="2020-04-22 17:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs I (23)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Livin' on a Prayer: Murray is feted by his old high school for his sporting prowess. Barry throws a party to impress his friends while his parents are away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 17:30:00" d="2020-04-22 18:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Love Is a Mix Tape: Adam tries to express his feelings for Dana by making her a mix tape, but disaster strikes when the tape falls into Beverly's hands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 18:00:00" d="2020-04-22 18:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (11)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% The Favor: Mobster Seamus Murphy returns to redeem the favour Holt owes him for helping to get Diaz and Peralta out of jail, so the team search for a loophole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 18:30:00" d="2020-04-22 19:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (12)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% Safe House: After mobster Seamus Murphy threatens Kevin, Captain Holt devises an elaborate plan to hide his husband in a safe house, with Peralta as his guard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 19:00:00" d="2020-04-22 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (24)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Commitment Determination: Sheldon pressures Leonard and Penny to choose a date for their wedding while dealing with changes in his own relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 19:30:00" d="2020-04-22 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Matrimonial Momentum: Penny struggles with Leonard's confession that he kissed another woman. Sheldon doesn't know how to act when Amy breaks up with him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 20:00:00" d="2020-04-22 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks Favourites</n><e>F</e>    <k>Kieron Richardson relives the soap's biggest stunts. Maxine and Sienna make their escape from Patrick - only to end up on a collision course of catastrophe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 20:30:00" d="2020-04-22 21:00:00"><n u="Man with a Plan">Man with a Plan III</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Man with a Plan
Brand new series - Adam's Wall Hole Bowl: Adam and the guys start hanging out at Lowell's new bachelor pad, to get away from their home lives. Ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 21:00:00" d="2020-04-22 21:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VII</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: The Goldbergs
Brand new series - It's a Wonderful Life: When Beverly signs everyone up for a holiday family photo, Geoff is excited</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 21:30:00" d="2020-04-22 22:00:00"><n u="Schooled">Schooled II</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Schooled
Brand new series - Beanie Babies: CB hopes that getting Lainey a Beanie Baby for Christmas will show his true feelings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 22:00:00" d="2020-04-22 23:00:00"><n>Celebrity Gogglebox</n><e>R</e>    <k>From First Dates to Serengeti, what do Jessie J, Jamal Edwards, Chris Eubank Sr, Chris Eubank Jr, Martin and Roman Kemp, Nick Grimshaw and other famous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-22 23:00:00" d="2020-04-23 00:00:00"><n>Zoey's Extraordinary Playlist</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Zoey's Extraordinary Playlist
Brand new series - Zoey's Extraordinary Glitch: After receiving heart-breaking news, Zoey suffers a mysterious 'glitch' in her powers. (Ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 00:00:00" d="2020-04-23 00:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Separation Oscillation: Sheldon films a special post-break-up episode of Fun with Flags. Bernadette feels guilty about withholding a secret from Penny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 00:30:00" d="2020-04-23 01:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Bachelor Party Corrosion: The guys' science skills are tested when they get a flat tyre during Leonard's surprise bachelor party weekend in Mexico</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 01:00:00" d="2020-04-23 02:05:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox XIV</n><e>R</e>    <k>What do Britain's favourite armchair critics make of Celebrity First Dates Hotel for SU2C, The Circle Vote Night, Strictly Come Dancing, This Morning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 02:05:00" d="2020-04-23 02:35:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VII</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Brand new series - It's a Wonderful Life: When Beverly signs everyone up for a holiday family photo, Geoff is excited to join in - despite Erica's reservations. Ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 02:35:00" d="2020-04-23 03:05:00"><n u="Schooled">Schooled II</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Brand new series - Beanie Babies: CB hopes getting Lainey a Beanie Baby for Christmas will show his true feelings for her, but it doesn't go as planned. Ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 03:05:00" d="2020-04-23 04:00:00"><n>First Dates</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>DJ Terry Turbo is back and he says he's changed his Jack-the-lad ways. Are Ben and Gary's dates more interested in each other? Model Rochelle's looking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 04:00:00" d="2020-04-23 04:55:00"><n>Zoey's Extraordinary Playlist</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Brand new series - Zoey's Extraordinary Glitch: After receiving heart-breaking news, Zoey suffers a mysterious 'glitch' in her powers. (Ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-23 04:55:00" d="2020-04-23 05:20:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (13)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Love Car Displacement: Tensions are high when Bernadette runs into her hulk of an ex-boyfriend at a science conference, leaving Howard feeling threatened</k>  </p>
</a>
