<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="37" t="2021-07-13 04:58:33"><p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 05:15:00" d="2021-07-20 05:40:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother I (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% The Wedding: Ted is relieved when Robin agrees to go with him to his friends' wedding and thinks his luck is changing. The bridal couple, however, don't fare so well</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 05:40:00" d="2021-07-20 07:00:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay visits Bazzini restaurant in New Jersey. Owner Paul is an award-winning chef, but he didn't realise how difficult running a restaurant would be</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 07:00:00" d="2021-07-20 07:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>A stag do leads to a confession from the husband-to-be. Elsewhere, a startling secret is uncovered, there's a heartfelt conversation in the Maalik</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 07:30:00" d="2021-07-20 08:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Wedding bells are chiming in Hollyoaks, but the bride-to-be has a devilish plan. Elsewhere, Warren is confronted, and Yazz and Tom struggle to get people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 08:00:00" d="2021-07-20 09:00:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay visits Mojito, a Cuban cafe in Brooklyn, New York, where owners Marcelo and Kata fight over everything, driving away customers with their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 09:00:00" d="2021-07-20 09:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother I (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Drumroll, Please: Ted meets a woman at a wedding. They agree that romance at weddings is false and decide not to swap numbers or surnames. Will Ted stick to their deal?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 09:30:00" d="2021-07-20 10:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother I (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Game Night: Marshall invents a new game - Marshgammon - after winning previous game nights. Unfortunately no one but Marshall understands how to play it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 10:00:00" d="2021-07-20 10:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Wherefore Art Thou Lennox: When Lennox starts an internship at Mel's office, she hits it off with a fellow intern who happens to work for Mel's biggest political rival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 10:30:00" d="2021-07-20 11:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% From Russia with Love: When Joe's Russian girlfriend Elena comes to visit, she soon starts to monopolise him, leaving no time for his domestic duties, which irritates Mel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 11:00:00" d="2021-07-20 11:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Flirty Dancing: Riley gives Ben and Danny the time capsules they made when they were at school. Tucker and Riley turn up uninvited at Bonnie's dance class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 11:30:00" d="2021-07-20 12:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Baby Steps: When a disappointed Ben misses out on seeing Emma's first steps, Bonnie, Tucker, Danny and Riley attempt to recreate the moment for him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 12:00:00" d="2021-07-20 12:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Have a Summer: Adam worries about being 'hazed' by the older students when he goes to high school, but he soon earns their respect by body-slamming Barry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 12:30:00" d="2021-07-20 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Breakfast Club: Adam works on a new persona that he hopes will make him seem cool on his first day at high school, while Beverly gets her teaching certificate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 13:00:00" d="2021-07-20 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Wednesday Incident: When Peralta notices that Captain Holt is in a bad mood, he teams up with Holt's husband Kevin to find out what has gone wrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 13:30:00" d="2021-07-20 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Boyle-Linetti Wedding: As the wedding day of Gina's mother and Boyle's father dawns, each member of the squad is given a task to complete for the nuptials</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 14:00:00" d="2021-07-20 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Paintball Scattering: Jealousy, trust issues and tension among the couples in the gang cause mayhem when Penny and Leonard organise a paintball game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 14:30:00" d="2021-07-20 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Propagation Proposition: Penny's ex-boyfriend Zack and his wife want a baby, but when they encounter fertility problems they ask Leonard for his help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 15:00:00" d="2021-07-20 15:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Monopolar Expedition: Leonard and Penny reconsider their feelings for each other, but then Leonard is offered the opportunity to spend the summer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 15:30:00" d="2021-07-20 16:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory III (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Electric Can Opener Fluctuation: Leonard's attempts to woo Penny are constantly thwarted. Sheldon heads to Texas after learning his friends meddled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 16:00:00" d="2021-07-20 16:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Han Ukkah Solo: When Beverly talks Erica into writing a Hanukkah song for the school holiday concert, she inspires Barry to prove his own musical prowess</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 16:30:00" d="2021-07-20 17:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>O Captain! My Captain!: Beverly hopes to inspire the students when she takes over as substitute teacher in Barry's chemistry class. Adam embarrasses Emmy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 17:00:00" d="2021-07-20 17:30:00"><n u="Black-ish">Black-ish VI</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: black-ish
Brand new series - A Game of Chicken: Dre and Bow disagree on where to send Devante to preschool. Junior helps Jack and Diane</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 17:30:00" d="2021-07-20 18:00:00"><n u="Black-ish">Black-ish VI</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: black-ish
Brand new series - Earl, Interrupted: Dre intervenes when Pops starts gambling and partying to mask his heartbreak. Bow hands school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 18:00:00" d="2021-07-20 18:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine III (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Boyle's Hunch: Peralta thinks Boyle might have found his soul-mate in art gallery owner Genevieve. Diaz deals with a case of theft in the precinct building</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 18:30:00" d="2021-07-20 19:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine III (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Oolong Slayer: Peralta enlists Captain Holt's help while investigating a serial killer. Diaz and Santiago are forced to deal with The Vulture's demands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 19:00:00" d="2021-07-20 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Plagiarism Schism: Barry Kripke finds proof that Dr Pemberton plagiarised his thesis in college. Should Sheldon and Amy turn their rival in or not?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 19:30:00" d="2021-07-20 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Maternal Conclusion: Leonard is surprised when his mother Beverly comes to visit and is kind to him, until he finds out the real reason she's there</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 20:00:00" d="2021-07-20 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Sienna doesn't know what to believe after a shocking accusation about Brody comes to light. Trish has a wicked plan for one of her dance students</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 20:30:00" d="2021-07-20 21:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Blackpool and Preston. Lady of leisure Jill, who's dined at The Ivy three times, plans to impress with her Italian menu and language skills. And Bernard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 21:00:00" d="2021-07-20 22:00:00"><n u="Below Deck Mediterranean">Below Deck Mediterranean IV</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Below Deck Mediterranean
Brand new series - All Hail the Queen: The Sirocco braces for its most exclusive charter guest yet: The Queen of Versailles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-20 22:00:00" d="2021-07-21 00:10:00"><n u="Ted">Ted 2</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Outrageous adult comedy sequel. Ted, the toy bear who came to life, faces a challenge to his marriage. With Mark Wahlberg. Very strong language</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-21 00:10:00" d="2021-07-21 01:15:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction II</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Psychology student Alesia is tired of dating 'boys' and hopes to meet a real man in the buff. And after 200 dates all over the world, Louise is ready</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-21 01:15:00" d="2021-07-21 02:20:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox IX</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>What do Britain's favourite viewers think of Kitchen 999: Emergency Chefs, The Voice final, Alone with the In-Laws, Line of Duty, Life Story</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-21 02:20:00" d="2021-07-21 03:25:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates XI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Flirtation turns to faux pas as the drinks flow on Kristina's date with Nicola. And will cheeky charmer Billy's fear of butter harm his chances of wooing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-21 03:25:00" d="2021-07-21 03:50:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty I (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>91% Rick and Morty [adult swim]
Something Ricked This Way Comes: Rick annoys Summer when he battles with the sinister owner of the second-hand shop where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-21 03:50:00" d="2021-07-21 04:15:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty I (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>91% Rick and Morty [adult swim]
Close Rick-Counters of the Rick Kind: When 27 Ricks from alternate dimensions are murdered and their respective Mortys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-21 04:15:00" d="2021-07-21 05:10:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox IX</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>What do Britain's favourite viewers think of Kitchen 999: Emergency Chefs, The Voice final, Alone with the In-Laws, Line of Duty, Life Story</k>  </p>
</a>
