<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="31" t="2020-05-31 04:33:21"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 05:30:00" d="2020-06-07 07:00:00"><n>Don't Tell the Bride</n><e>R</e>    <k>Nathan loves music and Stoke-on-Trent, so when bride-to-be Beccie gives him free rein to plan their wedding, he honours them with nuptials based on Northern Soul</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 07:00:00" d="2020-06-07 07:55:00"><n>Hollyoaks: Omnibus</n><t>S</t>    <k>49% Hollyoaks Omnibus
Nancy debates whether she can ever trust Kyle again. Jordan and Leela have a heart-to-heart. An uninvited guest makes a shock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 07:55:00" d="2020-06-07 08:50:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>R</e>    <k>Gordon travels to Atlanta to help first-time restaurant owners Richard and Jorge, whose establishment, Park's Edge, is in trouble due to their constant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 08:50:00" d="2020-06-07 09:50:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>R</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay travels to Ventura Harbor in southern California to help the owner of a family-run Greek restaurant turn its fortunes around. But he uncovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 09:50:00" d="2020-06-07 10:50:00"><n>Don't Tell the Bride</n><e>R</e>    <k>After a hilltop proposal, hopeless romantic Gavin plans nuptials in Somerset for his fiancée Sophie, with a combined theme of farmyard and Thai</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 10:50:00" d="2020-06-07 11:55:00"><n>Made in Chelsea Favourites</n>    <k>Miles, Emily and Harvey relive a racy summer in Ibiza. Emily's romance with Harry Baron is put to the test by his flirty friendship with Frankie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 11:55:00" d="2020-06-07 14:35:00"><n>Hulk</n><e>R</e>    <k>Marvel Comics fantasy starring Eric Bana. A scientific accident leaves a man cursed to become a large, destructive green monster whenever he loses his temper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 14:35:00" d="2020-06-07 15:05:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n>    <k>Manchester. The first host, DJ and hairdresser Mozz, makes garlic Stilton mushrooms and poached pear, and pulls out all the stops with a party atmosphere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 15:05:00" d="2020-06-07 15:35:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n>    <k>Manchester. Voiceover artist and film extra Matt serves a Jewish Friday night supper, featuring his mum's chicken soup. He has Sharon in hysterics</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 15:35:00" d="2020-06-07 16:05:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n>    <k>Manchester. Budding author and mum-of-five Cleona hosts with a menu based on her Jamaican roots and regales her guests with tales of her pastimes. (Ep3/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 16:05:00" d="2020-06-07 16:35:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n>    <k>Manchester. Australian radio content director James hopes some Chinese cuisine, his mum's cake recipe and a laid-back Aussie approach will lift the group's mood. (Ep4/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 16:35:00" d="2020-06-07 17:05:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n>    <k>Manchester. Events boss Sharon serves up a hearty, decadent menu. But her skills and decorum are put to the test by Cleona. (Ep5/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 17:05:00" d="2020-06-07 17:35:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (18)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% Suicide Squad: Desperate circumstances call for desperate measures as Peralta, Captain Holt and the team are forced to ally themselves with some old enemies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 17:35:00" d="2020-06-07 18:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VII</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Brand new series - Ransom: Holt asks for Jake's help in a case that is exceptionally meaningful to him. Charles and Terry work together on a side business. Ep12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 18:00:00" d="2020-06-07 18:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (9)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The White Asparagus Triangulation: Sheldon is delighted that Leonard has finally found a girlfriend who matches up to his high standards. perhaps a little too delighted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 18:30:00" d="2020-06-07 19:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (10)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Vartabedian Conundrum: Leonard goes to Penny for help when his relationship with Stephanie takes off faster than he'd like, but will he choose to act on her advice?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 19:00:00" d="2020-06-07 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (11)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Bath Item Gift Hypothesis: At Christmas, Leonard's handsome colleague starts dating Penny, while Sheldon's obsession with gift-giving etiquette torments his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 19:30:00" d="2020-06-07 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (12)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Killer Robot Instability: Kripke challenges the boys to a robot duel, while Howard is devastated when Penny finally tells him what she thinks of his chauvinism</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 20:00:00" d="2020-06-07 20:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (13)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Friendship Algorithm: Sheldon develops a scientific procedure for making friends when he discovers that Kripke has control of a new supercomputer at the university</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 20:30:00" d="2020-06-07 21:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (14)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Financial Permeability: When Sheldon lends Penny some money, it brings her ex-boyfriend Kurt back into her life, with negative consequences for the gang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 21:00:00" d="2020-06-07 21:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (11)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Santa Simulation: Sheldon unwillingly reveals painful memories of Christmas past when Leonard persuades him to join in with a seasonal game of Dungeons &amp; Dragons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 21:30:00" d="2020-06-07 22:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (12)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Egg Salad Equivalency: Sheldon is accused of sexual harassment and sent to Human Resources, where he ends up dragging Leonard, Raj and Howard into trouble too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 22:00:00" d="2020-06-07 23:00:00"><n>Batwoman</n><t>S</t>    <k>42% New: Batwoman
Brand new series - Take Your Choice: As Kate is pulled between two sisters, Luke and Mary are tasked with finding the cause behind Beth's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-07 23:00:00" d="2020-06-08 00:00:00"><n u="Misfits">Misfits I (6)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The gang realise something strange is going on in the town and it looks as though the Virtue organisation is behind it, but all is not as it seems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 00:00:00" d="2020-06-08 01:05:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction III</n><e>R</e>    <k>In the Naked Attraction studio, former club rep Chris hopes to meet someone to settle down with. Technophobe Louise wants an old-fashioned gentleman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 01:05:00" d="2020-06-08 02:10:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction III</n><e>R</e>    <k>Another two singletons join Anna Richardson in the Naked Attraction studio. One man hoping to find love is Ryan, who was born with the life-limiting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 02:10:00" d="2020-06-08 03:10:00"><n u="Supernatural">Supernatural XIV</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Supernatural
Brand new series - Damaged Goods: Dean spends time bonding with Mary and Donna. Sam is left to make an unimaginable choice. Nick finally</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 03:10:00" d="2020-06-08 03:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (15)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Maternal Capacitance: A disastrous visit from Leonard's mother Beverly has the unexpected side-effect of bringing Leonard and Penny closer together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 03:35:00" d="2020-06-08 04:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (16)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Cushion Saturation: A game of paintball leads to a squabble when Penny accidentally shoots paint at one of Sheldon's cushions. Romance blossoms between Howard and Leslie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 04:00:00" d="2020-06-08 04:45:00"><n>Batwoman</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>42% Brand new series - Take Your Choice: As Kate is pulled between two sisters, Luke and Mary are tasked with finding the cause behind Beth's debilitating headaches. (Ep11)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-08 04:45:00" d="2020-06-08 05:40:00"><n>Don't Tell the Bride</n><e>R</e>    <k>After a hilltop proposal, hopeless romantic Gavin plans nuptials in Somerset for his fiancée Sophie, with a combined theme of farmyard and Thai</k>  </p>
</a>
