<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="47" t="2020-05-28 04:35:33"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 05:20:00" d="2020-06-04 05:45:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Deception Verification: Leonard returns early from his research expedition as a surprise for Penny, but Sheldon becomes upset that he wasn't in on the secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 05:45:00" d="2020-06-04 06:10:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch VI (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>I Think I Love You: Josh tells Sabrina he loves her and she attempts to reciprocate, but every time she tries to profess her affection the words</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 06:10:00" d="2020-06-04 07:00:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch VI (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Arrangement: Great Aunt Irma turns up with a witch named Peter and claims that Sabrina must marry him immediately. But things get more complex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 07:00:00" d="2020-06-04 07:30:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Singing and Dancing: When Timmy joins an 'a cappella' group, he is keen to keep his new hobby a secret from Russell. Jeff and Audrey have an annoying new neighbour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 07:30:00" d="2020-06-04 08:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Jeff Day: When Jeff proclaims that it's 'Jeff Day', everything goes swimmingly until the cleaning lady arrives. Adam is baffled when his eye keeps twitching</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 08:00:00" d="2020-06-04 08:30:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch VI (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Time After Time: Sabrina uses magic to erase Zelda's broken heart after she breaks up with Professor Carlin, but changing the course of history leaves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 08:30:00" d="2020-06-04 09:00:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch VI (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Sabrina and the Kiss: Sabrina kisses her old boyfriend Derek, but when she tells Josh about it, he says he doesn't mind, leaving her troubled. Hilda hosts a charity auction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 09:00:00" d="2020-06-04 09:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Let's Get It Started: Joe wants Mel to stop using birth control so they can start a family, but she's unsure about whether she's ready for the responsibility</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 09:30:00" d="2020-06-04 10:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Failure to Communicate: The family gathers around the laptop to video chat with Ryder in New Orleans on his 18th birthday, but the computer suddenly crashes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 10:00:00" d="2020-06-04 10:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% The Wingmom: Bonnie sets Ben up with Bailey, a fast-talking, animated spitfire with plenty of attitude. Riley and Tucker take a cherished car out for a spin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 10:30:00" d="2020-06-04 11:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Send in the Clowns: Ben is determined to give Emma the perfect first birthday party at the ice cream parlour where he and Riley both worked as teenagers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 11:00:00" d="2020-06-04 11:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Scavenger Vortex: Raj organises an epic and demanding scavenger hunt for the group of friends, designed to test their scientific knowledge and common sense</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 11:30:00" d="2020-06-04 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Raiders Minimization: Amy ruins one of Sheldon's favourite films by pointing out a flaw in the storyline. Raj and Stuart decide to create online dating profiles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 12:00:00" d="2020-06-04 12:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Crazy Calls: After getting telephone answering machines, Murray and Pop-Pop wage a message war on one another. Adam finds a lunchtime home with the school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 12:30:00" d="2020-06-04 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Stefan King: Adam gets in trouble with Beverly for portraying her as a monster in a horror story, and Erica forces Barry to attend a Halloween costume dance with her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 13:00:00" d="2020-06-04 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Chocolate Milk: Holt's long-time nemesis arrives to carry out an inspection of his precinct. Boyle searches for a 'plus one' to take to his ex-wife's engagement party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 13:30:00" d="2020-06-04 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Jimmy Jab Games: When the squad has time to kill, Peralta launches the seventh annual Jimmy Jab Games, an eccentric series of contests held in the precinct building</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 14:00:00" d="2020-06-04 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Explosion Implosion: Howard and Sheldon bond on a trip to the desert to launch a model rocket. Leonard is annoyed when his mother befriends Penny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 14:30:00" d="2020-06-04 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Collaboration Contamination: Sheldon and Raj ask Bernadette for advice about their jealousy when Amy and Howard decide to collaborate on a new project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 15:00:00" d="2020-06-04 15:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% The Parent Trap: Mel is alarmed when her father gives Joe's mother some advice about drawing up a will and the pair start to get along a little too well</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 15:30:00" d="2020-06-04 16:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey V (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Melissa &amp; Joey's Frozen: During a skiing holiday, Mel and Joe become frozen after getting buried in an avalanche and are thawed out 100 years later</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 16:00:00" d="2020-06-04 16:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% You Can't Go Home Again: Ben and Riley have started dating again, but Riley wants to keep it a secret. Danny considers moving to Paris with Georgie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 16:30:00" d="2020-06-04 17:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy IV (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Strip or Treat: Ben, Danny and Tucker's plans to attend the biggest Halloween celebration in the city fall through, so they decide to gatecrash a party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 17:00:00" d="2020-06-04 17:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Beach House: The team is excited to visit Boyle's beach house for a detectives-only weekend getaway until Peralta ruins the fun by inviting Captain Holt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 17:30:00" d="2020-06-04 18:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Payback: The squad decides it's high time Peralta paid them back all the money they have lent him over the years. Santiago and Holt re-open an arson case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 18:00:00" d="2020-06-04 18:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Spencer's Gift: Erica is jealous of Barry's outstanding performance when they both get after-school jobs at Spencer's gift shop selling novelty presents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 18:30:00" d="2020-06-04 19:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>So Swayze It's Crazy: When Adam tries his hand at acting, an agent decides he's only good for 'nerd' roles, so Beverly sets out to turn him into a heartthrob</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 19:00:00" d="2020-06-04 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Separation Triangulation: Raj gets into a domestic drama with his new date Nell and her estranged husband. Sheldon rents his old room back from Leonard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 19:30:00" d="2020-06-04 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Novelization Correlation: Amy appears on the Professor Proton show. Penny hates the idea that the female protagonist in Leonard's novel is based on her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 20:00:00" d="2020-06-04 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks Favourites</n><e>F</e>    <k>A look back at a classic Hollyoaks villain. The villagers are stunned to discover that the serial killer has struck again, and Mercedes fears for her life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 20:30:00" d="2020-06-04 21:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% M.E. Time: Peralta meets an attractive medical examiner, but he annoys his colleagues when his attempts to get together with her cause a hold-up with an autopsy report</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 21:00:00" d="2020-06-04 21:30:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>75% A Financial Secret and Fish Sauce: George Sr asks Sheldon to keep a secret from Mary but the stress of not being honest drives Sheldon to hide at Tam's house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 21:30:00" d="2020-06-04 22:00:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>75% A Research Study and Czechoslovakian Wedding Pastries: Dr Sturgis recommends Sheldon and Missy for a university research study on twins, but Mary is unhappy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 22:00:00" d="2020-06-04 22:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VII</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Brooklyn Nine-Nine
Brand new series - Ransom: Holt asks for Jake's help in a case that is exceptionally meaningful to him. Charles and Terry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 22:30:00" d="2020-06-04 23:00:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty IV</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Rick and Morty [adult swim]
Brand new series - Childrick of Mort: The fourth series of the critically acclaimed, Emmy Award-winning animation returns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 23:00:00" d="2020-06-04 23:30:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty IV</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Rick and Morty [adult swim]
Brand new series - Star Mort Rickturn of the Jerri: The fourth series of the critically acclaimed, Emmy Award-winning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-04 23:30:00" d="2020-06-05 00:00:00"><n>Harley Quinn</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Harley Quinn
Brand new series - Being Harley Quinn: While trying to find a lair, Harley suffers a paralysing identity crisis. Using Dr Psycho's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 00:00:00" d="2020-06-05 01:00:00"><n u="Buffy the Vampire Slayer">Buffy the Vampire Slayer I (4)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Teacher's Pet: Buffy's biology teacher is killed by a giant praying mantis that assumes the form of a beautiful substitute teacher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 01:00:00" d="2020-06-05 01:30:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty I (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>92% Rick and Morty [adult swim]
Rick Potion #9: Rick helps Morty impress his classmate Jessica, the girl of his dreams, by giving his grandson a potion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 01:30:00" d="2020-06-05 01:45:00"><n u="Robot Chicken">Robot Chicken IX</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Robot Chicken [adult swim]
Things Look Bad for the Streepster: Daniel Tiger learns the toughest lesson of all. The Nerd takes a peek at Nick's Arcade</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 01:45:00" d="2020-06-05 02:00:00"><n u="Robot Chicken">Robot Chicken IX</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Robot Chicken [adult swim]
Mr Mozzarella's Hamburger Skateboard Depot: The team discover the emotions of adulthood in Inside Out 2. The pig from Black</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 02:00:00" d="2020-06-05 02:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Bath Item Gift Hypothesis: At Christmas, Leonard's handsome colleague starts dating Penny, while Sheldon's obsession with gift-giving etiquette torments his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 02:30:00" d="2020-06-05 03:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Killer Robot Instability: Kripke challenges the boys to a robot duel, while Howard is devastated when Penny finally tells him what she thinks of his chauvinism</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 03:00:00" d="2020-06-05 03:55:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Gym addict Sophie from Surrey is looking for a change from the usual body-builder types who lack sparkle, while Dom seeks his perfect man to waltz him down the aisle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 03:55:00" d="2020-06-05 04:20:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty IV</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Rick and Morty [adult swim]
Brand new series - Star Mort Rickturn of the Jerri: The fourth series of the critically acclaimed, Emmy Award-winning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 04:20:00" d="2020-06-05 04:45:00"><n>Harley Quinn</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series - Being Harley Quinn: While trying to find a lair, Harley suffers a paralysing identity crisis. Using Dr Psycho's telepathic powers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-06-05 04:45:00" d="2020-06-05 05:10:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VII</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series - Ransom: Holt asks for Jake's help in a case that is exceptionally meaningful to him. Charles and Terry work together on a side business. Ep12)</k>  </p>
</a>
