<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="41" t="2020-04-10 04:31:41"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 05:00:00" d="2020-04-17 05:25:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Irish Pub Formulation: A visit from Raj's sister Priya creates tension among the guys, especially when Leonard asks Sheldon to conceal his romantic past with her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 05:25:00" d="2020-04-17 05:50:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother VII (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Noretta: The gang realise that their partners bear some resemblance to their parents. Barney and Nora's romantic evening is ruined by a string of disasters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 05:50:00" d="2020-04-17 06:20:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother VII (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% The Slutty Pumpkin Returns: Ted finally meets the mystery girl who attracted his attention by wearing a pumpkin costume at a Halloween party a decade previously</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 06:20:00" d="2020-04-17 07:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>R</e>    <k>A Visit from Fay: Jennifer discovers some alarming things about Adam's mum. Jeff and Audrey are forced to entertain themselves when their TV stops working</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 07:00:00" d="2020-04-17 07:30:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Jen at Work: Adam and Jennifer realise that living and working together is harder than they anticipated when he hires her to do some freelance work for his company</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 07:30:00" d="2020-04-17 08:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Optimal Male: Jeff struggles to lose enough weight to be eligible for the 'optimal male' fitness category in his life insurance exam. Jennifer frets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 08:00:00" d="2020-04-17 08:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother VII (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Disaster Averted: Barney is desperate to get rid of the ducky tie and drives a hard bargain to be allowed to remove it. Later, the gang reminisce about Hurricane Irene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 08:30:00" d="2020-04-17 09:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother VII (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% The Rebound Girl: Ted and Barney plan to adopt a child together because as men they feel they understand each other better than a man and a woman ever could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 09:00:00" d="2020-04-17 09:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Auction Hero: Mel urges Joe to participate in a school charity auction, but when he does so, it seems that the winner of the event has ulterior motives for taking part</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 09:30:00" d="2020-04-17 10:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Waiting for Mr Right: Joe teases Mel when she brings home a guy who's boring, but she feels the pressure to be in a relationship when her last single friend gets engaged</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 10:00:00" d="2020-04-17 10:30:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly V</n><e>RF</e>    <k>The Last Temptation of Mike: Mike engages in some innocent flirting with a rookie police officer named Stacey, but when she reciprocates he starts to feel guilty. Ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 10:30:00" d="2020-04-17 11:00:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly V</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Support Your Local Samuel: Samuel receives a letter from his parents saying they're struggling financially and he considers moving back home to take care of them. Ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 11:00:00" d="2020-04-17 11:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Apology Insufficiency: Leonard thinks his dating problems are due to lack of confidence and vows to be self-assured around attractive females</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 11:30:00" d="2020-04-17 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The 21-Second Excitation: The gang's plans to attend a film screening are scuppered by Sheldon's nemesis Wil Wheaton. Penny and Bernadette invite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 12:00:00" d="2020-04-17 12:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs I (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Call Me When You Get There: Barry's thrilled at the freedom offered by his new driver's licence until Beverly lays down her ten unbreakable rules of the road</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 12:30:00" d="2020-04-17 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs I (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Kremps: Beverly tries to make friends with her reserved, softly-spoken neighbours the Kremp family and bombards them with invitations to a barbecue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 13:00:00" d="2020-04-17 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine IV (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Cop-Con: The squad visit the annual Cop-Con event, usually an excuse for a party, but Captain Holt spoils the fun by asking them to be on their best behaviour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 13:30:00" d="2020-04-17 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine IV (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Chasing Amy: Santiago vanishes hours before she is due to take her sergeant's exam. Peralta and Diaz try to locate her and bring her back before it's too late</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 14:00:00" d="2020-04-17 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Prom Equivalency: The girls decide to re-enact their high-school proms with their current partners, so they recreate the event on the roof of the apartment building</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 14:30:00" d="2020-04-17 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Septum Deviation: When Leonard has to have minor surgery on his nose, Sheldon is the one who seems to need sympathy. Raj is upset when his parents split up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 15:00:00" d="2020-04-17 15:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (29)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% Do As I Say, Not As I Did: Lennox plans to go to an all-night party with her boyfriend. Holly grows jealous when she and Ryder allow another girl into their study group</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 15:30:00" d="2020-04-17 16:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (30)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>68% The Settlement: Mel and Joe face some difficult decisions after Joe comes into some money. A small leak in the ceiling grows into a huge problem for Mel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 16:00:00" d="2020-04-17 16:30:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly V</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Cocktails and Calamine: Molly is nervous about Mike attending a party that her publisher is throwing, but his feelings are hurt when he realises</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 16:30:00" d="2020-04-17 17:00:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly V</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Mudlick or Bust: Molly reunites Peggy with her estranged sister Rosemary when they visit Peggy's home town of Mudlick to do some research for their book. Ep17)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 17:00:00" d="2020-04-17 17:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs I (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Lame Gretzky: Murray struggles to get Adam interested in hockey. Beverly tries to help Erica prepare for her college entrance exams, but her plans backfire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 17:30:00" d="2020-04-17 18:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs I (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>For Your Own Good: Beverly replaces Murray's favourite chair with a new one without consulting him first. Adam is picked on during the bus ride to school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 18:00:00" d="2020-04-17 18:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Bad Beat: To track down an arms dealer, Peralta and Jeffords go undercover at an illegal gambling club. Hitchcock and Scully have an unusual challenge for Diaz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 18:30:00" d="2020-04-17 19:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine V (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Venue: The Vulture makes an unwelcome return to Peralta and Santiago's lives. Boyle and Diaz must track down kidnapped NYPD horse Sergeant Peanut Butter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 19:00:00" d="2020-04-17 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Leftover Thermalization: A power cut at Mrs Wolowitz's house defrosts the last meal she prepared before her death, so the gang consume it in her honour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 19:30:00" d="2020-04-17 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Skywalker Incursion: When Leonard and Sheldon are invited to speak at Berkeley, they take a detour during the journey to try to meet one of their idols</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 20:00:00" d="2020-04-17 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks Favourites</n><e>F</e>    <k>Former Hollyoaks star Jorgie Porter revisits a classic episode about heartbreak. Everything falls into place as Cleo confronts Mitchell about sleeping with Scott</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 20:30:00" d="2020-04-17 21:00:00"><n u="Man with a Plan">Man with a Plan III</n><t>S</t><e>TF</e>    <k>New: Man with a Plan
Brand new series - Wife-Proof: Adam attempts to make the office more inviting since Andi will be joining him at work every day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 21:00:00" d="2020-04-17 21:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Graduation Transmission: Leonard is invited to give the commencement address at his former high school. Howard and Sheldon can't make a toy drone fly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 21:30:00" d="2020-04-17 22:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Maternal Combustion: Personalities collide when Sheldon and Leonard's mothers finally meet. Howard decides to 'man up' and do his share of the housework</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-17 22:00:00" d="2020-04-18 00:15:00"><n u="Red">Red 2</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>67% RED 2
(2013) Comedy-thriller sequel starring Bruce Willis and Mary-Louise Parker. A retired secret agent and his girlfriend get dragged into a perilous adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 00:15:00" d="2020-04-18 00:45:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Leftover Thermalization: A power cut at Mrs Wolowitz's house defrosts the last meal she prepared before her death, so the gang consume it in her honour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 00:45:00" d="2020-04-18 01:15:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Skywalker Incursion: When Leonard and Sheldon are invited to speak at Berkeley, they take a detour during the journey to try to meet one of their idols</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 01:15:00" d="2020-04-18 02:20:00"><n u="The Sex Clinic">The Sex Clinic II</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series: Sophie's worried she might've been put at risk, Johnnie and Liam need help in the bedroom, Cat needs an STI test and Matt needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 02:20:00" d="2020-04-18 03:10:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats">8 Out of 10 Cats XX</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Rob Beckett, Lethal Bizzle and Tiff Stevenson face Aisling Bea, Jessica Knappett and Nish Kumar in the comedy panel show. Ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 03:10:00" d="2020-04-18 04:05:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox XIII</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Britain's sharpest armchair critics react to What/If, Piers Morgan's Life Stories, Jeremy Wade's Dark Waters, Britain's Got Talent, Beat the Chef and the News. Ep15)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 04:05:00" d="2020-04-18 05:00:00"><n>First Dates</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Can metrosexual Jon find headstrong Mancunian Regan's soft side? Playboy Mostafa believes every girl would like to marry him. And opinionated heavy metal</k>  </p>
</a>
