<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="33" t="2019-08-11 01:29:08"><p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 05:25:00" d="2019-08-17 05:45:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Honeypot: Peralta and Captain Holt clash over the merits of Holt's newly hired assistant. The team attempt to clean and declutter the communal office</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 05:45:00" d="2019-08-17 06:10:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% He Said, She Said: Captain Holt suspects a cunning escape after discovering that his lifelong criminal arch-nemesis has died in a prison transport accident</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 06:10:00" d="2019-08-17 07:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother IX (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Daisy: Marshall tries to work out where Lily went when she stormed out of the hotel on the night of their big fight. Robin is worried by Barney's pre-wedding behaviour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 07:00:00" d="2019-08-17 07:10:00"><n u="Rude Tube Shorts">Rude(ish) Tube Shorts</n><e>RF</e>    <k>A short, cheeky clip from Rude Tube's naughty little sister Rude(ish) Tube, featuring food and animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 07:10:00" d="2019-08-17 07:35:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Refusing to Budget: When the utilities are turned off in Russell's flat, Timmy convinces him that he needs to budget sensibly and pay his bills on time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 07:35:00" d="2019-08-17 07:55:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Little Bummer Boy: Timmy thinks it's a total bummer that he and Alison have split up at Christmas, but he cheers himself up by dressing as an elf to greet party guests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 07:55:00" d="2019-08-17 08:25:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless III (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series - C-e--Celebrity S-u--Suite: The family ends up at the hospital at Thanksgiving. Jimmy is jealous when Kenneth bonds with his brother Billy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 08:25:00" d="2019-08-17 08:55:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless III (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series - F-o--Follow T-h-r--Through: Ray and Dylan take on government bureaucracy, Kenneth helps JJ to prepare for college, while Maya tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 08:55:00" d="2019-08-17 09:25:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless III (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series - J-i--Jingle T-h--Thon: A Christmas tree fire leads Maya to tell a small lie that has some big consequences. JJ encourages Kenneth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 09:25:00" d="2019-08-17 09:55:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless III (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series - J-a--Javier's P-a--Pants: Maya lends a helping hand to her frenemy Melanie and finds life taking a surprising turn. Dylan joins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 09:55:00" d="2019-08-17 10:25:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless III (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series - R-o--Roll M-o--Model: JJ challenges Maya's mentoring tactics when she takes a father and son under her wing. Dylan and Ray attend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 10:25:00" d="2019-08-17 11:30:00"><n u="Don't Tell the Bride Ireland">Don't Tell the Bride Ireland VII</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Bride Jane wants a country house wedding extravaganza, but Colm chooses a 1920s-themed reception at a race track featuring gangsters, gambling and the Charleston. Ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 11:30:00" d="2019-08-17 12:30:00"><n u="Wife Swap USA">Wife Swap USA I</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series: A high-tech mother who streams her family's entire life on the internet swaps places with a technophobe mum who keeps her family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 12:30:00" d="2019-08-17 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Eight-bit Goldbergs: Adam is thrilled when he is asked to design his own video game for a school project. Beverly frets that Pops is too keen on gambling. Ep19)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 13:00:00" d="2019-08-17 13:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>This Is This Is Spinal Tap: The Dropouts are booked to perform a gig at a charity carnival. Beverly's concerns about Murray's health push him to the limit. Ep20)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 13:30:00" d="2019-08-17 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Tattler: Peralta and Gina attend their 20-year high school reunion. Boyle helps Diaz with a decision. A radio show mystery sound contest baffles the guys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 14:00:00" d="2019-08-17 14:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Four Movements: Gina plays a game of chess with Captain Holt, goes out for lunch with Diaz and Santiago and infiltrates an expensive social club with Peralta</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 14:30:00" d="2019-08-17 15:00:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon II (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>74% A Broken Heart and a Crock Monster: The family help a broken-hearted Pastor Jeff through a rough patch in his marriage. Mary takes Sheldon to work for a day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 15:00:00" d="2019-08-17 15:30:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon II (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>74% A Swedish Science Thing and the Equation for Toast: Sheldon asks the entire school to a party for the Nobel Prize announcements. Georgie yearns for cable TV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 15:30:00" d="2019-08-17 16:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Change Constant: Sheldon and Amy stay up late awaiting a phone call that could bring big news from the Nobel Committee: are their lives about to change?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 16:00:00" d="2019-08-17 16:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Stockholm Syndrome: Howard and Bernadette go away on a trip without their children, Leonard and Penny try to keep a secret, and Raj makes a new friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 16:30:00" d="2019-08-17 17:30:00"><n>The Big Bang Theory of Everything</n><e>RF</e>    <k>A celebration of everything 'Big Bang' related, with comments from famous fans, exclusive behind-the-scenes and red-carpet footage and classic clips</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 17:30:00" d="2019-08-17 19:30:00"><n>101 Dalmatians</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Glenn Close, Jeff Daniels and Joely Richardson star in Disney's live-action remake of their classic animation. Can two Dalmatians stop their puppies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 19:30:00" d="2019-08-17 20:00:00"><n>The Big Bang Theory: Couple Goals</n>    <k>This special stack of Saturday episodes is the result of our viewer vote. Viewers will have their pick of two key episodes for each of the five couples within the series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 20:00:00" d="2019-08-17 20:30:00"><n>The Big Bang Theory: Couple Goals</n>    <k>This special stack of Saturday episodes is the result of our viewer vote. Viewers will have their pick of two key episodes for each of the five couples within the series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 20:30:00" d="2019-08-17 21:00:00"><n>The Big Bang Theory: Couple Goals</n>    <k>This special stack of Saturday episodes is the result of our viewer vote. Viewers will have their pick of two key episodes for each of the five couples within the series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 21:00:00" d="2019-08-17 21:30:00"><n>The Big Bang Theory: Couple Goals</n>    <k>This special stack of Saturday episodes is the result of our viewer vote. Viewers will have their pick of two key episodes for each of the five couples within the series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 21:30:00" d="2019-08-17 22:00:00"><n>The Big Bang Theory: Couple Goals</n>    <k>This special stack of Saturday episodes is the result of our viewer vote. Viewers will have their pick of two key episodes for each of the five couples within the series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 22:00:00" d="2019-08-18 01:10:00"><n>Transformers: Dark of the Moon</n><e>RF</e>    <k>The third movie in the sci-fi action franchise. The discovery of a spacecraft on the dark side of the moon sparks another violent battle between</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 01:10:00" d="2019-08-18 02:15:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox XII</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Britain's sharpest armchair critics return for another series. What do they think of The X Factor, Bodyguard, Reported Missing, The Joy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 02:15:00" d="2019-08-18 03:20:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox XII</n><e>RF</e>    <k>What do Britain's sharpest armchair critics think of a selection of programmes including 5 Gold Rings, The X Factor, Dragons' Den, Bodyguard and Wanderlust? Ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 03:20:00" d="2019-08-18 04:15:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates XII</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Serial dater Jack, who's looking for a 'naughty sort', thinks his luck's in when he meets glamorous fire-breather Safina. But will his laddish charm impress her? Ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-18 04:15:00" d="2019-08-18 05:10:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates XI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Make-up artist and model Danni meets bar manager Aiden, the tallest man to ever enter the First Dates restaurant. Meanwhile, Sachen and Priya discover</k>  </p>
</a>
