<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="33" t="2020-04-11 04:30:43"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 05:00:00" d="2020-04-18 05:25:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Apology Insufficiency: Leonard thinks his dating problems are due to lack of confidence and vows to be self-assured around attractive females</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 05:25:00" d="2020-04-18 05:50:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IV (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The 21-Second Excitation: The gang's plans to attend a film screening are scuppered by Sheldon's nemesis Wil Wheaton. Penny and Bernadette invite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 05:50:00" d="2020-04-18 06:15:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother VII (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Disaster Averted: Barney is desperate to get rid of the ducky tie and drives a hard bargain to be allowed to remove it. Later, the gang reminisce about Hurricane Irene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 06:15:00" d="2020-04-18 07:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother VII (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% The Rebound Girl: Ted and Barney plan to adopt a child together because as men they feel they understand each other better than a man and a woman ever could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 07:00:00" d="2020-04-18 07:15:00"><n u="Rude Tube Shorts">Rude(ish) Tube Shorts</n><e>R</e>    <k>A short, cheeky clip from Rude Tube's naughty little sister Rude(ish) Tube, featuring exercise and pets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 07:15:00" d="2020-04-18 08:05:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n>    <k>Gordon Ramsay travels to New York to visit PJ's Steakhouse, where owners Joe and Madalyn are in serious debt and struggling to keep the high-end restaurant afloat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 08:05:00" d="2020-04-18 09:05:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n>    <k>Gordon Ramsay visits Fleming, a Danish restaurant in Miami, Florida. It was once the best family-run restaurant in town but is now losing money fast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 09:05:00" d="2020-04-18 10:05:00"><n>Don't Tell the Bride</n><e>R</e>    <k>Jake wants the ultimate wedding knees-up, but image conscious bride-to-be Rosie dreams of a more intimate affair. Will Jake's festival wedding prove a headline act?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 10:05:00" d="2020-04-18 11:45:00"><n>The Rugrats Movie</n><e>R</e>    <k>Family animation. The feisty kids decide that Dil, the latest addition to the family, is too troublesome and needs taking to the hospital to be fixed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 11:45:00" d="2020-04-18 13:30:00"><n>Tad the Lost Explorer and the...</n>    <k>. ecret of King Midas: (2017) Animated adventure. Bumbling explorer Tad Jones returns to rescue the girl he fancies, using a notebook that contains clues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 13:30:00" d="2020-04-18 14:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VII</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Brand new series - The Beverly Goldberg Cookbook: Part 2: When a publisher shows interest in her recipes, Beverly prepares to finally realise her dream</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 14:00:00" d="2020-04-18 14:30:00"><n u="Schooled">Schooled II</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Brand new series - The Pokemon Society: Learning he's not into baseball cards, Coach Mellor encourages Toby to be competitive in CB's Pokemon club. Ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 14:30:00" d="2020-04-18 15:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine III (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% New Captain: After Holt is transferred to the NYPD Department of Public Relations, the arrival of a new captain causes the precinct to dissolve into chaos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 15:00:00" d="2020-04-18 15:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine III (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% The Funeral: The precinct gets another personnel change, putting Peralta and Santiago's budding relationship at risk. Boyle is attracted to a fellow officer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 15:30:00" d="2020-04-18 16:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (6)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% The Crime Scene: Peralta and Diaz doggedly work and rework a crime scene in an effort to solve a difficult murder case that is clouded by confusing evidence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 16:00:00" d="2020-04-18 16:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (7)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>83% The Honeypot: Peralta and Captain Holt clash over the merits of Holt's newly hired assistant. The team attempt to clean and declutter the communal office</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 16:30:00" d="2020-04-18 17:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (8)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Prom Equivalency: The girls decide to re-enact their high-school proms with their current partners, so they recreate the event on the roof of the apartment building</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 17:00:00" d="2020-04-18 17:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (9)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Septum Deviation: When Leonard has to have minor surgery on his nose, Sheldon is the one who seems to need sympathy. Raj is upset when his parents split up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 17:30:00" d="2020-04-18 18:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (10)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Champagne Reflection: Sheldon and Amy record the final episode of their internet show Fun with Flags. Penny tells Bernadette how her colleagues really feel about her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 18:00:00" d="2020-04-18 18:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (11)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Clean Room Infiltration: Amy hosts a Victorian Christmas Eve dinner, complete with party games, and Raj, Leonard and Howard have pigeon problems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 18:30:00" d="2020-04-18 19:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (12)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Space Probe Disintegration: Howard tries to calm a stressed Raj, who is anxiously awaiting the arrival of some data from a space probe he helped launch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 19:00:00" d="2020-04-18 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (13)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Anxiety Optimization: When Sheldon gets stuck in a rut with his research, he asks his friends to cure his mental block by raising his stress levels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 19:30:00" d="2020-04-18 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (22)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Graduation Transmission: Leonard is invited to give the commencement address at his former high school. Howard and Sheldon can't make a toy drone fly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 20:00:00" d="2020-04-18 20:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (23)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Maternal Combustion: Personalities collide when Sheldon and Leonard's mothers finally meet. Howard decides to 'man up' and do his share of the housework</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 20:30:00" d="2020-04-18 21:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (24)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Commitment Determination: Sheldon pressures Leonard and Penny to choose a date for their wedding while dealing with changes in his own relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 21:00:00" d="2020-04-18 21:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Matrimonial Momentum: Penny struggles with Leonard's confession that he kissed another woman. Sheldon doesn't know how to act when Amy breaks up with him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 21:30:00" d="2020-04-18 22:00:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon III</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Brand new series - An Academic Crime and a More Romantic Taco Bell: Dr Sturgis is mad when Sheldon accuses him of plagiarism. Mary finds a girl trophy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-18 22:00:00" d="2020-04-19 00:25:00"><n>The Heat</n><e>R</e>    <k>Broad-humoured comedy from the director of Bridesmaids. Sandra Bullock and Melissa McCarthy star as mismatched cops who are forced to work together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 00:25:00" d="2020-04-19 01:35:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox XIV</n><e>R</e>    <k>What do Britain's favourite armchair critics make of EastEnders, Britain's Got Talent: The Champions, Peaky Blinders, Gordon Ramsay: Uncharted and First Dates Hotel? Ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 01:35:00" d="2020-04-19 02:40:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox XIV</n><e>R</e>    <k>What do Britain's favourite armchair critics make of Peaky Blinders, The Cameron Interview, Jamie's Meat-Free Meals, The Great British Bake Off and World Chase Tag? Ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 02:40:00" d="2020-04-19 03:45:00"><n>First Dates</n><e>R</e>    <k>Can Kenny and his biceps 'James' and 'Andrew' sweep gym manager Claire off her feet? And will the stars align for former Countdown contestant Jonny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 03:45:00" d="2020-04-19 04:40:00"><n>First Dates</n><e>R</e>    <k>Will romance blossom between glamorous Rachel and unlucky-in-love Alan, as they discuss her experiences of living with OCD? And will Jess like Ross's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-04-19 04:40:00" d="2020-04-19 05:30:00"><n>Don't Tell the Bride</n><e>R</e>    <k>Jake wants the ultimate wedding knees-up, but image conscious bride-to-be Rosie dreams of a more intimate affair. Will Jake's festival wedding prove a headline act?</k>  </p>
</a>
