<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="38" t="2021-07-09 06:48:55"><p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 05:00:00" d="2021-07-16 05:25:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother I (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Matchmaker: Ted is coaxed into joining a matchmaking service that Robin has written about and which offers a 100% success rate at finding a soulmate in three days</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 05:25:00" d="2021-07-16 05:50:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother I (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% The Duel: Ted feels pushed out when Lily and Marshall dominate the household and tells them that he wants to take the flat after they get married</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 05:50:00" d="2021-07-16 06:15:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Mixed Doubles: Joe sets Mel up on a blind date with his pal, but in exchange for this favour he asks her to arrange a date for him with her attractive friend Ariel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 06:15:00" d="2021-07-16 07:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% The Donor: Mel's friend Jackie decides she wants a baby and settles on Joe as the man most suitable to be the father of her child. Lennox and Haskell buy a rare book</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 07:00:00" d="2021-07-16 07:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>An unwelcome visitor causes Shaq to make a shocking confession. Captive Liberty is desperate to return home to her daughter. Martine finds it difficult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 07:30:00" d="2021-07-16 08:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>The Maalik family are rattled by a shock confession, but there's another twist. Martine and Felix are drawn together. A minor slip-up allows captive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 08:00:00" d="2021-07-16 09:00:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>In rural New Jersey, Gordon Ramsay visits Flamangos, where mother and daughter Adele and Cheryl are stuck in their tropical ways. But their restaurant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 09:00:00" d="2021-07-16 09:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother I (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Belly Full of Turkey: Ted and Robin are surprised to see Barney when they volunteer at a homeless refuge at Thanksgiving. Lily's nerves are tested</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 09:30:00" d="2021-07-16 10:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother I (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% The Pineapple Incident: Ted goes on a boozy night out to try to stop himself from brooding and wakes up the next morning to find a stranger in his bed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 10:00:00" d="2021-07-16 10:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Eat, Pray, Date: Mel allows her new date Travis to believe she is an amazing chef without mentioning that it was Joe who really made their delicious food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 10:30:00" d="2021-07-16 11:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Pretty Big Liars: When Ryder decides to invest in stocks and shares, he turns to Joe for advice, but Joe thinks that Ryder's choice of investment is a poor one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 11:00:00" d="2021-07-16 11:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Play It Again, Bonnie: A lovesick Bonnie realises how much she misses her ex-boyfriend Brad, so she turns to Tucker for help in arranging a reunion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 11:30:00" d="2021-07-16 12:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Livin' on a Prom: When Bonnie goes on strike because she feels unappreciated, Ben tries to get back into her good books by taking her to a Bon Jovi concert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 12:00:00" d="2021-07-16 12:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Dungeons &amp; Dragons, Anyone?: Adam picks a team of popular athletes over his friends in gym class. Erica decides that she wants to leave home to attend college</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 12:30:00" d="2021-07-16 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Rush: When Barry insists that Beverly always favours Adam, she tries to make amends. Murray is not happy about Erica's new boyfriend, a fanatical music fan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 13:00:00" d="2021-07-16 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Beach House: The team are excited to visit Boyle's beach house for a detectives-only weekend getaway, until Peralta ruins the fun by inviting Captain Holt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 13:30:00" d="2021-07-16 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Payback: The squad decide it's high time that Peralta paid them back all the money they have lent him over the years. Santiago and Holt reopen an arson case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 14:00:00" d="2021-07-16 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Grant Allocation Derivation: Leonard is made responsible for distributing extra grant money. Bernadette turns the garden playhouse into a hideaway</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 14:30:00" d="2021-07-16 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Consummation Deviation: Sheldon aims to bond with Amy's father, but Howard lures Mr Fowler away with his magic tricks. Raj and Anu try to get physical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 15:00:00" d="2021-07-16 15:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Terminator Decoupling: Leonard, Sheldon, Howard and Raj discover that beautiful sci-fi actress Summer Glau is on board their train to San Francisco</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 15:30:00" d="2021-07-16 16:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Work Song Nanocluster: Penny's home-based business selling hair accessories gets out of hand when an overexcited Sheldon takes charge of production</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 16:00:00" d="2021-07-16 16:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Recipe for Death II: Kiss the Cook: Adam asks his father for money to film his own action movie, while Erica and Beverly go on a clothes shopping expedition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 16:30:00" d="2021-07-16 17:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Ho-ly K.I.T.T: A shared love of the TV show Knight Rider brings Murray and his brother Marvin together. Beverly invites Lainey and Bill to Thanksgiving dinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 17:00:00" d="2021-07-16 17:30:00"><n u="Black-ish">Black-ish VI</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: black-ish
Brand new series - Friendgame: Bow is heartbroken that Diane is no longer friends with Sophie. Dre finds a hole in the wall that Junior</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 17:30:00" d="2021-07-16 18:00:00"><n u="Black-ish">Black-ish VI</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: black-ish
Brand new series - You Don't Know Jack: Jack joins the robotics club, to Dre's dismay, while Ruby embellishes a story for Diane's school project. Ep17)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 18:00:00" d="2021-07-16 18:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Chopper: When Chief Madeline Wuntch allows Peralta to work on his dream case, a wary Captain Holt worries that she's setting the precinct up to fail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 18:30:00" d="2021-07-16 19:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Johnny and Dora: Peralta and Santiago go undercover to catch Brooklyn's most notorious identity thief, but working together brings them closer than before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 19:00:00" d="2021-07-16 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Conference Valuation: Penny and Bernadette go to San Diego for a sales convention, leaving Howard in charge of Michael and Halley while they are away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 19:30:00" d="2021-07-16 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Laureate Accumulation: When their academic competitors charm America on a publicity tour, Sheldon and Amy try to get some Nobel laureates on their side</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 20:00:00" d="2021-07-16 20:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Cognition Regeneration: Leonard isn't thrilled when he finds out that Penny is considering accepting a job offer from her ex-boyfriend Zack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 20:30:00" d="2021-07-16 21:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory X (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Gyroscopic Collapse: Amy is offered a fellowship at Princeton, Raj makes new living arrangements, and the guys' gyroscope project spins out of control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 21:00:00" d="2021-07-16 22:00:00"><n u="Below Deck Mediterranean">Below Deck Mediterranean IV</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Below Deck Mediterranean
Brand new series - 99 Problems But a Chef Ain't One: A recording artist charters Sirocco to shoot a music video</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-16 22:00:00" d="2021-07-17 00:05:00"><n>Central Intelligence</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Violent comedy action-adventure with Dwayne Johnson and Kevin Hart. Two old school buddies team up to thwart a terrorist plot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-17 00:05:00" d="2021-07-17 01:10:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Cathy wants to settle down and have kids. Adam, who's 24, hates online dating. Will baring all help them find their perfect partner?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-17 01:10:00" d="2021-07-17 02:10:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Gym addict Sophie from Surrey is looking for a change from the usual body-builder types who lack sparkle, while Dom seeks his perfect man to waltz him down the aisle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-17 02:10:00" d="2021-07-17 03:15:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox IX</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>What do Britain's favourite viewers think of Schofield's South African Adventure, Ant &amp; Dec's Saturday Night Takeaway, Dogs Behaving Badly, The Great</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-17 03:15:00" d="2021-07-17 04:10:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates XI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Make-up artist and model Danni meets bar manager Aiden, the tallest man to ever enter the First Dates restaurant. Meanwhile, Sachen and Priya discover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-17 04:10:00" d="2021-07-17 05:05:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Cathy wants to settle down and have kids. Adam, who's 24, hates online dating. Will baring all help them find their perfect partner?</k>  </p>
</a>
