<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="45" t="2019-08-10 01:36:45"><p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 05:05:00" d="2019-08-16 05:25:00"><n u="The Good Place">The Good Place II (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series - The Burrito: The friends consider how much they have (or have not) improved over time. Michael is left to deal with the consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 05:25:00" d="2019-08-16 05:50:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% A Tale of Two Bandits: Jeffords thinks the Pontiac Bandit's up to his old tricks again. The team battle some firefighters to keep Shaw's bar a police hangout</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 05:50:00" d="2019-08-16 06:10:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Crime Scene: Peralta and Diaz doggedly work and rework a crime scene in an effort to solve a difficult murder case that is clouded by confusing evidence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 06:10:00" d="2019-08-16 06:35:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother IX (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Rally: Barney can't get out of bed on the morning of his wedding because he had too much to drink the night before, so the gang try to make him a famous hangover cure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 06:35:00" d="2019-08-16 07:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother IX (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Vesuvius: On the morning of the wedding, Ted helps a stressed Barney decide which suit to wear. Lily thinks Robin isn't treating her big day with the gravity it deserves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 07:00:00" d="2019-08-16 07:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>The tension mounts as Ste is offered a way out of the far right group. Mercedes fools around with Liam while her husband is away, but she doesn't realise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 07:30:00" d="2019-08-16 08:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Stuart and Jonny have an alarming secret plan, which is discovered by an intruder. Goldie is burning all of her clothes from her exes, and Mercedes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 08:00:00" d="2019-08-16 08:30:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Uh-Oh It's Magic: Russell takes his date Jessica to a magic show, only to see the magician make her disappear and not return. Illusionist Criss Angel guest stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 08:30:00" d="2019-08-16 09:00:00"><n>Rules of Engagement</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Singing and Dancing: When Timmy joins an 'a cappella' group, he is keen to keep his new hobby a secret from Russell. Jeff and Audrey have an annoying new neighbour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 09:00:00" d="2019-08-16 09:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother IX (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Daisy: Marshall tries to work out where Lily went when she stormed out of the hotel on the night of their big fight. Robin is worried by Barney's pre-wedding behaviour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 09:30:00" d="2019-08-16 10:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother IX (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Gary Blauman: When an old friend of the gang, Gary Blauman, shows up at the hotel for Robin and Barney's wedding unexpectedly, the seating plan is thrown into disarray</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 10:00:00" d="2019-08-16 10:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Lost in Translation: Mel asks Joe to act as translator when she has a meeting with a Japanese businessman, but once they all get together for dinner, things turn awkward</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 10:30:00" d="2019-08-16 11:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Joe Versus the Reunion: Despite everything that has happened to him over the past year, Joe decides to go to his college reunion and meet up with his former classmates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 11:00:00" d="2019-08-16 11:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy I (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% A Wheeler Family Christmas Outing: Ben tries to bring everyone together for Emma's first Christmas photo, including his dad Ray, who's been keeping a secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 11:30:00" d="2019-08-16 12:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy I (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Something Borrowed, Something Ben: Riley organises a wedding for her friends Katie and Dave but is horrified when Ben invites his wild pal Gene to the event</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 12:00:00" d="2019-08-16 12:30:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless I (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>C-h--Cheater!: Maya and Kenneth hold JJ accountable for his academic future when he cheats in a test at school. Ray gets involved in a get-rich-quick scheme</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 12:30:00" d="2019-08-16 13:00:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless I (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>R-u-n--Runaway: When Maya learns that JJ attempted to run away from home, she's determined to help him complete the task, but her actions exasperate her son</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 13:00:00" d="2019-08-16 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Sal's Pizza: When Peralta's favourite restaurant burns down, the fire marshal assumes the owner is the prime suspect in the investigation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 13:30:00" d="2019-08-16 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Thanksgiving: Santiago hosts a Thanksgiving dinner at her apartment for all of her colleagues at the precinct, but the celebration risks turning into a holiday disaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 14:00:00" d="2019-08-16 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory V (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Stag Convergence: Leonard, Sheldon and Raj throw a bachelor party for Howard, during which some stories about his sexual history are accidentally revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 14:30:00" d="2019-08-16 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory V (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Launch Acceleration: When Nasa informs Howard that his space mission has been rescheduled to an earlier date, he tries to use the wedding as an excuse not to go</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 15:00:00" d="2019-08-16 15:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (25)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% The Other Longo: When Joe's photographer brother Tony visits, Mel is impressed by his work and asks him to take some shots of her. Lennox avoids Ryder when he has a cold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 15:30:00" d="2019-08-16 16:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey I (26)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Teacher/Teacher: Joe gets Ryder into trouble with his teacher when he helps him to complete a homework assignment. Mel sneaks Lennox into an 18-years-and-over concert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 16:00:00" d="2019-08-16 16:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% All's Flair in Love and War: Tucker's girlfriend Vanessa gets an assistant manager position at Ben's bar and makes Ben's life miserable with ridiculous hours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 16:30:00" d="2019-08-16 17:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy II (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% Test Anxiety: Ben's feelings are hurt when Riley wants to talk to Danny and not him about her bar exam woes, but she finally confides in him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 17:00:00" d="2019-08-16 17:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Tactical Village: The officers attend mandatory training exercises in which all regional precincts compete. Captain Holt becomes addicted to a game on his smartphone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 17:30:00" d="2019-08-16 18:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine I (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Fancy Brudgom: Boyle asks Peralta to be his best man. Jeffords, Santiago and Gina start a new diet but struggle to stick to it. Holt helps Diaz to make a sincere apology</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 18:00:00" d="2019-08-16 18:30:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>B-r-i--British I-n-v--Invasion: Maya's regal mother pays a visit at Thanksgiving and the family struggle to impress her. Kenneth's overbearing father arrives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 18:30:00" d="2019-08-16 19:00:00"><n u="Speechless">Speechless II (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>B-i--Bikini U-n--University: JJ convinces his parents to take him on a trip to explore a college he is interested in. Ray goes wild when he's left home alone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 19:00:00" d="2019-08-16 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The 43 Peculiarity: The guys notice that Sheldon disappears for 20 minutes after lunch every day. Filled with curiosity, they attempt to work out what he's been doing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 19:30:00" d="2019-08-16 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VI (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Parking Spot Escalation: When non-driver Sheldon finds out that his unused parking space at the university has been reallocated to Howard, he feels undermined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 20:00:00" d="2019-08-16 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Goldie is forced to lie to her mum about Joel. Maxine has some distressing news for Damon, and Liam tries to fix things with Bobby. There's a shocking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 20:30:00" d="2019-08-16 21:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>My Valentine Boy: Erica and Valley Erica find a new band member to replace Lainey. Adam and Murray plot to escape from Valentine's Day dinner with Beverly. Ep15)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 21:00:00" d="2019-08-16 21:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Anything Can Happen Recurrence: Penny and Leonard distract Sheldon from his career problems by reinstating Anything Can Happen Thursday. Raj asks for Howard's advice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 21:30:00" d="2019-08-16 22:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Proton Transmogrification: Sheldon struggles to process his feelings of grief when his idol Professor Proton passes away. The gang gather to celebrate Star Wars Day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-16 22:00:00" d="2019-08-17 00:15:00"><n>Now You See Me</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Thriller starring Jesse Eisenberg, Woody Harrelson, Mark Ruffalo, Isla Fisher and Morgan Freeman about four magicians who commit a series of impressively bold robberies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 00:15:00" d="2019-08-17 00:40:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty III (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>92% New: Rick and Morty [adult swim]
Brand new series - The Ricklantis Mixup: Rick and Morty have an amazing adventure in Atlantis, and the Citadel of Ricks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 00:40:00" d="2019-08-17 01:15:00"><n>Robot Chicken: DC Comics</n><t>S</t>    <k>77% New: Robot Chicken: DC Comics. 
. pecial II (adult swim): Brand new - Villains in Paradise: The Robot Chicken writers explore what happens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 01:15:00" d="2019-08-17 01:45:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty II (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>92% Rick and Morty [adult swim]
Big Trouble in Little Sanchez: Summer becomes terrified by the possibility of a vampire attack. Rick urges Beth and Jerry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 01:45:00" d="2019-08-17 02:15:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Sibling Realignment: When Sheldon learns that his mother won't attend his wedding unless he invites his brother Georgie, he and Leonard travel to Texas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 02:15:00" d="2019-08-17 02:45:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XI (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Bow Tie Asymmetry: Everyone focuses on making sure all the arrangements for Amy and Sheldon's big day go according to plan - except the bride and groom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 02:45:00" d="2019-08-17 03:15:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Honeypot: Peralta and Captain Holt clash over the merits of Holt's newly hired assistant. The team attempt to clean and declutter the communal office</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 03:15:00" d="2019-08-17 03:35:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine VI (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% He Said, She Said: Captain Holt suspects a cunning escape after discovering that his lifelong criminal arch-nemesis has died in a prison transport accident</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 03:35:00" d="2019-08-17 04:30:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox VI</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Britain's favourite viewers return for another series. What do they think of Strictly Come Dancing, The X Factor, Bake Off, First Dates, Time Crashers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2019-08-17 04:30:00" d="2019-08-17 05:25:00"><n u="Gogglebox Australia">Gogglebox Australia II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Gogglebox Australia
Brand new series: The Goggleboxers share opinions on The Bachelorette, World's Biggest Pets, Gruen, Celebrity Apprentice, Nigella</k>  </p>
</a>
