<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="39" t="2021-07-08 04:50:56"><p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 05:10:00" d="2021-07-13 05:35:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Purple Giraffe: Ted feels desperate when Robin doesn't turn up to a party he invited her to as a second date and he vows to continue throwing parties until she does</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 05:35:00" d="2021-07-13 06:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% I Can Manage: When Mel feels the pressure of balancing her home renovations with her duties at work, Joe convinces her to put him in charge of construction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 06:00:00" d="2021-07-13 06:25:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% If You Can't Stand the Heat: Mel is charmed by the good-looking young man who designs her new kitchen cabinets, but Joe's reaction to him leads to an argument</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 06:25:00" d="2021-07-13 07:00:00"><n u="Black-ish">Black-ish VI</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Brand new series - O Mother Where Art Thou?: When Dre discovers that Lynette is an art aficionado like himself, the two quickly bond and become close</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 07:00:00" d="2021-07-13 07:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Can James persuade DS Cohen to help with Sally's case? Donna-Marie tries to make amends with Juliet. Tony thanks Becky for spending time with Diane</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 07:30:00" d="2021-07-13 08:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>RF</e>    <k>After a shock intimate moment, one Hollyoaks resident is in hot water. A break-in leads Juliet to make a decision. Ste reflects on second chances</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 08:00:00" d="2021-07-13 09:00:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>In Chicago, Gordon Ramsay visits the upmarket Cafe 36, where husband-and-wife team Terry and Carol are stuck in the past and their head chef's cavalier</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 09:00:00" d="2021-07-13 09:30:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Sweet Taste of Liberty: Ted agrees that Barney should spice up his love life, as a result of which he ends up flying to Philadelphia for a crazy adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 09:30:00" d="2021-07-13 10:00:00"><n u="How I Met Your Mother">How I Met Your Mother I (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>82% Return of the Shirt: Ted's views about life and love change when he discovers an old shirt that he previously disliked and suddenly loves the look of it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 10:00:00" d="2021-07-13 10:30:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% Good to Go: Mel and Joe are shocked to discover that Lennox's boyfriend Aidan spent the night in her bedroom. Holly declares that it's time for Ryder to start shaving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 10:30:00" d="2021-07-13 11:00:00"><n u="Melissa &amp; Joey">Melissa &amp; Joey II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>69% All Up in My Business: When Joe starts to run Mel's finances he becomes convinced that her credit card statements reveal she is having an affair with a married man</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 11:00:00" d="2021-07-13 11:30:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% The Bet: Riley wagers Ben that he can't get a second date with Heather. Bonnie meets a handsome stranger and ponders ending her relationship with Brad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 11:30:00" d="2021-07-13 12:00:00"><n u="Baby Daddy">Baby Daddy III (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>71% A Knight to Remember: Ben helps Tucker to pose as a lawyer because Tucker hasn't told his father that he dropped out of law school and is now working in TV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 12:00:00" d="2021-07-13 12:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Lainey Loves Lionel: Barry takes inspiration from Lionel Richie and sets about creating a sculpture of Lainey as the ultimate Valentine's Day gift</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 12:30:00" d="2021-07-13 13:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Weird Al: Adam plans to reignite his fading relationship with Dana by taking her to a concert. Barry and Erica worry that Murray may be feeling depressed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 13:00:00" d="2021-07-13 13:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Jake and Sophia: Peralta hits it off with a woman in a bar, only to find out that she is the defence attorney representing a perpetrator he wants to put in jail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 13:30:00" d="2021-07-13 14:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Lockdown: Peralta is left in charge of the precinct at Thanksgiving because Holt and Jeffords are away, but chaos ensues when a strange package is delivered</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 14:00:00" d="2021-07-13 14:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Conjugal Configuration: Sheldon and Amy's honeymoon runs aground, while Penny and Leonard discover that they are uncomfortably similar to Amy's parents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 14:30:00" d="2021-07-13 15:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Wedding Gift Wormhole: A stressed Sheldon and Amy struggle to work out what the 'perfect gift' is that Leonard and Penny gave them on their wedding day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 15:00:00" d="2021-07-13 15:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Bath Item Gift Hypothesis: At Christmas, Leonard's hunky colleague starts dating Penny, while Sheldon's obsession with gift-giving etiquette torments everyone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 15:30:00" d="2021-07-13 16:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory II (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Killer Robot Instability: Kripke challenges the boys to a robot duel, while Howard is devastated when Penny finally tells him what she thinks of his chauvinism</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 16:00:00" d="2021-07-13 16:30:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Have a Summer: Adam worries about being 'hazed' by the older students when he goes to high school, but he soon earns their respect by body-slamming Barry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 16:30:00" d="2021-07-13 17:00:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs IV (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Breakfast Club: Adam works on a new persona that he hopes will make him seem cool on his first day at high school, while Beverly gets her teaching certificate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 17:00:00" d="2021-07-13 17:30:00"><n u="Black-ish">Black-ish VI</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: black-ish
Brand new series - Father Christmas: Dre is thrown off when Pops appears full of holiday cheer. The whole family gets into the spirit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 17:30:00" d="2021-07-13 18:00:00"><n u="Black-ish">Black-ish VI</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: black-ish
Brand new series - Hair Day: Bow takes Diane to a salon, wanting to bond. Diane is conflicted about relaxing her hair again and embarks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 18:00:00" d="2021-07-13 18:30:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% The Wednesday Incident: When Peralta notices that Captain Holt is in a bad mood, he teams up with Holt's husband Kevin to find out what has gone wrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 18:30:00" d="2021-07-13 19:00:00"><n u="Brooklyn Nine-Nine">Brooklyn Nine-Nine II (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>83% Boyle-Linetti Wedding: As the wedding day of Gina's mother and Boyle's father dawns, each member of the squad is given a task to complete for the nuptials</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 19:00:00" d="2021-07-13 19:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Paintball Scattering: Jealousy, trust issues and tension among the couples in the gang cause mayhem when Penny and Leonard organise a paintball game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 19:30:00" d="2021-07-13 20:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Propagation Proposition: Penny's ex-boyfriend Zack and his wife want a baby, but when they encounter fertility problems they ask Leonard for his help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 20:00:00" d="2021-07-13 20:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>An unwelcome visitor causes Shaq to make a shocking confession. Captive Liberty is desperate to return home to her daughter. Martine finds it difficult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 20:30:00" d="2021-07-13 21:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks Favourites</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Former Hollyoaks star Jorgie Porter continues her look back at a classic soap wedding. Myra knows exactly what her evil future son-in-law is capable</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 21:00:00" d="2021-07-13 22:00:00"><n u="Below Deck Mediterranean">Below Deck Mediterranean IV</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Below Deck Mediterranean
Brand new series - Recipe for Disaster: The crew's first beach picnic gets off to a rocky start. After surviving their first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-13 22:00:00" d="2021-07-14 00:15:00"><n>Atomic Blonde</n><e>F</e>    <k>Violent thriller starring Charlize Theron. A British spy is sent to Cold War Berlin to retrieve a very sensitive list. With Sofia Boutella and James McAvoy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 00:15:00" d="2021-07-14 01:20:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction II (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Adele has beaten cancer. She wants to 'grab life by the balls' and find a guy who feels the same. Jack has lost four stone. He wants to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 01:20:00" d="2021-07-14 02:25:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox IX</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>What do Britain's favourite opinionated TV viewers think of The Jump, Dragons' Den, Death in Paradise, Jon Richardson: How to Survive the End of the World and SS-GB? Ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 02:25:00" d="2021-07-14 03:30:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates XI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In a First Dates first, twins Rebecca and Stephen nervously embark on a double date, with engineer Kristian and legal assistant Emily. Meanwhile, Fred's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 03:30:00" d="2021-07-14 03:55:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>91% Rick and Morty [adult swim]
Anatomy Park: Rick has built a tiny amusement park inside the body of his homeless friend Ruben, but when problems arise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 03:55:00" d="2021-07-14 04:20:00"><n u="Rick and Morty">Rick and Morty I (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>91% Rick and Morty [adult swim]
M. Night Shaym-Aliens!: Rick and Morty try to get to the bottom of a twisted mystery when aliens transport</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2021-07-14 04:20:00" d="2021-07-14 05:15:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox IX</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>What do Britain's favourite opinionated TV viewers think of The Jump, Dragons' Den, Death in Paradise, Jon Richardson: How to Survive the End of the World and SS-GB? Ep1)</k>  </p>
</a>
