<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="31" t="2020-05-17 04:32:16"><p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 05:20:00" d="2020-05-24 07:00:00"><n>Don't Tell the Bride</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Mummy's boy Tiago plans to put his self-conscious bride Karlette on the big screen at his 1950s drive-in wedding, but she wants something intimate and contemporary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 07:00:00" d="2020-05-24 08:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks: Omnibus</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>49% Hollyoaks Omnibus
Will Verity jeopardise Edward's plan? Drug-dealer Jordan sets his sights on young Charlie. Tony makes a surprising decision</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 08:00:00" d="2020-05-24 08:55:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>T</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay revisits three restaurants - Mojito, The Junction (formerly known as Flamangos) and Bazzini - to check in with the owners he helped</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 08:55:00" d="2020-05-24 09:55:00"><n>Don't Tell the Bride</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Thrill-seeking Tom wants to give the love of his life Becca the ride of her life, as he plans their wedding at his favourite theme park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 09:55:00" d="2020-05-24 10:55:00"><n>Made in Chelsea Favourites</n><e>F</e>    <k>Cohabiting couple Jamie Laing and Sophie 'Habbs' Habboo relive Jamie's pursuit of his former love interest Lucy Watson. How will he react when Lucy attends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 10:55:00" d="2020-05-24 12:35:00"><n>Horton Hears a Who!</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Animated family adventure based on the Dr Seuss book. Horton the elephant, voiced by Jim Carrey, sets out to save the miniscule planet of the Whos from destruction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 12:35:00" d="2020-05-24 13:10:00"><n>Celebrity Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Tattoo Fixer Jay Hutton hosts first. He serves a basic dinner and pulls out no stops whatsoever! Can his hosting skills win over his guests? (Ep1/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 13:10:00" d="2020-05-24 13:40:00"><n>Celebrity Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The second to host is ex-Coronation Street actor and dinner party virgin Steven Arnold. Can his hearty northern grub match his impeccable hosting? (Ep2/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 13:40:00" d="2020-05-24 14:10:00"><n>Celebrity Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Real Housewives of Cheshire star Dawn Ward goes all out to throw the perfect dinner party with drag maids, a personal barman and a glamorous dress code. (Ep3/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 14:10:00" d="2020-05-24 14:40:00"><n>Celebrity Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The week hots up with The Office star Ewen MacIntosh's Mexican-themed night, an obliterated pinata, and the biggest sombrero any of the guests have ever seen! (Ep4/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 14:40:00" d="2020-05-24 15:10:00"><n>Celebrity Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Geordie Shore's Charlotte Crosby hosts the final night with an apres-ski-themed evening. There's fondue and a DIY dessert, but who will win the charity prize? (Ep5/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 15:10:00" d="2020-05-24 15:40:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Dungeons &amp; Dragons, Anyone?: Adam picks a team of popular athletes over his friends in gym class. Erica decides she wants to leave home to attend college</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 15:40:00" d="2020-05-24 16:10:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs III (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Rush: When Barry insists that Beverly always favours Adam, she tries to make amends. Murray is not happy about Erica's new boyfriend, a fanatical music fan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 16:10:00" d="2020-05-24 16:40:00"><n u="The Goldbergs">The Goldbergs VII</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series - The Preventa Mode: As Valentine's Day approaches, Barry is shocked when an attractive teaching assistant agrees to go out with him. Ep14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 16:40:00" d="2020-05-24 17:10:00"><n u="Schooled">Schooled II</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Brand new series - Singled Out: Lainey works out her feelings for Valentine's Day. Felicia has body image issues. Coach Mellor does a workout</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 17:10:00" d="2020-05-24 17:40:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Big Bran Hypothesis: Bothered by how messy Penny's flat is, Sheldon sneaks in to clean and organise it, but Penny isn't best pleased when she finds out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 17:40:00" d="2020-05-24 18:10:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Fuzzyboots Corollary: Leonard is depressed when he discovers that Penny is seeing someone, so he summons up the courage to ask a woman out on a date</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 18:10:00" d="2020-05-24 18:40:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Luminous Fish Effect: Getting fired forces Sheldon to ponder life outside physics, leaving Leonard to take drastic action to snap his friend out of his reverie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 18:40:00" d="2020-05-24 19:10:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Hamburger Postulate: Leonard fears he's wasting his time on Penny and ends up making a connection with Leslie. Sheldon frets over a change to his hamburger routine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 19:10:00" d="2020-05-24 19:40:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Middle Earth Paradigm: Penny decides to host a big Halloween party, putting Leonard, Sheldon, Howard and Raj through a demanding new test of their social skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 19:40:00" d="2020-05-24 20:10:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Dumpling Paradox: When Howard seduces Penny's friend and spends the night with her in Penny's flat, Penny asks if she can sleep on Leonard and Sheldon's sofa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 20:10:00" d="2020-05-24 22:00:00"><n>Paddington</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Part-animated family fun. Hugh Bonneville, Sally Hawkins and Nicole Kidman star in this adaptation of Michael Bond's tales of the adventures of a small</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 22:00:00" d="2020-05-24 23:00:00"><n>Batwoman</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>42% New: Batwoman
Brand new series - How Queer Everything Is Today!: While Gotham busies itself reacting to Batwoman's awkward encounter, Alice celebrates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-24 23:00:00" d="2020-05-25 00:00:00"><n u="Misfits">Misfits I (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Curtis tries to use his superpower to go back to the past and change what happened on the night he was caught by the cops. But he discovers that changing history isn't easy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-25 00:00:00" d="2020-05-25 01:05:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction II</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Ray from Swindon is fed up of dating bad boys and is looking for a nice naked guy. Barman Jimmy wants to settle down in Bristol. Can he find his perfect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-25 01:05:00" d="2020-05-25 02:10:00"><n u="Naked Attraction">Naked Attraction II</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Mark from Sussex appeared in series one as a body and was rejected - now he's back to choose himself a date. And Justin from London is done with being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-25 02:10:00" d="2020-05-25 03:10:00"><n u="Supernatural">Supernatural XIV</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Supernatural
Brand new series - The Spear: Sam and Dean enlist the help of their pal Garth to gain inside information on what Michael may be planning. Ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-25 03:10:00" d="2020-05-25 03:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Grasshopper Experiment: Raj panics when his parents arrange a blind date for him, only to discover he actually can talk to a member of the opposite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-25 03:35:00" d="2020-05-25 04:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Cooper-Hofstadter Polarization: Sheldon and Leonard are asked to give a paper at a physics conference, but Sheldon is reluctant to share the credit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-25 04:00:00" d="2020-05-25 04:50:00"><n>Batwoman</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>42% Brand new series - How Queer Everything Is Today!: While Gotham busies itself reacting to Batwoman's awkward encounter, Alice celebrates her ultimate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1083" o="2020-05-25 04:50:00" d="2020-05-25 05:15:00"><n u="Sabrina the Teenage Witch">Sabrina the Teenage Witch V (15)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Love Is a Many Complicated Thing: Morgan fixes Sabrina up with fellow student Kevin so that she and Josh can double-date with them on Valentine's Day</k>  </p>
</a>
