<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="14" t="2019-07-11 00:18:50"><p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-16 05:15:00" d="2019-07-16 06:45:00"><n>30 for 30: No Crossover: The Trial of Allen Iverson</n>    <k>In 1993, Allen Iverson went bowling in Hampton. What followed ended with the teen in jail and divided a city along racial lines. Part of the acclaimed 30 for 30 series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-16 06:45:00" d="2019-07-16 07:00:00"><n>BT Sport Goals Reload</n>    <k>A round-up of the best goals from Ligue 1 this season, including Memphis Depay's stunning free-kick against Guingamp and Max Gradel's spectacular overhead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-16 07:00:00" d="2019-07-16 07:30:00"><n>Irish Rally Review</n>    <k>Highlights of the Donegal International Rally, part of the Irish Rally series. (2/2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-16 07:30:00" d="2019-07-16 08:30:00"><n>Euroformula Open Championship</n>    <k>Highlights of races one and two from round six of the Euroformula Championship at The Red Bull Ring in Austria</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-16 08:30:00" d="2019-07-16 10:00:00"><n>International GT Open Championship</n>    <k>Highlights of races one and two from round four of the International GT Open Championship at The Red Bull Ring in Austria</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-16 10:00:00" d="2019-07-16 11:00:00"><n>Formula E Championship: Formula E Championship Highlights</n>    <k>All the thrills and spills from the Formula E Championship season finale in New York, USA</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-16 11:00:00" d="2019-07-16 13:00:00"><n>SGB Premiership: SGB: Peterborough v Belle Vue</n>    <k>Action from the SGB Premiership as Peterborough host Belle Vue at the East of England Showground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-16 13:00:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00"><n>Live WTA Tennis: Live WTA Tennis: Bucharest Open</n>    <k>Action from day two of the BRD Bucharest Open in Romania</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 21:30:00"><n>Heineken Champions Cup: Story of the Champions Cup</n>    <k>A look back at the most memorable moments from the 2018/19 campaign as Mark McCall's Saracens beat defending champions Leinster to win their third European</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-16 21:30:00" d="2019-07-16 22:00:00"><n>Classics in Europe: Liverpool v AZ Alkmaar 1981/82</n>    <k>We revisit the second leg of the 1981/82 European Cup second round between Liverpool and AZ Alkmaar. The first leg finished 2-2 thanks to goals from David</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-16 22:00:00" d="2019-07-17 01:00:00"><n>UFC: UFC: de Randamie v Ladd</n>    <k>Aspen Ladd puts her unbeaten record on the line against Germaine de Randamie in a bantamweight bout at UFC Fight Night in Sacramento</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-17 01:00:00" d="2019-07-17 04:00:00"><n>Live MLB</n>    <k>Action from Major League Baseball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-17 04:00:00" d="2019-07-17 04:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Ajax v AC Milan: 1994/95</n>    <k>We revisit the 1995 final in Vienna between Louis van Gaal's Ajax and AC Milan. A star-studded Ajax team featured Edwin van der Sar, Ronald and Frank</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-17 04:30:00" d="2019-07-17 05:00:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing: Classic Boxing: Hodkinson v Villasana</n>    <k>We revisit this classic featherweight title bout between Paul Hodkinson and Marcos Villasana in June 1990 at the G-Mex Leisure Centre, Manchester</k>  </p>
</a>
