<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="11" t="2019-08-15 22:29:42"><p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-21 05:00:00" d="2019-08-21 06:00:00"><n>World Poker Tour Series</n>    <k>Just three players remain at the Season XV WPT Borgata Poker Open final table. Jesse Sylvia is in the lead ahead of Zach Gruneberg and Taha Maruf</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-21 06:00:00" d="2019-08-21 07:00:00"><n>World Poker Tour Series</n>    <k>With 379 entries, the Season XV WPT bestbet Bounty Scramble generated a prize pool of more than $1.7 million. Defending champion Tyler Patterson returns to the final table</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-21 07:00:00" d="2019-08-21 08:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Fernando Nation</n>    <k>In 1981, a pudgy 19-year-old Mexican pitcher, Fernando Valenzuela, took the MLB by storm, shattering America's image of the ace pitcher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-21 08:00:00" d="2019-08-21 09:00:00"><n>30 for 30: This is What They Want</n>    <k>A look at the improbable run of Jimmy Connors at the 1991 US Open and how he helped make tennis a high-octane spectator sport. Part of the award-winning 30 for 30 series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-21 09:00:00" d="2019-08-21 21:00:00"><n>Live Badminton World Championships</n>    <k>Action from day three of the 2019 Badminton World Championships in Basel, Switzerland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-21 21:00:00" d="2019-08-21 22:00:00"><n>BT Sport Films: True Grit</n>    <k>With contributions from the sport's biggest names, BT Sport Films offers an extraordinary insight into the mental fortitude required in order to succeed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-21 22:00:00" d="2019-08-22 01:00:00"><n u="UFC: UFC 241: Cormier v Miocic">UFC: UFC 241: Cormier v Miocic 2</n>    <k>Heavyweight champion Daniel Cormier defends his title in a hotly-anticipated rematch against Stipe Miocic at UFC 241. This show may contain flashing images</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-22 01:00:00" d="2019-08-22 01:30:00"><n>UFC: Beyond the Octagon: UFC: Beyond The Octagon Classic Fights</n>    <k>We revisit the headline bout of UFC 193 in Melbourne as the undefeated bantamweight champion Ronda Rousey took on unbeaten challenger Holly Holm</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-22 01:30:00" d="2019-08-22 03:00:00"><n>BT Sport Films: BT Sport Films: The Crazy Gang</n>    <k>The story of Wimbledon FC in the 80s, the notorious win-at-all costs team which rose from non-league obscurity to winning the FA Cup in less than ten years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-22 03:00:00" d="2019-08-22 04:00:00"><n>World Poker Tour Series</n>    <k>With 379 entries, the WPT bestbet Bounty Scramble generated a prize pool of more than $1.7 million. Defending champion Tyler Patterson bids to win back-to-back titles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-22 04:00:00" d="2019-08-22 05:00:00"><n>World Poker Tour Series</n>    <k>Look back at all the action as Sam Panzica, Dickie Malone, Ankush Mandavia and Tyler Patterson square-off for the WPT bestbet Jacksonville Bounty Scramble title</k>  </p>
</a>
