<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="20" t="2020-05-10 04:20:46"><p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-17 06:30:00" d="2020-05-17 07:00:00"><n>Rugby Tonight On Tour</n>    <k>A round-up of the latest news and action from domestic and European rugby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-17 07:00:00" d="2020-05-17 07:30:00"><n>Scottish Football Extra: Scottish Football Extra: From Home</n>    <k>A look at all the key issues and talking points in Scottish football from home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-17 07:30:00" d="2020-05-17 08:30:00"><n>BT Sport FIFA Challenge</n>    <k>Coverage of the BT Sport FIFA Challenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-17 08:30:00" d="2020-05-17 09:30:00"><n>The Football's Not On</n>    <k>Ian Stone presents The Football's Not On looking at the funny side to missing the beautiful game. Guests, songs and pranks will keep spirits up until football returns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-17 09:30:00" d="2020-05-17 11:00:00"><n>Isolation eRacing Series</n>    <k>The biggest names in motorsport go head-to-head in this virtual motor racing series to identify the best simulator driver in motorsport</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-17 11:00:00" d="2020-05-17 15:00:00"><n>Live: MotoGP: The Greatest Years</n>    <k>The BT Sport MotoGP team discuss and debate the sport's greatest years. Each week the team discuss all the best moments from a great season of MotoGP action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-17 15:00:00" d="2020-05-17 15:30:00"><n>Rugby Tonight On Tour</n>    <k>A round-up of the latest news and action from domestic and European rugby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-17 15:30:00" d="2020-05-17 16:30:00"><n>Rugby Today</n>    <k>The BT Sport rugby team discuss the game and look at the domestic and international rugby world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-17 16:30:00" d="2020-05-17 17:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League Magazine</n>    <k>The latest news and updates from the UEFA Champions League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-17 17:00:00" d="2020-05-17 18:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Premier League: Best Goals 2006/07</n>    <k>A look back at the best goals from the 2006/07 season. Chelsea's Didier Drogba topped the scoring charts with 20 goals, ahead of Benni McCarthy (18) and Cristiano Ronaldo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-17 18:00:00" d="2020-05-17 18:30:00"><n>Bundesliga Weekly</n>    <k>All the latest news and information from the Bundesliga</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-17 18:30:00" d="2020-05-17 19:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League: Manchester City v PSG</n>    <k>Manchester City host PSG in the UEFA Champions League quarter-final second-leg at the Etihad. The tie is delicately poised after an enthralling first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-17 19:30:00" d="2020-05-17 20:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League: Man City v Barcelona 2016/17</n>    <k>We revisit the Group C clash between Manchester City and Barcelona. Pep Guardiola's men were aiming to avenge the 4-0 thrashing inflicted by his former</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-17 20:30:00" d="2020-05-17 21:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League: Napoli v Manchester City</n>    <k>We revisit the 2017/18 UEFA Champions League battle between Group F rivals Manchester City and Napoli. City needed just a point to secure a safe passage into the last 16</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-17 21:30:00" d="2020-05-17 22:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Bayern Munich v Man City 2013/14</n>    <k>We revisit the 2013/14 UEFA Champions League group stage clash between Bayern Munich and Manchester City in Berlin. Bayern were on a 10-match Champions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-17 22:00:00" d="2020-05-17 23:00:00"><n>WWE SmackDown Highlights</n>    <k>All the best highlights from the latest episode of WWE Friday Night SmackDown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-17 23:00:00" d="2020-05-18 00:45:00"><n>WWE NXT</n>    <k>All the action from WWE NXT as the next generation of Superstars showcase their talents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-18 00:45:00" d="2020-05-18 01:45:00"><n>WWE Raw Highlights</n>    <k>All the best highlights from the latest WWE Raw</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-18 01:45:00" d="2020-05-18 02:45:00"><n>Rugby Today</n>    <k>The BT Sport rugby team discuss the game and look at the domestic and international rugby world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-18 02:45:00" d="2020-05-18 06:45:00"><n>MotoGP: The Greatest Years</n>    <k>The BT Sport MotoGP team discuss and debate the sport's greatest years. Each week the team discuss all the best moments from a great season of MotoGP action</k>  </p>
</a>
