<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="20" t="2019-07-11 00:18:51"><p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-17 05:00:00" d="2019-07-17 06:00:00"><n>Playback - Football's Greatest Rivalries: The Manchester Derby</n>    <k>The Manchester Derby. A look at some of the best matches between Manchester's bitter footballing rivals. 4/4</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-17 06:00:00" d="2019-07-17 07:00:00"><n>Playback - Football's Greatest Rivalries: The North London Derby</n>    <k>The North London Derby. A look at some of the best matches between bitter rivals Arsenal and Tottenham Hotspur. 2/4</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-17 07:00:00" d="2019-07-17 07:30:00"><n>Irish Rally Review</n>    <k>Highlights of the Donegal International Rally, part of the Irish Rally series. (2/2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-17 07:30:00" d="2019-07-17 09:00:00"><n>International GT Open Championship</n>    <k>Highlights of races one and two from round four of the International GT Open Championship at The Red Bull Ring in Austria</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-17 09:00:00" d="2019-07-17 10:00:00"><n>Fishing: On The Bank</n>    <k>Highlights of the 2018 World Predator Classic hosted by the city of Hellevoetsluis in the Netherlands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-17 10:00:00" d="2019-07-17 11:00:00"><n>Virgin Australia Supercars Championship Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from race 17 of the Virgin Australia Supercars Championship in Townsville</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-17 11:00:00" d="2019-07-17 12:00:00"><n>Virgin Australia Supercars Championship Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from race 18 of the Virgin Australia Supercars Championship in Townsville</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-17 12:00:00" d="2019-07-17 12:30:00"><n>Red Bull Air Race Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from the third round of the Red Bull Air Race Championship at Lake Balaton in Hungary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-17 12:30:00" d="2019-07-17 13:00:00"><n>The Outdoor Sports Show</n>    <k>This exhilarating series captures the best action from extreme sports around the globe, including trail running, triathlon, skiing, snowboarding, climbing and paragliding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-17 13:00:00" d="2019-07-17 21:00:00"><n>Live WTA Tennis: Live WTA Tennis: Bucharest Open</n>    <k>Action from day three of the BRD Bucharest Open in Romania</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-17 21:00:00" d="2019-07-17 21:30:00"><n>Gallagher Premiership Rugby Union: Prem Rugby: Tries of the Season</n>    <k>The pick of the tries from the 2018/19 Gallagher Premiership season. Plus, interviews with Exeter Chiefs duo Henry Slade and Santiago Cordero</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-17 21:30:00" d="2019-07-17 22:00:00"><n>Red Bull Air Race Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from the third round of the Red Bull Air Race Championship at Lake Balaton in Hungary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-17 22:00:00" d="2019-07-18 00:00:00"><n>BT Sport Fight Night: Fight Night: Dubois v Gorman</n>    <k>Daniel Dubois and Nathan Gorman meet for the vacant British heavyweight title at London's O2 Arena. Olympic silver medallist Joe Joyce is also in action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-18 00:00:00" d="2019-07-18 01:00:00"><n>BT Sport Films: BT Sport Films: Cornered</n>    <k>This moving documentary follows the life and career of journeyman boxer Johnny Greaves, veteran of 100 professional fights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-18 01:00:00" d="2019-07-18 01:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Barcelona v Real Madrid 2001/02</n>    <k>We revisit the first leg of the 2001/02 UEFA Champions League semi-final between Barcelona and Real Madrid, who were chasing their first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-18 01:30:00" d="2019-07-18 02:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Feyenoord v Newcastle 2002/03</n>    <k>We revisit the 2001/02 UEFA Champions League group stage tie between Feyenoord and Newcastle in Rotterdam. The Toon had to win to secure a place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-18 02:00:00" d="2019-07-18 02:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Inter Milan v Arsenal 2003/04</n>    <k>A look back at the 2003/04 UEFA Champions League group stage tie between Inter Milan and Arsenal at the San Siro. Inter had thrashed the Gunners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-18 02:30:00" d="2019-07-18 03:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Greatest Premier League Goals</n>    <k>A selection of the best goals from the history of the Premier League. This episode features memorable goals from the 1992/93, 1993/94 and 1994/95 campaigns. 1/8</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-18 03:30:00" d="2019-07-18 04:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Greatest Premier League Goals</n>    <k>A selection of the best goals from the history of the Premier League. This episode features memorable goals from the 1995/96, 1996/97 and 1997/98 campaigns. 2/8</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-07-18 04:30:00" d="2019-07-18 05:30:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Greatest Premier League Goals</n>    <k>A selection of the best goals from the history of the Premier League. This episode features memorable goals from the 1998/99, 1999/00 and 2000/01 campaigns. 3/8</k>  </p>
</a>
