<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-08-15 22:29:39"><p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-20 05:00:00" d="2019-08-20 06:00:00"><n>World Poker Tour Series</n>    <k>The World Poker Tour continues from the storied Bicycle Hotel &amp; Casino in Los Angeles. Headlining the competition is Benjamin Zamani at his second</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-20 06:00:00" d="2019-08-20 07:00:00"><n>World Poker Tour Series</n>    <k>Action from the World Poker Tour in Los Angeles. Just three players remain, with Benjamin Zamani, Pat Lyons, and Upeshka De Silva battling for the $615,346 top prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-20 07:00:00" d="2019-08-20 08:00:00"><n>Bundesliga 2: Osnabruck v Darmstadt</n>    <k>Bundesliga 2 action as last season's 3. Liga winners Osnabruck host Darmstadt at Bremer Brucke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-20 08:00:00" d="2019-08-20 09:00:00"><n>Premier League Review</n>    <k>The best of the recent Premier League action as new boys Sheffield United met Crystal Palace, champions Man City entertained Spurs and Chelsea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-20 09:00:00" d="2019-08-20 21:00:00"><n>Live Badminton World Championships</n>    <k>Action from day two of the 2019 Badminton World Championships in Basel, Switzerland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-20 21:00:00" d="2019-08-20 22:30:00"><n>BT Sport Films: Shoulder to Shoulder</n>    <k>Former Ireland captain Brian O'Driscoll goes on a journey to tell the story of the Irish national rugby team which brings players and fans from two countries together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-20 22:30:00" d="2019-08-20 23:30:00"><n>Rugby Tonight: Rugby Tonight: Best Of</n>    <k>A round-up of all the best interviews, guests, challenges and more from another memorable season of Rugby Tonight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-20 23:30:00" d="2019-08-21 01:00:00"><n>Gallagher Premiership Rugby Union: Exeter Chiefs v Saracens</n>    <k>Look back as Exeter Chiefs took on Saracens in the 2018/19 Gallagher Premiership final at Twickenham. The pair had met in two of the last three finals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-21 01:00:00" d="2019-08-21 01:30:00"><n>Heineken Champions Cup: Story of the Champions Cup 18/19</n>    <k>A look back at the most memorable moments from the 2018/19 campaign as Mark McCall's Saracens beat defending champions Leinster to win their third European</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-21 01:30:00" d="2019-08-21 03:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Broke</n>    <k>More money, more problems. This 30 for 30 documentary digs into the psychology of men whose competitive nature carried them to victory on the field</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-21 03:00:00" d="2019-08-21 04:00:00"><n>World Poker Tour Series</n>    <k>The World Poker Tour continues from Borgata Hotel Casino &amp; Spa with nearly 1,200 entries and a prize pool just shy of $3.8 million. Farid Jattin leads the table</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2019-08-21 04:00:00" d="2019-08-21 05:00:00"><n>World Poker Tour Series</n>    <k>Action from the World Poker Tour in Atlantic City. The players are competing for an $800,000 prize pot, a luxurious Hublot watch and</k>  </p>
</a>
