<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2020-05-17 04:29:54"><p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 05:00:00" d="2020-05-24 05:30:00"><n>The Outdoor Sports Show</n>    <k>This exhilarating series captures the best action from extreme sports around the globe, including trail running, triathlon, skiing, snowboarding, climbing and paragliding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 05:30:00" d="2020-05-24 06:00:00"><n>Inside Sailing</n>    <k>We start in Miami and the 93rd Bacardi Cup, one of the best attended spring sailing events, before travelling to Australia for the 2020 RS:X Windsurfing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 06:00:00" d="2020-05-24 06:30:00"><n>Gearing Up</n>    <k>In this episode we travel to the Iberian Peninsula and to Spain to focus on the third edition of the Hispania Rally, the only European rally to take place in the desert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 06:30:00" d="2020-05-24 07:00:00"><n>Rugby Tonight On Tour</n>    <k>A round-up of the latest news and action from domestic and European rugby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 07:00:00" d="2020-05-24 07:30:00"><n>Badminton Unlimited</n>    <k>Catch up on all the latest news and information from the world of badminton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 07:30:00" d="2020-05-24 08:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League Extra: Champions League Extra: Zidane</n>    <k>A look back on all the best moments of Zinedine Zidane's career from the UEFA Champions League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 08:00:00" d="2020-05-24 08:30:00"><n>Bundesliga Weekly</n>    <k>All the latest news and information from the Bundesliga</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 08:30:00" d="2020-05-24 09:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League Magazine</n>    <k>The latest news and updates from the UEFA Champions League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 09:00:00" d="2020-05-24 09:30:00"><n>UEFA Europa League Magazine</n>    <k>A round-up of all the latest action from the UEFA Europa League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 09:30:00" d="2020-05-24 11:00:00"><n>Isolation eRacing Series</n>    <k>The biggest names in motorsport go head-to-head in this virtual motor racing series to identify the best simulator driver in motorsport</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 11:00:00" d="2020-05-24 15:00:00"><n>Live: MotoGP: The Greatest Years</n>    <k>The BT Sport MotoGP team discuss and debate the sport's greatest years. Each week the team discuss all the best moments from a great season of MotoGP action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 15:00:00" d="2020-05-24 15:30:00"><n>Rugby Tonight On Tour</n>    <k>A round-up of the latest news and action from domestic and European rugby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 15:30:00" d="2020-05-24 16:30:00"><n>Rugby Today</n>    <k>The BT Sport rugby team discuss the game and look at the domestic and international rugby world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 16:30:00" d="2020-05-24 17:00:00"><n>UEFA Europa League Magazine</n>    <k>A round-up of all the latest action from the UEFA Europa League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 17:00:00" d="2020-05-24 18:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Premier League: Best Goals 2003/04</n>    <k>A look back at the best goals from the 2003/04 season. Thierry Henry top-scored with 30 goals as Arsenal became the first side to finish a league campaign</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 18:00:00" d="2020-05-24 19:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Premier League: Best Goals 2002/03</n>    <k>A look back at the top goals from the 2002/03 season. Ruud van Nistelrooy hit the back of the net 25 times in total, pipping Thierry Henry to the Golden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 19:00:00" d="2020-05-24 20:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Premier League: Best Goals 2001/02</n>    <k>We revisit the top goals from the 2001/02 season. Thierry Henry won the Golden Boot with 24 goals, ahead of Jimmy Floyd Hasselbaink, Ruud van Nistelrooy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 20:00:00" d="2020-05-24 20:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Rangers v PSV Eindhoven 1999/00</n>    <k>We revisit the 1999/00 group stage tie between Dick Advocaat's Rangers and PSV at Ibrox. Spearheaded by Ruud van Nistelrooy, the visitors arrived unbeaten</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 20:30:00" d="2020-05-24 21:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Lyon v Rangers 2007/08</n>    <k>We revisit the 2007/08 UEFA Champions League group stage tie between Lyon and Rangers at the Stade Gerland. Rangers faced a tough group that also featured</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 21:00:00" d="2020-05-24 21:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Leeds v Rangers 1992/93</n>    <k>We revisit the second leg of the 1992/93 UEFA Champions League 'Battle of Britain' second round tie between Leeds United and Rangers at Elland Road</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 21:30:00" d="2020-05-24 22:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Rangers v Porto 2005/06</n>    <k>We revisit this 2005/06 UEFA Champions League group stage epic at Ibrox between Rangers and 2004 champions Porto. A tough group also included Inter Milan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 22:00:00" d="2020-05-24 23:00:00"><n>WWE Ruthless Aggression: WWE Ruthless Aggression: Evolution</n>    <k>As The Ruthless Aggression Era dawned, Triple H pushed forward the Evolution of sports-entertainment with Ric Flair, Randy Orton &amp; Batista</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-24 23:00:00" d="2020-05-25 00:00:00"><n>WWE Ruthless Aggression</n>    <k>Seeking 'The Next Big Thing,' WWE finds Brock Lesnar. He becomes an in-ring monster - and a master of Ruthless Aggression behind the scenes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-25 00:00:00" d="2020-05-25 01:00:00"><n>WWE SmackDown Highlights</n>    <k>All the best highlights from the latest episode of WWE Friday Night SmackDown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-25 01:00:00" d="2020-05-25 01:45:00"><n>WWE NXT</n>    <k>All the action from WWE NXT as the next generation of Superstars showcase their talents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-25 01:45:00" d="2020-05-25 02:45:00"><n>Rugby Today</n>    <k>The BT Sport rugby team discuss the game and look at the domestic and international rugby world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1084" o="2020-05-25 02:45:00" d="2020-05-25 06:45:00"><n>MotoGP: The Greatest Years</n>    <k>The BT Sport MotoGP team discuss and debate the sport's greatest years. Each week the team discuss all the best moments from a great season of MotoGP action</k>  </p>
</a>
