<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-05-12 04:30:25"><p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-19 05:00:00" d="2020-05-19 06:30:00"><n>30 for 30: I Hate Christian Laettner</n>    <k>Basketball player Christian Laettner helped Duke win two national titles in four trips to the Final Four. So why is he intensely disliked by so many? Part of the 30 for 30 series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-19 06:30:00" d="2020-05-19 07:00:00"><n>Premier League World</n>    <k>A special look into the career of former Liverpool star, John Arne Riise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-19 07:00:00" d="2020-05-19 07:30:00"><n>BT Sport Goals Reload</n>    <k>A round-up of the greatest goals from around the world, including action from Ligue 1 and the Bundesliga</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-19 07:30:00" d="2020-05-19 08:30:00"><n>Men's FIH Olympic Qualifiers: Men's Hockey: GBR v MYS 2019</n>    <k>Action from the Men's FIH Olympic Qualifiers as Great Britain meet Malaysia at Lee Valley in London back in October 2019</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-19 08:30:00" d="2020-05-19 11:00:00"><n>Gallagher Premiership Rugby Highlights</n>    <k>All the best action from the opening weekend of the Gallagher Premiership, including Saracens v Northampton Saints, Exeter Chiefs v Harlequins and Sale v Gloucester</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-19 11:00:00" d="2020-05-19 12:00:00"><n>V8 Supercars Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from the Virgin Australia Supercars Championship race 26 on the Gold Coast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-19 12:00:00" d="2020-05-19 13:00:00"><n>Irish Rally Review</n>    <k>Highlights from the Killarney Historic Rally, part of the Irish Rally series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-19 13:00:00" d="2020-05-19 14:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Phi Slama Jama</n>    <k>This 30 for 30 documentary chronicles the success of the 'Phi Slama Jama' Houston Cougars basketball team of the 1980s, when they reached three consecutive NCAA Final Fours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-19 14:30:00" d="2020-05-19 15:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Nixon's National Champs</n>    <k>ESPN Films takes a look into the story of how the 1969 college football national champion was crowned by President Richard Nixon and the drama that surrounded it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-19 15:00:00" d="2020-05-19 16:30:00"><n>30 for 30: ESPN Films: Elevate</n>    <k>ESPN Films follows the high-stakes journey of four young men from Africa who follow their dream of making it in the NBA from the SEEDS Academy in Dakar, Senegal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-19 16:30:00" d="2020-05-19 18:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: This Magic Moment</n>    <k>In the 1990s, the Orlando Magic, Shaquille O'Neal and Penny Hardaway were the talk of the NBA. This 30 for 30 documentary explores how this remarkable</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-19 18:30:00" d="2020-05-19 20:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Brothers in Exile</n>    <k>The incredible story of half-brothers Livan and Orlando Hernandez, both of whom risked their lives to leave Cuba and become baseball stars in the US</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-19 20:00:00" d="2020-05-19 20:30:00"><n>In Depth with Graham Bensinger</n>    <k>In this episode Graham sits down with former Man Utd and Everton goalkeeper Tim Howard. The stopper talks about his life with tourettes and his time playing in England</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-19 20:30:00" d="2020-05-19 21:00:00"><n>BT Sport Films Shorts: State of Play: Sam Allardyce</n>    <k>A unique insight into the game by those who play it, coach it, shape it and cherish it. Sam Allardyce discusses the strains of life under the lens with Michael Calvin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-19 21:00:00" d="2020-05-19 23:00:00"><n>Live: Champions League Throwback: Live: UCL Battles of Britain</n>    <k>A look back at the Champions League Battles of Britain. Relive all the drama and excitement from Liverpool v Arsenal (2008) and Man City v Liverpool (2018)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-19 23:00:00" d="2020-05-20 00:00:00"><n>BT Sport Films: Golazzo: The Football Italia Story</n>    <k>This BT Sport Films documentary, presented by James Richardson, explores the surge in popularity Italian football enjoyed in the UK in the years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-20 00:00:00" d="2020-05-20 01:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Benji</n>    <k>In 1984, 17-year-old Ben Wilson was America's most talented basketball prospect until the sweet-natured boy was senselessly murdered</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-20 01:30:00" d="2020-05-20 02:00:00"><n>In Depth with Graham Bensinger</n>    <k>Graham sits down with skateboarding legend Tony Hawk, discuss skating as a future Olympic sport, video game successes, obsessing over and accomplishing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-20 02:00:00" d="2020-05-20 03:30:00"><n>30 for 30: ESPN Films: The Announcement</n>    <k>NBA All-Star Magic Johnson narrates this powerful and moving documentary centered around his announcement in 1991 that he was HIV-positive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-20 03:30:00" d="2020-05-20 04:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Hit It Hard</n>    <k>This documentary explores the career and subsequent struggles of ex-golfer John Daly, who shocked the world by winning the PGA Championship in 1991</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-20 04:30:00" d="2020-05-20 06:30:00"><n>30 for 30: The Gospel According to Mac</n>    <k>This 30 for 30 documentary examines Bill McCartney and his sometimes-controversial mixture of American football and evangelicalism as Colorado Buffaloes</k>  </p>
</a>
