<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2020-05-13 04:30:28"><p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-20 06:30:00" d="2020-05-20 07:00:00"><n>Premier League World</n>    <k>In this week's episode Declan Rice and Mason Mount join us to discuss their friendship, we visit a Manchester United fan in Kenya and Shinji Okazaki tallks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-20 07:00:00" d="2020-05-20 07:30:00"><n>BT Sport Goals Reload</n>    <k>A round-up of the greatest goals from around the world, including action from Ligue 1 and the Bundesliga</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-20 07:30:00" d="2020-05-20 08:30:00"><n>Women's FIH Olympic Qualifiers: Women's Hockey: GBR v CHL 2019</n>    <k>Action from the Women's FIH Olympic Qualifiers as Great Britain face Chile at Lee Valley in London in 2019</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-20 08:30:00" d="2020-05-20 11:00:00"><n>Gallagher Premiership Rugby Highlights</n>    <k>All the best action from the latest fixtures in the Gallagher Premiership, including Bath v Exeter, Northampton v Worcester, Harlequins v Bristol</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-20 11:00:00" d="2020-05-20 12:00:00"><n>V8 Supercars Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from the Virgin Australia Supercars Championship race 27 on the Gold Coast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-20 12:00:00" d="2020-05-20 13:00:00"><n>V8 Supercars Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from race 28 of the Virgin Australia Supercars Championship from the Sandown 500</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-20 13:00:00" d="2020-05-20 14:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Silly Little Game</n>    <k>Fantasy sports is a $4 billion industry, but for all of its success, the story of the game's inception is little known. Part of the award-winning 30 for 30 series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-20 14:00:00" d="2020-05-20 15:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Of Miracles &amp; Men</n>    <k>The 'miracle' win of the 1980 US men's Olympic hockey team had a flip side: the devastating impact that game had on the Russian coaches and players</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-20 15:30:00" d="2020-05-20 16:30:00"><n>Nine for IX: Pat XO</n>    <k>This documentary tells the remarkable story of the late Pat Summitt, ex-women's college basketball head coach, as it has never been told before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-20 16:30:00" d="2020-05-20 18:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Sole Man</n>    <k>This 30 for 30 documentary examines how Sonny Vaccaro rose from Pennsylvania steel town roots to become one of the most powerful and influential men in basketball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-20 18:00:00" d="2020-05-20 19:30:00"><n>30 for 30: Winning Time: Reggie Miller vs The NY Knicks</n>    <k>Part of the award-winning 30 for 30 series, this documentary looks at how NBA legend Reggie Miller became an enemy to New York Knicks fans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-20 19:30:00" d="2020-05-20 21:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30 When the Garden Was Eden</n>    <k>This 30 for 30 documentary chronicles the glory years of the New York Knicks, when they made the NBA Finals in three out of four seasons, winning two titles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-20 21:00:00" d="2020-05-20 23:00:00"><n>Live: Champions League Throwback: Live: UCL Battles of Britain</n>    <k>A look back at the Champions League Battles of Britain. Relive all the drama and excitement from Man Utd v Chelsea (2008) and Arsenal v Man Utd (2009)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-20 23:00:00" d="2020-05-21 00:15:00"><n>Iron Men</n>    <k>Go behind the scenes with the fans of West Ham United as they move to a new home after 112 years at Upton Park. Featuring Slaven Bilic, Mark Noble Mabel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-21 00:15:00" d="2020-05-21 00:30:00"><n>BT Sport Films Shorts: State of Play: Dawn Astle</n>    <k>BT Sport Films Shorts is a series of documentaries offering insight into why sport matters to elite sportsmen and women and fans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-21 00:30:00" d="2020-05-21 02:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Chasing Tyson</n>    <k>This documentary chronicles boxing's long-awaited first meeting of Mike Tyson and Evander Holyfield in 1996, and the rematch seven months later</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-21 02:00:00" d="2020-05-21 03:00:00"><n>30 for 30: ESPN Films: Charismatic</n>    <k>This documentary tells the story of the 1999 miracle that was Charismatic, a horse that emerged from nowhere to win the first two races in the Triple Crown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-21 03:00:00" d="2020-05-21 04:00:00"><n>Nine for IX: No Limits</n>    <k>This documentary tells the dark fate of open-water free diver Audrey Mestre. Part of ESPN's Nine for IX series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-21 04:00:00" d="2020-05-21 05:30:00"><n>30 for 30: No Crossover: The Trial of Allen Iverson</n>    <k>In 1993, Allen Iverson went bowling in Hampton. What followed ended with the teen in jail and divided a city along racial lines. Part of the acclaimed 30 for 30 series</k>  </p>
</a>
