<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-05-10 04:20:46"><p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-17 06:30:00" d="2020-05-17 07:00:00"><n>Premier League World</n>    <k>This week we talk to former Nottingham Forest man Lars Bohinen about his time in England and how he moved into management in Norway</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-17 07:00:00" d="2020-05-17 08:00:00"><n>Fishing: On The Bank</n>    <k>Monster Carp are Robs target in Italy, whilst Andy looks at tips and tactics for small water trout fishing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-17 08:00:00" d="2020-05-17 09:00:00"><n>Fishing: On The Bank</n>    <k>A big carp special as Rob and England International Carper Ryan Need catch the biggest carp ever caught for tv in the UK, a monster of over 60lbs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-17 09:00:00" d="2020-05-17 09:30:00"><n>Spirit of Yachting</n>    <k>Series capturing the unique lifestyle, adventure and excitement that surround the world of professional sailing, including action from the Rolex Middle Sea Race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-17 09:30:00" d="2020-05-17 10:00:00"><n>Spirit of Yachting</n>    <k>Take a look at the unique lifestyle, adventure and excitement that surrounds the Rolex Sydney Hobart Yacht Race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-17 10:00:00" d="2020-05-17 11:00:00"><n>WWE Raw Highlights</n>    <k>All the best highlights from the latest WWE Raw</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-17 11:00:00" d="2020-05-17 12:00:00"><n>WWE NXT Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from the latest episode of WWE NXT</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-17 12:00:00" d="2020-05-17 13:30:00"><n>Gallagher Premiership Rugby Union: Exeter C v Northampton S 2019/20</n>    <k>Exeter Chiefs and Northampton Saints are in Gallagher Premiership Rugby action as they meet at Sandy Park. The Chiefs have lost just one of their last six in the league</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-17 13:30:00" d="2020-05-17 15:00:00"><n>Gallagher Premiership Rugby Union: Harlequins v Exeter Chiefs 2019/20</n>    <k>Harlequins take on table-toppers Exeter Chiefs in the Gallagher Premiership Rugby at Twickenham Stoop. Harlequins stormed to victory earlier this month</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-17 15:00:00" d="2020-05-17 15:30:00"><n>In Depth with Graham Bensinger</n>    <k>Graham sits down with tennis star Caroline Wozniacki. Wozniacki shares stories about everything from her rise to a No. 1 ranking to her desire to settle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-17 15:30:00" d="2020-05-17 17:00:00"><n>WWE Friday Night SmackDown</n>    <k>See all your favourite WWE SmackDown Superstars deliver edge-of-your-seat action, including Roman Reigns, Sasha Banks, `The Fiend' Bray Wyatt and Brock Lesnar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-17 17:00:00" d="2020-05-17 18:00:00"><n>Backstory: Banned for Life</n>    <k>The legacy of Major League Baseball's punishments of 'Shoeless' Joe Jackson and Pete Rose is examined in the thought-provoking and revelatory second</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-17 18:00:00" d="2020-05-17 19:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Believeland</n>    <k>This 30 for 30 documentary chronicles the struggles of Cleveland's major sports franchises over the past 50 years and its impact on the psyche of a typical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-17 19:30:00" d="2020-05-17 20:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Four Days in October</n>    <k>The Yankees were leading the Red Sox in the ALCS 3-0 back in 2004, a deficit no team had overcome. The Red Sox defied the inevitable</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-17 20:30:00" d="2020-05-17 22:00:00"><n>BT Sport Films: Shoulder to Shoulder</n>    <k>Former Ireland captain Brian O'Driscoll goes on a journey to tell the story of the Irish national rugby team which brings players and fans from two countries together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-17 22:00:00" d="2020-05-17 23:30:00"><n>Cricket Documentaries: Cricket's Greatest Blunders and Wonders</n>    <k>. Wonders. From captains to commentators, and questionable coin tosses to under arm deliveries, we'll look at some of the strangest situations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-17 23:30:00" d="2020-05-18 01:00:00"><n>Cricket Documentaries: Cricket: Captains Courageous</n>    <k>An in-depth look at some of cricket's most successful captains to tour on Australian soil</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-18 01:00:00" d="2020-05-18 01:30:00"><n>BT Sport Films Shorts: State of Play: Sam Allardyce</n>    <k>A unique insight into the game by those who play it, coach it, shape it and cherish it. Sam Allardyce discusses the strains of life under the lens with Michael Calvin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-18 01:30:00" d="2020-05-18 02:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Jordan Rides the Bus</n>    <k>Part of the acclaimed 30 for 30 series, this documentary examines why Michael Jordan quit basketball for baseball, despite being in his prime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-18 02:30:00" d="2020-05-18 04:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Once Brothers</n>    <k>Vlade Divac and Drazen Petrovic were NBA players who were friends from Yugoslavia. Their friendship ended before Petrovic was killed in a car crash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-18 04:00:00" d="2020-05-18 05:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: What Carter Lost</n>    <k>In 1988, a Texas high school fielded the football team that many consider the greatest ever, yet it's likely you have never heard their story</k>  </p>
</a>
