<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="30" t="2019-08-13 01:58:42"><p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 05:00:00" d="2019-08-19 06:00:00"><n>30 for 30: The Legend of Jimmy the Greek</n>    <k>Part of the award-winning 30 for 30 series, this documentary follows the career of Jimmy Synder, a professional gambler who helped legitimise betting in NFL games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 06:00:00" d="2019-08-19 07:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Jordan Rides the Bus</n>    <k>Part of the acclaimed 30 for 30 series, this documentary examines why Michael Jordan quit basketball for baseball, despite being in his prime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 07:00:00" d="2019-08-19 07:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Borussia Dortmund v Juventus: 1996/97 Final</n>    <k>We revisit the 1996/97 UEFA Champions League final between Borussia Dortmund and Juventus in Munich. Armed with an expensively assembled squad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 07:30:00" d="2019-08-19 08:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Real Madrid v Bayer Leverkusen 2001/02</n>    <k>The 2001/02 UEFA Champions League final saw a star-studded Real Madrid face Bayer Leverkusen in Glasgow. The match featured arguably the greatest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 08:00:00" d="2019-08-19 08:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Arsenal v Chelsea 2003/04</n>    <k>A look back at the second leg of the 2003/04 UEFA Champions League quarter-final between Arsenal and Chelsea at Highbury. The visitors had not beaten</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 08:30:00" d="2019-08-19 09:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Deportivo v AC Milan 2003/04</n>    <k>We revisit the second leg of the 2003/04 UEFA Champions League quarter-final between Deportivo La Coruna and AC Milan at the Riazor Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 09:00:00" d="2019-08-19 09:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Rangers v Porto 2005/06</n>    <k>We revisit this 2005/06 UEFA Champions League group stage epic at Ibrox between Rangers and 2004 champions Porto. A tough group also included Inter Milan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 09:30:00" d="2019-08-19 10:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Bayern Munich v Inter Milan 2009/10</n>    <k>We revisit the 2010 final between Bayern Munich and Inter Milan at the Bernabeu. Inter boss Jose Mourinho was looking to become the third man in history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 10:00:00" d="2019-08-19 10:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Celtic v AC Milan 2007/08</n>    <k>We revisit a dramatic night in Glasgow as Celtic hosted AC Milan in the 2007/08 UEFA Champions League group stage. Celtic were chasing their first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 10:30:00" d="2019-08-19 11:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Tottenham v Inter Milan 2010/11</n>    <k>A look back at the 2010/11 UEFA Champions League group stage clash between Tottenham Hotspur and Inter Milan at White Hart Lane as Gareth Bale announced</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 11:00:00" d="2019-08-19 11:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Celtic v Barcelona 2012/13</n>    <k>A look back at another dramatic European night in Glasgow as Neil Lennon's Celtic took on Spanish giants Barcelona in the group stages of the 2012/13</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 11:30:00" d="2019-08-19 12:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Man Utd v Real Madrid 2012/13</n>    <k>Cristiano Ronaldo made an emotional return to Manchester for the second leg of this last 16 tie from the 2012/13 UEFA Champions League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 12:00:00" d="2019-08-19 12:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Bayern Munich v Man City 2013/14</n>    <k>We revisit the 2013/14 UEFA Champions League group stage clash between Bayern Munich and Manchester City in Berlin. Bayern were on a 10-match Champions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 12:30:00" d="2019-08-19 13:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Juventus v Barcelona 2014/15</n>    <k>We revisit the enthralling 2014/15 UEFA Champions League final between Juventus and Barcelona in Berlin. Barcelona were chasing their third Champions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 13:00:00" d="2019-08-19 14:00:00"><n>BT Sport Films: BT Sport Films: O Arise, All You Sons</n>    <k>The tale of how cricket united one of the most dangerous, disparate and poverty stricken countries on Earth and gave the people of Papua New Guinea purpose and identity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 14:00:00" d="2019-08-19 16:00:00"><n>WTA Tennis: WTA Tennis: Cincinnati</n>    <k>Coverage of the final from the Western &amp; Southern Open in Cincinnati</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 16:00:00" d="2019-08-19 16:30:00"><n>Irish Rally Review</n>    <k>Highlights of the Cork Forest National Championship, part of the Irish Rally series. 2/2</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 16:30:00" d="2019-08-19 17:00:00"><n>The Outdoor Sports Show</n>    <k>This exhilarating series captures the best action from extreme sports around the globe, including trail running, triathlon, skiing, snowboarding, climbing and paragliding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 17:00:00" d="2019-08-19 17:30:00"><n>GC32 Racing Tour Sailing</n>    <k>Action from the GC32 Racing Tour, a European yacht racing circuit sailed in state of the art foiling catamarans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 17:30:00" d="2019-08-19 18:30:00"><n>Vanarama National League: Barrow v Yeovil Town</n>    <k>Barrow take on Yeovil Town in the Vanarama National League at the Progression Solicitors Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 18:30:00" d="2019-08-19 19:30:00"><n>30 for 30: Little Big Men</n>    <k>Part of the award-winning 30 for 30 series, this documentary focuses on the 1982 Little League baseball champions from Kirkland, Washington</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 19:30:00" d="2019-08-19 21:30:00"><n>WTA Tennis: WTA Tennis: Cincinnati</n>    <k>Coverage of the final from the Western &amp; Southern Open in Cincinnati</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 21:30:00" d="2019-08-19 22:00:00"><n>The WRC Magazine</n>    <k>The latest news and action from the FIA World Rally Championship, plus a look ahead to the next round in Germany</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 22:00:00" d="2019-08-19 23:00:00"><n>Fishing: On The Bank: Fishing: On The Bank - 2019</n>    <k>Angling magazine show presented by Rob Hughes and Andy Ford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 23:00:00" d="2019-08-19 23:30:00"><n>EnduroGP: EnduroGP: Spain</n>    <k>The best of the action from the third round of the EnduroGP season in Santiago de Compostela, Spain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-19 23:30:00" d="2019-08-20 02:30:00"><n u="UFC: UFC 241: Cormier v Miocic">UFC: UFC 241: Cormier v Miocic 2</n>    <k>Heavyweight champion Daniel Cormier defends his title in a hotly-anticipated rematch against Stipe Miocic at UFC 241. This show may contain flashing images</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 02:30:00" d="2019-08-20 03:00:00"><n>BT Sport Goals Reload</n>    <k>A round-up of the greatest goals from around the world, including action from Ligue 1 and the Bundesliga</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 03:00:00" d="2019-08-20 03:30:00"><n>The WRC Magazine</n>    <k>The latest news and action from the FIA World Rally Championship, plus a look ahead to the next round in Germany</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 03:30:00" d="2019-08-20 04:30:00"><n>Fishing: On The Bank: Fishing: On The Bank - 2019</n>    <k>Angling magazine show presented by Rob Hughes and Andy Ford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 04:30:00" d="2019-08-20 05:30:00"><n>30 for 30: The Birth of Big Air</n>    <k>This documentary, part of the acclaimed 30 for 30 series, profiles BMX star Mat Hoffman, a trailblazing biker who went pro at just 16 and helped build</k>  </p>
</a>
