<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-04-12 04:26:56"><p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-19 05:00:00" d="2020-04-19 06:00:00"><n>30 for 30: The Day the Series Stopped</n>    <k>The 1989 World Series saw the A's sweep the Giants. But that's not what people remember after a 6.9 earthquake brought death and destruction. Part of the 30 for 30 series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-19 06:00:00" d="2020-04-19 07:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Four Days in October</n>    <k>The Yankees were leading the Red Sox in the ALCS 3-0 back in 2004, a deficit no team had overcome. The Red Sox defied the inevitable</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-19 07:00:00" d="2020-04-19 07:30:00"><n>Spirit of Yachting</n>    <k>A series capturing the unique lifestyle, adventure and excitement that surround the world of professional sailing, including action from the Rolex TP52 World Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-19 07:30:00" d="2020-04-19 08:00:00"><n>Spirit of Yachting</n>    <k>A series capturing the unique lifestyle, adventure and excitement that surround the world of professional sailing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-19 08:00:00" d="2020-04-19 09:00:00"><n>Fishing: On The Bank: Fishing: On The Bank - 2019</n>    <k>Highlights from the 2019 British Carp Angling Championships</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-19 09:00:00" d="2020-04-19 10:00:00"><n>Fishing: On The Bank: Fishing: On The Bank - 2019</n>    <k>All the best action from the 2019 Parkdean Masters held at the White Acres complex in Cornwall</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-19 10:00:00" d="2020-04-19 11:00:00"><n>WWE Raw Highlights</n>    <k>All the best highlights from the latest WWE Raw</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-19 11:00:00" d="2020-04-19 12:00:00"><n>WWE NXT Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from the latest episode of WWE NXT</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-19 12:00:00" d="2020-04-19 13:00:00"><n>Barclays FA Women's Super League: Birmingham LFC v Chelsea W</n>    <k>Your chance to relive Chelsea Women's 6-0 demolition of Birmingham City Ladies in the 2019/20 Barclay's FA Women's Super League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-19 13:00:00" d="2020-04-19 14:00:00"><n>UEFA Women's Champions League: Lyon Women v Barcelona Women</n>    <k>Look back as Lyon Women met Barcelona Women in the 2018/19 UEFA Women's Champions League final in Budapest, Hungary. Lyon hoped to lift the trophy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-19 14:00:00" d="2020-04-19 15:00:00"><n>The Action Woman Show: Action Woman of the Year Awards</n>    <k>Coverage of the 2019 Action Woman of the Year Awards, celebrating the most spectacular sporting performances by British women over the past year</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-19 15:00:00" d="2020-04-19 15:30:00"><n>Badminton Unlimited</n>    <k>Catch up on all the latest news and information from the world of badminton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-19 15:30:00" d="2020-04-19 17:00:00"><n>WWE Friday Night SmackDown</n>    <k>See all your favourite WWE SmackDown Superstars deliver edge-of-your-seat action, including Roman Reigns, Sasha Banks, `The Fiend' Bray Wyatt and Brock Lesnar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-19 17:00:00" d="2020-04-19 19:00:00"><n>30 for 30: ESPN Films: Fab Five</n>    <k>This film chronicles the recruitment, notorious time-out fiasco and cultural impact of the 1990s Michigan Wolverines men's basketball players known</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-19 19:00:00" d="2020-04-19 21:00:00"><n>30 for 30: SMU Pony Exce$$</n>    <k>SMU's American football team received the NCAA's 'death penalty' in 1987 because of corruption and greed, stripping a community of its identity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-19 21:00:00" d="2020-04-19 22:00:00"><n>ESPN Films: The Little Master</n>    <k>The tale of how India's Sachin Tendulkar achieved legendary status as one of the finest batsmen in cricket's history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-19 22:00:00" d="2020-04-19 23:30:00"><n>BT Sport Films: BT Sport Films: State of Play</n>    <k>This BT Sport Film looks at the strengths and flaws of the modern game from the perspective of players, managers, clubs and society. Featuring Gareth Bale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-19 23:30:00" d="2020-04-20 01:00:00"><n>30 for 30: The Year of the Scab</n>    <k>This documentary, part of the acclaimed 30 for 30 series, details the incredible tale of the Washington Redskins' replacement team that played during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-20 01:00:00" d="2020-04-20 02:30:00"><n>30 for 30: ESPN Films: Baltimore Boys</n>    <k>ESPN Films looks at the untold story of one of the greatest high school basketball teams ever, Dunbar High School in Baltimore, and the tumultuous times</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-20 02:30:00" d="2020-04-20 04:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Benji</n>    <k>In 1984, 17-year-old Ben Wilson was America's most talented basketball prospect until the sweet-natured boy was senselessly murdered</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-20 04:00:00" d="2020-04-20 05:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Bernie and Ernie</n>    <k>This documentary, part of the 30 for 30 series, tells the story of a pair of New Yorkers who went to Tennessee and formed one of college basketball's</k>  </p>
</a>
