<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-05-27 04:31:22"><p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-03 06:00:00" d="2020-06-03 06:15:00"><n>30 for 30 Shorts: Collision Course: The Murder of Don Aronow</n>    <k>Director Billy Corben recounts the rarely told fast life of Don Aronow, one of the world's most intriguing adventurers and explorers. A 30 for 30 Shorts documentary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-03 06:15:00" d="2020-06-03 06:30:00"><n>30 for 30 Shorts: 30 for 30 Shorts: Every Day</n>    <k>This 30 for 30 Shorts documentary looks at the stunning story of Joy Johnson who took up running at the age of 59 and went on to run 25 New York City Marathons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-03 06:30:00" d="2020-06-03 07:00:00"><n>Premier League World</n>    <k>Liverpool club legend John Barnes discusses his memories of the last Liverpool title winning side and shares his thoughts on Jurgen Klopps' red revolution</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-03 07:00:00" d="2020-06-03 07:30:00"><n>BT Sport Goals Reload</n>    <k>The greatest goals from around the world this week, including Thorgan Hazard's strike for Dortmund against Gladbach, and Ross Barkley's goal against</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-03 07:30:00" d="2020-06-03 08:30:00"><n>FIM Speedway Highlights</n>    <k>All the thrills and spills from round three of the 2019 FIM Speedway Grand Prix in Prague, Czech Republic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-03 08:30:00" d="2020-06-03 11:00:00"><n>Gallagher Premiership Rugby Highlights</n>    <k>The best of the action from round 12 of the Gallagher Premiership, including Northampton Saints v Saracens, Harlequins v Exeter Chiefs and Leicester Tigers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-03 11:00:00" d="2020-06-03 12:00:00"><n>World Rallycross Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from the third round of the 2019 FIA World Rallycross Championship in Spa, Belgium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-03 12:00:00" d="2020-06-03 13:00:00"><n>Sailing World Cup</n>    <k>Highlights from round three of the 2019 Sailing World Cup in Genoa, Italy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-03 13:00:00" d="2020-06-03 14:00:00"><n>SEC Storied: Miracles on the Plains</n>    <k>This moving documentary takes a look at the fabled 2013 Auburn Tigers' college football season. Part of ESPN's SEC Storied series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-03 14:00:00" d="2020-06-03 16:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: One and Not Done</n>    <k>Who is John Calipari? To his fans, he is one of college basketball's greatest coaches. To his critics, he represents everything wrong with college sports</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-03 16:00:00" d="2020-06-03 18:00:00"><n>30 for 30: It's Not Crazy, It's Sports</n>    <k>ESPN Films explore the inspiring, dramatic and unexpected things in sports that capture the experience of being a fan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-03 18:00:00" d="2020-06-03 19:00:00"><n>WWE SmackDown Highlights</n>    <k>All the best highlights from the latest episode of WWE Friday Night SmackDown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-03 19:00:00" d="2020-06-03 20:00:00"><n>WWE Raw Highlights</n>    <k>All the best highlights from the latest WWE Raw</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-03 20:00:00" d="2020-06-03 21:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: The Two Bills</n>    <k>The story of a turbulent relationship between legendary NFL coaches Bill Parcells and Bill Belichick. From their successes to their dramatic split</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-03 21:30:00" d="2020-06-03 21:45:00"><n>30 for 30 Shorts: Arnold's Blueprint</n>    <k>This 30 for 30 Shorts documentary reveals how Arnold Schwarzenegger's mandatory military service in the Austrian Army played a critical role in his journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-03 21:45:00" d="2020-06-03 22:00:00"><n>30 for 30 Shorts: Arthur &amp; Johnnie</n>    <k>In this exclusive first person account, Johnnie Ashe relays a previously unknown chapter of his brother Arthur's legacy. Part of the 30 for 30 Short series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-03 22:00:00" d="2020-06-03 23:00:00"><n>BT Sport Films: BT Sport Films: Cornered</n>    <k>This moving documentary follows the life and career of journeyman boxer Johnny Greaves, veteran of 100 professional fights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-03 23:00:00" d="2020-06-04 00:00:00"><n>WWE NXT UK</n>    <k>All the action from WWE NXT UK as the next generation of Superstars showcase their talents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-04 00:00:00" d="2020-06-04 01:00:00"><n>WWE NXT Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from the latest episode of WWE NXT</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-04 01:00:00" d="2020-06-04 02:30:00"><n>30 for 30: ESPN Films: The Marinovich Project</n>    <k>This documentary tells the story of Todd Marinovich, raised with the purpose of creating the perfect athlete. Documenting his ascent to stardom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-04 02:30:00" d="2020-06-04 03:00:00"><n>30 for 30 Shorts: 30 for 30 Shorts: Mack Wrestles</n>    <k>A look behind the scenes as Mack Beggs, a gifted athlete from Euless, Texas, struggles against the outside forces that stigmatize transgender athletes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-04 03:00:00" d="2020-06-04 05:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Rodman: For Better or Worse</n>    <k>This documentary chronicles the unforgettable and at times unbelievable story of one of the most unpredictable stars in sports history, Dennis Rodman</k>  </p>
</a>
