<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-04-15 04:27:42"><p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-22 05:00:00" d="2020-04-22 06:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Mike and the Mad Dog</n>    <k>A look at the rise of sports talk radio pioneers Mike Francesca and Chris 'Mad Dog' Russo and how they ruled American radio for nearly two decades</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-22 06:00:00" d="2020-04-22 06:30:00"><n>Premier League World</n>    <k>This week we take a trip down memory lane with Wes Brown. We also speak to Watford boss Nigel Pearson, and West Ham's Felipe Anderson speaks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-22 06:30:00" d="2020-04-22 07:00:00"><n>Premier League World</n>    <k>On this week's episode, former Stoke City, Crystal Palace and West Brom manager Tony Pulis opens up on his journey into management and how he dealt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-22 07:00:00" d="2020-04-22 07:30:00"><n>BT Sport Goals Reload</n>    <k>A round-up of the greatest goals from around the world, including action from Ligue 1 and the Bundesliga</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-22 07:30:00" d="2020-04-22 08:30:00"><n>MotoGP: Moto3: Grand Prix of Malaysia</n>    <k>Coverage of the Moto3 race from the Grand Prix of Malaysia, round 18 of the 2019 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-22 08:30:00" d="2020-04-22 09:30:00"><n>MotoGP: Moto2: Grand Prix of Malaysia</n>    <k>Coverage of the Moto2 race from the Grand Prix of Malaysia, round 18 of the 2019 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-22 09:30:00" d="2020-04-22 10:30:00"><n>MotoGP: MotoGP: Grand Prix of Malaysia</n>    <k>Coverage of the MotoGP race from the Grand Prix of Malaysia, round 18 of the 2019 season. Marc Marquez was narrowly edged out by teammate Maverick Vinales in this tight race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-22 10:30:00" d="2020-04-22 11:30:00"><n>FIM Speedway Highlights</n>    <k>All the best action from round six of the FIM Speedway Grand Prix season from Teterow, Germany</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-22 11:30:00" d="2020-04-22 12:30:00"><n>Heineken Champions Cup Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from the Heineken Champions Cup, including Bath v Clermont Auvergne, Munster v Saracens, Ulster v Harlequins and La Rochelle v Glasgow Warriors</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-22 12:30:00" d="2020-04-22 13:00:00"><n>BT Sport Reload</n>    <k>The best bits from BT Sport from the last week, exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-22 13:00:00" d="2020-04-22 14:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Fernando Nation</n>    <k>In 1981, a pudgy 19-year-old Mexican pitcher, Fernando Valenzuela, took the MLB by storm, shattering America's image of the ace pitcher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-22 14:00:00" d="2020-04-22 15:30:00"><n>30 for 30: Phi Slama Jama</n>    <k>This 30 for 30 documentary chronicles the success of the 'Phi Slama Jama' Houston Cougars basketball team of the 1980s, when they reached three consecutive NCAA Final Fours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-22 15:30:00" d="2020-04-22 17:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Slaying the Badger</n>    <k>Greg LeMond helped teammate Bernard 'the Badger' Hinault win the Tour de France. In 1986, it was supposed to be LeMond's turn, but would it be? Part of the 30 for 30 series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-22 17:00:00" d="2020-04-22 18:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Unmatched</n>    <k>Chris Evert and Martina Navratilova were fierce tennis rivals in the 70s and 80s, but through it all they forged an unbreakable friendship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-22 18:00:00" d="2020-04-22 19:30:00"><n>30 for 30: Hawaiian: The Legend of Eddie Aikau</n>    <k>This documentary, part of the award-winning 30 for 30 series, chronicles the remarkable life and times of Eddie Aikau, the legendary Hawaiian big wave surfer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-22 19:30:00" d="2020-04-22 21:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Sole Man</n>    <k>This 30 for 30 documentary examines how Sonny Vaccaro rose from Pennsylvania steel town roots to become one of the most powerful and influential men in basketball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-22 21:00:00" d="2020-04-22 23:00:00"><n>Live: Champions League Throwback</n>    <k>Jake Humphrey and guests look back at Liverpool's 2018/19 UEFA Champions League semi-final trip to the Camp Nou to face Barcelona</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-22 23:00:00" d="2020-04-23 00:30:00"><n>BT Sport Films: BT Sport Films: Stop The Tour</n>    <k>Stop The Tour discovers the extraordinary story of how sport helped bring an end to Apartheid which paved the way towards the multi racial 2019 Springbok champions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-23 00:30:00" d="2020-04-23 02:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Nature Boy</n>    <k>To be the man, you gotta beat the man. And for one of wrestling's most legendary performers, Ric Flair did whatever it took to be the man. A 30 for 30 documentary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-23 02:00:00" d="2020-04-23 04:00:00"><n u="30 for 30: 30 for 30: Vick - Part">30 for 30: 30 for 30: Vick - Part 2</n>    <k>This documentary looks at the remarkable rise, fall and divisive return of former NFL star, Michael Vick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-23 04:00:00" d="2020-04-23 04:30:00"><n>30 for 30 Shorts: The Deal</n>    <k>In the winter of 2003 two cities chased the same man. On one side, New York. On the other, Boston. In the middle, the hired gun: Alex Rodriguez</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-23 04:30:00" d="2020-04-23 06:00:00"><n>30 for 30: No Crossover: The Trial of Allen Iverson</n>    <k>In 1993, Allen Iverson went bowling in Hampton. What followed ended with the teen in jail and divided a city along racial lines. Part of the acclaimed 30 for 30 series</k>  </p>
</a>
