<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2019-07-11 00:18:50"><p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-16 05:00:00" d="2019-07-16 06:00:00"><n>Fishing: On The Bank</n>    <k>Highlights of the 2018 World Predator Classic hosted by the city of Hellevoetsluis in the Netherlands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-16 06:00:00" d="2019-07-16 07:00:00"><n>Football Classics: Arsenal Classics</n>    <k>Classic Arsenal matches from the football archives, featuring memorable league clashes with Crystal Palace (1971) and Nottingham Forest (1977). 2/8</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-16 07:00:00" d="2019-07-16 08:00:00"><n>MotoGP Highlights</n>    <k>The best of the action from the Grand Prix of Qatar, as the finest of margins saw Andrea Dovizioso triumph in a thrilling season opener at the Losail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-16 08:00:00" d="2019-07-16 10:00:00"><n>MotoGP Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from the Grand Prix of Argentina at the Autodromo Termas de Rio Hondo, round two of the season. Marc Marquez was looking to take his first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-16 10:00:00" d="2019-07-16 11:00:00"><n>MotoGP Films: Marc Marquez: Trophy Collector</n>    <k>In this fascinating and revealing MotoGP Films documentary, three-time champion Marc Marquez and his crew discuss just what it is that makes the Spaniard so successful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-16 11:00:00" d="2019-07-16 12:00:00"><n>Playback - Football's Greatest Rivalries: The Merseyside Derby - Part Two</n>    <k>The Merseyside Derby. A look at some of the best matches between Liverpool's bitter footballing rivals. 2/3</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-16 12:00:00" d="2019-07-16 13:45:00"><n>BT Sport Films: Brothers in Football</n>    <k>BT Sport commemorates the centenary of armistice with an inspiring film that tells the story of non-league side Corinthians-Casuals and their links</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-16 13:45:00" d="2019-07-16 14:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Stories of the Finals</n>    <k>A look back at the 1993 UEFA Champions League final between Marseille and AC Milan in Munich. Marseille were looking to become the first French</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-16 14:00:00" d="2019-07-16 16:00:00"><n>Ashes Classics - 2010/11</n>    <k>A look back at the best moments from the first Test of the 2010/11 Ashes in Brisbane. Alastair Cook broke Donald Bradman's record for the highest Test score at the Gabba</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-16 16:00:00" d="2019-07-16 19:30:00"><n>ESPN Classic Boxing: Top 25 Knockouts</n>    <k>Ringside - Top 25 Knockouts. Another chance to see a classic bout from the boxing archives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-16 19:30:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00"><n>International GT Open Championship</n>    <k>Highlights of races one and two from round four of the International GT Open Championship at The Red Bull Ring in Austria</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 21:30:00"><n>Red Bull Air Race Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from the third round of the Red Bull Air Race Championship at Lake Balaton in Hungary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-16 21:30:00" d="2019-07-16 22:00:00"><n>The Outdoor Sports Show</n>    <k>This exhilarating series captures the best action from extreme sports around the globe, including trail running, triathlon, skiing, snowboarding, climbing and paragliding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-16 22:00:00" d="2019-07-17 00:00:00"><n>30 for 30: The U</n>    <k>In the 80s, America was shifting racially and culturally. The University of Miami American football team was a microcosm for this evolution</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-17 00:00:00" d="2019-07-17 01:00:00"><n>Fishing: On The Bank</n>    <k>Highlights of the 2018 World Predator Classic hosted by the city of Hellevoetsluis in the Netherlands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-17 01:00:00" d="2019-07-17 02:00:00"><n>Women's T20 Challenge</n>    <k>Action from the 2019 Women's T20 Challenge as Supernovas face Trailblazers in Jaipur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-17 02:00:00" d="2019-07-17 03:00:00"><n>Women's T20 Challenge</n>    <k>Action from the 2019 Women's T20 Challenge as the Trailblazers face Velocity in Jaipur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-17 03:00:00" d="2019-07-17 04:00:00"><n>Women's T20 Challenge</n>    <k>Action from the 2019 Women's T20 Challenge as Supernovas take on Velocity in Jaipur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-17 04:00:00" d="2019-07-17 05:00:00"><n>Women's T20 Challenge</n>    <k>Action from the final of the 2019 Women's T20 Challenge as Supernovas and Velocity meet in Jaipur</k>  </p>
</a>
