<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2020-05-29 04:31:23"><p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 05:00:00" d="2020-06-05 06:00:00"><n>30 for 30: The Prince of Pennsylvania</n>    <k>The tragic story of the turbulent relationship between Olympic wrestling stars Mark and Dave Schultz and multimillionaire John du Pont</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 06:00:00" d="2020-06-05 06:15:00"><n>30 for 30 Shorts: Friedman's Shoes</n>    <k>In the '80s and '90's, Friedman's Shoes was the preferred shoe store, and de facto Atlanta clubhouse, of the biggest athletes in the United States</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 06:15:00" d="2020-06-05 06:30:00"><n>30 for 30 Shorts: From Harlem With Love</n>    <k>It's 1959 and the Cold War rages on. A group of heroes step forward, not in a warzone, but on a basketball court. Part of the 30 for 30 Shorts series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 06:30:00" d="2020-06-05 07:00:00"><n>Premier League World</n>    <k>Alan Shearer sits down to discuss a career that saw him make 441 Premier League appearances, become the league's top scorer and also saw him win a Premier League title</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 07:00:00" d="2020-06-05 07:30:00"><n>Bundesliga Special</n>    <k>In Bundesliga Special ?4, you will discover the roots of Leon Bailey, Serge Gnabry and Yussuf Poulsen and learn what it took to become</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 07:30:00" d="2020-06-05 08:30:00"><n>FIM Speedway Highlights</n>    <k>All the best action from round five of the FIM Speedway Grand Prix season from Wroclaw, Poland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 08:30:00" d="2020-06-05 09:30:00"><n>FIM Speedway Highlights</n>    <k>All the best action from round six of the FIM Speedway Grand Prix season from Malilla, Sweden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 09:30:00" d="2020-06-05 10:00:00"><n>No Filter Rugby</n>    <k>The No Filter Rugby team go behind-the-scenes of Saracens' 2019 Heineken Champions Cup final victory over Leinster at St James' Park in Newcastle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 10:00:00" d="2020-06-05 11:00:00"><n>Heineken Champions Cup Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from the opening round of the 2019/20 Heineken Champions Cup, including Gloucester v Toulouse, Bath v Ulster, Racing 92 v Saracens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 11:00:00" d="2020-06-05 12:00:00"><n>World Rallycross Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from the fifth round of the 2019 FIA World Rallycross Championship in Hell, Norway</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 12:00:00" d="2020-06-05 12:30:00"><n>Spirit of Yachting</n>    <k>A series capturing the unique lifestyle, adventure and excitement that surround the world of professional sailing. This episode includes action from the Rolex Giraglia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 12:30:00" d="2020-06-05 13:00:00"><n>Spirit of Yachting</n>    <k>A series capturing the unique lifestyle, adventure and excitement that surround the world of professional sailing. This episode includes action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 13:00:00" d="2020-06-05 14:00:00"><n>Home Field Advantage</n>    <k>Former French captain Thierry Dusautoir returns to his roots in Ivory Coast with All Black Conrad Smith, while Christian Califano visits a South African</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 14:00:00" d="2020-06-05 15:15:00"><n>Home Field Advantage</n>    <k>Thierry Dusautoir is joined by former Springbok Joe Van Niekerk on a visit to India, while Christian Califano and former Wallaby Matt Giteau</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 15:15:00" d="2020-06-05 16:15:00"><n>Home Field Advantage</n>    <k>Matt Giteau and Christian Califano accept the challenge of training in the mystic Fijian sand dunes, while Jonny Wilkinson returns to Kamaishi in Japan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 16:15:00" d="2020-06-05 18:15:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: This Magic Moment</n>    <k>In the 1990s, the Orlando Magic, Shaquille O'Neal and Penny Hardaway were the talk of the NBA. This 30 for 30 documentary explores how this remarkable</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 18:15:00" d="2020-06-05 19:15:00"><n>30 for 30: This is What They Want</n>    <k>A look at the improbable run of Jimmy Connors at the 1991 US Open and how he helped make tennis a high-octane spectator sport. Part of the award-winning 30 for 30 series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 19:15:00" d="2020-06-05 19:31:00"><n>30 for 30 Shorts: Ali: The Mission</n>    <k>This 30 for 30 Shorts documentary delves into perhaps one of the most important, but least known, feats of Muhammad Ali's remarkable life, his intervention in Iraq in 1990</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 19:31:00" d="2020-06-05 21:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30 When the Garden Was Eden</n>    <k>This 30 for 30 documentary chronicles the glory years of the New York Knicks, when they made the NBA Finals in three out of four seasons, winning two titles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 21:00:00" d="2020-06-05 22:00:00"><n>BT Sport FIFA Challenge</n>    <k>BT Sport FIFA Challenge is gaming like you've never seen. We're taking the fun of playing FIFA and adding an all star cast including, Ugo Monye, Chelcee</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 22:00:00" d="2020-06-05 23:00:00"><n>Live: UFC Live: Live: UFC Live - 250 Preview</n>    <k>The UFC Live crew look ahead to a huge night of UFC action at UFC 250</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 23:00:00" d="2020-06-05 23:30:00"><n>UFC Fight Camp: SC: UFC Fight Camp</n>    <k>Exclusive access, interviews and features with fighters, analysis from experts and the best from the world of UFC ahead of 250</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 23:30:00" d="2020-06-06 00:00:00"><n>UFC: Inside the Octagon</n>    <k>A detailed break down of potential tactics ahead of UFC 250</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-06 00:00:00" d="2020-06-06 01:00:00"><n>UFC Countdown: UFC 250 Countdown</n>    <k>All the news and build-up ahead to UFC 250 between Amanda Nunes and Felicia Spencer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-06 01:00:00" d="2020-06-06 01:30:00"><n>UFC Ultimate Knockouts</n>    <k>This episode looks at UFC stars that have sent opponents face-first into the canvas. Featuring Fedor Emelianenko, Nick Diaz, Alistair Overeem, Dan Henderson and Mark Hunt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-06 01:30:00" d="2020-06-06 02:30:00"><n u="UFC: The Ultimate Fighter: UFC The Ultimate Fighter - Series">UFC: The Ultimate Fighter: UFC The Ultimate Fighter - Series 22</n>    <k>Episode 5. The 22nd series of the Ultimate Fighter sees a United States team, coached by veteran Urijah Faber, take on a European team, headed up by Irish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-06 02:30:00" d="2020-06-06 03:00:00"><n>UFC: Inside the Octagon</n>    <k>A detailed break down of potential tactics ahead of UFC 250</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-06 03:00:00" d="2020-06-06 04:00:00"><n>UFC Countdown: UFC 250 Countdown</n>    <k>All the news and build-up ahead to UFC 250 between Amanda Nunes and Felicia Spencer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-06 04:00:00" d="2020-06-06 05:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: The Price of Gold</n>    <k>This documentary examines figure skater Tonya Harding's involvement with the attack on competitor Nancy Kerrigan prior to the 1994 Winter Olympics</k>  </p>
</a>
