<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2019-08-15 22:29:49"><p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 05:30:00" d="2019-08-20 06:30:00"><n>30 for 30: Run Ricky Run</n>    <k>Ricky Williams recorded himself during his year away from American football. This is the misunderstood athlete's story in his own words</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 06:30:00" d="2019-08-20 07:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Real Madrid v Valencia 1999/00</n>    <k>A look back at the 1999/00 UEFA Champions League final between Real Madrid and Valencia in Paris. Steve McManaman, signed from Liverpool the previous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 07:00:00" d="2019-08-20 07:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Man Utd v Fenerbahce 2004/05</n>    <k>We revisit the 2004/05 UEFA Champions League group stage tie between Manchester United and Fenerbahce at Old Trafford. The match saw Wayne Rooney</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 07:30:00" d="2019-08-20 08:00:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: Chelsea v Barcelona 2004/05</n>    <k>We revisit the last 16 second leg from the 2004/05 UEFA Champions League between Chelsea and Barcelona at Stamford Bridge. Barca were in the driving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 08:00:00" d="2019-08-20 08:30:00"><n>UEFA Champions League - Classics: R.Madrid v A.Madrid 2013/14</n>    <k>The 2013/14 UEFA Champions League final in Lisbon saw Real Madrid go head-to-head with arch-rivals Atletico Madrid. Real aimed to become the first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 08:30:00" d="2019-08-20 09:00:00"><n>GC32 Racing Tour Sailing</n>    <k>Action from the GC32 Racing Tour, a European yacht racing circuit sailed in state of the art foiling catamarans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 09:00:00" d="2019-08-20 11:00:00"><n>SGB Premiership: SGB: Poole v Swindon</n>    <k>SGB Premiership action as Poole Pirates and Swindon Robins battle it out at Poole Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 11:00:00" d="2019-08-20 11:30:00"><n>The WRC Magazine</n>    <k>The latest news and action from the FIA World Rally Championship, plus a look ahead to the next round in Germany</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 11:30:00" d="2019-08-20 12:00:00"><n>Early Kick-Off</n>    <k>Jake Humphrey, Robbie Savage, Jules Breach and big name guests bring you debate, laughs and all the news ahead of the weekend's Premier League action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 12:00:00" d="2019-08-20 12:30:00"><n>BT Sport Score Highlights: BT Sport Score Best Bits</n>    <k>A round-up of all the best bits from the latest episode of BT Sport Score</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 12:30:00" d="2019-08-20 13:00:00"><n>Vanarama National League Highlights</n>    <k>The best of the action from this weekend's Vanarama National League fixtures, including Boreham Wood v Sutton United, Barnet v Chesterfield and Dover v Torquay United</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 13:00:00" d="2019-08-20 14:00:00"><n>Fishing: On The Bank: Fishing: On The Bank - 2019</n>    <k>Angling magazine show presented by Rob Hughes and Andy Ford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 14:00:00" d="2019-08-20 16:00:00"><n>FIM Speedway Grand Prix</n>    <k>Action from all the races of round six of the FIM Speedway Grand Prix in Malilla, Sweden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 16:00:00" d="2019-08-20 18:00:00"><n>SGB Premiership: SGB: Poole v Swindon</n>    <k>SGB Premiership action as Poole Pirates and Swindon Robins battle it out at Poole Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 18:00:00" d="2019-08-20 18:15:00"><n>BT Sport Goals Reload</n>    <k>A round-up of the greatest goals from around the world, including action from Ligue 1 and the Bundesliga</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 18:15:00" d="2019-08-20 18:45:00"><n>Vanarama National League Highlights</n>    <k>The best of the action from this weekend's Vanarama National League fixtures, including Boreham Wood v Sutton United, Barnet v Chesterfield and Dover v Torquay United</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 18:45:00" d="2019-08-20 19:15:00"><n>Early Kick-Off</n>    <k>Jake Humphrey, Robbie Savage, Jules Breach and big name guests bring you debate, laughs and all the news ahead of the weekend's Premier League action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 19:15:00" d="2019-08-20 20:15:00"><n>Premier League Review</n>    <k>The best of the recent Premier League action as new boys Sheffield United met Crystal Palace, champions Man City entertained Spurs and Chelsea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 20:15:00" d="2019-08-20 20:45:00"><n>BT Sport Score Highlights: BT Sport Score Best Bits</n>    <k>A round-up of all the best bits from the latest episode of BT Sport Score</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 20:45:00" d="2019-08-20 23:00:00"><n>Live UEFA Champions League: Live: APOEL v Ajax</n>    <k>APOEL welcome a young and exciting Ajax side to Cyprus for the first leg of their UEFA Champions League play-off tie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 23:00:00" d="2019-08-20 23:30:00"><n>BT Sport Films Shorts: State of Play: The Manager</n>    <k>BT Sport Films Shorts gives a unique look at modern football. Frank Lampard, Sam Allardyce, Sean Dyche and Emma Hayes describe the pressures of managing in the modern game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-20 23:30:00" d="2019-08-21 01:15:00"><n>BT Sport Films: Too Good to Go Down</n>    <k>BT Sport films explores the difficulty of the post-Sir Matt Busby era at Manchester United and why hitting rock bottom was the only way for a new United to come of age</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-21 01:15:00" d="2019-08-21 03:00:00"><n>UFC Reloaded</n>    <k>Relive the exhilarating UFC middleweight bout between Michael Bisping and Kelvin Gastelum at the Mercedes-Benz Arena in Shanghai, China</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-08-21 03:00:00" d="2019-08-21 05:00:00"><n>SGB Premiership: SGB: Poole v Swindon</n>    <k>SGB Premiership action as Poole Pirates and Swindon Robins battle it out at Poole Stadium</k>  </p>
</a>
