<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2020-05-16 04:44:25"><p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-23 05:00:00" d="2020-05-23 06:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Playing For The Mob</n>    <k>Mobster Henry Hill, made infamous in the movie Goodfellas, helped fix college basketball games. This is a tale of greed, betrayal and reckoning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-23 06:30:00" d="2020-05-23 07:00:00"><n>Premier League World</n>    <k>Wayne Rooney charts his path from a youngster at Everton through to his current club Derby County. He details why he's decided to become a coach and his future hopes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-23 07:00:00" d="2020-05-23 08:00:00"><n>Fishing: On The Bank</n>    <k>Highlights of the 2018 World Predator Classic hosted by the city of Hellevoetsluis in the Netherlands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-23 08:00:00" d="2020-05-23 09:00:00"><n>Fishing: On The Bank: British Carp Cup Ladies 2018</n>    <k>Highlights of the 2018 Ladies British Carp Cup at Old Mill Lakes in Lincolnshire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-23 09:00:00" d="2020-05-23 10:00:00"><n>UEFA Women's Champions League: Women's UCL final 2018/19</n>    <k>Look back as Lyon Women met Barcelona Women in the 2018/19 UEFA Women's Champions League final in Budapest, Hungary. Lyon hoped to lift the trophy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-23 10:00:00" d="2020-05-23 11:00:00"><n>Barclays FA Women's Super League: Man Utd Women v Arsenal W 2019/20</n>    <k>Look back as Manchester United Women hosted reigning champions Arsenal Women at Leigh Sports Village in the 2018/19 FA Women's Super League earlier this season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-23 11:00:00" d="2020-05-23 12:00:00"><n>Barclays FA Women's Super League: West Ham Women v Spurs W 2019/20</n>    <k>West Ham United Women went toe-to-toe with rivals Tottenham Women in the Barclays FA Women's Super League at the London Stadium, their first ever match at the stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-23 12:00:00" d="2020-05-23 13:00:00"><n>Cricket: Big Bash League: Sydney S v Melbourne R 2019/20</n>    <k>Re-live the action as Sydney Sixers and Melbourne Renegades went toe-to-toe in the Big Bash League at Sydney Cricket Ground in December</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-23 13:00:00" d="2020-05-23 14:00:00"><n>Cricket: Big Bash League: Melbourne S v Brisbane H 2019/20</n>    <k>Action from Big Bash League Cricket as Melbourne Stars and Brisbane Heat went head-to-head at Melbourne Cricket Ground back in January</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-23 14:00:00" d="2020-05-23 15:00:00"><n>Super League Triathlon</n>    <k>Action from the Super League Triathlon in Jersey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-23 15:00:00" d="2020-05-23 17:30:00"><n>WWE Monday Night Raw</n>    <k>Watch Becky Lynch, Kevin Owens, Charlotte Flair, Seth Rollins and more of your favourite WWE Superstars face-off inside the ring on WWE Monday Night Raw</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-23 17:30:00" d="2020-05-23 18:30:00"><n u="30 for 30: 30 for 30: June 17th">30 for 30: 30 for 30: June 17th, 1994</n>    <k>Part of the acclaimed 30 for 30 series, this documentary covers the events on the day OJ Simpson was pursued and arrested on charges of murdering</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-23 18:30:00" d="2020-05-23 20:00:00"><n>SEC Storied: It's Time</n>    <k>The moving story of College Football's Chucky Mullins who was paralysed and later died after tackling Brad Gaines. Features emotional interviews</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-23 20:00:00" d="2020-05-23 22:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: One and Not Done</n>    <k>Who is John Calipari? To his fans, he is one of college basketball's greatest coaches. To his critics, he represents everything wrong with college sports</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-23 22:00:00" d="2020-05-23 23:30:00"><n>BT Sport Films: BT Sport Films: State of Play</n>    <k>This BT Sport Film looks at the strengths and flaws of the modern game from the perspective of players, managers, clubs and society. Featuring Gareth Bale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-23 23:30:00" d="2020-05-24 01:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: The Price of Gold</n>    <k>This documentary examines figure skater Tonya Harding's involvement with the attack on competitor Nancy Kerrigan prior to the 1994 Winter Olympics</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-24 01:00:00" d="2020-05-24 02:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Without Bias</n>    <k>A look back at the death of Len Bias from a cocaine-induced heart attack, two days after Boston selected him in the 1986 NBA Draft. Part of the acclaimed 30 for 30 series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-24 02:00:00" d="2020-05-24 04:00:00"><n>30 for 30: ESPN Films: Catching Hell</n>    <k>This film uses the case of Steve Bartman - the fan who interfered with an in-play ball in the 2003 NLCS and was vilified for it - to examine scapegoating</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-24 04:00:00" d="2020-05-24 06:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: The U</n>    <k>In the 80s, America was shifting racially and culturally. The University of Miami American football team was a microcosm for this evolution</k>  </p>
</a>
