<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-04-09 04:28:30"><p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-16 06:00:00" d="2020-04-16 06:30:00"><n>Premier League World: Premier League World: Xabi Alonso</n>    <k>This week we sit catch up with Liverpool legend Xabi Alonso who talks us through his time at Anfield and why he decided to leave the club in 2009</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-16 06:30:00" d="2020-04-16 07:00:00"><n>Premier League World: Premier League World: Carlos Tevez</n>    <k>This week we head to Buenos Aires to speak exclusively to Carlos Tevez. He tells us why he came to West Ham and lifts the lid on his fallout with Roberto Mancini</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-16 07:00:00" d="2020-04-16 07:30:00"><n>BT Sport Goals Reload</n>    <k>A round-up of the greatest goals from around the world, including action from Ligue 1 and the Bundesliga</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-16 07:30:00" d="2020-04-16 08:30:00"><n>MotoGP: Moto3: Grand Prix of Aragon</n>    <k>The Moto3 race at the Grand Prix of Aragon, round 14 of the season. Japan's Tatsuki Suzuki secured an emotional maiden victory last time out at Misano</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-16 08:30:00" d="2020-04-16 09:30:00"><n>MotoGP: Moto2: Grand Prix of Aragon</n>    <k>The Moto2 race at the Grand Prix of Aragon, round 14 of the season. The home crowd can expect to see a host of their local stars, including Augusto</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-16 09:30:00" d="2020-04-16 10:30:00"><n>MotoGP: MotoGP: Grand Prix of Aragon</n>    <k>The MotoGP race at the Grand Prix of Aragon, round 14 of the season. Home hero Marc Marquez looks to extend his 93-point lead and take another</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-16 10:30:00" d="2020-04-16 11:30:00"><n>FIM Speedway Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from the opening round of the 2019 FIM Speedway Grand Prix in Warsaw, Poland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-16 11:30:00" d="2020-04-16 12:30:00"><n>FIM Speedway Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from the second round of the 2019 FIM Speedway Grand Prix in Krsko, Slovenia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-16 12:30:00" d="2020-04-16 13:00:00"><n>BT Sport Reload</n>    <k>The best bits from BT Sport from the last week, exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-16 13:00:00" d="2020-04-16 14:30:00"><n>30 for 30: ESPN Films: The Clemente Effect</n>    <k>ESPN Films chronicles the life and accomplishments of Roberto Clemente, from his upbringing in Puerto Rico to becoming a World Series hero for the Pirates in 1960 and 1971</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-16 14:30:00" d="2020-04-16 15:30:00"><n>30 for 30: Into the Wind</n>    <k>Terry Fox, an amputee with cancer, attempted running across Canada for cancer awareness. In the process, he captured the heart of a nation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-16 15:30:00" d="2020-04-16 16:30:00"><n>30 for 30: Small Potatoes: Who Killed the USFL?</n>    <k>Part of the acclaimed 30 for 30 series, this documentary examines Donald Trump's involvement in the demise of the United States Football League in the mid-1980s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-16 16:30:00" d="2020-04-16 17:30:00"><n>SEC Storied: Shaq and Dale</n>    <k>This documentary follows ex-basketball star Shaquille O'Neal as he returns to LSU with Dale Brown, the coach who helped make it all possible</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-16 17:30:00" d="2020-04-16 19:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Elway to Marino</n>    <k>A look at the 1983 NFL Draft that was highlighted by a record six quarterbacks being taken in the first round, including John Elway and Dan Marino</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-16 19:00:00" d="2020-04-16 20:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Marion Jones: Press Pause</n>    <k>From Olympic athlete to inmate, Marion Jones recounts how it felt in that long and yet all-too short drive to prison. Part of the award-winning 30 for 30 series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-16 20:00:00" d="2020-04-16 21:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Jordan Rides the Bus</n>    <k>Part of the acclaimed 30 for 30 series, this documentary examines why Michael Jordan quit basketball for baseball, despite being in his prime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-16 21:00:00" d="2020-04-16 23:00:00"><n>Live: Europa League Throwback</n>    <k>Jake Humphrey and guests look back at the 2018/19 UEFA Europa League quarter final second leg between Chelsea and Slavia Prague</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-16 23:00:00" d="2020-04-17 00:00:00"><n>BT Sport Films: BT Sport Films: Cornered</n>    <k>This moving documentary follows the life and career of journeyman boxer Johnny Greaves, veteran of 100 professional fights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 00:00:00" d="2020-04-17 02:00:00"><n>O.J.: Made in America</n>    <k>Episode four of this Oscar-winning documentary focuses on the evidence presented at OJ's controversial trial. Contains graphic images which some viewers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 02:00:00" d="2020-04-17 03:30:00"><n>30 for 30: No Mas</n>    <k>A look back at the two boxing matches between Sugar Ray Leonard and Roberto Duran in the 80s, with analysis from experts and the fighters themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 03:30:00" d="2020-04-17 05:00:00"><n>30 for 30: This Was The XFL</n>    <k>In 2001, two sports entertainment titans launched the XFL. It was a bold challenge, a fearless experiment and ultimately, a spectacular failure</k>  </p>
</a>
