<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-04-10 04:28:58"><p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 05:00:00" d="2020-04-17 06:00:00"><n>30 for 30: The Legend of Jimmy the Greek</n>    <k>Part of the award-winning 30 for 30 series, this documentary follows the career of Jimmy Synder, a professional gambler who helped legitimise betting in NFL games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 06:00:00" d="2020-04-17 06:30:00"><n>Premier League World</n>    <k>We sit down with ex-Manchester United star Ryan Giggs to chart his incredible career from one of Fergie's fledglings, to his current role as manager</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 06:30:00" d="2020-04-17 07:00:00"><n>Premier League World</n>    <k>This week BT Sport speak to those who know Allison Becker best, as he reveals how he made it from humble beginnings to Liverpool's number 1</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 07:00:00" d="2020-04-17 07:30:00"><n>BT Sport Goals Reload</n>    <k>A round-up of the greatest goals from around the world, including action from Ligue 1 and the Bundesliga</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 07:30:00" d="2020-04-17 08:30:00"><n>MotoGP: Moto3: Grand Prix of Thailand</n>    <k>The Moto3 race at the Grand Prix of Thailand, round 15 of the season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 08:30:00" d="2020-04-17 09:30:00"><n>MotoGP: Moto2: Grand Prix of Thailand</n>    <k>The Moto2 race at the Grand Prix of Thailand, round 15 of the season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 09:30:00" d="2020-04-17 10:30:00"><n>MotoGP: MotoGP: Grand Prix of Thailand</n>    <k>The MotoGP race at the Grand Prix of Thailand, round 15 of the season. Marc Marquez needs two points more than Andrea Dovizioso to wrap up his sixth championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 10:30:00" d="2020-04-17 11:30:00"><n>FIM Speedway Highlights</n>    <k>All the thrills and spills from round three of the 2019 FIM Speedway Grand Prix in Prague, Czech Republic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 11:30:00" d="2020-04-17 12:30:00"><n>FIM Speedway Highlights</n>    <k>All the thrills and spills from round four of the 2019 FIM Speedway Grand Prix in Hallstavik, Sweden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 12:30:00" d="2020-04-17 13:00:00"><n>BT Sport Reload</n>    <k>The best bits from BT Sport from the last week, exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 13:00:00" d="2020-04-17 15:00:00"><n>30 for 30: It's Not Crazy, It's Sports</n>    <k>ESPN Films explore the inspiring, dramatic and unexpected things in sports that capture the experience of being a fan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 15:00:00" d="2020-04-17 16:00:00"><n>Home Field Advantage</n>    <k>Former French captain Thierry Dusautoir returns to his roots in Ivory Coast with All Black Conrad Smith, while Christian Califano visits a South African</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 16:00:00" d="2020-04-17 17:15:00"><n>Home Field Advantage</n>    <k>Thierry Dusautoir is joined by former Springbok Joe Van Niekerk on a visit to India, while Christian Califano and former Wallaby Matt Giteau</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 17:15:00" d="2020-04-17 18:15:00"><n>Home Field Advantage</n>    <k>Matt Giteau and Christian Califano accept the challenge of training in the mystic Fijian sand dunes, while Jonny Wilkinson returns to Kamaishi in Japan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 18:15:00" d="2020-04-17 18:45:00"><n>30 for 30 Shorts</n>    <k>Dick Weber was the matinee idol of bowling. But times changed and people started to move on until a rebel took to the lanes to claim the new throne: Dick's son Pete</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 18:45:00" d="2020-04-17 20:45:00"><n>30 for 30: This Magic Moment</n>    <k>In the 1990s, the Orlando Magic, Shaquille O'Neal and Penny Hardaway were the talk of the NBA. This 30 for 30 documentary explores how this remarkable</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 20:45:00" d="2020-04-17 21:00:00"><n>30 for 30 Shorts: The Irrelevant Giant</n>    <k>This 30 for 30 Short takes a look back at John Tuggle, the 1983 NFL draft's Mr. Irrelevant, who was anything but irrelevant to legendary coach Bill Parcells</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 21:00:00" d="2020-04-17 22:00:00"><n u="30 for 30: June 17th">30 for 30: June 17th, 1994</n>    <k>Part of the acclaimed 30 for 30 series, this documentary covers the events on the day OJ Simpson was pursued and arrested on charges of murdering</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 22:00:00" d="2020-04-17 23:00:00"><n>BT Sport Films: Ref: Stories From the Weekend</n>    <k>BT Sport Films presents an in-depth look at the world of referees, contrasting those at the elite level to the men and women doing the job at different levels of the game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-17 23:00:00" d="2020-04-18 01:00:00"><n>O.J.: Made in America</n>    <k>Episode five of this Oscar-winning documentary examines OJ's life in the years that followed his controversial murder acquittal. From the makers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-18 01:00:00" d="2020-04-18 03:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Catholics vs Convicts</n>    <k>In 1988, Notre Dame hosted Miami Hurricanes in what was one of the greatest games in college football history. This 30 for 30 documentary tells the story</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-18 03:00:00" d="2020-04-18 04:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Run Ricky Run</n>    <k>Ricky Williams recorded himself during his year away from American football. This is the misunderstood athlete's story in his own words</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-18 04:00:00" d="2020-04-18 06:00:00"><n>30 for 30: The Two Escobars</n>    <k>Part of the award-winning 30 for 30 series, this documentary looks at how two men with the same surname uplifted the Colombian football team from obscurity</k>  </p>
</a>
