<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2020-05-15 04:45:41"><p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-22 05:30:00" d="2020-05-22 06:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Rand University</n>    <k>The story of American football star Randy Moss's incredible journey from isolated Rand, West Virginia, to the top of the NFL. Part of the award-winning 30 for 30 series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-22 06:30:00" d="2020-05-22 07:00:00"><n>Premier League World</n>    <k>This week we talk former Portsmouth man Dario Silva whose life was turned upside down after a car crash in Uruguay</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-22 07:00:00" d="2020-05-22 07:30:00"><n>BT Sport Goals Reload</n>    <k>A round-up of the greatest goals from around the world, including action from Ligue 1 and the Bundesliga</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-22 07:30:00" d="2020-05-22 08:30:00"><n u="Hockey: Men's Hockey: AUS v GBR">Hockey: Men's Hockey: AUS v GBR 2020</n>    <k>A look back as Australia host Greated Britain in the 2020 Men's FIH Hockey Pro League at Sydney Olympic Park. This was GB's first fixture of the year</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-22 08:30:00" d="2020-05-22 11:00:00"><n>Gallagher Premiership Rugby Highlights</n>    <k>All the best action from the latest fixtures in the Gallagher Premiership, including Gloucester v Saracens, Bath v Northampton Saints and Exeter Chiefs v Bristol Bears</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-22 11:00:00" d="2020-05-22 13:00:00"><n>V8 Supercars Highlights: V8 Supercars: Season Review</n>    <k>Highlights from the Virgin Australia Supercars Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-22 13:00:00" d="2020-05-22 15:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: The Best That Never Was</n>    <k>Marcus Dupree was the biggest, fastest running back in high school history. In college, his career ended before it ever truly began</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-22 15:00:00" d="2020-05-22 17:00:00"><n>30 for 30: It's Not Crazy, It's Sports</n>    <k>ESPN Films explore the inspiring, dramatic and unexpected things in sports that capture the experience of being a fan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-22 17:00:00" d="2020-05-22 19:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: SMU Pony Exce$$</n>    <k>SMU's American football team received the NCAA's 'death penalty' in 1987 because of corruption and greed, stripping a community of its identity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-22 19:00:00" d="2020-05-22 21:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Survive and Advance</n>    <k>In 1983, Jim Valvano led the NC State Wolfpack through nine consecutive do-or-die matches. But one game and one play will be remembered forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-22 21:00:00" d="2020-05-22 22:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: The Birth of Big Air</n>    <k>This documentary, part of the acclaimed 30 for 30 series, profiles BMX star Mat Hoffman, a trailblazing biker who went pro at just 16 and helped build</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-22 22:00:00" d="2020-05-22 23:15:00"><n>BT Sport Films: Team Of The Eighties</n>    <k>BT Sport Films explores how Malcolm Allison and Terry Venables hatched an audacious plan to transform Crystal Palace into the team of the 1980's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-22 23:15:00" d="2020-05-22 23:30:00"><n>BT Sport Films Shorts: State of Play: Jadon Sancho</n>    <k>Modern football stripped bare. Jadon Sancho discusses the next generation of English talent with Michael Calvin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-22 23:30:00" d="2020-05-22 23:45:00"><n>BT Sport Films Shorts: State of Play: Thomas Hitzlsperger</n>    <k>An in-depth interview with Thomas Hitzlsperger on the issue of homophobia in the modern game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-22 23:45:00" d="2020-05-23 00:45:00"><n>30 for 30: The Prince of Pennsylvania</n>    <k>The tragic story of the turbulent relationship between Olympic wrestling stars Mark and Dave Schultz and multimillionaire John du Pont</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-23 00:45:00" d="2020-05-23 01:00:00"><n>30 for 30 Shorts: The Arnold Palmer</n>    <k>This 30 for 30 Shorts documentary explores the history, mystery and industry surrounding 'The Arnold Palmer', the lemonade-and-iced tea beverage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-23 01:00:00" d="2020-05-23 02:00:00"><n>30 for 30: The Day the Series Stopped</n>    <k>The 1989 World Series saw the A's sweep the Giants. But that's not what people remember after a 6.9 earthquake brought death and destruction. Part of the 30 for 30 series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-23 02:00:00" d="2020-05-23 03:30:00"><n>30 for 30: ESPN Films: Crossroads</n>    <k>ESPN Films looks at the inspiring story of how a group of kids went from awkward lacrosse neophytes to North Carolina state finalists in just three seasons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-23 03:30:00" d="2020-05-23 05:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: No Mas</n>    <k>A look back at the two boxing matches between Sugar Ray Leonard and Roberto Duran in the 80s, with analysis from experts and the fighters themselves</k>  </p>
</a>
