<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2019-07-11 00:18:49"><p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-15 05:30:00" d="2019-07-15 06:30:00"><n>Football Classics: Arsenal Classics</n>    <k>Classic Arsenal matches from the football archives, featuring memorable league clashes with Manchester United (1973) and Liverpool (1975). 1/8</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-15 06:30:00" d="2019-07-15 07:00:00"><n>Football Classics: Manchester City Classics</n>    <k>Classic Manchester City matches from the football archives, featuring the memorable 1979 First Division clash against Tottenham Hotspur at White Hart Lane. 4/4</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-15 07:00:00" d="2019-07-15 08:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Greatest Premier League Goals</n>    <k>A selection of the best goals from the history of the Premier League. This episode features memorable goals from the 2007/08 and 2008/09 campaigns. 7/8</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-15 08:00:00" d="2019-07-15 09:00:00"><n>Classic Premier League: Greatest Premier League Goals</n>    <k>A selection of the best goals from the history of the Premier League. This episode features memorable goals from the 2009/10 and 2010/11 campaigns. 8/8</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-15 09:00:00" d="2019-07-15 10:00:00"><n>Virgin Australia Supercars Championship Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from race 17 of the Virgin Australia Supercars Championship in Townsville</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-15 10:00:00" d="2019-07-15 11:00:00"><n>Virgin Australia Supercars Championship Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from race 18 of the Virgin Australia Supercars Championship in Townsville</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-15 11:00:00" d="2019-07-15 12:00:00"><n>British RallyCross Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from round three of the British Rallycross Championship at Pembrey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-15 12:00:00" d="2019-07-15 13:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Unmatched</n>    <k>Chris Evert and Martina Navratilova were fierce tennis rivals in the 70s and 80s, but through it all they forged an unbreakable friendship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-15 13:00:00" d="2019-07-15 21:00:00"><n>Live WTA Tennis: Live WTA Tennis: Bucharest Open</n>    <k>Action from day one of the BRD Bucharest Open in Romania</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-15 21:00:00" d="2019-07-15 21:30:00"><n>WTA All Access</n>    <k>All the latest news from the women's tennis tour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-15 21:30:00" d="2019-07-15 22:00:00"><n u="Classics in Europe: Nottingham Forest v Liverpool">Classics in Europe: Nottingham Forest v Liverpool 1978</n>    <k>Brian Clough's Nottingham Forest hosted holders Liverpool, boasting the likes of Kenny Dalglish, in this enthralling European Cup first round clash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-15 22:00:00" d="2019-07-15 23:00:00"><n>UFC Main Event</n>    <k>Relive all the action from UFC 235 as Jon Jones made his return to the Octagon to fight Anthony Smith in a light heavyweight bout at the T-Mobile Arena in Las Vegas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-15 23:00:00" d="2019-07-16 00:00:00"><n>IPL: IPL: Indians v Super Kings</n>    <k>Relive the first qualifier of the 2019 Indian Premier League at MA Chidambaram Stadium as Mumbai Indians hosted Chennai Super Kings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-16 00:00:00" d="2019-07-16 01:00:00"><n>IPL: IPL: Capitals v Sunrisers</n>    <k>Look back as Delhi Capitals took on Sunrisers Hyderabad in the 2019 Indian Premier League Eliminator game at the ACA-VDCA Cricket Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-16 01:00:00" d="2019-07-16 02:00:00"><n>IPL: IPL: Super Kings v Capitals</n>    <k>Look back as Chennai Super Kings and Delhi Capitals squared-off in the second 2019 Vivo IPL qualifier. A place in the final against Mumbai Indians</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-16 02:00:00" d="2019-07-16 03:00:00"><n>IPL: IPL Final: Indians v Super Kings</n>    <k>Relive the thrilling final of the 2019 Vivo Indian Premier League as the Mumbai Indians faced the Chennai Super Kings at the Rajiv Gandhi International Cricket Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-16 03:00:00" d="2019-07-16 04:30:00"><n>BT Sport Films: Packer: The Man Who Changed Cricket</n>    <k>This BT Sport Films documentary explores the influence Australian media mogul Kerry Packer had on the game with his controversial World Series Cricket competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-16 04:30:00" d="2019-07-16 05:00:00"><n>Classic MOTD - Thrillers: Arsenal v Sheffield United 1965/66</n>    <k>We delve into the Match of the Day archives to revisit highlights of the 1965/66 First Division clash between Arsenal and Sheffield United at Highbury</k>  </p>
</a>
