<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2020-05-25 04:34:39"><p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-01 05:00:00" d="2020-06-01 06:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Doc &amp; Darryl</n>    <k>Reunited at a Queens diner, ex-MLB stars Doc Gooden and Darryl Strawberry look back on the glory days of the mid-80s and their subsequent downfalls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-01 06:30:00" d="2020-06-01 07:00:00"><n>Premier League World</n>    <k>This week we take a trip down memory lane with Wes Brown. We also speak to Watford boss Nigel Pearson, and West Ham's Felipe Anderson speaks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-01 07:00:00" d="2020-06-01 07:30:00"><n>BT Sport Goals Reload</n>    <k>We bring you the greatest goals from around the world this week, including action from Ligue 1 and the Bundesliga</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-01 07:30:00" d="2020-06-01 08:30:00"><n>FIM Speedway Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from the opening round of the 2019 FIM Speedway Grand Prix in Warsaw, Poland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-01 08:30:00" d="2020-06-01 11:00:00"><n>Gallagher Premiership Rugby Highlights</n>    <k>All the best action from round 10 of the Gallagher Premiership, including Gloucester v Exeter Chiefs, Saracens v Sale and Leicester Tigers v Wasps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-01 11:00:00" d="2020-06-01 12:00:00"><n>World Rallycross Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from the opening round of the 2019 FIA World Rallycross Championship at the Yas Marina Circuit in Abu Dhab</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-01 12:00:00" d="2020-06-01 13:00:00"><n>Sailing World Cup</n>    <k>Highlights from the opening round of the 2019 Sailing World Cup in Enoshima</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-01 13:00:00" d="2020-06-01 14:01:00"><n>SEC Storied: Lolo Jones</n>    <k>This documentary explores USA's track and field star Lori `Lolo' Jones' extraordinary journey; rising from poverty and homelessness to stardom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-01 14:01:00" d="2020-06-01 15:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Four Days in October</n>    <k>The Yankees were leading the Red Sox in the ALCS 3-0 back in 2004, a deficit no team had overcome. The Red Sox defied the inevitable</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-01 15:00:00" d="2020-06-01 19:00:00"><n>MotoGP: The Greatest Years</n>    <k>The BT Sport MotoGP team discuss and debate the sport's greatest years. Each week the team discuss all the best moments from a great season of MotoGP action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-01 19:00:00" d="2020-06-01 20:30:00"><n>Live: Isolation eRacing Series</n>    <k>The biggest names in motorsport go head-to-head in this virtual motor racing series to identify the best simulator driver in motorsport</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-01 20:30:00" d="2020-06-01 20:45:00"><n>30 for 30 Shorts</n>    <k>This documentary looks at Greg Louganis, who had to juggle the pressure of winning an unprecedented second gold medal at the Seoul Olympics</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-01 20:45:00" d="2020-06-01 22:00:00"><n>BT Sport Films: Rocky &amp; Wrighty: From Brockley To The Big Time</n>    <k>BT Sport films presents the extraordinary story of how a young David Rocastle's meteoric rise to stardom inspired another legend in the shape of Ian Wright</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-01 22:00:00" d="2020-06-02 00:00:00"><n u="30 for">30 for 30</n>    <k>An unprecedented documentary series featuring films from some of today's finest storytellers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-02 00:00:00" d="2020-06-02 01:00:00"><n>30 for 30: ESPN Films: Charismatic</n>    <k>This documentary tells the story of the 1999 miracle that was Charismatic, a horse that emerged from nowhere to win the first two races in the Triple Crown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-02 01:00:00" d="2020-06-02 02:30:00"><n>30 for 30: I Hate Christian Laettner</n>    <k>Basketball player Christian Laettner helped Duke win two national titles in four trips to the Final Four. So why is he intensely disliked by so many? Part of the 30 for 30 series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-02 02:30:00" d="2020-06-02 04:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: No Mas</n>    <k>A look back at the two boxing matches between Sugar Ray Leonard and Roberto Duran in the 80s, with analysis from experts and the fighters themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-02 04:00:00" d="2020-06-02 05:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Chuck and Tito</n>    <k>A look at the career, friendship and rivalry of legendary MMA fighters Chuck Liddell and Tito Ortiz</k>  </p>
</a>
