<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-05-14 04:45:54"><p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-21 05:30:00" d="2020-05-21 06:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Run Ricky Run</n>    <k>Ricky Williams recorded himself during his year away from American football. This is the misunderstood athlete's story in his own words</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-21 06:30:00" d="2020-05-21 07:00:00"><n>Premier League World</n>    <k>We look back at Bradford City's iconic season in the English top flight in 1999-2000. We also sit down with Chelsea star Tammy Abraham about life at the bridge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-21 07:00:00" d="2020-05-21 07:30:00"><n>BT Sport Goals Reload</n>    <k>A round-up of the greatest goals from around the world, including action from Ligue 1 and the Bundesliga</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-21 07:30:00" d="2020-05-21 08:30:00"><n>Men's FIH Olympic Qualifiers: Men's Hockey: GBR v Malaysia</n>    <k>Action from the Men's FIH Olympic qualifiers as Great Britain meet Malaysia Lee Valley in London</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-21 08:30:00" d="2020-05-21 11:00:00"><n>Gallagher Premiership Rugby Highlights</n>    <k>All the best action from the latest fixtures in the Gallagher Premiership, including Wasps v Bath, Saracens v London Irish and Leicester Tigers v Gloucester</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-21 11:00:00" d="2020-05-21 12:00:00"><n>V8 Supercars Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from race 29 of the Virgin Australia Supercars Championship in Newcastle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-21 12:00:00" d="2020-05-21 13:00:00"><n>V8 Supercars Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from the Virgin Australia Supercars Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-21 13:00:00" d="2020-05-21 15:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30 Requiem for the Big East</n>    <k>This documentary, part of the 30 for 30 series, chronicles the meteoric rise of the Big East conference and how it became the most successful college</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-21 15:00:00" d="2020-05-21 15:15:00"><n>BT Sport Films Shorts: State of Play: Ramsey &amp; Ferdinand</n>    <k>A unique insight into the game by those who play it, coach it, shape it and cherish it. Les Ferdinand &amp; Chris Ramsey discuss opportunities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-21 15:15:00" d="2020-05-21 15:30:00"><n>BT Sport Films Shorts: State of Play: Sean Dyche</n>    <k>BT Sport Films Shorts is a series of documentaries offering insight into why sport matters to elite sportsmen and women and fans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-21 15:30:00" d="2020-05-21 17:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Brian and The Boz</n>    <k>Former Oklahoma linebacker Brian Bosworth looks back on the mistakes he made as his alter ego `The Boz', and passes on the lessons he learned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-21 17:00:00" d="2020-05-21 18:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Slaying the Badger</n>    <k>Greg LeMond helped teammate Bernard 'the Badger' Hinault win the Tour de France. In 1986, it was supposed to be LeMond's turn, but would it be? Part of the 30 for 30 series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-21 18:30:00" d="2020-05-21 19:30:00"><n>30 for 30: This is What They Want</n>    <k>A look at the improbable run of Jimmy Connors at the 1991 US Open and how he helped make tennis a high-octane spectator sport. Part of the award-winning 30 for 30 series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-21 19:30:00" d="2020-05-21 21:00:00"><n>BT Sport Films: BT Sport Films: Stop The Tour</n>    <k>Stop The Tour discovers the extraordinary story of how sport helped bring an end to Apartheid which paved the way towards the multi racial 2019 Springbok champions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-21 21:00:00" d="2020-05-21 22:00:00"><n>BT Sport Films: Football Outposts: When They Were Giants</n>    <k>Tom Watt travels across Europe to find out what has happened to the unlikely giants of European football</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-21 22:00:00" d="2020-05-21 23:15:00"><n>BT Sport Films: Packer: The Man Who Changed Cricket</n>    <k>This BT Sport Films documentary explores the influence Australian media mogul Kerry Packer had on the game with his controversial World Series Cricket competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-21 23:15:00" d="2020-05-22 00:15:00"><n u="E:60: E:60 Alex Smith - Project">E:60: E:60 Alex Smith - Project 11</n>    <k>Project 11 is a riveting look at the life of Alex Smith, from former number one NFL draft pick to fighting his way back from an injury that almost cost him everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-22 00:15:00" d="2020-05-22 00:45:00"><n>In Depth with Graham Bensinger</n>    <k>In this episode Graham sits down with Arnold Schwarzenegger who shares stories including the tribulations of his critical father, making</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-22 00:45:00" d="2020-05-22 01:00:00"><n>30 for 30 Shorts: Slick, Nancy and the Telethon</n>    <k>When the Pacers were on the brink of extinction, the state's first couple of basketball stood up, rallied the fans and attempted to save their team</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-22 01:00:00" d="2020-05-22 02:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Mike and the Mad Dog</n>    <k>A look at the rise of sports talk radio pioneers Mike Francesca and Chris 'Mad Dog' Russo and how they ruled American radio for nearly two decades</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-22 02:00:00" d="2020-05-22 03:00:00"><n>30 for 30: ESPN Films: Roll Tide War Eagle</n>    <k>Find out about one of the fiercest rivalries in college sport between Alabama and Auburn. Hear from the school's icons on how the rivalry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-22 03:00:00" d="2020-05-22 04:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Muhammad &amp; Larry</n>    <k>Unseen-filmed-build-up to the 1980 heavyweight title showdown between Muhammad Ali and his friend and former sparring partner Larry Holmes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-22 04:00:00" d="2020-05-22 05:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Chuck and Tito</n>    <k>A look at the career, friendship and rivalry of legendary MMA fighters Chuck Liddell and Tito Ortiz</k>  </p>
</a>
