<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="20" t="2019-07-11 00:18:51"><p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-17 05:00:00" d="2019-07-17 05:30:00"><n>Gallagher Premiership Rugby Union: Prem Rugby: Tries of the Season</n>    <k>The pick of the tries from the 2018/19 Gallagher Premiership season. Plus, interviews with Exeter Chiefs duo Henry Slade and Santiago Cordero</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-17 05:30:00" d="2019-07-17 06:00:00"><n>AMA Endurocross</n>    <k>All the best action from the opening round of the AMA EnduroCross in Orofino, Idaho</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-17 06:00:00" d="2019-07-17 06:30:00"><n>Red Bull Air Race Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from the third round of the Red Bull Air Race Championship at Lake Balaton in Hungary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-17 06:30:00" d="2019-07-17 07:00:00"><n>The Outdoor Sports Show</n>    <k>This exhilarating series captures the best action from extreme sports around the globe, including trail running, triathlon, skiing, snowboarding, climbing and paragliding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-17 07:00:00" d="2019-07-17 09:00:00"><n>AFL: AFL: Geelong Cats v St Kilda</n>    <k>Action from round 17 of the Australian Football League season as Geelong Cats and St Kilda go toe-to-toe at GMHBA Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-17 09:00:00" d="2019-07-17 11:00:00"><n>AFL: AFL: Richmond v GWS Giants</n>    <k>Action from round 17 of the Australian Football League as Richmond and GWS Giants face-off at the MCG</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-17 11:00:00" d="2019-07-17 13:00:00"><n>AFL: AFL: Port Adelaide v Brisbane</n>    <k>Action from round 17 of the Australian Football League season as Port Adelaide take on Brisbane Lions at the Adelaide Oval</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-17 13:00:00" d="2019-07-17 15:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Youngstown Boys</n>    <k>This documentary explores class and power dynamics in college sports through the parallel, interconnected journeys of Maurice Clarett and Jim Tressel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-17 15:00:00" d="2019-07-17 17:00:00"><n>Ashes Classics - 2010/11</n>    <k>A look back at the best moments from the second Test of the 2010/11 Ashes in Adelaide. England passed the 500-run mark in successive innings in the Ashes for the first time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-17 17:00:00" d="2019-07-17 19:00:00"><n>SGB Premiership: SGB: Peterborough v Belle Vue</n>    <k>Action from the SGB Premiership as Peterborough host Belle Vue at the East of England Showground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-17 19:00:00" d="2019-07-17 19:30:00"><n u="Classics in Europe: Liverpool v Saint-Etienne">Classics in Europe: Liverpool v Saint-Etienne 1977</n>    <k>We revisit this thrilling third round second leg clash at Anfield between Bob Paisley's Liverpool and French champions Saint-Etienne</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-17 19:30:00" d="2019-07-17 20:00:00"><n>Premier League 100: Premier League 100: Darren Bent</n>    <k>A brand new series celebrating some of the leading Premier League names to have achieved iconic milestones within the game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-17 20:00:00" d="2019-07-17 21:45:00"><n>BT Sport Films: BT Sport Films: State of Play</n>    <k>This BT Sport Film looks at the strengths and flaws of the modern game from the perspective of players, managers, clubs and society. Featuring Gareth Bale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-17 21:45:00" d="2019-07-17 22:00:00"><n>What I Wore: What I Wore: Jesse Lingard</n>    <k>Manchester United star Jesse Lingard describes his passion for football via the shirts which have defined his life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-17 22:00:00" d="2019-07-18 00:00:00"><n u="30 for 30: The U Part">30 for 30: The U Part 2</n>    <k>The University of Miami's American football team rose from the ashes to win another national championship, only to face new controversies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-18 00:00:00" d="2019-07-18 01:00:00"><n>Playback - Football's Greatest Rivalries: The Red Rivalry</n>    <k>The Red Rivalry. A look at the rivalry between Liverpool and Manchester United, including action from some of the more memorable matches. 2/5</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-18 01:00:00" d="2019-07-18 02:00:00"><n>Fishing: On The Bank</n>    <k>Highlights of the 2018 World Predator Classic hosted by the city of Hellevoetsluis in the Netherlands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-18 02:00:00" d="2019-07-18 03:00:00"><n>Euroformula Open Championship</n>    <k>Highlights of races one and two from round six of the Euroformula Championship at The Red Bull Ring in Austria</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-18 03:00:00" d="2019-07-18 04:30:00"><n>International GT Open Championship</n>    <k>Highlights of races one and two from round four of the International GT Open Championship at The Red Bull Ring in Austria</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2019-07-18 04:30:00" d="2019-07-18 05:00:00"><n>Irish Rally Review</n>    <k>Highlights of the Donegal International Rally, part of the Irish Rally series. (2/2)</k>  </p>
</a>
