<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-05-11 04:28:22"><p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-18 05:30:00" d="2020-05-18 06:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Little Big Men</n>    <k>Part of the award-winning 30 for 30 series, this documentary focuses on the 1982 Little League baseball champions from Kirkland, Washington</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-18 06:30:00" d="2020-05-18 07:00:00"><n>Premier League World</n>    <k>On this week's episode we sit down with Leonardo Ulloa to talk about Leicester City's title-winning season, plus Alan Pardew reflects on his time managing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-18 07:00:00" d="2020-05-18 07:30:00"><n>BT Sport Goals Reload</n>    <k>A round-up of the greatest goals from around the world, including action from Ligue 1 and the Bundesliga</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-18 07:30:00" d="2020-05-18 08:30:00"><n>Women's FIH Olympic Qualifiers: Women's Hockey: GBR v CHL 2019</n>    <k>Action from the Women's FIH Olympic Qualifiers as Great Britain met Chile at Lee Valley in London back in October</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-18 08:30:00" d="2020-05-18 10:00:00"><n>Heineken Champions Cup: Saracens v Racing 92 2019/20</n>    <k>Action from the Heineken Champions Cup as Saracens take on Racing 92 at Allianz Park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-18 10:00:00" d="2020-05-18 12:00:00"><n>V8 Supercars Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from race 25 of the Virgin Australia Supercars Championship at the Mount Panorama Circuit in Bathurst, New South Wales</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-18 12:00:00" d="2020-05-18 12:30:00"><n>Irish Rally Review</n>    <k>Highlights of the Cork 20 Tarmac Rally, part of the Irish Rally series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-18 12:30:00" d="2020-05-18 13:00:00"><n>Irish Rally Review</n>    <k>Highlights from the Skibbereen Rally National Championship, part of the Irish Rally series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-18 13:00:00" d="2020-05-18 14:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Deion's Double Play</n>    <k>The story of how NFL Hall of Famer Deion Sanders played an NFL game for the Atlanta Falcons in between two MLB games for the Atlanta Braves in a twenty-four hour window</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-18 14:00:00" d="2020-05-18 15:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Fernando Nation</n>    <k>In 1981, a pudgy 19-year-old Mexican pitcher, Fernando Valenzuela, took the MLB by storm, shattering America's image of the ace pitcher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-18 15:00:00" d="2020-05-18 16:30:00"><n>30 for 30: ESPN Films: The Marinovich Project</n>    <k>This documentary tells the story of Todd Marinovich, raised with the purpose of creating the perfect athlete. Documenting his ascent to stardom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-18 16:30:00" d="2020-05-18 18:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Bad Boys</n>    <k>The Detroit Pistons of the late 1980s and early '90s seemed willing to do anything to win. That characteristic made them loved - and hated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-18 18:30:00" d="2020-05-18 19:30:00"><n>30 for 30: The House of Steinbrenner</n>    <k>A shipbuilder named George Steinbrenner bought the sagging Yankees in 1973. He not only changed the face of a franchise, but also an entire sport</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-18 19:30:00" d="2020-05-18 20:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Unmatched</n>    <k>Chris Evert and Martina Navratilova were fierce tennis rivals in the 70s and 80s, but through it all they forged an unbreakable friendship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-18 20:30:00" d="2020-05-18 22:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Tommy</n>    <k>This documentary explores the rise and fall of one-time heavyweight boxing champion Tommy Morrison, who found his toughest fight lay outside the ring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-18 22:00:00" d="2020-05-18 23:00:00"><n>30 for 30: ESPN Films: The Real Rocky</n>    <k>Filmmaker Jeff Feuerzeig examines the story of Chuck 'The Bayonne Bleeder' Wepner, the real man behind the myth in Sylvester Stallone's Rocky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-18 23:00:00" d="2020-05-19 00:00:00"><n>BT Sport Films: BT Sport Films: Cornered</n>    <k>This moving documentary follows the life and career of journeyman boxer Johnny Greaves, veteran of 100 professional fights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-19 00:00:00" d="2020-05-19 01:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Broke</n>    <k>More money, more problems. This 30 for 30 documentary digs into the psychology of men whose competitive nature carried them to victory on the field</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-19 01:30:00" d="2020-05-19 01:45:00"><n>BT Sport Films Shorts: State of Play: Dawn Astle</n>    <k>BT Sport Films Shorts is a series of documentaries offering insight into why sport matters to elite sportsmen and women and fans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-19 01:45:00" d="2020-05-19 02:00:00"><n>30 for 30 Shorts</n>    <k>A look at Penn State's path from the 2011 scandal to their new campus statue, which is inspired by the 1948 side that overcame racial adversity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-19 02:00:00" d="2020-05-19 03:30:00"><n>30 for 30: ESPN Films: Renee</n>    <k>This documentary tells the story of Dr. Richard Raskin, a surgeon and nationally ranked professional tennis player who underwent life-altering surgery to become Dr. Renee Richards</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-05-19 03:30:00" d="2020-05-19 05:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Doc &amp; Darryl</n>    <k>Reunited at a Queens diner, ex-MLB stars Doc Gooden and Darryl Strawberry look back on the glory days of the mid-80s and their subsequent downfalls</k>  </p>
</a>
