<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-04-13 04:26:22"><p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-20 05:00:00" d="2020-04-20 05:30:00"><n>30 for 30 Shorts: 30 for 30 Shorts: Mack Wrestles</n>    <k>A look behind the scenes as Mack Beggs, a gifted athlete from Euless, Texas, struggles against the outside forces that stigmatize transgender athletes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-20 05:30:00" d="2020-04-20 07:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Brothers in Exile</n>    <k>The incredible story of half-brothers Livan and Orlando Hernandez, both of whom risked their lives to leave Cuba and become baseball stars in the US</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-20 07:00:00" d="2020-04-20 07:30:00"><n>BT Sport Goals Reload</n>    <k>A round-up of the greatest goals from around the world, including action from Ligue 1 and the Bundesliga</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-20 07:30:00" d="2020-04-20 08:30:00"><n>MotoGP: Moto3: Grand Prix of Japan</n>    <k>A look back at the action from the 2019 Moto3 race at the Grand Prix of Japan, round 16 of the season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-20 08:30:00" d="2020-04-20 09:30:00"><n>MotoGP: Moto2: Grand Prix of Japan</n>    <k>A look back at the action from the 2019 Moto2 race at the Grand Prix of Japan, round 16 of the season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-20 09:30:00" d="2020-04-20 10:30:00"><n>MotoGP: MotoGP: GP of Japan</n>    <k>A look back at the action from the 2019 MotoGP Grand Prix of Japan, round 16 of the season, as Marc Marquez secured all 25 points at Honda's home race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-20 10:30:00" d="2020-04-20 11:30:00"><n>FIM Speedway Highlights</n>    <k>All the best action from round five of the FIM Speedway Grand Prix season from Wroclaw, Poland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-20 11:30:00" d="2020-04-20 12:30:00"><n>Heineken Champions Cup Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from the opening round of the Heineken Champions Cup, including Gloucester v Toulouse, Bath v Ulster, Racing 92 v Saracens and La Rochelle v Exeter Chiefs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-20 12:30:00" d="2020-04-20 13:00:00"><n>BT Sport Reload</n>    <k>The best bits from BT Sport from the last week, exclusive interviews, the best action and so much more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-20 13:00:00" d="2020-04-20 15:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Bad Boys</n>    <k>The Detroit Pistons of the late 1980s and early '90s seemed willing to do anything to win. That characteristic made them loved - and hated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-20 15:00:00" d="2020-04-20 16:00:00"><n>30 for 30: This is What They Want</n>    <k>A look at the improbable run of Jimmy Connors at the 1991 US Open and how he helped make tennis a high-octane spectator sport. Part of the award-winning 30 for 30 series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-20 16:00:00" d="2020-04-20 17:00:00"><n>30 for 30: The Band That Wouldn't Die</n>    <k>This documentary, part of the acclaimed 30 for 30 series, tells the story of how Baltimore's fans coped with losing their NFL team in 1984</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-20 17:00:00" d="2020-04-20 18:00:00"><n>Nine for IX: Pat XO</n>    <k>This documentary tells the remarkable story of the late Pat Summitt, ex-women's college basketball head coach, as it has never been told before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-20 18:00:00" d="2020-04-20 19:30:00"><n>30 for 30: Believeland</n>    <k>This 30 for 30 documentary chronicles the struggles of Cleveland's major sports franchises over the past 50 years and its impact on the psyche of a typical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-20 19:30:00" d="2020-04-20 20:30:00"><n>30 for 30: Silly Little Game</n>    <k>Fantasy sports is a $4 billion industry, but for all of its success, the story of the game's inception is little known. Part of the award-winning 30 for 30 series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-20 20:30:00" d="2020-04-20 22:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Trojan War</n>    <k>Pete Carroll led the USC Trojans back to the top of college football. But in Hollywood, you don't always get the perfect ending. Part of the award-winning 30 for 30 series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-20 22:00:00" d="2020-04-20 23:30:00"><n>BT Sport Films: BT Sport Films: The Crazy Gang</n>    <k>The story of Wimbledon FC in the 80s, the notorious win-at-all costs team which rose from non-league obscurity to winning the FA Cup in less than ten years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-20 23:30:00" d="2020-04-21 01:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Playing For The Mob</n>    <k>Mobster Henry Hill, made infamous in the movie Goodfellas, helped fix college basketball games. This is a tale of greed, betrayal and reckoning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-21 01:00:00" d="2020-04-21 02:00:00"><n>30 for 30: ESPN Films: Charismatic</n>    <k>This documentary tells the story of the 1999 miracle that was Charismatic, a horse that emerged from nowhere to win the first two races in the Triple Crown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-21 02:00:00" d="2020-04-21 03:30:00"><n>30 for 30: The Year of the Scab</n>    <k>This documentary, part of the acclaimed 30 for 30 series, details the incredible tale of the Washington Redskins' replacement team that played during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-04-21 03:30:00" d="2020-04-21 05:00:00"><n>30 for 30: Winning Time: Reggie Miller vs The NY Knicks</n>    <k>Part of the award-winning 30 for 30 series, this documentary looks at how NBA legend Reggie Miller became an enemy to New York Knicks fans</k>  </p>
</a>
