<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-05-28 04:32:44"><p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-04 05:00:00" d="2020-06-04 06:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Playing For The Mob</n>    <k>Mobster Henry Hill, made infamous in the movie Goodfellas, helped fix college basketball games. This is a tale of greed, betrayal and reckoning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-04 06:30:00" d="2020-06-04 07:00:00"><n>Premier League World</n>    <k>This week we take a trip down memory lane with Mick McCarthy, and also speak to the first Tanzanian footballer to ever play in the Premier League, Aston</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-04 07:00:00" d="2020-06-04 07:30:00"><n>Bundesliga Special: Bundesliga: Mission Meisterschale</n>    <k>With the race for the Bundesliga title set to go down to the wire yet again this season, take a look at Bayern Munich and Borussia Dortmund's title chances</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-04 07:30:00" d="2020-06-04 08:30:00"><n>FIM Speedway Highlights</n>    <k>All the thrills and spills from round four of the 2019 FIM Speedway Grand Prix in Hallstavik, Sweden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-04 08:30:00" d="2020-06-04 11:00:00"><n>Gallagher Premiership Rugby Highlights</n>    <k>The best of the action from round 13 of the Gallagher Premiership, including Bristol Bears v Harlequins, Exeter Chiefs v Bath Rugby and Saracens v Leicester Tigers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-04 11:00:00" d="2020-06-04 12:00:00"><n>World Rallycross Highlights</n>    <k>Highlights from the fourth round of the 2019 FIA World Rallycross Championship at Silverstone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-04 12:00:00" d="2020-06-04 13:00:00"><n>Sailing World Cup</n>    <k>Highlights from the 2019 Sailing World Cup Series final in Marseille, France</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-04 13:00:00" d="2020-06-04 13:30:00"><n>SEC Storied: Coach Bernie</n>    <k>This documentary chronicles the career of Bernadette Locke-Mattox, the first woman to serve as an assistant coach in Division I men's basketball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-04 13:30:00" d="2020-06-04 14:00:00"><n>SEC Storied: The Bo You Don't Know</n>    <k>Bo Jackson hit 500-foot home runs and ran over linebackers. This documentary looks at the man considered one of the greatest athletes in history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-04 14:00:00" d="2020-06-04 16:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Catholics vs Convicts</n>    <k>In 1988, Notre Dame hosted Miami Hurricanes in what was one of the greatest games in college football history. This 30 for 30 documentary tells the story</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-04 16:00:00" d="2020-06-04 17:00:00"><n>30 for 30: The Band That Wouldn't Die</n>    <k>This documentary, part of the acclaimed 30 for 30 series, tells the story of how Baltimore's fans coped with losing their NFL team in 1984</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-04 17:00:00" d="2020-06-04 17:30:00"><n>30 for 30: Nixon's National Champs</n>    <k>ESPN Films takes a look into the story of how the 1969 college football national champion was crowned by President Richard Nixon and the drama that surrounded it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-04 17:30:00" d="2020-06-04 18:00:00"><n>30 for 30: ESPN Films: Two Points, One title</n>    <k>On January 2nd 1984 Nebraska Head Coach Tom Osborne made a coaching decision that decided the fate of two programs in a single play. Part of the ESPN Films series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-04 18:00:00" d="2020-06-04 19:30:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: What Carter Lost</n>    <k>In 1988, a Texas high school fielded the football team that many consider the greatest ever, yet it's likely you have never heard their story</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-04 19:30:00" d="2020-06-04 20:30:00"><n>30 for 30: Small Potatoes: Who Killed the USFL?</n>    <k>Part of the acclaimed 30 for 30 series, this documentary examines Donald Trump's involvement in the demise of the United States Football League in the mid-1980s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-04 20:30:00" d="2020-06-04 22:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: The Year of the Scab</n>    <k>This documentary, part of the acclaimed 30 for 30 series, details the incredible tale of the Washington Redskins' replacement team that played during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-04 22:00:00" d="2020-06-04 23:00:00"><n>BT Sport Films: True Grit</n>    <k>With contributions from the sport's biggest names, BT Sport Films offers an extraordinary insight into the mental fortitude required in order to succeed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-04 23:00:00" d="2020-06-05 00:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Ghosts of Ole Miss</n>    <k>In 1962, the University of Mississippi erupted into violence over integration while swelling with pride over their unbeaten American football team</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 00:00:00" d="2020-06-05 01:00:00"><n>30 for 30: 30 for 30: Run Ricky Run</n>    <k>Ricky Williams recorded himself during his year away from American football. This is the misunderstood athlete's story in his own words</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 01:00:00" d="2020-06-05 03:00:00"><n>30 for 30: ESPN Films: Catching Hell</n>    <k>This film uses the case of Steve Bartman - the fan who interfered with an in-play ball in the 2003 NLCS and was vilified for it - to examine scapegoating</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1085" o="2020-06-05 03:00:00" d="2020-06-05 05:00:00"><n>30 for 30: The Gospel According to Mac</n>    <k>This 30 for 30 documentary examines Bill McCartney and his sometimes-controversial mixture of American football and evangelicalism as Colorado Buffaloes</k>  </p>
</a>
