<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="15" t="2019-08-10 01:40:55"><p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-16 05:00:00" d="2019-08-16 06:00:00"><n>Skywalker: The David Thompson Story</n>    <k>Sports legend David Thompson at 6-foot-3 was the player who revolutionized &quot;above the rim&quot; basketball. Inventor of the &quot;Alley Oop,&quot; conqueror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-16 06:00:00" d="2019-08-16 08:00:00"><n u="Nuggets/Sonics, 1994 Western Conference 1st Round - Game">Nuggets/Sonics, 1994 Western Conference 1st Round - Game 5</n>    <k>The Nuggets stunned the Sonics to win the deciding game in the 1st Round Series. It was the first time an 8 seed defeated a 1 seed in a Playoff series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-16 08:00:00" d="2019-08-16 10:00:00"><n u="Blazers/Nuggets, 1977 Western Conference Semifinals - Game">Blazers/Nuggets, 1977 Western Conference Semifinals - Game 5</n>    <k>David &quot;Skywalker&quot; Thompson lead all scorers with 31 points as the Nuggets defeat Bill Walton, 15 points and 14 rebounds, and the Trail Blazers 114-105</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-16 10:00:00" d="2019-08-16 12:00:00"><n>Celtics/Nuggets, 11/5</n>    <k>Jamal Murray scored a career-high 48 points, including 19 in the fourth quarter, and the Denver Nuggets overcame a sluggish start to beat the Boston Celtics 115-107</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-16 12:00:00" d="2019-08-16 12:30:00"><n>Centers of the Universe: Shaq &amp; Yao</n>    <k>Every time they met on the court, it was a colossal event, Shaquille O'Neal and Yao Ming, two giants battling for supremacy in the league</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-16 12:30:00" d="2019-08-16 14:30:00"><n>Magic/Nets, 4/23/1993</n>    <k>Magic G Nick Anderson scored 50 points, despite coming off the bench, to help defeat the Nets. Magic C Shaquille O'Neal also broke the backboard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-16 14:30:00" d="2019-08-16 16:30:00"><n>Magic/Hornets, 11/9/1994</n>    <k>Shaquille O'Neal had 46 points and 20 rebounds and the Magic rallied from an 18 point deficit to take the Hornets into overtime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-16 16:30:00" d="2019-08-16 17:00:00"><n>2008 NBA Dunk Contest</n>    <k>Magic C Dwight Howard and Timberwolves G Gerald Green compete in the Finals of the 2008 NBA Slam Dunk Contest from New Orleans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-16 17:00:00" d="2019-08-16 19:00:00"><n u="Cavaliers/Magic, 2009 Eastern Conference Finals - Game">Cavaliers/Magic, 2009 Eastern Conference Finals - Game 6</n>    <k>Dwight Howard dominated inside for 40 points, Rashard Lewis added 18 as the Magic defeated LeBron James and the Cleveland Cavaliers in Game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-16 19:00:00" d="2019-08-16 21:00:00"><n u="Magic/Celtics">Magic/Celtics (Apr. 7)</n>    <k>When the horn sounded on their 116-108 win over the Celtics to clinch the Magic's first postseason berth since 2012, they took some extra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-16 21:00:00" d="2019-08-16 22:00:00"><n u="Magic/Raptors, Game">Magic/Raptors, Game 1</n>    <k>D.J. Augustin scored 25 points, including the tiebreaking 3-pointer with 3.5 seconds left, and the Magic beat the Toronto Raptors 104-101</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-16 22:00:00" d="2019-08-17 00:00:00"><n u="Pacers/Magic, 1995 Eastern Conference Finals - Game">Pacers/Magic, 1995 Eastern Conference Finals - Game 2</n>    <k>Magic C. Shaquille O'Neal put the team on his back with 39 points to topple the pesky Pacers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-17 00:00:00" d="2019-08-17 02:00:00"><n u="Magic/Bulls, 1995 Eastern Conference Semifinals - Game">Magic/Bulls, 1995 Eastern Conference Semifinals - Game 6</n>    <k>Shaquille O'Neal and the up-and-coming Orlando Magic defeated Michael Jordan and the Bulls. This was Jordan's only Playoff Series loss between 1991 and 1998</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-17 02:00:00" d="2019-08-17 04:00:00"><n u="USA White vs USA Blue">USA White vs USA Blue (Las Vegas, Nevada)</n>    <k>The USA Basketball team, in preparation for the 2019 FIBA World Cup, will play an inter-squad exhibition game in Las Vegas. Players participating</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-17 04:00:00" d="2019-08-17 06:00:00"><n u="USA vs Spain">USA vs Spain (Anaheim, California)</n>  </p>
</a>
