<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2019-08-09 01:39:20"><p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-15 05:00:00" d="2019-08-15 06:00:00"><n u="Cavaliers/Pacers, Game">Cavaliers/Pacers, Game 3</n>    <k>On the one-year anniversary of a historic playoff collapse against Cleveland, Indiana flipped the script by rallying from a 17-point halftime deficit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-15 06:00:00" d="2019-08-15 07:30:00"><n u="Stars/Pacers, 1973 ABA Western Division Finals - Game">Stars/Pacers, 1973 ABA Western Division Finals - Game 6</n>    <k>Pacers F George McGinnis scored 23 points to lead the Pacers to a clinching victory over the Utah Stars in the ABA Playoffs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-15 07:30:00" d="2019-08-15 08:00:00"><n>2004 NBA Dunk Contest</n>    <k>Pacers G. Fred Jones and Warriors G. Jason Richardson compete in the Finals of the 2004 NBA Slam Dunk Contest from Los Angeles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-15 08:00:00" d="2019-08-15 10:00:00"><n u="Pacers/Bulls">Pacers/Bulls (Jan. 4)</n>    <k>Pacers G Victor Oladipo banked in a 3-pointer from just above the top of the arc with 0.3 seconds left in overtime to give Indiana its sixth straight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-15 10:00:00" d="2019-08-15 12:00:00"><n>Pacers/Hornets, 11/28/1992</n>    <k>Pacers G Reggie Miller scores a career-high 57 points to lead Indiana</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-15 12:00:00" d="2019-08-15 13:00:00"><n u="Spurs/Nuggets, Game">Spurs/Nuggets, Game 7</n>    <k>Nikola Jokic had another triple-double, 21 points, 15 rebounds and 10 assists, Jamal Murray hit a clutch floater with 36.8 seconds remaining</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-15 13:00:00" d="2019-08-15 14:00:00"><n u="Nuggets/Trail Blazers, Game">Nuggets/Trail Blazers, Game 4</n>    <k>Nikola Jokic had 21 points, 12 rebounds and 11 assists for his second straight triple-double and fourth of the playoffs, and the Denver Nuggets evened</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-15 14:00:00" d="2019-08-15 15:00:00"><n u="Trail Blazers/Nuggets, Game">Trail Blazers/Nuggets, Game 5</n>    <k>Nikola Jokic scored 25 points and tied a team playoff high with 19 rebounds, and Paul Millsap injected some experience into a series dominated by youth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-15 15:00:00" d="2019-08-15 17:00:00"><n u="Nuggets/Sonics, 1994 Western Conference 1st Round - Game">Nuggets/Sonics, 1994 Western Conference 1st Round - Game 5</n>    <k>The Nuggets stunned the Sonics to win the deciding game in the 1st Round Series. It was the first time an 8 seed defeated a 1 seed in a Playoff series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-15 17:00:00" d="2019-08-15 17:30:00"><n>NBA Journey: Dikembe Mutombo</n>    <k>This half-hour special follows the journey of Dikembe Mutombo, a charismatic basketball player and humanitarian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-15 17:30:00" d="2019-08-15 19:30:00"><n>Bucks/Nuggets, 4/1</n>    <k>Nikola Jokic had 35 points and 13 rebounds, Jamal Murray scored 18 of his 27 points after the third quarter and the Denver Nuggets rallied from eight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-15 19:30:00" d="2019-08-15 20:00:00"><n>Association: Denver Nuggets #1, The</n>    <k>As the 2011-12 season nears, the Denver Nuggets face many questions with only seven players signed to the roster. Viewers will go behind-the-scenes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-15 20:00:00" d="2019-08-15 20:30:00"><n>Association: Denver Nuggets #2, The</n>    <k>The Nuggets visit New York, and their old teammate Carmelo Anthony. Later, mid-season injuries strain the team and leave the future in doubt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-15 20:30:00" d="2019-08-15 21:00:00"><n>Association: Denver Nuggets #3, The</n>    <k>After injuries plague their starting lineup, the Denver Nuggets look to ride out a tough stretch against playoff-level Western Conference opponents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-15 21:00:00" d="2019-08-15 21:30:00"><n>Association: Denver Nuggets #4, The</n>    <k>A behind-the-scenes look at how the Denver Nuggets handled one of the biggest deals made at the Trade Deadline--sending veteran Nene to Washington</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-15 21:30:00" d="2019-08-15 22:00:00"><n>Association: Denver Nuggets #5, The</n>    <k>The Nuggets face their longest road trip of the season, with a Playoff spot hanging in the balance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-15 22:00:00" d="2019-08-15 22:30:00"><n>Association: Denver Nuggets #6, The</n>    <k>The Nuggets continue battling for one of the final Playoff spots in the West. Nuggets Head Coach George Karl, a cancer survivor who lives with the disease</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-15 22:30:00" d="2019-08-15 23:00:00"><n>Association: Denver Nuggets #7, The</n>    <k>The Nuggets try to pull the upset over Kobe Bryant and the Lakers in the 1st Round of the NBA Playoffs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-15 23:00:00" d="2019-08-16 01:00:00"><n u="Nuggets/Mavericks, 2009 NBA Western Conference Semifinals - Game">Nuggets/Mavericks, 2009 NBA Western Conference Semifinals - Game 3</n>    <k>Behind 30 points from Carmelo Anthony and 28 from Chauncey Billups, the Denver Nuggets beat the Dallas Mavericks 124-110 to wrap up their semifinal series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-16 01:00:00" d="2019-08-16 03:00:00"><n>Celtics/Nuggets, 2/20/1985</n>    <k>Larry Bird led all scorers with 40 points, but it wasn't enough to overcome Alex English, 38 points, the Denver Nuggets who defeated the Boston Celtics 129-132</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-16 03:00:00" d="2019-08-16 04:00:00"><n u="Spurs/Nuggets, Game">Spurs/Nuggets, Game 7</n>    <k>Nikola Jokic had another triple-double, 21 points, 15 rebounds and 10 assists, Jamal Murray hit a clutch floater with 36.8 seconds remaining</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1099" o="2019-08-16 04:00:00" d="2019-08-16 05:00:00"><n u="Nuggets/Trail Blazers, Game">Nuggets/Trail Blazers, Game 4</n>    <k>Nikola Jokic had 21 points, 12 rebounds and 11 assists for his second straight triple-double and fourth of the playoffs, and the Denver Nuggets evened</k>  </p>
</a>
