<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="51" t="2019-07-11 00:20:30"><p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 05:10:00" d="2019-07-15 05:35:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Scarlet Mark/The Last Yogi Standing
Max tries to find out who tried to drop a piano on him. Gark learns Max was a yoga champion and signs himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 05:35:00" d="2019-07-15 06:00:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Vet/No Pranks Thanks
Gark goes to the vet in place of Max, not realising he may explode if prodded, endangering the planet. Max plays pranks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 06:00:00" d="2019-07-15 06:29:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% Welcome Back, Catfish!/All the Juice that's Fish to Swim: Catfish Booray returns to Norrisville as a substitute teacher. As a result of a fad for frozen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 06:29:00" d="2019-07-15 07:00:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% Julian's Birthday Surprise/True Bromance
Randy takes a green ball of evil to a party and the door to an evil dimension is opened. The Sorcerer transforms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 07:00:00" d="2019-07-15 07:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Spider-Man">Marvel's Spider-Man I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Stark Expo
Spider-Man partners with Iron Man to stop Ghost from taking over and destroying the Stark Expo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 07:29:00" d="2019-07-15 08:00:00"><n u="Space Chickens In Space">Space Chickens In Space I (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Presidential Coop/Pale Blue Rock
To be elected student president candidates face daft tasks. Sentient Space Rocks show up to party and cause trouble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 08:00:00" d="2019-07-15 08:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (30)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Doofapus/Norm Unleashed
The boys' device accidentally liquefies Candace. Doof has jury duty so robot Norm takes over the day's evil scheme - using weapons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 08:29:00" d="2019-07-15 09:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (31)</n><t>S</t>    <k>When Worlds Collide/The Road to Danville
A planet is hurtling towards Earth and the boys must avert it. Doof and Perry get lost in the desert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 09:00:00" d="2019-07-15 09:29:00"><n u="Mech-X4">Mech-X4 I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>59% Let's Call It Mech-X4 - Part One
When Ryan Walker's mysterious new power leads him to a giant robot, he and his friends go up against a monstrous threat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 09:29:00" d="2019-07-15 10:00:00"><n u="Mech-X4">Mech-X4 II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>59% Versus the Mountain
Ryan gets a lead on his biological father Randall, only to find him in mortal danger. The team races against time, and a collapsing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 10:00:00" d="2019-07-15 10:29:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law II (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Abducting Murphy's Law
Milo is abducted by the evil octopus aliens and, their ship is destroyed. Zack and Melissa re-inspire Doof to help try to find Milo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 10:29:00" d="2019-07-15 11:00:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law II (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% The Goulash Legacy/The Dog Who Knew Too Much
Milo tries to save Mom's goulash using Doof's hand-held-inators. Diogee eats a jump drive enemy agents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 11:00:00" d="2019-07-15 11:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Hiya Henry/People Watching
Cricket Green's family moves from country to Big City. As they acclimatize, their perspectives on differences between country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 11:29:00" d="2019-07-15 12:00:00"><n u="Kick Buttowski Suburban Daredevil">Kick Buttowski Suburban Daredevil I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Kicked Out/Kick the Habit
Kick's favourite hang-out, The Gully, has been taken over by Brad. Kick must go stunt free for 24 hours to stop being sent to military school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 12:00:00" d="2019-07-15 12:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Double Dipper
Stan throws a big party to promote Mystery Shack, while Dipper uses a strange photocopier to make clones of himself, so that he can impress Wendy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 12:29:00" d="2019-07-15 13:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Fight Fighters
When Dipper falls out with Robbie over Wendy, he brings a character from his favourite arcade game to help him fight it out. Mabel tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 13:00:00" d="2019-07-15 13:29:00"><n u="Supa Strikas">Supa Strikas II (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>62% Hypno-Test
The most prized artifact in Supa Strikas' club history is the Secret Training Manual. Shakes uncovers a plot involving hypnosis and their own training manual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 13:29:00" d="2019-07-15 14:00:00"><n u="Ducktales S2">Ducktales S2 II (9) (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Treasure of the Found Lamp
The boys track a missing artefact across Duckburg, Scrooge and Webby stall a warrior looking for it with a phoney quest! S2</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 14:00:00" d="2019-07-15 14:29:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bionic Birthday Fail
It's Leo's birthday. The Lab Rats have never had a party of their own so decide to throw a surprise one for Leo, but they forget to ask him!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 14:29:00" d="2019-07-15 15:00:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Death Spiral Smackdown
Leo hopes to capitalise on Adam's strength and teams up with him for a fitness contest. He feeds Adam pellets which activate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 15:00:00" d="2019-07-15 15:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>At Last
Candace's dream comes true when Mum finally comes home. Phineas and Ferb are sent to military school. But she's surprised to discover she misses them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 15:29:00" d="2019-07-15 16:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Greece Lightning/Leave the Busting to Us
Greek mythology inspires the boys to hold a motorised chariot race. They build a giant water slide and Candace</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 16:00:00" d="2019-07-15 16:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Spider-Man">Marvel's Spider-Man I (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Venom
When Spidey discovers a symbiote has escaped the Avengers' compound and attached itself to a new host, he must find out how to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 16:29:00" d="2019-07-15 17:00:00"><n u="Space Chickens In Space">Space Chickens In Space I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Atori/Players Gotta Play
The Chickens need jobs - bounty hunting pays well! When a play organised by chickens starts an intergalactic war, they must stage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 17:00:00" d="2019-07-15 17:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Swimming Fool/Tilly's Goat
The family visits an indoor pool for the first time. Will Tilly enter the family goat in a dog show?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 17:29:00" d="2019-07-15 18:00:00"><n u="Big Hero 6 The Series">Big Hero 6 The Series I (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mini-Max
Hiro invents a tiny bot sidekick, Mini-max. Later, he begins an investigation into Professor Granville's mysterious past and suspicious activity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 18:00:00" d="2019-07-15 18:29:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Going the Extra Milo/The Undergrounders
New kid Zack meets accident prone Milo Murphy, While on the subway Milo's car goes off course and he discovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 18:29:00" d="2019-07-15 19:00:00"><n u="Ducktales">Ducktales I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Mising Links of Moorshire
Scrooge and Glomgold discover a lost golf course. Scrooge wants to share it with his nephews, until he realizes Dewey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 19:00:00" d="2019-07-15 19:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Druselsteinoween/Face Your Fear
Vanessa holds her Halloween party in Doof's castle in Druselstein. When Vanessa asks Doof to babysit her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 19:29:00" d="2019-07-15 20:00:00"><n u="Mech-X4">Mech-X4 II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>59% Versus the Dark Knight
A new monster creates a city-wide blackout and disables Mech-X4. The team must get the robot working again to stop the beast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 20:00:00" d="2019-07-15 20:50:00"><n>Star Wars Resistance: The Recruit</n>    <k>Kaz embarks on his mission for the Resistance and must take part in a dangerous sky race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 20:50:00" d="2019-07-15 21:00:00"><n u="Disney Mickey Mouse">Disney Mickey Mouse III (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Turkish Delights
A pair of jealous merchants threatens Mickey's treats stand inside the Grand Bazaar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 21:00:00" d="2019-07-15 21:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Avengers: Black Panther's">Marvel's Avengers: Black Panther's V (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>T'Chanda
Black Panther discovers secrets about his grandfather, T'Chanda</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 21:29:00" d="2019-07-15 22:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Dreamscaperers
Lil' Gideon is defeated by Grunkle Stan. He uses a mind demon to lure Dipper, Mabel and Soos into Stan's mind to gain the knowledge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 22:00:00" d="2019-07-15 22:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Gideon Rises
After Lil' Gideon takes over the Mystery Shack, Dipper and Mabel try to get it back. But Lil' Gideon is always one step ahead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 22:29:00" d="2019-07-15 23:00:00"><n u="Kick Buttowski Suburban Daredevil">Kick Buttowski Suburban Daredevil II (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>K-Nein/Bromance
Kick brings home an injured stray then finds it's a &quot;safety dog&quot;. He must choose between the dog and being a daredevil. Brad needs Kick's help to get a date</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 23:00:00" d="2019-07-15 23:29:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% The Little Engine that Couldn't/ The Llama Incident: Melissa hopes her dad will see Milo is more than a disaster area. Milo and Melissa tell Zack the story</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-15 23:29:00" d="2019-07-16 00:00:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Star Struck/Disaster of my Dreams
Chaos ensues when Milo tries to get an actor's autograph. Elliot must cope with Milo to be school safety monitor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 00:00:00" d="2019-07-16 00:25:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Demolition Cube/Peanutland
Andre ends up as Pepita's pawn in a school demolition derby. Andre and Chobado go in search of a legendary peanut land</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 00:25:00" d="2019-07-16 00:50:00"><n u="Dude That's My Ghost">Dude That's My Ghost I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Billy Joe the Scholar/Cuckoo's Nest
Ponzi finds a &quot;no weirdos&quot; rule in the school handbook so invites himself to the Wright home to get the evidence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 00:50:00" d="2019-07-16 01:15:00"><n u="Dude That's My Ghost">Dude That's My Ghost I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>School of Rockers/How to Impress Ladies
Spencer fears he's going to bomb at the school talent show, but when Billy gets mixed into a batch of Jane's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 01:15:00" d="2019-07-16 01:35:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja II (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% Mastermind of Disastermind/The Brawn Also Rises
Howard convinces Randy he'd be an undefeatable villain. Howard and Randy pretend to be chased</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 01:35:00" d="2019-07-16 02:00:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja II (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% Debbie Meddle/Aplopalypse Now
Randy must convince Debbie he is not the Ninja before she announces it to everyone. Randy asks Plop Plop to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 02:00:00" d="2019-07-16 02:25:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Shelby Holmes/Boyster Clone
Rafik and Boyster envy the Nerds and their detective club. Boyster is so obsessed with his new video game that he creates a clone of himself!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 02:25:00" d="2019-07-16 02:45:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (26)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Now You See/Rash Decision It
Shelby's addicted to his phone but won't admit it. Can Boyster cure him? Why is Eugene is scratching? Boyster must find out or go back to the sea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 02:45:00" d="2019-07-16 03:10:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Gark Knight Rises/Any Takers
Gark becomes a superhero to fight a chameleon supervillain. Max tries to fake an alien abduction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 03:10:00" d="2019-07-16 03:35:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>I, Maxine/Gark's Got Talent
After Max wishes he had powers like Gark, Gark helps him go robotic to earn respect. Max becomes Gark's agent when he shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 03:35:00" d="2019-07-16 04:00:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja I (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% McSatchle/Fart-Topia
Randy and Howard need money so get jobs at McFist-O-Plex. Randy helps Terry take over McFist Industries turning Whoopee World</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 04:00:00" d="2019-07-16 04:20:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja I (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% The McHugger Games/The McFreak Show
Ninja steals a pair of shorts. His actions jeopardise his secret identity. Randy wants a McFreak as a pet, but finds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 04:20:00" d="2019-07-16 04:45:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Shelby the Art Lover/Skeleton
Shelby steals a painting of a clam shell: he's in love! Boyster discovers he has no skeleton, so he swallows one belonging to a monkey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 04:45:00" d="2019-07-16 05:10:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Strange New Friend/Go Fish
Boyster doesn't realise that new boy Bruno is a chef with a liking for oysters. Boyster breaks Shelby's TV and replaces</k>  </p>
</a>
