<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="37" t="2020-05-26 04:33:46"><p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 05:10:00" d="2020-06-02 05:35:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Happy Earthday/Zaxos Returns
Gark gets a surprise party to celebrate his first year on Earth. Max deduces a giant wart on Betty's nose means Zaxos is back, then she is!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 05:35:00" d="2020-06-02 06:00:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Virtual Insanity/Birthdaystruction
Max and Gark are transported back through video game time. Max summons The Flarshaman, galactic birthday taskmaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 06:00:00" d="2020-06-02 06:29:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Burrito Hotel/ Brenda Gets the Boot
Andre and Champion's contest leads them into Gordon's trap. Gordon takes Andre to traffic court for reckless driving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 06:29:00" d="2020-06-02 07:00:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Brenda's Got Soul/Fifteen Minutes of Furiki
Andre lies to Chobado when he pretends to be Brenda, putting their friendship at risk. Andre becomes famous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 07:00:00" d="2020-06-02 07:29:00"><n u="Star Vs The Forces Of Evil">Star Vs The Forces Of Evil III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Puddle Defender/King Ludo
Moon and Star's safety is compromised so they hide at Buffrog's house. King Ludo reigns over the Butterfly castle but is controlled by Toffee</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 07:29:00" d="2020-06-02 08:00:00"><n u="Star Vs The Forces Of Evil">Star Vs The Forces Of Evil III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Toffee
Star comes home and is determined to stop Ludo's tyrannical reign over the Butterfly Kingdom. Ludo rejects her help, but she is determined to stop Toffee for good</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 08:00:00" d="2020-06-02 08:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Traffic Cam Caper/Bowl-R-Ama Drama
Candace borrows the traffic camera DVD to prove to her mother what the boys have been doing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 08:29:00" d="2020-06-02 09:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>How to Make a Monster/Oil on Candace
Grandfather tells the boys about a relative called Phineastein who built a monster platypus. The boys tour round</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 09:00:00" d="2020-06-02 09:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Double Dipper
Stan throws a big party to promote Mystery Shack, while Dipper uses a strange photocopier to make clones of himself, so that he can impress Wendy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 09:29:00" d="2020-06-02 10:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Irrational Treasure
The kids try to expose Pacifica Northwest's fraudulent claim that her great-grandfather was the founder of Gravity Falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 10:00:00" d="2020-06-02 10:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Tri-State Trilogy of Terror
In this show's three short stories Perry becomes evil, Doof meets a giant floating baby head that grants wishes, and Candace's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 10:29:00" d="2020-06-02 11:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Druselsteinoween/Face Your Fear
Vanessa holds her Halloween party in Doof's castle in Druselstein. When Vanessa asks Doof to babysit her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 11:00:00" d="2020-06-02 11:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Phineas and Ferb must help Love Handel prove Klimpaloon's existence in time for an awards ceremony, or he'll be barred forever from the world of fact-based song writing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 11:29:00" d="2020-06-02 12:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Doof 101/Father's Day
Doof is sent to teach science for his community service to Vanessa's embarrassment. Doof finds the precious lawn gnome</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 12:00:00" d="2020-06-02 12:29:00"><n u="Right Now Kapow">Right Now Kapow I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Crime Scene/Bulkbodies
A detective investigates a robbery. A basketball deflates. A stinkpeasant becomes king. A trash barge is cool. A beautiful monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 12:29:00" d="2020-06-02 13:00:00"><n u="Right Now Kapow">Right Now Kapow I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>R &amp; B/ The Sphinx
A singer has brown eyes. A werewolf is not a mind reader. A sphinx is such a drama queen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 13:00:00" d="2020-06-02 13:29:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats III (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Which Father Knows Best? Davenport's attempts at rebuilding Bree's bionic chip fail, forcing Leo to go behind his back and ask Douglas for help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 13:29:00" d="2020-06-02 14:00:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats III (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cyborg Shark Attack
After Leo sees a shark movie that terrifies him, Adam and Chase scare him with a cyborg shark. But the shark goes rogue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 14:00:00" d="2020-06-02 14:29:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats III (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Brother Battle
Leo and Principal Terry battle to be the millionth customer in the shop where Bree works. Donald and his brother squabble, while Chase</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 14:29:00" d="2020-06-02 15:00:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats III (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Armed and Dangerous
Leo shows off his new bionic arm to Janelle, but it goes out of control. When Agent Graham turns the kids into celebrities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 15:00:00" d="2020-06-02 15:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cricketsitter/Backflip Bill
Cricket has a list of crazy stunts to do while Bill is away. Cricket tries to help Bill realise his childhood dream</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 15:29:00" d="2020-06-02 16:00:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Photo Op/Remy Rescue
Bill tries to trick the family into having a photo taken. Can Cricket stop Remy's parents sending him away to school?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 16:00:00" d="2020-06-02 16:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Delivery of Destiny/ Let's Bounce:Delivery man Paul (Simon Pegg) is a hero when he saves the town. Ferb's anti-gravity device inspires Phineas to suspend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 16:29:00" d="2020-06-02 17:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quietest Day Ever/Bully Bromance Breakup
The boys must be quiet while Mum sits an online knitting test. Baljeet stops being Buford's nerd. Buford joins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 17:00:00" d="2020-06-02 17:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Oh There You are Perry/Swiss Family Phineas
Perry goes missing and Candace thinks it's her fault, but he's been relocated. The Flynn family takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 17:29:00" d="2020-06-02 18:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Phineas and Ferb's Cliptastic Countdown
Here's a chance to see viewers' favourite muscial numbers in a cliptastic special compilation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 18:00:00" d="2020-06-02 18:29:00"><n u="New: Disney">New: Disney 11 III (52)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Episode 212
The team can't believe Gabo has been suspended. Lorenzo and Delfina arrange a date. Ricky and Dede follow Laura's secretary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 18:29:00" d="2020-06-02 19:00:00"><n u="Ducktales">Ducktales II (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Happy Birthday, Doofus Drake! Louie teams with Goldie to scam their way through Doofus' dangerous party. Huey pushes himself out of his comfort</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 19:00:00" d="2020-06-02 19:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Coffee Quest/Phoenix Rises
There's a coffee shortage. Can Cricket get some? The Greens' dog Phoenix runs away. Can the family find her?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 19:29:00" d="2020-06-02 20:00:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Uncaged
Cricket tries to impress Nancy by releasing an orang-utan from the zoo but accidentally sets free all the animals, who run riot in the city</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 20:00:00" d="2020-06-02 20:29:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Rats Strike Back
Sick of constantly working without time off, the Rats go on strike in an attempt to get what they want, even though Davenport</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 20:29:00" d="2020-06-02 21:00:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats II (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Parallel Universe
Davenport creates an invention that accidentally transports Leo to a parallel Universe, where he has bionic powers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 21:00:00" d="2020-06-02 21:29:00"><n u="Disney">Disney 11 III (52)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Episode 212
The team can't believe Gabo has been suspended. Lorenzo and Delfina arrange a date. Ricky and Dede follow Laura's secretary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 21:29:00" d="2020-06-02 22:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Traffic Cam Caper/Bowl-R-Ama Drama
Candace borrows the traffic camera DVD to prove to her mother what the boys have been doing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 22:00:00" d="2020-06-02 22:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Golf War
After being belittled by Pacifica too many times, Mabel challenges her to a miniature golf-off, which gets out of control when some local</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 22:29:00" d="2020-06-02 23:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Sock Opera
Attempting to impress a local puppeteer Mabel puts on a sock puppet rock opera but her show goes wrong when Dipper's drive to uncover journal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-02 23:00:00" d="2020-06-03 02:00:00"><n u="Right Now Kapow">Right Now Kapow I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Beach Detectives/Order Number Nine
A pair of detectives goes north of the boardwalk. A chicken sandwich is ordered</k>  </p>
</a>
