<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="35" t="2020-04-16 04:31:05"><p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 05:10:00" d="2020-04-23 05:35:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Fat Cat/Bathtub of Terror
Max emulates his new TV idol by over-eating. Max is terrified of looking into the bath as he's scared something terrifying will emerge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 05:35:00" d="2020-04-23 06:00:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (14) (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>9 Lives/ Breaking Bread
Max panics when he realizes he's lost six of his nine lives! Max and Gark harness Gark's laser-toasting powers to make delicious bread crumbs.(S1</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 06:00:00" d="2020-04-23 06:29:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Need for Speed/A Tight Spot
Andre is suspended for reckless driving and must live at his family's speed. Chobado takes Andre's place when he panics</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 06:29:00" d="2020-04-23 07:00:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Andre Furiki
Sloth Genius/Monkey Wrench in the Works: Andre tries hypnosis to become a genius stunt-sloth. Andre loses everything to a con-artist croc</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 07:00:00" d="2020-04-23 07:29:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Jet Wing
Davenport raises money for a new lab by doing a death-defying stunt, flying over Mission Creek on rocket propelled wings but makes a crash landing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 07:29:00" d="2020-04-23 08:00:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mission - Mission Creek High
Principal Perry tries to force the Lab Rats to take her on a mission. The kids stage a fake one to distract</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 08:00:00" d="2020-04-23 08:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Excaliferb
In this episode the boys are transported to the Middle Ages. They set out to find the legendary sword Excaliferb, which they need to defeat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 08:29:00" d="2020-04-23 09:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Tri-Stone Area/Doof Dynasty
The boys are in the Stone Age and invent the wheel. Back in history, the boys are in China where they must rescue a princess</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 09:00:00" d="2020-04-23 09:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls II (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Society of the Blind Eye
The kids, with Old Man McGucket's help, discover there is a secret society in Gravity Falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 09:29:00" d="2020-04-23 10:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls II (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Blendin's Game
Blendin Blandin, the time traveller featured in season one, returns to face off with Dipper and Mabel in a futuristic battle that could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 10:00:00" d="2020-04-23 10:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Fly on the Wall/My Sweet Ride
Candace is accidentally turned into a fly. Candace has always dreamed of having her own car, and finally gets her wish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 10:29:00" d="2020-04-23 11:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bully Bust/Backyard Hodge Podge Candace challenges Buford to guard the boys' invention for the day so she can bust them. The boys create a backyard hodge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 11:00:00" d="2020-04-23 11:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Knot my Problem/Mind Share
Can Candace finally outwit the boys and out them to Mum if they get stuck in their giant knot? The gang is tricked</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 11:29:00" d="2020-04-23 12:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bee Day
Doof plans to become the ruler of all the bees. The Fireside Girls want to get their bee-keeping badge but the bees are missing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 12:00:00" d="2020-04-23 12:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Hiya Henry/People Watching
Cricket Green's family moves from country to Big City. As they acclimatize, their perspectives on differences between country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 12:29:00" d="2020-04-23 13:00:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Hiya Henry/People Watching
Cricket Green's family moves from country to Big City. As they acclimatize, their perspectives on differences between country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 13:00:00" d="2020-04-23 13:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mud, Mud, Mud, Mud World/The Ballad of Badbeard
Candace worries about her driving test. The boys build a monster truck. Grandpa takes the boys camping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 13:29:00" d="2020-04-23 14:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Dude We're Getting the Band Back Together
The boys decide on a great present for mum and dad's anniversary - they'll persuade their parents' favourite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 14:00:00" d="2020-04-23 14:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ready for the Bettys/The Flying Fishmonger
Candace and Stacey win a day with a girl band. It's a disaster. The gang learns Gramps was a daredevil</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 14:29:00" d="2020-04-23 15:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>At Last
Candace's dream comes true when Mum finally comes home. Phineas and Ferb are sent to military school. But she's surprised to discover she misses them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 15:00:00" d="2020-04-23 15:29:00"><n u="Star Vs the Forces of Evil">Star Vs the Forces of Evil I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mewberty/Pixtopia
Hearts sprout on Star's body, a sign of Mewberty. Marco helps her cope. Marco and mates work in mines to pay the Magic Mirror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 15:29:00" d="2020-04-23 16:00:00"><n u="Star Vs the Forces of Evil">Star Vs the Forces of Evil I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sleep Spells/ Lobster Claws
Marco tries to help Star stop casting spells in her sleep, then discovers there's a good reason. Star and Marco</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 16:00:00" d="2020-04-23 16:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Photo Op/Remy Rescue
Bill tries to trick the family into having a photo taken. Can Cricket stop Remy's parents sending him away to school?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 16:29:00" d="2020-04-23 17:00:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Gridlocked/Mama Bird
The family takes a road trip and ends up in a traffic jam! Tilly babysits chicks, hoping they will imprint on her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 17:00:00" d="2020-04-23 17:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>La Candace-Cabra/Happy Birthday Isabella
Can the boys prove the existence of the elusive Chupacabra? The gang celebrates Isabella's birthday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 17:29:00" d="2020-04-23 18:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Thanks but No Thanks/Troy Story
Gordon Ramsay and actress Goldie Hawn guest star in this show which sees Carl bribe Monty. The boys decide to re-enact</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 18:00:00" d="2020-04-23 18:25:00"><n u="Amphibia">Amphibia I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% Lily Pad Thai/Plantar's Last Stand
Anne tries to turn the diner into a Thai restaurant. After a rent increase on the food stand Anne convinces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 18:25:00" d="2020-04-23 18:29:00"><n>AAA - Star Wars: The Rise Of Skywalker</n>    <k>The saga ends, but the story lives on, in Star Wars: The Rise of Skywalker. Peek behind the scenes with fascinating interviews and footage from the latest blockbuster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 18:29:00" d="2020-04-23 19:00:00"><n u="Walk The Prank S3">Walk The Prank S3 III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lord of the Gummy Worms
The kids are stranded alone in the woods on a school camping trip. Bailey and Chance split into rival groups over their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 19:00:00" d="2020-04-23 19:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Agent Doof/Phineas and Ferb and the Temple of the Juatchadoon: Doof stops being evil and joins the agency as a probationer. The boys travel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 19:29:00" d="2020-04-23 20:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Monster from the Id/Gi-Ants
Candace loses Jeremy's present, so the boys make her another - a drain unblocker. Phineas and Ferb build a special farm which</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 20:00:00" d="2020-04-23 20:29:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats IV (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Space Elevator
Davenport's top scientist Dr. Ryan arrives to test his latest advance in space technology. Chase feels threatened. The rivalry heats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 20:29:00" d="2020-04-23 21:00:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats IV (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bionic Action Hero - Part One
Douglas's ex-colleague is a movie director who wants to make a movie about the Lab Rats. When she shows up to do research</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 21:00:00" d="2020-04-23 21:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mom's in the House/Minor Monogram
The boys can't find Perry, so decide to build a giant replica. The boys look back on Summer and forward to Fall (Autumn)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-23 21:29:00" d="2020-04-24 00:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Delivery of Destiny/ Let's Bounce:Delivery man Paul (Simon Pegg) is a hero when he saves the town. Ferb's anti-gravity device inspires Phineas to suspend</k>  </p>
</a>
