<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="35" t="2020-04-15 04:30:44"><p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 05:10:00" d="2020-04-22 05:35:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Staring Dog/28 Seconds Later
Gark's determined to find out why Staring Dog stares at Max. When Max makes Gark better with the orb, he infects the whole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 05:35:00" d="2020-04-22 06:00:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Kitty Latte/The Big One
A jealous Max is convinced Betty is seeing another cat behind his back. After an ominous message on his codex, Gark knows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 06:00:00" d="2020-04-22 06:29:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Furry Road/Chillaxation Overdrive
Andre and Chobado steal Gordon's peanut oil tanker. Andre relieves Mouki, only to create total chaos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 06:29:00" d="2020-04-22 07:00:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (26)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Chillax Chobado/Andre's Dead End
Andre stresses out Chobado and loses his best friend. Can Andre prevent Brenda being scrapped?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 07:00:00" d="2020-04-22 07:29:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sink or Swim - Part One
On the run, the Lab Rats stow away on a freighter. When they rescue an endangered sub they are captured. They escape but realise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 07:29:00" d="2020-04-22 08:00:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats III (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sink or Swim - Part Two
With Victor Krane's help, Davenport's evil brother has enabled the Triton app and got control of the Lab Rats. Can they override</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 08:00:00" d="2020-04-22 08:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bad Hair Day/Meatloaf Surprise
Candace overuses the boys' hair growing machine and is mistaken for a rare orangutan. The boys build a bounce house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 08:29:00" d="2020-04-22 09:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mommy Can You Hear Me?/Road Trip
Candace has an injured ankle, so the boys help stop her getting bored. On a family trip, the boys decide to build a diner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 09:00:00" d="2020-04-22 09:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Soos and the Real Girl
When Soos finds himself in need of a date for his cousin Reggie's engagement party, he looks to a dating simulator game to help him talk to girls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 09:29:00" d="2020-04-22 10:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Little Gift Shop of Horrors
Stan tells a new customer stories to make a sale, including one about the time they were almost turned into clay monsters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 10:00:00" d="2020-04-22 10:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mission Marvel - Part Two
Spider-Man, Iron Man, Thor and Hulk stand powerless after being struck by Doof's inator</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 10:29:00" d="2020-04-22 11:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mission Marvel - Part Two
Phineas and Ferb do everything they can to restore the superheroes' powers before the evil villains take over the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 11:00:00" d="2020-04-22 11:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Tri-State Trilogy of Terror
In this show's three short stories Perry becomes evil, Doof meets a giant floating baby head that grants wishes, and Candace's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 11:29:00" d="2020-04-22 12:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Steampunx/It's No Picnic
Phineas and Ferb discover a time capsule left by kids from 1902 who were like them. Isabella plans a picnic with Phineas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 12:00:00" d="2020-04-22 12:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Harvest Dinner/Winner Winner
Cricket Green's family moves from country to Big City. As they acclimatize, their perspectives on differences between country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 12:29:00" d="2020-04-22 13:00:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Harvest Dinner/Winner Winner
Cricket Green's family moves from country to Big City. As they acclimatize, their perspectives on differences between country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 13:00:00" d="2020-04-22 13:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>One Good Scare Ought to Do It
Isabella has hiccups, so the boys make their scariest ever haunted house in the back yard, in the hope of curing her of them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 13:29:00" d="2020-04-22 14:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Hard Day's Knight/I, Robot
The family is on holiday in England and holds a medieval tournament. The boys build robots called Phineas and Ferbots</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 14:00:00" d="2020-04-22 14:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mom's Birthday Episode/Journey to the Centre of Candace: Her children want to make Mom's birthday the best ever. Isabella's dog eats her sash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 14:29:00" d="2020-04-22 15:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Run Away Runaway/I Scream, You Scream
The girls help at the fashion show to get sewing badges. Isabella has her tonsils out so the</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 15:00:00" d="2020-04-22 15:29:00"><n u="Star Vs the Forces of Evil">Star Vs the Forces of Evil I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cheer Up Star/Quest Buy
Star cheers up Marco after a bad day so he tries to return the favour, with disastrous results. Star and Marco try</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 15:29:00" d="2020-04-22 16:00:00"><n u="Star Vs the Forces of Evil">Star Vs the Forces of Evil I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Diaz Family Vacation/ Brittney's Party
 Star and Marco save the Diazes from a serpent. Star fights off Ludo and his monster army when they crash Brittney</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 16:00:00" d="2020-04-22 16:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Swimming Fool/Tilly's Goat
The family visits an indoor pool for the first time. Will Tilly enter the family goat in a dog show?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 16:29:00" d="2020-04-22 17:00:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cricketsitter/Backflip Bill
Cricket has a list of crazy stunts to do while Bill is away. Cricket tries to help Bill realise his childhood dream</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 17:00:00" d="2020-04-22 17:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Return Policy/ Imperfect Storm
Doof uses an inator to return things to the store. Doof invents a Have-A-Bad-Day-Inator to ruin Mum's garden party. Guest star Simon Pegg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 17:29:00" d="2020-04-22 18:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Phineas and Ferb must help Love Handel prove Klimpaloon's existence in time for an awards ceremony, or he'll be barred forever from the world of fact-based song writing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 18:00:00" d="2020-04-22 18:29:00"><n u="Amphibia">Amphibia I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% Contagi-Anne/Family Shrub
Anne fakes sickness to get off work, but then the family gets sick. Sprig and Polly think family history is boring, until</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 18:29:00" d="2020-04-22 19:00:00"><n u="Walk The Prank S3">Walk The Prank S3 III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Walk the Prank
NBA Edition: When Dusty posts a rude comment about him, NBA superstar Caron Butler pays him a visit to teach the gang a lesson about online safety</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 19:00:00" d="2020-04-22 19:25:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Skiddley Whiffers/ Tour de Ferb
The boys make a giant version of Candace's game, Skiddley Whiffers. The boys invite Tour de France winning cyclist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 19:25:00" d="2020-04-22 19:29:00"><n>AAA - Star Wars: The Rise Of Skywalker</n>    <k>The saga ends, but the story lives on, in Star Wars: The Rise of Skywalker. Peek behind the scenes with fascinating interviews and footage from the latest blockbuster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 19:29:00" d="2020-04-22 20:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>My Fair Goalie
Ferb's English cousins accuse Ferb of having lost his Britishness. American friends disagree, and the row escalates until the two sides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 20:00:00" d="2020-04-22 20:29:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats IV (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Spider Island
An extinct species of spider is re-animated and escapes. It bites Adam, injecting him with deadly venom. Can Doug make an antidote in time?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 20:29:00" d="2020-04-22 21:00:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Spike vs Spikette
Spike won't subdue a female bionic student with the same commando app as Chase, as he's a gentleman. The Lab Rats install</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 21:00:00" d="2020-04-22 21:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Perry the Actorpus/Bullseye
Perry becomes spokesanimal for Totally Tools, jeopardising his secret identity. Dad competes in the Lovemuffin Pageant of Evil against Doof</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-22 21:29:00" d="2020-04-23 00:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>That's the Spirit/The Curse of Candace
The brothers help a boy get rid of ghosts. Guest stars Michael Douglas and son Dylan. Candace sees a vampire movie</k>  </p>
</a>
