<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="51" t="2019-08-10 01:36:17"><p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 05:10:00" d="2019-08-16 05:35:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mere Mortals/ The Garkest Time Line
Max wanders into the park and is horrified to find Gark exercising. Gark plays Trash-Ball with other animals in the park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 05:35:00" d="2019-08-16 06:00:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Gark Knight Rises/Any Takers
Gark becomes a superhero to fight a chameleon supervillain. Max tries to fake an alien abduction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 06:00:00" d="2019-08-16 06:29:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Musical Muffler Mystery/Mama at the Wheel
Chobado steals the school's musical muffler. Andre is embarrassed by Moka-Moka's slothy behaviour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 06:29:00" d="2019-08-16 07:00:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Burrito Hotel/ Brenda Gets the Boot
Andre and Champion's contest leads them into Gordon's trap. Gordon takes Andre to traffic court for reckless driving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 07:00:00" d="2019-08-16 07:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Spider-Man">Marvel's Spider-Man I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Osborn Academy
Norman Osborn creates an cademy for Geniuses to save his son the embarrassment of suspension from Horizon High for sabotaging another student's experiment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 07:29:00" d="2019-08-16 08:00:00"><n u="Space Chickens In Space">Space Chickens In Space I (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cadet Clarkk/Stop Bugging Me! Glargg does empathy training and learns important lessons. An outbreak of beserkerbugs causes chaos aboard the academy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 08:00:00" d="2019-08-16 08:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Phineas and Ferb's Cliptastic Countdown
Here's a chance to see viewers' favourite muscial numbers in a cliptastic special compilation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 08:29:00" d="2019-08-16 09:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Phineas and Ferb's Quantum Boogaloo
The boys need material from 20 years in the future so borrow a time machine. Candace returns from the future, changing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 09:00:00" d="2019-08-16 09:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Boss Mabel
Mabel thinks Stan is a bad boss, and is sure she can do it better than him. While Stan takes a holiday, Mabel tries to run the Mystery Shack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 09:29:00" d="2019-08-16 10:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Bottomless Pit
Stan, Soos, Mabel and Dipper accidentally fall down the Bottomless Pit. To pass time until they are rescued they tell stories including</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 10:00:00" d="2019-08-16 10:29:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% The Doctor Zone Files/ The Note
Sara wants to see The Doctor Zone Files movie with Milo, but worries about potential problems. Milo spends the day chasing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 10:29:00" d="2019-08-16 11:00:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Party of Peril/Smooth Operator
Melissa and Zack throw Milo his first real birthday party. Milo goes to the opera and ends up centre stage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 11:00:00" d="2019-08-16 11:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cricket Versus/Blue Tater
Cricket must wrestle a wild animal for a rite of passage. Bill unearths a mysterious blue potato. Is it cursed?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 11:29:00" d="2019-08-16 12:00:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Parade Day/DIY Guys
Cricket's working but doesn't want to miss the Big Parade, so re-routes it. Bill uses a trip to the hardware store to teach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 12:00:00" d="2019-08-16 12:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Golf War
After being belittled by Pacifica too many times, Mabel challenges her to a miniature golf-off, which gets out of control when some local</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 12:29:00" d="2019-08-16 13:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Sock Opera
Attempting to impress a local puppeteer Mabel puts on a sock puppet rock opera but her show goes wrong when Dipper's drive to uncover journal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 13:00:00" d="2019-08-16 13:29:00"><n u="Supa Strikas">Supa Strikas V (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Last Action Figure
El Matador is about to release his action figure dolls but his rivals swap them with dolls that insult the fans.They start booing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 13:29:00" d="2019-08-16 14:00:00"><n u="Supa Strikas">Supa Strikas V (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Heels Over Head
Twisting Tiger hurts his knee in training. Unable to play he looks for a Capoeira master who can teach him new moves, but he only learns half the lesson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 14:00:00" d="2019-08-16 14:29:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats III (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Alien Gladiators
Leo and Davenport compete in an epic fire staff battle for a role in the next film in a blockbuster sci-fi franchise. They are surprised</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 14:29:00" d="2019-08-16 15:00:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats III (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Face Off
Bree attempts to play a prank on Adam, but it goes horribly right before her big date for the school's winter dance, causing an embarrassing scene at the event</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 15:00:00" d="2019-08-16 15:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Crack that Whip/The Best Lazy Day Ever
Grandma was a roller skater so the boys build her a track. The boys have a lazy day. Candace is bored and decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 15:29:00" d="2019-08-16 16:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Traffic Cam Caper/Bowl-R-Ama Drama
Candace borrows the traffic camera DVD to prove to her mother what the boys have been doing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 16:00:00" d="2019-08-16 16:29:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Snow Way Out/Teacher Feature
Milo and Zack encounter dangerous, snow-related obstacles. Scott the Undergrounder gets a date with Miss Murawski</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 16:29:00" d="2019-08-16 17:00:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Picture Day/Agee Ientee Diogee
Milo has never managed to have a school photo taken. Diogee is mistaken for a secret agent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 17:00:00" d="2019-08-16 17:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Welcome Home/Raccooned
The Green family moves to the city. Their truck is towed. Cricket and Bill accidentally disturb a nest of raccoons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 17:29:00" d="2019-08-16 18:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Hide and Seek/That Sinking Feeling
The boys use a machine to shrink themselves. Candace steals it to show to Mum. Baljeet asks the</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 18:00:00" d="2019-08-16 18:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Baljeatles/Vanessassary Roughness
Baljeet enrols for a geology course that's really about becoming a rock star. Ferb fancies Vanessa and helps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 18:29:00" d="2019-08-16 19:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>No More Bunny Business/Spa Day
Candace adopts a stray rabbit, then the boys discover it's a spy. Candace and Stacey are going for a spa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 19:00:00" d="2019-08-16 19:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bubble Boys/Isabella and the Temple of Sap
The boys make a huge bubble and float round in it. Isabella's Fireside Girls help the boys hunt for a Maracanut</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 19:29:00" d="2019-08-16 20:00:00"><n u="Mech-X4">Mech-X4 II (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Versus the Arctic
Mech-X4 rockets to the Arctic for a devastating showdown with Traeger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 20:00:00" d="2019-08-16 20:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Spider-Man">Marvel's Spider-Man I (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Rise of Doc Ock - Part Three
Peter spends a day at Oz Academy in the hopes of finding a clue that will convince Harry that his Dad is out to destroy Spider-Man</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 20:29:00" d="2019-08-16 21:00:00"><n u="Marvel's Spider-Man">Marvel's Spider-Man I (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Rise of Doc Ock - Part Four
The Jackal sends a sleeper drone in the form of the Rhino to Oz Academy in order to help him gain access to Norman's secret lab</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 21:00:00" d="2019-08-16 21:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Avengers: Black Panther's">Marvel's Avengers: Black Panther's V (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Widowmaker
Black Panther explores a secret enemy facility with a nefarious past</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 21:29:00" d="2019-08-16 22:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Summerween
It's Gravity Falls' summer version of Halloween, with Jack-o-Melons. Dipper insults a candy monster that threatens to eat him if his candy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 22:00:00" d="2019-08-16 22:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Boss Mabel
Mabel thinks Stan is a bad boss, and is sure she can do it better than him. While Stan takes a holiday, Mabel tries to run the Mystery Shack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 22:29:00" d="2019-08-16 23:00:00"><n u="Kick Buttowski Suburban Daredevil">Kick Buttowski Suburban Daredevil I (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mellowbrook Drift/Gift of Wacky
After losing a sidewalk cart race Kick challenges the resident physics nerd bully to a re-match</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 23:00:00" d="2019-08-16 23:29:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Love Toboggan/The Island of Lost Dakotas
Sara feels safe to go on a date when Milo goes skiing. Dakota time travels to stop Cavendish creating a paradox</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 23:29:00" d="2019-08-17 00:00:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Doof's Day Out/Disco Do-Over
Doof is a guest who won't leave - and Sara wants him out. Brigette and Martin want to be disco dance champions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 00:00:00" d="2019-08-17 00:25:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Me and Rocket Magoo/Time Bamboozler
Chobado wins a contest to co-host a show with his idol. Andre and Chobado go back in time to settle an argument</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 00:25:00" d="2019-08-17 00:50:00"><n u="Dude That's My Ghost">Dude That's My Ghost I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Place in the Sun/ Copycat Cobra
Spencer stands up to Lolo and unwittingly becomes the new &quot;king of the school&quot;. Another ghost shows up at the mansion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 00:50:00" d="2019-08-17 01:15:00"><n u="Dude That's My Ghost">Dude That's My Ghost I (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bad Publicity/Soccer Star
When a top publicist discovers Spencer and vows to make him famous, Billy becomes insanely jealous. Billy decides to inhabit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 01:15:00" d="2019-08-17 01:35:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% Monster Dump/So You Think You Can Stank
Disaster strikes on a volcano trip and the Ninja must save his classmates. Talent show judges Randy and Howard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 01:35:00" d="2019-08-17 02:00:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% 30 Seconds to Math/Monster Drill
Randy becomes Howard's friend and also do his duty as the Ninja. A monster interrupts the annual Monster Drill, and Randy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 02:00:00" d="2019-08-17 02:25:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Local Hero/ Full Speed Ahead
Boyster uses his powers to save a baby, but telling the truth may reveal his secret. Boyster uses Shelby as a water scooter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 02:25:00" d="2019-08-17 02:45:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Three Hours of the Condor/Boyster Pox
Boyster is addicted to a TV show about surviving in the wild. Boyster catches oysterpox. Will he be able to compete</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 02:45:00" d="2019-08-17 03:10:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Kitty Latte/The Big One
A jealous Max is convinced Betty is seeing another cat behind his back. After an ominous message on his codex, Gark knows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 03:10:00" d="2019-08-17 03:35:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Fat Cat/Bathtub of Terror
Max emulates his new TV idol by over-eating. Max is terrified of looking into the bath as he's scared something terrifying will emerge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 03:35:00" d="2019-08-17 04:00:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja II (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% Randy Cunningham's Day Off/Bro-ing Down the House
Howard is upset when Randy fakes a sick day. Randy breaks into McFist's house to retrieve a boomerang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 04:00:00" d="2019-08-17 04:20:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja II (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% Shoot First
Ask Questions Laser/Ninjeception: Randy and Howard use Ninja-ing to help with wonk laser tag. Stuck in a dream-within-a-dream-within-a-dream</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 04:20:00" d="2019-08-17 04:45:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Pranks a Lot/Tough Hombre
Ozzy plays a trick on Rafik. He thinks Boyster is to blame. Shelby mediates. Boyster enters a Mexican wrestling match</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 04:45:00" d="2019-08-17 05:10:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Boyster sneezes blue ink when he has a cold, and turns Alicia's drawings blue. Magic is Rafik's new hobby. His audition attracts the attention of an evil</k>  </p>
</a>
