<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="37" t="2020-05-27 04:33:44"><p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 05:10:00" d="2020-06-03 05:35:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Cat Crib/Lost in Throckmorton
Max and Gark sign up for a reality show. Max cheats. Max gets angry when playing an alien board game and causes things to disappear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 05:35:00" d="2020-06-03 06:00:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Dreamcatcher/Room of Panic
Gark feels left out when he realizes he doesn't have dreams. Max panics when he finds out Betty is leaving him alone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 06:00:00" d="2020-06-03 06:29:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Fun and Thunder/Chasing Waterfalls
Andre must learn to be patient on a scavenger hunt. Andre and Pepita team up for a photography contest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 06:29:00" d="2020-06-03 07:00:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Dude Don't Scratch my Car/Moles of Anarchy
Andre trades cars with Champion and becomes paranoid. Andre would rather become part of a gang of moles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 07:00:00" d="2020-06-03 07:29:00"><n u="Star Vs The Forces Of Evil">Star Vs The Forces Of Evil III (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Scent of a Hoodie/Rest in Pudding
Star goes to the Royal Laundry. Star has recurring visions of Glossaryck and believes he's haunting her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 07:29:00" d="2020-06-03 08:00:00"><n u="Star Vs The Forces Of Evil">Star Vs The Forces Of Evil III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Club-Snubbed/Stranger Danger
Tom snubs Star at the Silver Bell Ball. Star meets a relative</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 08:00:00" d="2020-06-03 08:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Unfair Science Fair/Unfair Science Fair Redux
The boys help Baljeet with his science project. Candace tries Baljeet's Portal to Mars and finds herself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 08:29:00" d="2020-06-03 09:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Out to Launch (Part One and Two)
The boys' dad names a star after them. They build a rocket to go to see it. Candace stows away. The boys are left behind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 09:00:00" d="2020-06-03 09:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Time Traveller's Pig
Dipper discovers there's a machine in Gravity Falls that can help him travel back through time. Meanwhile, it's love at first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 09:29:00" d="2020-06-03 10:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Fight Fighters
When Dipper falls out with Robbie over Wendy, he brings a character from his favourite arcade game to help him fight it out. Mabel tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 10:00:00" d="2020-06-03 10:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Operation Crumb Cake/ Mandace
Isabella writes to Phineas admitting her feelings, then tries to get the letter back. Doof invents an Inator</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 10:29:00" d="2020-06-03 11:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Tales from Resistance
Now Doofenshmirtz is in jail Candace is feeling restless. Then a new threat appears in the Second Dimension and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 11:00:00" d="2020-06-03 11:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lost in Danville/ The Inator Method
A strange capsule falls into the yard. It unleashes something the boys cannot control. Doof hosts a motivational seminar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 11:29:00" d="2020-06-03 12:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (26)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Act Your Age
Looking into the future, the kids are all teenagers. Phineas has a crush on Isa, Candace has given up busting, and Doof is selling inators for cash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 12:00:00" d="2020-06-03 12:29:00"><n u="Right Now Kapow">Right Now Kapow I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Truth or Dare/Sir Anthony
A slumber party plays truth or dare. A battle hammer falls on a foot. A mermaid spills her drink. A knight is defined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 12:29:00" d="2020-06-03 13:00:00"><n u="Right Now Kapow">Right Now Kapow I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Pied Piper/Monster House
A leader gets an earworm. A vampire does the right thing. A chalkboard is scratched. A cowboy is shot. A house mustn't have parties</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 13:00:00" d="2020-06-03 13:29:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats III (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Alien Gladiators
Leo and Davenport compete in an epic fire staff battle for a role in the next film in a blockbuster sci-fi franchise. They are surprised</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 13:29:00" d="2020-06-03 14:00:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats III (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Face Off
Bree attempts to play a prank on Adam, but it goes horribly right before her big date for the school's winter dance, causing an embarrassing scene at the event</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 14:00:00" d="2020-06-03 14:29:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats III (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Spike Fright
When Chase finally gets a girl interested in him, Adam gets jealous and sabotages their date by causing Chase to turn into Spike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 14:29:00" d="2020-06-03 15:00:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats III (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Merry Glitchmas
The Lab Rats learn that, even at Christmas, things don't always go smoothly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 15:00:00" d="2020-06-03 15:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Gridlocked/Mama Bird
The family takes a road trip and ends up in a traffic jam! Tilly babysits chicks, hoping they will imprint on her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 15:29:00" d="2020-06-03 16:00:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Welcome Home/Raccooned
The Green family moves to the city. Their truck is towed. Cricket and Bill accidentally disturb a nest of raccoons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 16:00:00" d="2020-06-03 16:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Doonkelberry Imperative/Buford Confidential
Mom has run out of Doonkelberries, so the boys go out to find some. Visiting French Fireside Girls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 16:29:00" d="2020-06-03 17:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (26)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sleepwalk Surprise/Sci-fi Pie Fly
Candace covers for the boys when Jeremy plays jet pack volleyball with them. The boys investigate crop circles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 17:00:00" d="2020-06-03 17:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Phineas and Ferb's Quantum Boogaloo
The boys need material from 20 years in the future so borrow a time machine. Candace returns from the future, changing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 17:29:00" d="2020-06-03 18:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Hide and Seek/That Sinking Feeling
The boys use a machine to shrink themselves. Candace steals it to show to Mum. Baljeet asks the</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 18:00:00" d="2020-06-03 18:29:00"><n u="New: Disney">New: Disney 11 III (53)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Episode 53
Ricky and Dede photograph the referee and the secretary. Lorenzo organizes a date for Delfina, who loves the surprise. The secretary confesses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 18:29:00" d="2020-06-03 19:00:00"><n u="Ducktales">Ducktales II (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Nightmare on Killmotor Hill! When the kids' journey through a dream world turns into a nightmare, Lena fears she's destined to become just like her evil aunt Magica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 19:00:00" d="2020-06-03 19:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Big Deal/Forbidden Feline
Cricket persuades the family to hit up a Thanksgiving sale for a sweet deal on a new TV. Tilly hits it off with Anoosh, the neighborhood cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 19:29:00" d="2020-06-03 20:00:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Harvest Dinner/Winner Winner
Cricket Green's family moves from country to Big City. As they acclimatize, their perspectives on differences between country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 20:00:00" d="2020-06-03 20:29:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats II (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Leo vs Evil
When Leo records a secret conversation between Marcus and an unseen mastermind he is targeted by Marcus's deadly robot. Can he escape?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 20:29:00" d="2020-06-03 21:00:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats II (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Spike's Got Talent
To improve their popularity Leo and Chase compete for the magician's spot in the school talent show. Chase's angry alter ego Spike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 21:00:00" d="2020-06-03 21:29:00"><n u="Disney">Disney 11 III (53)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Episode 53
Ricky and Dede photograph the referee and the secretary. Lorenzo organizes a date for Delfina, who loves the surprise. The secretary confesses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 21:29:00" d="2020-06-03 22:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Unfair Science Fair/Unfair Science Fair Redux
The boys help Baljeet with his science project. Candace tries Baljeet's Portal to Mars and finds herself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 22:00:00" d="2020-06-03 22:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Little Gift Shop of Horrors
Stan tells a new customer stories to make a sale, including one about the time they were almost turned into clay monsters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 22:29:00" d="2020-06-03 23:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls II (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Society of the Blind Eye
The kids, with Old Man McGucket's help, discover there is a secret society in Gravity Falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-03 23:00:00" d="2020-06-04 02:00:00"><n u="Right Now Kapow">Right Now Kapow I (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Secret Baseland/One Man Band
A villain opens a theme park. A one man band breaks up</k>  </p>
</a>
