<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="35" t="2019-08-11 01:29:08"><p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 05:10:00" d="2019-08-17 05:35:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>I, Maxine/Gark's Got Talent
After Max wishes he had powers like Gark, Gark helps him go robotic to earn respect. Max becomes Gark's agent when he shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 05:35:00" d="2019-08-17 06:00:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mirror, Mirror/Arugula
Gark does not see his reflection in the mirror. Gark invents an invisible girlfriend named Arugula</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 06:00:00" d="2019-08-17 06:29:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mission Piston/Chobado Loses his Head
Andre and Chobado launch a rescue mission for Miss Piston. Andre loses Chobado's lucky helmet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 06:29:00" d="2019-08-17 07:00:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Brenda's Got Soul/Fifteen Minutes of Furiki
Andre lies to Chobado when he pretends to be Brenda, putting their friendship at risk. Andre becomes famous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 07:00:00" d="2019-08-17 07:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Spider-Man">Marvel's Spider-Man I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Day in the Life
Spider-Man must stop Black Cat from committing a series of burglaries, while still fulfilling his school obligations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 07:29:00" d="2019-08-17 08:00:00"><n u="Space Chickens In Space">Space Chickens In Space I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>No Brian No Pain/Chicken Feed
Finley can't stop learning. Will his brain explode? Pipi creates a viral video sensation starring the chickens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 08:00:00" d="2019-08-17 08:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Invasion of the Ferb Snatchers/Ain't No Kiddie Ride: After a sci-fi marathon, Candace is convinced Ferb is an alien. The boys try some kiddies' rides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 08:29:00" d="2019-08-17 09:00:00"><n u="New: Marvel's Guardians Of The Galaxy">New: Marvel's Guardians Of The Galaxy III (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>You Don't Own Me
Phyla-Vell reluctantly teams up with the Guardians to bring The Collector to justice for destroying her home planet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 09:00:00" d="2019-08-17 09:29:00"><n u="Star Vs The Forces Of Evil">Star Vs The Forces Of Evil III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Return to Mewni/Moon the Undaunted
Returning to Mewni, Star and Queen Moon discover their homeland's magic is weakened. Queen Moon tells Star how she first met Toffee</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 09:29:00" d="2019-08-17 10:00:00"><n u="Star Vs The Forces Of Evil">Star Vs The Forces Of Evil III (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Book be Gone/Marco and the King
Ludo wants to write his own chapter in the Book of Spells. The King likes partyig and the kingdom is soon exhausted. Can Marco help?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 10:00:00" d="2019-08-17 10:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Avengers: Black Panther's">Marvel's Avengers: Black Panther's V (109)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Zemo Sanction
Black Panther's quest leads him to Baron Zemo and a surprise revelation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 10:29:00" d="2019-08-17 11:00:00"><n u="Mech-X4">Mech-X4 II (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Versus the Wolves at the Door
 Fearing Ryan dead, the team splits up to find him in the arctic before it's too late but discover themselves hunted by an unexpected enemy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 11:00:00" d="2019-08-17 11:29:00"><n u="Kickin' It">Kickin' It II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Kickin' It Old School
Rudy's excited to hear he may be elected into Seaford High's Hall of Fame, but then realises he has to finish high school first! Eddie and Milton help him get his diploma</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 11:29:00" d="2019-08-17 12:00:00"><n u="Kickin' It">Kickin' It II (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Oh Christmas Nuts!
While working at the mall's Santa attraction, Jack, Jerry and Milton's good intentions backfire when lead elf Tinsel frames them for stealing presents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 12:00:00" d="2019-08-17 12:29:00"><n u="Kickin' It">Kickin' It II (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% The Chosen One
The gang gets a surprise while training with the legendary Shaolin Warriors, when ancient Grandmaster Po announces Jerry is the Chosen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 12:29:00" d="2019-08-17 13:00:00"><n u="Kickin' It">Kickin' It II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Hit the Road, Jack
When Jack dominates a dojo tournament, grand sensei Tanaka offers him a scholarship to a very prestigious academy in Japan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 13:00:00" d="2019-08-17 13:29:00"><n u="Kickin' It">Kickin' It II (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% A Slip Down Memory Lane
Jack is preparing to set the world power break record when he slips and loses his memory. The gang recall some hilarious moments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 13:29:00" d="2019-08-17 14:00:00"><n u="Kickin' It">Kickin' It II (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Wedding Crashers
Bobby's friends get him a date with Leona, the Black Belt Widow, who's notorious for stealing rich karate-movie stars' fortunes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 14:00:00" d="2019-08-17 14:29:00"><n u="Kickin' It">Kickin' It II (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Wazombie Warriors
Kim goes to a zombie movie and falls asleep, dreaming her friends, including Tootsie the goat, have turned into &quot;zompyres&quot;, and she has to fight them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 14:29:00" d="2019-08-17 15:00:00"><n u="Kickin' It">Kickin' It II (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Sole Brothers
Jack and Jerry are delighted to get jobs at the new shoe shop in the mall. Things go wrong when Jerry is made manager. Jack is fired</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 15:00:00" d="2019-08-17 15:29:00"><n u="Kickin' It">Kickin' It I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Wax on, wax off
As a gift for becoming the top dojo in his chain, Bobby Wasabi sends the gang a life-size wax statue of himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 15:29:00" d="2019-08-17 16:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Got Game?/Comet Kermillian
Isabella and Buford argue about who's best at games so the boys organise a tournament. The boys build a giant observatory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 16:00:00" d="2019-08-17 16:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Gramma's Licence/Bear Trapped
Cricket and Gramma end up at a dangerous demolition derby. Cricket hates bears so helps Officer Keys catch one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 16:29:00" d="2019-08-17 17:00:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cricketsitter/Backflip Bill
Cricket has a list of crazy stunts to do while Bill is away. Cricket tries to help Bill realise his childhood dream</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 17:00:00" d="2019-08-17 17:29:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Battle of the Bands/The Math Book
Milo, Melissa and Zack overcome Murphy's Law to be ready for a contest. Milo goes a quest to help Melissa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 17:29:00" d="2019-08-17 18:00:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Missing Milo - Part One
Milo is stopped from destroying a pistachio plant, which inadvertently affects the future. The plants survive, become sentient</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 18:00:00" d="2019-08-17 18:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Avengers: Black Panther's">Marvel's Avengers: Black Panther's V (107)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Into the Deep
Black Panther and his sister Shuri undertake a dangerous mission to sneak into the undersea kingdom of Atlantis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 18:29:00" d="2019-08-17 19:00:00"><n u="Marvel's Guardians Of The Galaxy">Marvel's Guardians Of The Galaxy III (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>You Don't Own Me
Phyla-Vell reluctantly teams up with the Guardians to bring The Collector to justice for destroying her home planet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 19:00:00" d="2019-08-17 19:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>That's the Spirit/The Curse of Candace
The brothers help a boy get rid of ghosts. Guest stars Michael Douglas and son Dylan. Candace sees a vampire movie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 19:29:00" d="2019-08-17 20:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Phineas and Ferb create a new form of communication, Ferb Latin. The Tri-State area has run out of potatoes, so the boys extract DNA from their last crisp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 20:00:00" d="2019-08-17 20:50:00"><n>Saving the People Who Save People</n>    <k>The comic book world comes to life for teenagers Oliver and Kaz, who find a hidden entrance to Mighty Med, a secret hospital for superheroes, and are offered jobs there</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 20:50:00" d="2019-08-17 21:00:00"><n u="Disney Mickey Mouse">Disney Mickey Mouse III (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Roughin' It
Mickey's dream of camping the old fashioned way is threatened after Donald shows up in a state-of-the-art RV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 21:00:00" d="2019-08-17 21:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Spider-Man">Marvel's Spider-Man I (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Spider Island - Part Two
Spider-Man and Spider-Gwen must help Black Widow track down Crossbones before he delivers stolen vibranium to Arnim Zola and Hydra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 21:29:00" d="2019-08-17 22:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Bottomless Pit
Stan, Soos, Mabel and Dipper accidentally fall down the Bottomless Pit. To pass time until they are rescued they tell stories including</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-17 22:00:00" d="2019-08-18 01:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Deep End
It's hot in Gravity Falls so the Pines head down to the pool. Dipper gets a job as a life guard, and Mabel meets a boy who's confined</k>  </p>
</a>
