<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2020-04-09 04:30:50"><p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 05:10:00" d="2020-04-16 05:35:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>I, Maxine/Gark's Got Talent
After Max wishes he had powers like Gark, Gark helps him go robotic to earn respect. Max becomes Gark's agent when he shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 05:35:00" d="2020-04-16 06:00:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mirror, Mirror/Arugula
Gark does not see his reflection in the mirror. Gark invents an invisible girlfriend named Arugula</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 06:00:00" d="2020-04-16 06:29:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Hiccups and the Headless Racer
Andre tries to scare Chobado to get rid of his hiccups. Andre thinks he's got rid of Gordon. He appears with amnesia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 06:29:00" d="2020-04-16 07:00:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Taxi Furiki/Garage Games
Andre's horn buying business runs into trouble. Fighting over the new garage endangers friendships. Fighting over the new garage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 07:00:00" d="2020-04-16 07:29:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats II (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bionic Showdown - Part One
Douglas and Marcus capture Davenport and use him to lure the Lab Rats into a trap. Douglas reveals a secret and his plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 07:29:00" d="2020-04-16 08:00:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats II (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bionic Showdown - Part Two
Now alone except for Eddy, Leo must work out how to rescue the Lab Rats. A gruelling battle with Marcus ensues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 08:00:00" d="2020-04-16 08:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (37)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Summer Belongs To You - Part One
On the longest day of the year the boys plan to travel round the world in one day. Candace is left in charge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 08:29:00" d="2020-04-16 09:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (38)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Summer Belongs To You - Part Two
Candace joins the boys on their one day round the world trip. She wants to see Jeremy in Paris and prove he loves her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 09:00:00" d="2020-04-16 09:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Boyz Crazy
When Mabel discovers that her favourite boy band is actually a bunch of imprisoned clones, she attempts to rescue them, then decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 09:29:00" d="2020-04-16 10:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Land before Swine
When Stan causes Waddles to get snatched up by a pterodactyl, the gang journeys to a land trapped in time to rescue him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 10:00:00" d="2020-04-16 10:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Excaliferb
In this episode the boys are transported to the Middle Ages. They set out to find the legendary sword Excaliferb, which they need to defeat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 10:29:00" d="2020-04-16 11:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Tri-Stone Area/Doof Dynasty
The boys are in the Stone Age and invent the wheel. Back in history, the boys are in China where they must rescue a princess</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 11:00:00" d="2020-04-16 11:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Agent Doof/Phineas and Ferb and the Temple of the Juatchadoon: Doof stops being evil and joins the agency as a probationer. The boys travel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 11:29:00" d="2020-04-16 12:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quietest Day Ever/Bully Bromance Breakup
The boys must be quiet while Mum sits an online knitting test. Baljeet stops being Buford's nerd. Buford joins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 12:00:00" d="2020-04-16 12:29:00"><n u="Ducktales">Ducktales II (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Happy Birthday, Doofus Drake! Louie teams with Goldie to scam their way through Doofus' dangerous party. Huey pushes himself out of his comfort</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 12:29:00" d="2020-04-16 13:00:00"><n u="Ducktales">Ducktales II (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Nightmare on Killmotor Hill! When the kids' journey through a dream world turns into a nightmare, Lena fears she's destined to become just like her evil aunt Magica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 13:00:00" d="2020-04-16 13:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>For Your Ice Only/Happy New Year
The kids play in an exhibition hockey game and take it to the extreme. To celebrate the New Year</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 13:29:00" d="2020-04-16 14:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Thanks but No Thanks/Troy Story
Gordon Ramsay and actress Goldie Hawn guest star in this show which sees Carl bribe Monty. The boys decide to re-enact</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 14:00:00" d="2020-04-16 14:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Druselsteinoween/Face Your Fear
Vanessa holds her Halloween party in Doof's castle in Druselstein. When Vanessa asks Doof to babysit her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 14:29:00" d="2020-04-16 15:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Tri-State Trilogy of Terror
In this show's three short stories Perry becomes evil, Doof meets a giant floating baby head that grants wishes, and Candace's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 15:00:00" d="2020-04-16 15:29:00"><n u="Amphibia">Amphibia I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% Cane Crazy/Flood, Sweat &amp; Tears
Anne breaks Hop Pop's favourite cane, she sets out to replace it. Anne's basement bedroom is flooded, so she and Sprig</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 15:29:00" d="2020-04-16 16:00:00"><n u="Amphibia">Amphibia I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% Anne or Beast?/Best Fronds
Sprig tries to take down a mysterious beast to prove that he's responsible. Sprig takes Anne swimming in a nearby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 16:00:00" d="2020-04-16 16:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Elevator Action/Bad Influencer
Gloria gets stuck on an elevator with the Greens. Remy falls for a huckster internet influencer and Tilly makes an online video with Bill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 16:29:00" d="2020-04-16 17:00:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Reckoning Ball/Clubbed
Chip Whistler returns to take revenge on the Greens, but is forced to apologize. Andromeda and Tilly follow Gloria</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 17:00:00" d="2020-04-16 17:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (27)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Meapless in Seattle
Returning to the scenario from The Chronicles of Meap, the boys are attacked by an alien robot. Meap rescues them, and in return</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 17:29:00" d="2020-04-16 18:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (28)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Mom Attractor/Cranius Maximus
Candace gets the boys to create a Mom Attractor, and it works! The boys invent a brain booster hat for Baljeet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 18:00:00" d="2020-04-16 18:29:00"><n u="Amphibia">Amphibia I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% The Domino Effect/Taking Charge
Anne finds a caterpillar and wants it as a pet, but must keep it secret from Hop Pop. Anne introduces the Plantars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 18:29:00" d="2020-04-16 19:00:00"><n u="New: Walk The Prank S3">New: Walk The Prank S3 III (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Penultimate
Chance gets into trouble when his phone pocket-likes a controversial message</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 19:00:00" d="2020-04-16 19:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (39)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Rollercoaster - The Musical
One of the boys' early adventures, where they built a rollercoaster in the yard and Candace tried to bust them by showing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 19:29:00" d="2020-04-16 20:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Interview with a Platypus/Tip of the Day
The boys build a Perry translator and use it to let the other animals air their grievances. Dad's doing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 20:00:00" d="2020-04-16 20:29:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats IV (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bionic Rebellion - Part One
The Lab Rats discover a confidante has secretly plotted to kill Davenport in revenge for his father's death, leading</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 20:29:00" d="2020-04-16 21:00:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats IV (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bionic Rebellion - Part Two
The Lab Rats discover a confidante has secretly plotted to kill Davenport in revenge for his father's death, leading</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 21:00:00" d="2020-04-16 21:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (1) (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Lake Nose Monster
Candace teases the boys about the Lake Nose Monster but is scared when she imagines seeing it. When the boys meet the monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-16 21:29:00" d="2020-04-17 00:29:00"><n u="Walk The Prank S3">Walk The Prank S3 III (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Penultimate
Chance gets into trouble when his phone pocket-likes a controversial message</k>  </p>
</a>
