<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2020-04-10 04:31:20"><p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 05:10:00" d="2020-04-17 05:35:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (26)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Gone Gark
Max gives Gark the seemingly impossible task of moving the moon but the unexpected results attracts the attention of a mysterious alien being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 05:35:00" d="2020-04-17 06:00:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>When Gark, a naive nine year old alien disguised as a cat, lands on Earth he meets pampered puss Max and it's a recipe for a fun-filled buddy comedy that's out of this world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 06:00:00" d="2020-04-17 06:29:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Furiki Family Vacation/Furiki Fashion Freakout
Andre takes the family for the ride of their lives. Andre finds a scarf. It's really a sleeping panther cub!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 06:29:00" d="2020-04-17 07:00:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Santa Sloth/Stuck in a Truck
Andre worries he won't get a present on Jungle Jam Day. Chobado sticks a bug in Gordon's truck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 07:00:00" d="2020-04-17 07:29:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats II (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Avalanche
Chase heads for the Arctic to get some rare minerals Davenport needs and is trapped in an avalanche. He's rescued by Douglas Davenport</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 07:29:00" d="2020-04-17 08:00:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats II (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Adam Up
To get Adam out of training duties he and Leo use Davenport's experimental cloning device to create another Adam. But the clone creates its own clones</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 08:00:00" d="2020-04-17 08:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Perry Lays an Egg/Gaming the System
The boys build an incubator for an egg they think Perry has laid. Candace looks after it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 08:29:00" d="2020-04-17 09:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Chronicles of Meap
When a space ship crashes carrying a cute alien called Meap, it causes trouble for the boys, culminating in their kidnap</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 09:00:00" d="2020-04-17 09:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Dreamscaperers
Lil' Gideon is defeated by Grunkle Stan. He uses a mind demon to lure Dipper, Mabel and Soos into Stan's mind to gain the knowledge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 09:29:00" d="2020-04-17 10:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Gideon Rises
After Lil' Gideon takes over the Mystery Shack, Dipper and Mabel try to get it back. But Lil' Gideon is always one step ahead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 10:00:00" d="2020-04-17 10:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (26)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sleepwalk Surprise/Sci-fi Pie Fly
Candace covers for the boys when Jeremy plays jet pack volleyball with them. The boys investigate crop circles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 10:29:00" d="2020-04-17 11:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (34)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Blackout/What'd I Miss
Candace is in charge of the boys during a power cut. Ferb and Perry return to find Phineas and the gang have been training domestic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 11:00:00" d="2020-04-17 11:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Great Indoors/Canderemy
The rain ruins Isabella's chance of a Fireside Girl patch. The boys create a biodome. Candace's obsession with Jeremy harms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 11:29:00" d="2020-04-17 12:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Birthday Clip O'Rama
It's Phineas' birthday. Ferb comes up with a plan to help him celebrate - with a clip show featuring highlights of their outrageous exploits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 12:00:00" d="2020-04-17 12:29:00"><n u="Ducktales">Ducktales II (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Golden Armoury of Cornelius Coot
With the Beagles on their tails, Webby and the Boys hunt for lost family treasure while Della teaches Launchpad how to actually fly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 12:29:00" d="2020-04-17 13:00:00"><n u="Ducktales">Ducktales II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Last Christmas
Scrooge celebrates Christmas with his time-travelling ghost buddies while time-lost Dewey teams with Young Donald to find his mum at Christmas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 13:00:00" d="2020-04-17 13:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cheers for Fears/Just our Luck
Candace reluctantly asks Phineas and Ferb's help to create the ride of Jeremy's life for his birthday. Doof has a lucky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 13:29:00" d="2020-04-17 14:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (27)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Phineas and Ferb Save Summer - Part One
Phineas and Ferb host a global summer concert, just as Doofenshmirtz's latest invention moves the Earth, putting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 14:00:00" d="2020-04-17 14:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (28)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Phineas and Ferb Save Summer - PartTwo
Phineas and Ferb host a global summer concert - just as Doofenshmirtz's latest invention moves the Earth, putting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 14:29:00" d="2020-04-17 15:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Return Policy/ Imperfect Storm
Doof uses an inator to return things to the store. Doof invents a Have-A-Bad-Day-Inator to ruin Mum's garden party. Guest star Simon Pegg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 15:00:00" d="2020-04-17 15:29:00"><n u="Amphibia">Amphibia I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% The Domino Effect/Taking Charge
Anne finds a caterpillar and wants it as a pet, but must keep it secret from Hop Pop. Anne introduces the Plantars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 15:29:00" d="2020-04-17 16:00:00"><n u="Amphibia">Amphibia I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% Hop Luck/Stakeout
To win a contest, Anne leads the family to make a new human food - pizza. Sprig wants Anne and Hop Pop to get along so he tricks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 16:00:00" d="2020-04-17 16:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Impopstar/Football Camp
Cricket is mistaken for a pop star so exploits the situation for the perks of fame. Remy and Cricket attend football</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 16:29:00" d="2020-04-17 17:00:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens II (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Heat Beaters/Bill-iever
Cricket and Remy play a contentious game of &quot;H-O-R-S-E&quot; on the hottest day of the year. To avoid punishment, Cricket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 17:00:00" d="2020-04-17 17:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Candace Disconnected/Magic Carpet Ride
Candace's mum won't buy her a new phone so she asks Phineas and Ferb to help. Inspired by Dad, the boys create</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 17:29:00" d="2020-04-17 18:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mommy Can You Hear Me?/Road Trip
Candace has an injured ankle, so the boys help stop her getting bored. On a family trip, the boys decide to build a diner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 18:00:00" d="2020-04-17 18:29:00"><n u="Amphibia">Amphibia I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% Anne Theft Auto/Breakout Star
While learning to drive the family snail wagon, Anne and Sprig take it for a joy ride. Anne's pimple breakout makes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 18:29:00" d="2020-04-17 19:00:00"><n u="New: Walk The Prank S3">New: Walk The Prank S3 III (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Wedding
Bailey tries to sabotage her mum's wedding to Uncle Will by giving her cold feet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 19:00:00" d="2020-04-17 19:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Oh There You are Perry/Swiss Family Phineas
Perry goes missing and Candace thinks it's her fault, but he's been relocated. The Flynn family takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 19:29:00" d="2020-04-17 20:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Hide and Seek/That Sinking Feeling
The boys use a machine to shrink themselves. Candace steals it to show to Mum. Baljeet asks the</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 20:00:00" d="2020-04-17 20:29:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Left Behind
When Adam, Bree and Chase decide to take the students off the Island for the night they accidentally leave Spin and Bob behind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 20:29:00" d="2020-04-17 21:00:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Under Siege
With suspicious things still happening the Lab Rats must find the rebel. Leo starts behaving oddly but he's doing it in his sleep</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 21:00:00" d="2020-04-17 21:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Baljeatles/Vanessassary Roughness
Baljeet enrols for a geology course that's really about becoming a rock star. Ferb fancies Vanessa and helps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-04-17 21:29:00" d="2020-04-18 00:29:00"><n u="Walk The Prank S3">Walk The Prank S3 III (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Wedding
Bailey tries to sabotage her mum's wedding to Uncle Will by giving her cold feet</k>  </p>
</a>
