<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="37" t="2020-05-29 04:33:45"><p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 05:10:00" d="2020-06-05 05:35:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>I, Maxine/Gark's Got Talent
After Max wishes he had powers like Gark, Gark helps him go robotic to earn respect. Max becomes Gark's agent when he shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 05:35:00" d="2020-06-05 06:00:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mirror, Mirror/Arugula
Gark does not see his reflection in the mirror. Gark invents an invisible girlfriend named Arugula</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 06:00:00" d="2020-06-05 06:29:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Taxi Furiki/Garage Games
Andre's horn buying business runs into trouble. Fighting over the new garage endangers friendships. Fighting over the new garage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 06:29:00" d="2020-06-05 07:00:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Santa Sloth/Stuck in a Truck
Andre worries he won't get a present on Jungle Jam Day. Chobado sticks a bug in Gordon's truck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 07:00:00" d="2020-06-05 07:29:00"><n u="Star Vs The Forces Of Evil">Star Vs The Forces Of Evil III (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Princess Turdina/Starfari
A return to St Olga's reveals it is not the same school it used to be. Star goes out into the field to understand why Mewmans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 07:29:00" d="2020-06-05 08:00:00"><n u="Star Vs The Forces Of Evil">Star Vs The Forces Of Evil III (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lava Lake Beach/Sweet Dreams
Star and Tom go to Lava Lake Beach. Star discovers she travels through multiple dimensions in her dreams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 08:00:00" d="2020-06-05 08:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Rollercoaster/Candace Loses her Head
The boys build a really cool rollercoaster in the back yard. While visiting Mount Rushmore, the boys have an unusual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 08:29:00" d="2020-06-05 09:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Fast and the Phineas/Lawn Gnome Beach Party of Terror: Candace causes trouble when the boys enter a car race. The boys hold a beach party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 09:00:00" d="2020-06-05 09:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Boss Mabel
Mabel thinks Stan is a bad boss, and is sure she can do it better than him. While Stan takes a holiday, Mabel tries to run the Mystery Shack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 09:29:00" d="2020-06-05 10:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Bottomless Pit
Stan, Soos, Mabel and Dipper accidentally fall down the Bottomless Pit. To pass time until they are rescued they tell stories including</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 10:00:00" d="2020-06-05 10:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bee Day
Doof plans to become the ruler of all the bees. The Fireside Girls want to get their bee-keeping badge but the bees are missing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 10:29:00" d="2020-06-05 11:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sidetracked
Agent P must stop a hijacked train running along the US/Canadian border, defeat Doof, save the train's passengers and rescue Canada's national</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 11:00:00" d="2020-06-05 11:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Knot my Problem/Mind Share
Can Candace finally outwit the boys and out them to Mum if they get stuck in their giant knot? The gang is tricked</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 11:29:00" d="2020-06-05 12:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Primal Perry
His life is in danger when Perry comes face to face with an Australian platypus hunter set on destroying him. He must defeat him while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 12:00:00" d="2020-06-05 12:29:00"><n u="Right Now Kapow">Right Now Kapow I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ugly Earthlings/The Dolphin
A team of heroes helps an ally. A reporter asks the hard-hitting questions. A bank robber posts a lot of really interesting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 12:29:00" d="2020-06-05 13:00:00"><n u="Right Now Kapow">Right Now Kapow I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Prank War/Invisible Girlfriend
A college prank war escalates. A shoplifter is so mad he could eat a screaming horse. A werewolf learns a lesson about love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 13:00:00" d="2020-06-05 13:29:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Left Behind
When Adam, Bree and Chase decide to take the students off the Island for the night they accidentally leave Spin and Bob behind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 13:29:00" d="2020-06-05 14:00:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Under Siege
With suspicious things still happening the Lab Rats must find the rebel. Leo starts behaving oddly but he's doing it in his sleep</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 14:00:00" d="2020-06-05 14:29:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats IV (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bionic Dog
When Douglas' long lost dog, Otis, shows up on the island, Chase becomes severely allergic and Adam instantly bonds with him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 14:29:00" d="2020-06-05 15:00:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats IV (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mission Mania
Feeling left out when no one recognizes him as the fourth member of the bionic team, Leo does his own self-promotion, resulting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 15:00:00" d="2020-06-05 15:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Parade Day/DIY Guys
Cricket's working but doesn't want to miss the Big Parade, so re-routes it. Bill uses a trip to the hardware store to teach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 15:29:00" d="2020-06-05 16:00:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Gargoyle Gals/Supermarket Scandal
Tilly claims she saw stone gargoyles come to life. Cricket can't fulfil an order for veg. What will he do?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 16:00:00" d="2020-06-05 16:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (29)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sleeping with Enemy/Tri State Treasure
Book of Secrets: Candace tries to bust the boys for doing a magic show then looks for an item to trade</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 16:29:00" d="2020-06-05 17:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (30)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Doofapus/Norm Unleashed
The boys' device accidentally liquefies Candace. Doof has jury duty so robot Norm takes over the day's evil scheme - using weapons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 17:00:00" d="2020-06-05 17:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bubble Boys/Isabella and the Temple of Sap
The boys make a huge bubble and float round in it. Isabella's Fireside Girls help the boys hunt for a Maracanut</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 17:29:00" d="2020-06-05 18:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cheer Up Candace/Fireside Girl Jamboree
The boys try to cheer Candace up. She's in a bad mood because Jeremy cancelled their date. Candace joins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 18:00:00" d="2020-06-05 18:29:00"><n u="New: Disney">New: Disney 11 III (55)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Episode 215
Ezequiel asks Delfina not to see Lorenzo. Gabo tells Amelia they've not done the challenge. Vitto asks a favour of Francisco. The teams are ready to play</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 18:29:00" d="2020-06-05 19:00:00"><n u="Ducktales">Ducktales II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Last Christmas
Scrooge celebrates Christmas with his time-travelling ghost buddies while time-lost Dewey teams with Young Donald to find his mum at Christmas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 19:00:00" d="2020-06-05 19:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Hurty Tooth/Sleepover Sisters
Cricket tries to avoid the dentist, while Bill struggles with a puzzle in the waiting room. Tilly and Andromeda</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 19:29:00" d="2020-06-05 20:00:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (26)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Nancy's trailer is stolen by her old biker gang, and the kids resolve to get it back. Cricket house-sits for Remy, but things go awry when the rest of the Greens visit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 20:00:00" d="2020-06-05 20:29:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats II (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Trucked Out
Adam gets his driving licence so Davenport suggests buying him a nice safe vehicle, but Adam wants a monster truck. What will he end up getting?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 20:29:00" d="2020-06-05 21:00:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats II (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Memory Wipe
The Lab Rats are grounded. They hear Davenport has won an award for a memory erasing device. Leo uses it to wipe some of Davenport's memory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 21:00:00" d="2020-06-05 21:29:00"><n u="Disney">Disney 11 III (55)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Episode 215
Ezequiel asks Delfina not to see Lorenzo. Gabo tells Amelia they've not done the challenge. Vitto asks a favour of Francisco. The teams are ready to play</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 21:29:00" d="2020-06-05 22:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Rollercoaster/Candace Loses her Head
The boys build a really cool rollercoaster in the back yard. While visiting Mount Rushmore, the boys have an unusual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 22:00:00" d="2020-06-05 22:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls II (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Northwest Mansion Noir
Pacifica enlists Dipper's help to rid the Northwest Mansion of a ghost before he wreaks havoc on her fancy party. Nathan Fillion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 22:29:00" d="2020-06-05 23:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls II (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Return of Stan
Government agents take Stan into custody, making Dipper and Mabel question how much they really know about their Grunkle Stan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2020-06-05 23:00:00" d="2020-06-06 02:00:00"><n u="Right Now Kapow">Right Now Kapow I (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Conscience/All You Can Eat
A child weighs her options. A buffet line wages war</k>  </p>
</a>
