<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="51" t="2019-08-09 01:34:37"><p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 05:10:00" d="2019-08-15 05:35:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Cat Crib/Lost in Throckmorton
Max and Gark sign up for a reality show. Max cheats. Max gets angry when playing an alien board game and causes things to disappear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 05:35:00" d="2019-08-15 06:00:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Dreamcatcher/Room of Panic
Gark feels left out when he realizes he doesn't have dreams. Max panics when he finds out Betty is leaving him alone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 06:00:00" d="2019-08-15 06:29:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Andre Furiki
Sloth Genius/Monkey Wrench in the Works: Andre tries hypnosis to become a genius stunt-sloth. Andre loses everything to a con-artist croc</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 06:29:00" d="2019-08-15 07:00:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Demolition Cube/Peanutland
Andre ends up as Pepita's pawn in a school demolition derby. Andre and Chobado go in search of a legendary peanut land</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 07:00:00" d="2019-08-15 07:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Spider-Man">Marvel's Spider-Man I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Horizon High - Part Two
Peter finds that he can use the new school lab and his classes to build Spider-Man tech and keep his identity a secret!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 07:29:00" d="2019-08-15 08:00:00"><n u="Space Chickens In Space">Space Chickens In Space I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Phil My Heart/Blibli Squared
Barnetta and Phil split up. The Chickens try to reunite them. Finley's latest invention makes Blibli multiply very fast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 08:00:00" d="2019-08-15 08:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Thaddeus and Thor/De Plane! De Plane!
Candace meets Mandy, who also looks after two boys. A rivalry develops. Phineas and Ferb decide to build the biggest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 08:29:00" d="2019-08-15 09:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Let's Take a Quiz/The Car Wash
Candace is jealous when Jeremy is in a TV commercial as she wants to be on TV too. The boys help Isabella raise money</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 09:00:00" d="2019-08-15 09:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Summerween
It's Gravity Falls' summer version of Halloween, with Jack-o-Melons. Dipper insults a candy monster that threatens to eat him if his candy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 09:29:00" d="2019-08-15 10:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Deep End
It's hot in Gravity Falls so the Pines head down to the pool. Dipper gets a job as a life guard, and Mabel meets a boy who's confined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 10:00:00" d="2019-08-15 10:29:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Going the Extra Milo/The Undergrounders
New kid Zack meets accident prone Milo Murphy, While on the subway Milo's car goes off course and he discovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 10:29:00" d="2019-08-15 11:00:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Rooting for the Enemy/Sunny Side Up
Milo goes to his first football game. Milo, Melissa, and Zack try to protect an egg for a science experiment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 11:00:00" d="2019-08-15 11:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Hiya Henry/People Watching
Cricket Green's family moves from country to Big City. As they acclimatize, their perspectives on differences between country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 11:29:00" d="2019-08-15 12:00:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Fill Bill/Critterball Crisis
The Greens eat out. Cricket and Tilly rescue the octopus instead of eating it. Trouble erupts when a neighbour won't return</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 12:00:00" d="2019-08-15 12:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Gideon Rises
After Lil' Gideon takes over the Mystery Shack, Dipper and Mabel try to get it back. But Lil' Gideon is always one step ahead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 12:29:00" d="2019-08-15 13:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Into the Bunker
Dipper's secret journal pages lead the gang to the author's hidden bunker. They find themselves coming face to face with a mysterious</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 13:00:00" d="2019-08-15 13:29:00"><n u="Supa Strikas">Supa Strikas V (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Man in the Iron Tank mask
Iron Tank plan to disrupt the Strikas by making Klaus a TV star. He becomes so selfish it stops him being a team player</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 13:29:00" d="2019-08-15 14:00:00"><n u="Supa Strikas">Supa Strikas V (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>64% Depth Charge
The team must play FC Hydra in their floating stadium. North Shaw has a strong rivalry with the Hydra's star Giorgio Liquido, but has it doomed the stadium?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 14:00:00" d="2019-08-15 14:29:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats III (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Brother Battle
Leo and Principal Terry battle to be the millionth customer in the shop where Bree works. Donald and his brother squabble, while Chase</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 14:29:00" d="2019-08-15 15:00:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats III (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Armed and Dangerous
Leo shows off his new bionic arm to Janelle, but it goes out of control. When Agent Graham turns the kids into celebrities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 15:00:00" d="2019-08-15 15:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Dude We're Getting the Band Back Together
The boys decide on a great present for mum and dad's anniversary - they'll persuade their parents' favourite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 15:29:00" d="2019-08-15 16:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Greece Lightning/Leave the Busting to Us
Greek mythology inspires the boys to hold a motorised chariot race. They build a giant water slide and Candace</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 16:00:00" d="2019-08-15 16:29:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Love Toboggan/The Island of Lost Dakotas
Sara feels safe to go on a date when Milo goes skiing. Dakota time travels to stop Cavendish creating a paradox</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 16:29:00" d="2019-08-15 17:00:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Fungus Among Us
A trip to 1965 upsets the time stream and everyone Milo knows seems to become possessed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 17:00:00" d="2019-08-15 17:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Gridlocked/Mama Bird
The family takes a road trip and ends up in a traffic jam! Tilly babysits chicks, hoping they will imprint on her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 17:29:00" d="2019-08-15 18:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Boss Mabel
Mabel thinks Stan is a bad boss, and is sure she can do it better than him. While Stan takes a holiday, Mabel tries to run the Mystery Shack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 18:00:00" d="2019-08-15 18:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Bottomless Pit
Stan, Soos, Mabel and Dipper accidentally fall down the Bottomless Pit. To pass time until they are rescued they tell stories including</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 18:29:00" d="2019-08-15 19:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Boyz Crazy
When Mabel discovers that her favourite boy band is actually a bunch of imprisoned clones, she attempts to rescue them, then decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 19:00:00" d="2019-08-15 19:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Carpet Diem
After a sleepover, Dipper and Mabel decide they can't share a room any more. They find a spare one, which contains an old carpet that it turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 19:29:00" d="2019-08-15 20:00:00"><n u="Mech-X4">Mech-X4 II (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Versus Velocity and Veracity
Veracity's first mission on the team could be her last as the team's attempt to give Mech-X4 a flight mode goes terribly, terribly wrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 20:00:00" d="2019-08-15 20:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Spider-Man">Marvel's Spider-Man I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Rise of Dock Ock - Part One
When Otto Octavius is caught in an explosion that fuses his robot arms to his body, Spidey tries to recruit The Octopus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 20:29:00" d="2019-08-15 21:00:00"><n u="Marvel's Spider-Man">Marvel's Spider-Man I (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Rise of Dock Ock - Part Two
Spidey invites The Octopus to patrol the streets alongside Kid Arachnid and himself until it becomes clear Otto isn't a team player</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 21:00:00" d="2019-08-15 21:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Avengers: Black Panther's">Marvel's Avengers: Black Panther's V (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>King Breaker Part Two
With an attack coming from multiple sides, Black Panther turns to help from an unlikely source</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 21:29:00" d="2019-08-15 22:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Fight Fighters
When Dipper falls out with Robbie over Wendy, he brings a character from his favourite arcade game to help him fight it out. Mabel tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 22:00:00" d="2019-08-15 22:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Little Dipper
Mabel realises she's a bit taller than Dipper, and boasts to him. Jealous, Dipper treks into the forest to find height altering crystals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 22:29:00" d="2019-08-15 23:00:00"><n u="Kick Buttowski Suburban Daredevil">Kick Buttowski Suburban Daredevil I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>For the love of Gunther/Father from the Truth
Gunther has a crush on Wacky Jackie and wants to be a daredevil for her. On Bring your Dad to school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 23:00:00" d="2019-08-15 23:29:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Some Like It Yacht/ Backward to School Night
The students become stranded on a deserted island. Parents are transformed into kids by a time travel snafu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-15 23:29:00" d="2019-08-16 00:00:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Picture Day/Agee Ientee Diogee
Milo has never managed to have a school photo taken. Diogee is mistaken for a secret agent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 00:00:00" d="2019-08-16 00:25:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Andre the Sloth Burglar/Wheels of Change
Andre accidentally steals Wheeloville's first ever car. Andre accidentally signs up for synchronised driving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 00:25:00" d="2019-08-16 00:50:00"><n u="Dude That's My Ghost">Dude That's My Ghost I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Little Billy/ Lolo in Love
Billy unwittingly turns a vintage Billy doll into a voodoo doll. Billy helps Rajeev win Lolo's affection by teaching</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 00:50:00" d="2019-08-16 01:15:00"><n u="Dude That's My Ghost">Dude That's My Ghost I (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Billy's Achilles/ Reality Showdown
Madame X is no longer interested in capturing him Billy so he goes on a search for a new obsessed fan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 01:15:00" d="2019-08-16 01:35:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% Gossip Boy/The Tale of the Golden Doctor's note 
Howard says he knows who the ninja is. McFist kidnaps him for the secret. Randy explores</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 01:35:00" d="2019-08-16 02:00:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% House of 1000 Boogers/Attack of the Killer Potatoes: Randy crashes Bash's party. He finds it's a plot to unmask the Ninja. Randy hears his enemy's science</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 02:00:00" d="2019-08-16 02:25:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Girlster/Video Star Vanilla
Auditions are being held for Shelby's favourite TV show but they want a girl. Boyster borrows Alicia's cat Vanilla for a viral</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 02:25:00" d="2019-08-16 02:45:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Wings of Love/Blackmailed
Mr Pluss sees Shelby dressed as a girl and is smitten. Franck, Boyster's nasty neighbour learns he's an oyster-child and blackmails him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 02:45:00" d="2019-08-16 03:10:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (10) (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Flea Bag/Humanoid
Max gets fleas before a date Gark shrinks himself to eliminate them. Gark makes Betty a humanoid date. Throckmorton downloads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 03:10:00" d="2019-08-16 03:35:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Staring Dog/28 Seconds Later
Gark's determined to find out why Staring Dog stares at Max. When Max makes Gark better with the orb, he infects the whole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 03:35:00" d="2019-08-16 04:00:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja II (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% Otto Know Better/Brolateral Damage
Randy falls in love with Viceroy's pet Otto and won't give it back. Randy goes undercover to discover the secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 04:00:00" d="2019-08-16 04:20:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja II (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% The Curse of Mudfart/Let the Wonk One In
Randy inadvertently brings the terrifying Mudfart to life. Randy unleashes the terrifying orange HalloweeNja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 04:20:00" d="2019-08-16 04:45:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Three Hours of the Condor/Boyster Pox
Boyster is addicted to a TV show about surviving in the wild. Boyster catches oysterpox. Will he be able to compete</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-16 04:45:00" d="2019-08-16 05:10:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Stache/Bust a Move
Boyster wants to be grown up. He gets a sushi seaweed moustache, but it's poisonous. Lola is out of work so Boyster's parents</k>  </p>
</a>
