<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="51" t="2019-08-13 02:06:04"><p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 05:10:00" d="2019-08-18 05:35:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (26)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Gone Gark
Max gives Gark the seemingly impossible task of moving the moon but the unexpected results attracts the attention of a mysterious alien being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 05:35:00" d="2019-08-18 06:00:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>When Gark, a naive nine year old alien disguised as a cat, lands on Earth he meets pampered puss Max and it's a recipe for a fun-filled buddy comedy that's out of this world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 06:00:00" d="2019-08-18 06:29:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Fun and Thunder/Chasing Waterfalls
Andre must learn to be patient on a scavenger hunt. Andre and Pepita team up for a photography contest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 06:29:00" d="2019-08-18 07:00:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Furiki Day/Andre learns to respect his family's traditions while rescuing his dad. Andre puts his friends in danger when he becomes friends with a carnivore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 07:00:00" d="2019-08-18 07:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Spider-Man">Marvel's Spider-Man I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Party Animals
Horizon High throws a dance in honour of Harry being exonerated, but Norman asks Harry to stay at Osborn academy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 07:29:00" d="2019-08-18 08:00:00"><n u="Space Chickens In Space">Space Chickens In Space I (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Presidential Coop/Pale Blue Rock
To be elected student president candidates face daft tasks. Sentient Space Rocks show up to party and cause trouble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 08:00:00" d="2019-08-18 08:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb II (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bubble Boys/Isabella and the Temple of Sap
The boys make a huge bubble and float round in it. Isabella's Fireside Girls help the boys hunt for a Maracanut</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 08:29:00" d="2019-08-18 09:00:00"><n u="New: Marvel's Guardians Of The Galaxy">New: Marvel's Guardians Of The Galaxy III (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Black Vortex - Part One
The Guardians, desperate to escape, jump into the Black Vortex mirror, get separated in the Black Vortex and find themselves in a different world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 09:00:00" d="2019-08-18 09:29:00"><n u="Star Vs The Forces Of Evil">Star Vs The Forces Of Evil III (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Puddle Defender/King Ludo
Moon and Star's safety is compromised so they hide at Buffrog's house. King Ludo reigns over the Butterfly castle but is controlled by Toffee</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 09:29:00" d="2019-08-18 10:00:00"><n u="Star Vs The Forces Of Evil">Star Vs The Forces Of Evil III (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Toffee
Star comes home and is determined to stop Ludo's tyrannical reign over the Butterfly Kingdom. Ludo rejects her help, but she is determined to stop Toffee for good</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 10:00:00" d="2019-08-18 10:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Avengers: Black Panther's">Marvel's Avengers: Black Panther's V (110)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mists of Attilan
Black Panther and Ms. Marvel head to the Inhuman city of Attilan on a secret mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 10:29:00" d="2019-08-18 11:00:00"><n u="Mech-X4">Mech-X4 II (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Versus the Thirty
Ryan meets more of Leo's technopathy test subjects including his birth mother. Harris, Spyder, and Veracity try to help Mark mend fences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 11:00:00" d="2019-08-18 11:29:00"><n u="Kickin' It">Kickin' It II (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Jack and Rudy attend a competition in San Francisco, where Rudy runs into an old rival. Meanwhile, Milton gets carried away giving others advice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 11:29:00" d="2019-08-18 12:00:00"><n u="Kickin' It">Kickin' It II (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% New Jack City
Jack feels slighted when Rudy's previous star pupil and friend of the gang, Carson, moves back to Seaford and rejoins the dojo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 12:00:00" d="2019-08-18 12:29:00"><n u="Kickin' It">Kickin' It II (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Karate Games
Jack and Kim are offered Hollywood roles after catching an escaped convict but are absolutely horrified when they realise the movie's finale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 12:29:00" d="2019-08-18 13:00:00"><n u="Kickin' It">Kickin' It II (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Kickin' It On Our Own - Part One
The kids help Rudy look good when his uncle, who invested in his company, visits. Their kindness backfires when he offers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 13:00:00" d="2019-08-18 13:29:00"><n u="Kickin' It">Kickin' It II (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Kickin' It On Our Own - Part Two
Rudy visits the dojo. He's horrified to find Ty is the new sensei and that the gang have all left. Ty offers to fight him for it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 13:29:00" d="2019-08-18 14:00:00"><n u="KiCKiN' It">KiCKiN' It III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% New. Spyfall
When a government agent mistakenly identifies Phil as an assassin whose target is a visiting prince, Jack takes on the role of a James</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 14:00:00" d="2019-08-18 14:29:00"><n>KiCKiN' It</n>    <k>New. Duelling Dojos: Jack takes over running the dojo when Rudy is babysitting a young boy for a few days. Jerry doesn't like it and he and Jack argue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 14:29:00" d="2019-08-18 15:00:00"><n>KiCKiN' It</n>    <k>New. Glove Hurts: Milton's winning entry for the invention fair is spotted by an entrepreneur who offers him a job. But Milton is shocked</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 15:00:00" d="2019-08-18 15:29:00"><n>KiCKiN' It</n>    <k>New. Sub Sinker: When Jerry drives away yet another substitute teacher in his geometry class, the principal can't find a replacement, until</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 15:29:00" d="2019-08-18 16:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Magnificent Few/S'Winter
The boys want to be cowboys but stampede the cows and must round them up. The boys get a snow cone machine and turn summer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 16:00:00" d="2019-08-18 16:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Photo Op/Remy Rescue
Bill tries to trick the family into having a photo taken. Can Cricket stop Remy's parents sending him away to school?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 16:29:00" d="2019-08-18 17:00:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Parade Day/DIY Guys
Cricket's working but doesn't want to miss the Big Parade, so re-routes it. Bill uses a trip to the hardware store to teach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 17:00:00" d="2019-08-18 17:29:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Missing Milo - Part Two
Milo and the gang face down sentient pistachio plants to save the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 17:29:00" d="2019-08-18 18:00:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% The Little Engine that Couldn't/ The Llama Incident: Melissa hopes her dad will see Milo is more than a disaster area. Milo and Melissa tell Zack the story</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 18:00:00" d="2019-08-18 18:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Avengers: Black Panther's">Marvel's Avengers: Black Panther's V (108)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Panther and the Wolf
To uncover enemies within Wakanda, Black Panther and Shuri cross paths with someone from their past</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 18:29:00" d="2019-08-18 19:00:00"><n u="Marvel's Guardians Of The Galaxy">Marvel's Guardians Of The Galaxy III (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Black Vortex - Part One
The Guardians, desperate to escape, jump into the Black Vortex mirror, get separated in the Black Vortex and find themselves in a different world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 19:00:00" d="2019-08-18 19:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>What a Croc!/Ferb TV
Phineas and Ferb hunt for an escaped crocodile. Doof plans to replace his brother with a chicken. See what the boys' TV channel would be like</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 19:29:00" d="2019-08-18 20:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Excaliferb
In this episode the boys are transported to the Middle Ages. They set out to find the legendary sword Excaliferb, which they need to defeat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 20:00:00" d="2019-08-18 20:50:00"><n>Lab Rats: Space Colony</n>    <k>Donald takes everyone for a visit to Davenportia, the first human space colony located on a remote planet in another galaxy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 20:50:00" d="2019-08-18 21:00:00"><n u="Disney Mickey Mouse">Disney Mickey Mouse III (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sock Burglar
Minnie knits a plan to catch a dastardly villain who is stealing everyone's socks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 21:00:00" d="2019-08-18 21:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Spider-Man">Marvel's Spider-Man I (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Spider Island - Part Three
Can Peter Parker find a way to contain and cure Gwen Stacy and Norman Osborn, who have turned into Spider-Monsters?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 21:29:00" d="2019-08-18 22:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Carpet Diem
After a sleepover, Dipper and Mabel decide they can't share a room any more. They find a spare one, which contains an old carpet that it turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 22:00:00" d="2019-08-18 22:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Boyz Crazy
When Mabel discovers that her favourite boy band is actually a bunch of imprisoned clones, she attempts to rescue them, then decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 22:29:00" d="2019-08-18 23:00:00"><n u="Star Wars Resistance">Star Wars Resistance I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The New Trooper
When Kel and Eila seek out Kaz's help after knocking out a stormtrooper, Kaz dons the trooper's armour to protect the kids and spy on the First Order</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 23:00:00" d="2019-08-18 23:29:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% The Doctor Zone Files/ The Note
Sara wants to see The Doctor Zone Files movie with Milo, but worries about potential problems. Milo spends the day chasing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-18 23:29:00" d="2019-08-19 00:00:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Party of Peril/Smooth Operator
Melissa and Zack throw Milo his first real birthday party. Milo goes to the opera and ends up centre stage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-19 00:00:00" d="2019-08-19 00:25:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Attack of the Killer Tires/Secrets and Snails
Andre causes an epidemic, endangering the village. Andre reveals Miss Piston's scandalous past</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-19 00:25:00" d="2019-08-19 00:50:00"><n u="Dude That's My Ghost">Dude That's My Ghost I (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Spencer gets what he deserves when he cons Hugh into taking him on a camping trip so he can shoot a desert-themed horror movie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-19 00:50:00" d="2019-08-19 01:15:00"><n u="Dude That's My Ghost">Dude That's My Ghost I (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Summertime Rules/Merman
Spencer gets a job as a head towel boy and discovers his assistant is Principal Ponzi! Rajeev mixes muscle-building cream</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-19 01:15:00" d="2019-08-19 01:35:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% Silent Punch, Deadly Punch/Ninja Camp
Randy hunts for a special tree whose sap makes smoke bombs. Randy must stop a former Norrisville Ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-19 01:35:00" d="2019-08-19 02:00:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% Stanked to the Future/Wave Slayers 
Randy thaws a frozen student from the 1980s then must re-unite him with his lost love. The Wave Slayer gets stanked</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-19 02:00:00" d="2019-08-19 02:25:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Boyster sneezes blue ink when he has a cold, and turns Alicia's drawings blue. Magic is Rafik's new hobby. His audition attracts the attention of an evil</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-19 02:25:00" d="2019-08-19 02:45:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Wavester/Hand in Sticky Hand
When Shelby's favourite show ends, Boyster makes him a powerful aerial but it interferes with Boyster's sonar. A spider bites</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-19 02:45:00" d="2019-08-19 03:10:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>It's Christmas and Max explains to Gark how mean Santa is, because he never got the toy he wanted. It's New Year's Day and Betty's already struggling with her resolution</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-19 03:10:00" d="2019-08-19 03:35:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cat Box of Fear/Max Me No Questions
Gark wantss to rid cats of all their fears. Gark receives a box with an emoji interface that answers all his questions Max gets jealous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-19 03:35:00" d="2019-08-19 04:00:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja II (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% Mastermind of Disastermind/The Brawn Also Rises
Howard convinces Randy he'd be an undefeatable villain. Howard and Randy pretend to be chased</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-19 04:00:00" d="2019-08-19 04:20:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja II (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% Debbie Meddle/Aplopalypse Now
Randy must convince Debbie he is not the Ninja before she announces it to everyone. Randy asks Plop Plop to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-19 04:20:00" d="2019-08-19 04:45:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>He's Got Legs/Boyster Claus
Lola makes Shelby some false legs, Boyster and Rafik enter him in a contest. Boyster thinks he's injured Father Christmas so fills in for him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-08-19 04:45:00" d="2019-08-19 05:10:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>It Takes a Thief/Lab Coat Party
Boyster worries his brother is a thief then finds the real culprit. Shelby won't go to a party so Boyster surprises</k>  </p>
</a>
