<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="51" t="2019-07-11 00:20:30"><p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 05:10:00" d="2019-07-17 05:35:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Kitty Latte/The Big One
A jealous Max is convinced Betty is seeing another cat behind his back. After an ominous message on his codex, Gark knows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 05:35:00" d="2019-07-17 06:00:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Fat Cat/Bathtub of Terror
Max emulates his new TV idol by over-eating. Max is terrified of looking into the bath as he's scared something terrifying will emerge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 06:00:00" d="2019-07-17 06:29:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% M-M-M-my Bologna/Everybody Ninj-along
When Randy and Howard take care of a bologna &quot;baby&quot; it mysteriously comes to life. Bucky creates a Ninja theme</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 06:29:00" d="2019-07-17 07:00:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% Fudge Factory/Best Buds
Randy goes to great lengths to prove he's a good liar and puts himself in danger. Randy uses the Nomicon to cheat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 07:00:00" d="2019-07-17 07:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Spider-Man">Marvel's Spider-Man I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ultimate Spider-Man
When Miles Morales is bitten by a radioactive spider and gets spider powers, Spider-Man must teach him the responsibilities of being a superhero</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 07:29:00" d="2019-07-17 08:00:00"><n u="Space Chickens In Space">Space Chickens In Space I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Floofy, Fibby Kiss-Kiss/You Snooze, You Cruise
Finley's in trouble. His siblings are too obsessed with a video game to help. The Chickens investigate a strange pilot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 08:00:00" d="2019-07-17 08:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Fly on the Wall/My Sweet Ride
Candace is accidentally turned into a fly. Candace has always dreamed of having her own car, and finally gets her wish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 08:29:00" d="2019-07-17 09:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>For Your Ice Only/Happy New Year
The kids play in an exhibition hockey game and take it to the extreme. To celebrate the New Year</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 09:00:00" d="2019-07-17 09:29:00"><n u="Mech-X4">Mech-X4 I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>59% Let's Get Some Air
As Ryan and the team race to cure Harris of a strange ailment, they find themselves trapped in a cave-in</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 09:29:00" d="2019-07-17 10:00:00"><n u="Mech-X4">Mech-X4 II (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>59% Versus the Tech Army
A fun day with Dad turns deadly when Ryan and Mark are attacked by unfriendly tech. Spyder and Harris encounter their new enemy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 10:00:00" d="2019-07-17 10:29:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law II (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Safety First/Cavendish Unleashed
Elliot begins to understand why he's obsessed with safety. Cavendish accidentally unleashes a giant alien cyclops</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 10:29:00" d="2019-07-17 11:00:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law II (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% First Impressions/The Speech and Debate League of Death and Destruction Cross Town Explosion Event; Six-year-old Milo meets Melissa. Zack and Milo join Melissa's team</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 11:00:00" d="2019-07-17 11:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cricket Versus/Blue Tater
Cricket must wrestle a wild animal for a rite of passage. Bill unearths a mysterious blue potato. Is it cursed?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 11:29:00" d="2019-07-17 12:00:00"><n u="Kick Buttowski Suburban Daredevil">Kick Buttowski Suburban Daredevil I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Kickasaurus Wrecks/Battle for the Snax
Kick presents a fire-breathing Kickasaurus as half time entertainment at a football match. Kick helps Gunther</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 12:00:00" d="2019-07-17 12:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Deep End
It's hot in Gravity Falls so the Pines head down to the pool. Dipper gets a job as a life guard, and Mabel meets a boy who's confined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 12:29:00" d="2019-07-17 13:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Boss Mabel
Mabel thinks Stan is a bad boss, and is sure she can do it better than him. While Stan takes a holiday, Mabel tries to run the Mystery Shack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 13:00:00" d="2019-07-17 13:29:00"><n u="Supa Strikas">Supa Strikas II (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>62% Beautiful Gaming
Pro gamer Hack wins a prize to go to Japan for a Strikas' game but runs away. The team's coach is kidnapped and they must find Hack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 13:29:00" d="2019-07-17 14:00:00"><n u="Ducktales">Ducktales I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Woo-oo! Donald takes Huey, Dewey and Louie to their reclusive Uncle Scrooge McDuck's mansion where they uncover family secrets and accidentally</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 14:00:00" d="2019-07-17 14:29:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats I (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Chip Switch
The Lab Rats defy Davenport's warnings and swap bionic chips. They wreck the elevator, trapping Principal Perry with Leo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 14:29:00" d="2019-07-17 15:00:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Drone Alone
Davenport and Tasha go to Australia thinking Eddy's looking after the kids, only to discover he's stowed away on their plane</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 15:00:00" d="2019-07-17 15:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Put that Putter Away/Does This Duckbill Make Me Look Fat: The mini golf course is shutting so the boys build their own. The boys' teleporting device</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 15:29:00" d="2019-07-17 16:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Traffic Cam Caper/Bowl-R-Ama Drama
Candace borrows the traffic camera DVD to prove to her mother what the boys have been doing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 16:00:00" d="2019-07-17 16:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Spider-Man">Marvel's Spider-Man I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Rise of Dock Ock - Part One
When Otto Octavius is caught in an explosion that fuses his robot arms to his body, Spidey tries to recruit The Octopus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 16:29:00" d="2019-07-17 17:00:00"><n u="Space Chickens In Space">Space Chickens In Space I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>All Flying and Chill/Jail Birds
The chickens' mission to return an artefact gets serious. Chuck and Starley insult an alien race and end up in jail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 17:00:00" d="2019-07-17 17:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Photo Op/Remy Rescue
Bill tries to trick the family into having a photo taken. Can Cricket stop Remy's parents sending him away to school?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 17:29:00" d="2019-07-17 18:00:00"><n u="Big Hero 6 The Series">Big Hero 6 The Series I (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Big Hero 7
Richardson Mole goads Fred into accidentally revealing Big Hero 6's secret identities and then blackmails his way into the team, becoming its seventh member</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 18:00:00" d="2019-07-17 18:29:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% The Doctor Zone Files/ The Note
Sara wants to see The Doctor Zone Files movie with Milo, but worries about potential problems. Milo spends the day chasing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 18:29:00" d="2019-07-17 19:00:00"><n u="Ducktales">Ducktales I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>McMystery at McDuck McManor! Scrooge mysteriously disappears while Huey tries to throw him the perfect birthday party. The boys now have to host a locked room mystery party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 19:00:00" d="2019-07-17 19:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Tales from Resistance
Now Doofenshmirtz is in jail Candace is feeling restless. Then a new threat appears in the Second Dimension and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 19:29:00" d="2019-07-17 20:00:00"><n u="Mech-X4">Mech-X4 II (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>59% Versus Traeger
At a secret weapons facility, the team has their first real battle with their mysterious new enemy - Traeger - who catches them off guard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 20:00:00" d="2019-07-17 20:50:00"><n>Milo Murphy's Law - Missing Milo</n>    <k>When Milo is stopped from destroying pistachio plants, they become sentient and try to take over the planet, He must confront them to save the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 20:50:00" d="2019-07-17 21:00:00"><n u="Disney Mickey Mouse">Disney Mickey Mouse III (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Entombed
Mickey and Minnie get separated inside a spooky tomb while on an excavation in the Valley of the Kings in Egypt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 21:00:00" d="2019-07-17 21:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Avengers: Black Panther's">Marvel's Avengers: Black Panther's V (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bashenga
Black Panther discovers secrets about his ancestor, Bashenga, the founder of Wakanda</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 21:29:00" d="2019-07-17 22:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls II (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Sock Opera
Attempting to impress a local puppeteer Mabel puts on a sock puppet rock opera but her show goes wrong when Dipper's drive to uncover journal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 22:00:00" d="2019-07-17 22:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Soos and the Real Girl
When Soos finds himself in need of a date for his cousin Reggie's engagement party, he looks to a dating simulator game to help him talk to girls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 22:29:00" d="2019-07-17 23:00:00"><n u="Kick Buttowski Suburban Daredevil">Kick Buttowski Suburban Daredevil II (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Swap Meet/Bee Awesome
Disaster strikes when Mum's anniversary present is in a pile of stuff due to be swapped. Kick's entered the spelling bee, and trains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 23:00:00" d="2019-07-17 23:29:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% World without Milo/The Race
Elliot gets to see what the world would be like without Milo. Milo runs a race, as Cavendish and Dakota get stuck in the Old West</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 23:29:00" d="2019-07-18 00:00:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Milo's Halloween Scream-A-Torium!
Zack doesn't believe anything about Halloween can scare him anymore, but Murphy's Law makes sure everyone gets a scare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-18 00:00:00" d="2019-07-18 00:25:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Burrito Hotel/ Brenda Gets the Boot
Andre and Champion's contest leads them into Gordon's trap. Gordon takes Andre to traffic court for reckless driving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-18 00:25:00" d="2019-07-18 00:50:00"><n u="Dude That's My Ghost">Dude That's My Ghost I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Billy Joe's Last Fan/ Let's Do Lunch
None of Billy's fans show up for the anniversary of his first number one hit. Spencer disguises himself as an adult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-18 00:50:00" d="2019-07-18 01:15:00"><n u="Dude That's My Ghost">Dude That's My Ghost I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Billy Do Joe/ Billy Blob
Billy promises to have Spencer's back in a kung fu battle against Kleet. Billy's ectoplasm bring a bubble gum bubble to life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-18 01:15:00" d="2019-07-18 01:35:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja II (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% When Howie Met Randy/ Bro Money, Bro Problems
Randy tries to convince Howard Norrisville has a Ninja. The boys unwittingly sell used Ninja weapons to Viceroy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-18 01:35:00" d="2019-07-18 02:00:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja II (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% The Three Mascot-eers/Escape from Scrap City
Howard becomes school mascot causing problems with Randy. McFist and Ninja crash in Scrap</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-18 02:00:00" d="2019-07-18 02:25:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Shelby the Art Lover/Skeleton
Shelby steals a painting of a clam shell: he's in love! Boyster discovers he has no skeleton, so he swallows one belonging to a monkey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-18 02:25:00" d="2019-07-18 02:45:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Strange New Friend/Go Fish
Boyster doesn't realise that new boy Bruno is a chef with a liking for oysters. Boyster breaks Shelby's TV and replaces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-18 02:45:00" d="2019-07-18 03:10:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>When Gark, a naive nine year old alien disguised as a cat, lands on Earth he meets pampered puss Max and it's a recipe for a fun-filled buddy comedy that's out of this world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-18 03:10:00" d="2019-07-18 03:35:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>When Gark, a naive nine year old alien disguised as a cat, lands on Earth he meets pampered puss Max and it's a recipe for a fun-filled buddy comedy that's out of this world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-18 03:35:00" d="2019-07-18 04:00:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja I (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% McOne Armed and Dangerous
During McFist Industries' 50th anniversary celebrations the Ninja reveals McFist as a villain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-18 04:00:00" d="2019-07-18 04:20:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja I (26)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% Randy Cunningham
13th Century Ninja: Randy and Howard accidentally stumble back in time and must help the original Ninja battle the Sorcerer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-18 04:20:00" d="2019-07-18 04:45:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Third Arm/Pool Partay
When Boyster is in danger, a third arm grows out of his head and saves him. Boyster and Rafik decide to become The Kings of Summer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-18 04:45:00" d="2019-07-18 05:10:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Marble Mischief/Puffed Up
Boyster must take on a fearsome adversary in an extreme marble tournament. Boyster decides to use a puffer fish as an original</k>  </p>
</a>
