<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="51" t="2019-07-11 00:20:30"><p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 05:10:00" d="2019-07-16 05:35:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (10) (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Flea Bag/Humanoid
Max gets fleas before a date Gark shrinks himself to eliminate them. Gark makes Betty a humanoid date. Throckmorton downloads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 05:35:00" d="2019-07-16 06:00:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Staring Dog/28 Seconds Later
Gark's determined to find out why Staring Dog stares at Max. When Max makes Gark better with the orb, he infects the whole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 06:00:00" d="2019-07-16 06:29:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja II (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% Flume-igation/On the Poolfront
The ninja accidentally releases an angry, dry-skinned monster. The Ninja tries to make Howard's dad look</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 06:29:00" d="2019-07-16 07:00:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% Unstank My Heart/The Wrath of Whopee 2
The Ninja intervenes when Randy's ex band mate takes his revenge. Whopee is replaced by the evil Whopee 2</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 07:00:00" d="2019-07-16 07:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Spider-Man">Marvel's Spider-Man I (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Halloween Moon
On Halloween Night, Spider-Man must team up with the Incredible Hulk to stop Man-Wolf, a super-strong gamma-powered werewolf</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 07:29:00" d="2019-07-16 08:00:00"><n u="Space Chickens In Space">Space Chickens In Space I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Green Eyed Monster/I Believe I Can Fly
Adele pairs up with Finley on a project. Chuck is jealous. Starley must control her emotions as she yearns to fly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 08:00:00" d="2019-07-16 08:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (34)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Blackout/What'd I Miss
Candace is in charge of the boys during a power cut. Ferb and Perry return to find Phineas and the gang have been training domestic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 08:29:00" d="2019-07-16 09:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb III (35)</n><t>S</t>    <k>This is your Back Story
Norm is the host of a reality show looking back at the eventful life of his creator, Doof. Perry works out there's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 09:00:00" d="2019-07-16 09:29:00"><n u="Mech-X4">Mech-X4 I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>59% Let's Call It Mech-X4 - Part Two
Ryan and the team set out to prove to Bay City they're heroes, only to find themselves targeted by a terrifying new monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 09:29:00" d="2019-07-16 10:00:00"><n u="Mech-X4">Mech-X4 II (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>59% Versus the Dark Knight
A new monster creates a city-wide blackout and disables Mech-X4. The team must get the robot working again to stop the beast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 10:00:00" d="2019-07-16 10:29:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Adventure Buddies/Ride Along Little Doggie
Doof misses Perry, so Vanessa suggests that Doof find a new 'adventure buddy.' Diogee mistakenly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 10:29:00" d="2019-07-16 11:00:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law II (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Look at this Ship/Cast Party
Cavendish finds a crashed UFO. Zack's party guests show up wearing casts because of freak accidents that are nothing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 11:00:00" d="2019-07-16 11:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Space Chicken/Steak Night
Cricket tries to launch a chicken into outer space. On steak night, Cricket leaves the steaks on the subway</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 11:29:00" d="2019-07-16 12:00:00"><n u="Kick Buttowski Suburban Daredevil">Kick Buttowski Suburban Daredevil I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Knocked Out/Not without my Cereal
Kick wants to demonstrate to a talent show what awesome means. Kick wants the Billy Stumps cereal, but must babysit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 12:00:00" d="2019-07-16 12:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Little Dipper
Mabel realises she's a bit taller than Dipper, and boasts to him. Jealous, Dipper treks into the forest to find height altering crystals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 12:29:00" d="2019-07-16 13:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls I (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Summerween
It's Gravity Falls' summer version of Halloween, with Jack-o-Melons. Dipper insults a candy monster that threatens to eat him if his candy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 13:00:00" d="2019-07-16 13:29:00"><n u="Supa Strikas">Supa Strikas II (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>62% Big Bo,To Go
Big Bo loses his memory in a fall.The opposition team wastes no time ensuring he won't make it to the match. Can Shakes discover the big man's whereabouts?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 13:29:00" d="2019-07-16 14:00:00"><n u="Ducktales S2">Ducktales S2 II (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The 87 Cent Solution
The kids must stop Scrooge's unhealthy obsession with a few missing coins to keep him from becoming the next Glomgold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 14:00:00" d="2019-07-16 14:29:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats I (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Can I Borrow the Helicopter?
Leo confides to Davenport that he's nervous to ask a girl out, and Davenport lets it slip so Tasha decides to help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 14:29:00" d="2019-07-16 15:00:00"><n u="Lab Rats">Lab Rats I (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Back from the Future
Future Leo arrives in a time machine to stop Adam, Bree and Chase from taking part in a dangerous mission to stop a particle collider</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 15:00:00" d="2019-07-16 15:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Crack that Whip/The Best Lazy Day Ever
Grandma was a roller skater so the boys build her a track. The boys have a lazy day. Candace is bored and decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 15:29:00" d="2019-07-16 16:00:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb I (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Boyfriend from 27,000 BC/Voyage to the Bottom of Buford: The boys find a frozen caveman in a glacier and defrost him. The boys help Buford the bully</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 16:00:00" d="2019-07-16 16:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Spider-Man">Marvel's Spider-Man I (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Screwball Live
New costumed figure Screwball pranks Spidey, so when Screwball is captured by Hammerhead and Absorbing Man he must decide whether or not to help her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 16:29:00" d="2019-07-16 17:00:00"><n u="Space Chickens In Space">Space Chickens In Space I (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Alpha Chuck/Being Glargg
Chuck makes a more handsome, intelligent clone of himself. Chuck falls into a portal to Glargg's mind and gets control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 17:00:00" d="2019-07-16 17:29:00"><n u="Big City Greens">Big City Greens I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Cricketsitter/Backflip Bill
Cricket has a list of crazy stunts to do while Bill is away. Cricket tries to help Bill realise his childhood dream</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 17:29:00" d="2019-07-16 18:00:00"><n u="Big Hero 6 The Series">Big Hero 6 The Series I (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Steamer's Revenge
Hiro and the gang plan the ultimate birthday surprise for Wasabi by recovering his car from the bottom of the bay, but Baron Von Steamer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 18:00:00" d="2019-07-16 18:29:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Rooting for the Enemy/Sunny Side Up
Milo goes to his first football game. Milo, Melissa, and Zack try to protect an egg for a science experiment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 18:29:00" d="2019-07-16 19:00:00"><n u="Ducktales">Ducktales I (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Beware the B.U.D.D.Y. System
When Mark Beaks invents an uncrashable self-driving car, Launchpad recruits Gyro's eager intern Fenton to help defeat the mechanical menace</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 19:00:00" d="2019-07-16 19:29:00"><n u="Phineas and Ferb">Phineas and Ferb IV (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Doof 101/Father's Day
Doof is sent to teach science for his community service to Vanessa's embarrassment. Doof finds the precious lawn gnome</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 19:29:00" d="2019-07-16 20:00:00"><n u="Mech-X4">Mech-X4 II (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>59% Versus the Tech Army
A fun day with Dad turns deadly when Ryan and Mark are attacked by unfriendly tech. Spyder and Harris encounter their new enemy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 20:00:00" d="2019-07-16 20:50:00"><n>Lab Rats: Bionic Rebellion</n>    <k>The Lab Rats discover a confidante has secretly formed an evil rebellion to take revenge for his father's death by killing Davenport, leading to a bionic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 20:50:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00"><n u="Disney Mickey Mouse">Disney Mickey Mouse III (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Split Decision
Mickey is forced to wrangle two very different Donalds after Professor Von Drake's latest invention splits him in half</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 21:29:00"><n u="Marvel's Avengers: Black Panther's">Marvel's Avengers: Black Panther's V (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Yemandi
Black Panther discovers secrets about his ancestor, Yemandi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 21:29:00" d="2019-07-16 22:00:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% Into the Bunker
Dipper's secret journal pages lead the gang to the author's hidden bunker. They find themselves coming face to face with a mysterious</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 22:00:00" d="2019-07-16 22:29:00"><n u="Gravity Falls">Gravity Falls II (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>87% The Golf War
After being belittled by Pacifica too many times, Mabel challenges her to a miniature golf-off, which gets out of control when some local</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 22:29:00" d="2019-07-16 23:00:00"><n u="Kick Buttowski Suburban Daredevil">Kick Buttowski Suburban Daredevil II (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Attic-A/Free Gunther
The Buttowski men are trapped in the loft at the mercy of the Evil Attic Gnome. Gunther is grounded and Kick has to break</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 23:00:00" d="2019-07-16 23:29:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% A Clockwork Origin/Perchance to Sleepwalk
Milo and friends hunt a robot that's fled from its creators. Milo sleepwalks with no-one awake to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-16 23:29:00" d="2019-07-17 00:00:00"><n u="Milo Murphy's Law">Milo Murphy's Law I (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% Some Like It Yacht/ Backward to School Night
The students become stranded on a deserted island. Parents are transformed into kids by a time travel snafu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 00:00:00" d="2019-07-17 00:25:00"><n u="Furiki Wheels">Furiki Wheels I (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Musical Muffler Mystery/Mama at the Wheel
Chobado steals the school's musical muffler. Andre is embarrassed by Moka-Moka's slothy behaviour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 00:25:00" d="2019-07-17 00:50:00"><n u="Dude That's My Ghost">Dude That's My Ghost I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Ghost of Spencer Wright/Axe Maniac 
Billy turns Spencer into a ghost but Billy has no idea how to turn him back. Billy accidentally brings Spencer's video game to life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 00:50:00" d="2019-07-17 01:15:00"><n u="Dude That's My Ghost">Dude That's My Ghost I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sports Hero/Biopic Trap
Spencer's plan to use Billy's ectoplasm to become famous goes badly wrong. Spencer's blackmailed into filming Ponzi's life story</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 01:15:00" d="2019-07-17 01:35:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja II (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% Rorg - Hero of the Past/Mort-al Combat
Ninja thinks he's got a cheat sheet for every battle. Is he right? Randy blames the Ninja for trashing Howard's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 01:35:00" d="2019-07-17 02:00:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja II (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% Wonkin' for the Weekend/Ninjafan
Howard suddenly becomes evil. Can Randy get him back to normal? Randy's reaction to a fan opens him up to attack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 02:00:00" d="2019-07-17 02:25:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Supermollusc/ The Necklace
Boyster dresses as a super-hero to change his friends' dislike of molluscs. Boyster uses yoghurt to make Alicia a necklace</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 02:25:00" d="2019-07-17 02:45:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Teachinator/The Alien
Boyster decides to sneak into the very scary Mr. Pluss's house and steal the answers to a test. Boyster dresses as an alien to cheer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 02:45:00" d="2019-07-17 03:10:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (25)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mirror, Mirror/Arugula
Gark does not see his reflection in the mirror. Gark invents an invisible girlfriend named Arugula</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 03:10:00" d="2019-07-17 03:35:00"><n u="Counterfeit Cat">Counterfeit Cat I (26)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Gone Gark
Max gives Gark the seemingly impossible task of moving the moon but the unexpected results attracts the attention of a mysterious alien being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 03:35:00" d="2019-07-17 04:00:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja I (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% Lucius O'Thunderpunch/Bring me the Head of Ranginald Bagel! McFist introduces himself as superhero, Lucius O'Thunderpunch. Randy accidentally endangers a kid at school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 04:00:00" d="2019-07-17 04:20:00"><n u="Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja">Randy Cunningham: 9th Grade Ninja I (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>66% Weinerman Tested, Cunningham Approved/ Sorcerer in Love 2: Sorceress' Revenge: The boys inadvertently help create a Ninja-seeking robot. The Sorceress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 04:20:00" d="2019-07-17 04:45:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Love at First Sight/Go Fish
As Axelle prepares to beat up Boyster up, they are struck by lightning, Boyster accidentally breaks Shelby's precious</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1103" o="2019-07-17 04:45:00" d="2019-07-17 05:10:00"><n u="Boyster">Boyster I (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quiz Show No No/Fish Humour
Shelby enters a TV game show but the other competitors aren't very honest. Boyster thinks he's got no sense of humour</k>  </p>
</a>
