<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="67" t="2019-07-11 00:20:30"><p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 05:10:00" d="2019-07-16 05:35:00"><n>Henry Hugglemonster</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. Geri Halliwell stars in this episode in which Summer auditions to sing with her idol Isabella Roarson. Then, Henry keeps a tiny hugglefish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 05:35:00" d="2019-07-16 05:45:00"><n>The Hive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Grasshopper organises a navigation lesson and Buzzbee, Jasper, Rubee and Debee make it a race. However, they get too competitive and play tricks on one another</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 05:45:00" d="2019-07-16 06:00:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>The villainous side-kicks of moths and ninjalinos team up to form one evil villain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 06:00:00" d="2019-07-16 06:15:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cartoon adventures with Connor, Amaya and Greg, who by day are ordinary schoolkids, but by night are pyjama-wearing superheroes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 06:15:00" d="2019-07-16 06:30:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Catboy was turned into a cat by Romeo and Owlette and Gekko must deal with Catboy's feline behavior as well as stopping Romeo transform everyone into pets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 06:30:00" d="2019-07-16 06:55:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cartoon adventures with Connor, Amaya and Greg, who by day are ordinary schoolkids, but by night are pyjama-wearing superheroes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 06:55:00" d="2019-07-16 07:00:00"><n>Minnie's Bow-Toons</n><t>D</t>    <k>A Pizza Parlour mix-up sends Minnie and Daisy to Luigi's Pizzeria, to make pizzas for the hungry crowd. Minnie and Daisy make some funny looking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 07:00:00" d="2019-07-16 07:15:00"><n>Muppet Babies</n><t>D</t>    <k>Summer and Piggy build a blanket fort, but the fun takes a turn when Queen Piggy imposes her strict rules upon the Blanket Kingdom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 07:15:00" d="2019-07-16 07:30:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Gekko doesn't want to admit he needs help underwater</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 07:30:00" d="2019-07-16 08:00:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. Romeo uses his newest device to make the PJ Masks and their HQ float away. Then, Romeo steals the PJ Masks' super vehicles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 08:00:00" d="2019-07-16 08:30:00"><n>Vampirina</n><t>D</t>    <k>Vee's friends try to keep her surprise party a secret, then learn it's the guests that get the surprises. Vee and Poppy set off a dance craze that could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 08:30:00" d="2019-07-16 09:00:00"><n>Fancy Nancy Clancy</n><t>D</t>    <k>Nancy wants to win a poetry contest but gets writer's block. Nancy's Valentine's card is accidentally delivered to Grace</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 09:00:00" d="2019-07-16 09:30:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Gekko's powers are increased by Power Pondweeds. Owlette breaks the ltelescope and tries to blame Luna Girl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 09:30:00" d="2019-07-16 10:00:00"><n>Vampirina</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cartoon adventure about a vampire girl whose family run a guest house for ghouls and goblins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 10:00:00" d="2019-07-16 10:30:00"><n>Sofia the First</n><t>D</t>    <k>Sofia is to sing the anthem at the Harvest Festival. She boasts about it, so her amulet turns her voice into a croak! But Disney Princess Belle is on hand to help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 10:30:00" d="2019-07-16 11:00:00"><n>Sofia the First</n><t>D</t>    <k>Snow White visits the kingdom and helps Sofia realise a sorceress is not what she seems to be</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 11:00:00" d="2019-07-16 11:20:00"><n>Fancy Nancy Clancy</n><t>D</t>    <k>When Nancy's favourite waitress gives Jo Jo special attention, Nancy's behaviour threatens to ruin dinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 11:20:00" d="2019-07-16 11:40:00"><n>Fancy Nancy Clancy</n><t>D</t>    <k>When a neighborhood climibng tree is declared off-limits, Nancy shows her friends how to stand up for they believe in</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 11:40:00" d="2019-07-16 12:00:00"><n>Fancy Nancy Clancy</n><t>D</t>    <k>Nancy dreams of becoming a synchronized swimmer, but first must overcome her fear of going underwater</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 12:00:00" d="2019-07-16 12:20:00"><n>Puppy Dog Pals</n><t>D</t>    <k>A friend's puppy arrives for a visit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 12:20:00" d="2019-07-16 12:40:00"><n>Puppy Dog Pals</n><t>D</t>    <k>Bob is disappointed his archaeologist sister Bonnie won't make her annual visit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 12:40:00" d="2019-07-16 13:00:00"><n>Puppy Dog Pals</n><t>D</t>    <k>When a noisy squirrel in the attic is keeping Bob from getting any work done, the Pugs make it their mission to get the squirrel out of the attic and back to its family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 13:00:00" d="2019-07-16 13:20:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Courtesy of Romeo's Invisibility Ray, Owlette becomes invisible. Gekko and Catboy try to reverse the process but forget to include Owlette in their plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 13:20:00" d="2019-07-16 13:40:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>The P J Masks are happy to share Mystery Mountain, but the Wolfy kids want it for themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 13:40:00" d="2019-07-16 14:00:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Moon Crystal has been stolen from the PJM and though PJ Robot tries to warn them Romeo did this, the PJM are convinced Luna Girl is the culprit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 14:00:00" d="2019-07-16 14:20:00"><n>Vampirina</n><t>D</t>    <k>Oxana is thrilled to have the bed and breakfast open, but when it gets double booked with humans and vampires things get a little complicated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 14:20:00" d="2019-07-16 14:40:00"><n>Vampirina</n><t>D</t>    <k>Vee invites friends Poopy and Bridget for a sleepover, then realise it's a full moon. What's more pet Wolfie has escaped</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 14:40:00" d="2019-07-16 15:00:00"><n>Vampirina</n><t>D</t>    <k>Vee's nervous when she's due to have her school photo taken and flips, becoming a bat. She learns that's why vampires usually have their portraits painted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 15:00:00" d="2019-07-16 15:30:00"><n>Sofia the First</n><t>D</t>    <k>Sofia visits her secret library, and learns the tale of the Noble Knight seeking the Ice Fire Shield</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 15:30:00" d="2019-07-16 16:00:00"><n>Sofia the First</n><t>D</t>    <k>Sofia visits the kingdom of Wei Ling to attend the Festival of Kites, where her friend Jun has the honour of launching the first kite. But Jun is ill - can Sofia help?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 16:00:00" d="2019-07-16 16:30:00"><n>The Lion Guard</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Lion Guard must work together to chase away a baboon comedy troupe that has been distracting the other animals with their antics and stealing their food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 16:30:00" d="2019-07-16 17:00:00"><n>101 Dalmatian Street</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dylan and Dolly clash over their differing puppy-sitting styles. Now he's royal, Dylan expects the pups to wait on him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 17:00:00" d="2019-07-16 17:25:00"><n>Gigantosaurus</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tiny performs a triceratops rite of passage. Rocky sets out to prove that he's the ultimate tough guy, like Giganto, but discovers that everyone needs help sometimes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 17:25:00" d="2019-07-16 17:30:00"><n>PJ Masks Shorts</n><t>D</t>    <k>Catboy and Night Ninja embark on a competition to ascertain who's the Master of the Mountain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 17:30:00" d="2019-07-16 18:00:00"><n>Mickey &amp; the Roadster Racers</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. On Halloween, Mickey meets the legendary Haunted Hot Rod. Then, three real ghosts sabotage Pete's Haunted House party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 18:00:00" d="2019-07-16 18:30:00"><n>Fancy Nancy Clancy</n><t>D</t>    <k>After the family goldfish dies, Nancy must confront her feelings of loss. When Nancy spies on her parents, she thinks she hears them plotting to give away the family dog!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 18:30:00" d="2019-07-16 19:00:00"><n>Vampirina</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cartoon adventure about a vampire girl whose family run a guest house for ghouls and goblins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 19:00:00" d="2019-07-16 19:30:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. Romeo creates a space laser to carve his face into the moon. Then, Romeo plans to use a device to make everyone so clumsy that they cannot stop him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 19:30:00" d="2019-07-16 20:00:00"><n>Puppy Dog Pals</n><t>D</t>    <k>The pups return Chloe's lost toy to her at Space Camp. Bob throws a ball too hard. The pugs follow clues to find it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 20:00:00" d="2019-07-16 20:25:00"><n>The Lion Guard</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 20:25:00" d="2019-07-16 20:30:00"><n>PJ Masks Shorts</n><t>D</t>    <k>Catboy and Night Ninja embark on a competition to ascertain who's the Master of the Mountain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 20:30:00" d="2019-07-16 20:55:00"><n>Sofia the First</n><t>D</t>    <k>Zandar wrongly accuses Kazeem of making mischief. He protests his innocence but Zandar won't believe him. There's monkey business afoot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 20:55:00" d="2019-07-16 21:25:00"><n>Sofia the First</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tizzy's misfired spell causes Sofia to endlessly repeat the events of her disaster-filled birthday until she can learn what it means to have a truly happy birthday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 21:25:00" d="2019-07-16 21:30:00"><n>Elena of Avalor</n><t>D</t>    <k>Carla, in disguise, infiltrates the castle and tries to steal Elena's mother's tiara</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 21:30:00" d="2019-07-16 22:00:00"><n>Elena of Avalor</n><t>D</t>    <k>When a moth fairy tries to bring the gift of eternal darkness to Avalor during a solar eclipse, Elena must learn how to control the magic in her royal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 22:00:00" d="2019-07-16 22:30:00"><n>Fancy Nancy Clancy</n><t>D</t>    <k>After the family goldfish dies, Nancy must confront her feelings of loss. When Nancy spies on her parents, she thinks she hears them plotting to give away the family dog!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 22:30:00" d="2019-07-16 23:00:00"><n>Vampirina</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cartoon adventure about a vampire girl whose family run a guest house for ghouls and goblins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 23:00:00" d="2019-07-16 23:30:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. Romeo creates a space laser to carve his face into the moon. Then, Romeo plans to use a device to make everyone so clumsy that they cannot stop him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 23:30:00" d="2019-07-17 00:00:00"><n>Puppy Dog Pals</n><t>D</t>    <k>The pups return Chloe's lost toy to her at Space Camp. Bob throws a ball too hard. The pugs follow clues to find it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-17 00:00:00" d="2019-07-17 00:25:00"><n>The Lion Guard</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-17 00:25:00" d="2019-07-17 00:30:00"><n>Disney Junior Music Nursery Rhymes</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-17 00:30:00" d="2019-07-17 01:00:00"><n>Trulli Tales</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cloudy with a Chance of Onions/Stella's Ribbons Zip wants to play a game of Trulliball over again because he lost the last one. Stella wants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-17 01:00:00" d="2019-07-17 01:25:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. Romeo discovers PJ Masks' HQ's secret rocket ship ability. Then, Catboy learns appearances don't matter so long as the day is saved</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-17 01:25:00" d="2019-07-17 01:50:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Wolfies run amok. Gekko doubts if he can be good. The Wolfies get into the HQ and transform it into their den!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-17 01:50:00" d="2019-07-17 02:00:00"><n>The Hive</n><t>D</t>    <k>When Pappa tries to get fit, he discovers that doing a good deed can be just as good as a strict exercise programme</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-17 02:00:00" d="2019-07-17 02:15:00"><n>Zou</n><t>D</t>    <k>Zou must bake a cake for the sale so he can go on a school trip. Mum is away, and Grandpa and Dad end up making pancakes. Happily, Mum gets back in time to help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-17 02:15:00" d="2019-07-17 02:30:00"><n>Zou</n><t>D</t>    <k>Elzee and Zou's big race is placed on hold when Dad injures his foot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-17 02:30:00" d="2019-07-17 02:55:00"><n>Henry Hugglemonster</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. Henry is thrilled when Gertie turns up, but she's come for a piano lesson with Momma, so he tries to sabotage it. Then, Henry learns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-17 02:55:00" d="2019-07-17 03:20:00"><n>Henry Hugglemonster</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. Henry searches Roarsville for Beckett when he runs off to play with Meg's monsterpet Shakey. Then, Henry tries to teach his friends Gertie and Denzel to fly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-17 03:20:00" d="2019-07-17 03:30:00"><n>The Hive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Princess Beetrice comes up with a plan to show Buzzbee and friends that she's more than just royalty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-17 03:30:00" d="2019-07-17 03:40:00"><n>The Hive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buzzbee gets the wrong idea when he overhears a conversation and thinks that Miss Ladybird is leaving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-17 03:40:00" d="2019-07-17 03:55:00"><n>Zou</n><t>D</t>    <k>The young zebra finds his grandfather's old walkie-talkie while clearing out the garage, and tries to find someone to test it with</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-17 03:55:00" d="2019-07-17 04:10:00"><n>Zou</n><t>D</t>    <k>Zak's cuddly toy is missing and Zou helps him find it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-17 04:10:00" d="2019-07-17 04:25:00"><n>Zou</n><t>D</t>    <k>Zinnia does not like heights, so Zou helps her to overcome her fear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-17 04:25:00" d="2019-07-17 04:35:00"><n>The Hive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mr Millipede calls Buzzbee a Superfixer, which makes Buzzbee determined to fix everything - until he runs into trouble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-17 04:35:00" d="2019-07-17 04:45:00"><n>The Hive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buzzbee and his classmates are in for a surprise when Miss Ladybird goes away for the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-17 04:45:00" d="2019-07-17 07:45:00"><n>Henry Hugglemonster</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. Henry searches Roarsville for Beckett when he runs off to play with Meg's monsterpet Shakey. Then, Henry tries to teach his friends Gertie and Denzel to fly</k>  </p>
</a>
