<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="67" t="2019-08-15 22:35:51"><p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 05:10:00" d="2019-08-21 05:35:00"><n>Henry Hugglemonster</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. Cobby's model spaceship flies away and Henry rescues it. Then, Henry loses his voice while practising for the loudest roar contest, but still</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 05:35:00" d="2019-08-21 05:45:00"><n>The Hive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buzzbee and Jasper are on their way to the playground when they pop into Anthill Stores to run an errand for Mamma Bee. Then they are asked to look after the shop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 05:45:00" d="2019-08-21 06:00:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Gekko is not taking care of his things</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 06:00:00" d="2019-08-21 06:15:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>There is a chance that Night Ninja could ruin the school concert, but Catboy does not seem too upset at the prospect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 06:15:00" d="2019-08-21 06:30:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Romeo creates a space laser to carve his face into the moon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 06:30:00" d="2019-08-21 06:55:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. Romeo uses his newest device to make the PJ Masks and their HQ float away. Then, Romeo steals the PJ Masks' super vehicles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 06:55:00" d="2019-08-21 07:00:00"><n>Minnie's Bow-Toons</n><t>D</t>    <k>A Pizza Parlour mix-up sends Minnie and Daisy to Luigi's Pizzeria, to make pizzas for the hungry crowd. Minnie and Daisy make some funny looking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 07:00:00" d="2019-08-21 07:30:00"><n>Mickey Mouse Clubhouse</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mickey loses his lucky coin, which has fallen to the bottom of the lake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 07:30:00" d="2019-08-21 08:00:00"><n>Mickey &amp; the Roadster Racers</n><t>D</t>    <k>High-speed fun with Mickey Mouse and his pals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 08:00:00" d="2019-08-21 08:30:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Night Ninja made Armadylan believe the P J Masks stole all the new Flossy Flash comics in order to distract their attention from him stealing the city's food supplies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 08:30:00" d="2019-08-21 09:00:00"><n>Vampirina</n><t>D</t>    <k>Edna enters a gardening contest but her plants are spooky. At a museum the kids meet an old family friend - a mummy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 09:00:00" d="2019-08-21 09:30:00"><n>Vampirina</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cartoon adventure about a vampire girl whose family run a guest house for ghouls and goblins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 09:30:00" d="2019-08-21 10:00:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. Catboy has to get Amaya's and Greg's stolen superhero pyjamas back from Romeo. Then, Owlette's prized Giving Owl statue is stolen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 10:00:00" d="2019-08-21 10:20:00"><n>Fancy Nancy Clancy</n><t>D</t>    <k>Nancy wants to win a Valentine's Day poetry contest but gets a terrible case of writer's block. (S1 Ep15a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 10:20:00" d="2019-08-21 10:40:00"><n>Fancy Nancy Clancy</n><t>D</t>    <k>When Nancy's Valentine's Day card to Bree is accidentally delivered to Grace, Grace believes she and Nancy are now best friends!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 10:40:00" d="2019-08-21 11:00:00"><n>Muppet Babies</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cartoon chaos with the junior Muppets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 11:00:00" d="2019-08-21 11:55:00"><n>Sofia the First</n><t>D</t>    <k>Amber steals Sofia's magic amulet, only to end up summoning an evil princess who wants to destroy the kingdom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 11:55:00" d="2019-08-21 12:00:00"><n>Marvel Super Hero Adventures</n><t>D</t>    <k>After a battle with Doc Ock, Spidey and Miles Morales scare a cat named Mittens, sending her scampering into the city. Our heroes try to catch the runaway feline</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 12:00:00" d="2019-08-21 12:20:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>When Romeo's new robot, Robette, gets a screw loose she decides to take over the world by herself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 12:20:00" d="2019-08-21 12:40:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Owlette finds a bird in HQ and decides that she'll be the perfect pet owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 12:40:00" d="2019-08-21 13:00:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Night Ninja creates a fortress of his own to take down the PJ Masks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 13:00:00" d="2019-08-21 13:30:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. Romeo's remote controls the PJ Masks. Then, Night Ninja breaks Owlette's statue, who gets revenge by destroying Night Ninja's masterpiece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 13:30:00" d="2019-08-21 13:50:00"><n>Vampirina</n><t>D</t>    <k>Family Heritage Day is coming up at school and Vee is excited to make a family tree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 13:50:00" d="2019-08-21 14:10:00"><n>Vampirina</n><t>D</t>    <k>Vee and her family paint spooky-themed eggs for Vee's first Easter egg hunt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 14:10:00" d="2019-08-21 14:30:00"><n>Vampirina</n><t>D</t>    <k>Vampirina, Poppy, and Edgar get new neighbours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 14:30:00" d="2019-08-21 15:00:00"><n>Vampirina</n><t>D</t>    <k>It's Vee's first birthday in Pennsylvania, and she is gifted a Hover Haunt Spook-Thousand broom. Vee volunteers to sub-in on Poppy's basketball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 15:00:00" d="2019-08-21 15:20:00"><n>Puppy Dog Pals</n><t>D</t>    <k>Bingo and Rolly travel to France to get Bob some French toast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 15:20:00" d="2019-08-21 15:40:00"><n>Puppy Dog Pals</n><t>D</t>    <k>The pugs chase Bob's prized baseball across the city</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 15:40:00" d="2019-08-21 16:00:00"><n>Puppy Dog Pals</n><t>D</t>    <k>Bongo and Rolly travel to Egypt to find the Great Pyramids. The pugs try to deliver a Mother's Day card for Bob</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 16:00:00" d="2019-08-21 16:30:00"><n>The Lion Guard</n><t>D</t>    <k>Ono grudgingly hatches and fosters a cuckoo egg left in his nest, then joins forces with the cuckoo mom when the baby is captured by vultures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 16:30:00" d="2019-08-21 17:00:00"><n>Elena of Avalor</n><t>D</t>    <k>Isabel tries to prove she can babysit three baby jaquins by herself, but when the babies get loose it's a mad dash to find them before their parents get back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 17:00:00" d="2019-08-21 17:15:00"><n>Gigantosaurus</n><t>D</t>    <k>Rocky decides not to practise for a talent show, but his partner in the show is Giganto</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 17:15:00" d="2019-08-21 17:28:00"><n>Gigantosaurus</n><t>D</t>    <k>Bill is tired of being a little brachiosaurus, so he looks for the secret to growing big</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 17:28:00" d="2019-08-21 17:30:00"><n>Disney Junior Music Nursery Rhymes</n><t>D</t>    <k>While digging holes in search of a bone Bingo buried, Bingo and Rolly discover a lot of buried treasures along the way!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 17:30:00" d="2019-08-21 18:00:00"><n>Mickey &amp; the Roadster Racers</n><t>D</t>    <k>Daisy and Minnie help Daisy's cousin photo a rare bird. Team Mickey competes in a game of Roadster Soccer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 18:00:00" d="2019-08-21 18:30:00"><n>Fancy Nancy Clancy</n><t>D</t>    <k>Nancy tries to prevent her old toy from being sold at the family yard sale without revealing that she still loves it. When Nancy produces Lionel's first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 18:30:00" d="2019-08-21 19:00:00"><n>Vampirina</n><t>D</t>    <k>Boris wants to sell some antiques. Gregoria gets mixed up with them. Edna is a dog show judge. Vee and Poppy decide to enter Wolfie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 19:00:00" d="2019-08-21 19:30:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>The PJ Masks face the newest villains in town: the Wolfies. Gekko's knowledge of dinosaurs helps the team get back prehistoric bones from the Wolfy Kids</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 19:30:00" d="2019-08-21 20:00:00"><n>Puppy Dog Pals</n><t>D</t>    <k>Snow monkeys help the pups to save Bob's ski trip. A.R.F. gets a robo-cold before an important demonstration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 20:00:00" d="2019-08-21 20:28:00"><n>The Lion Guard</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Guard must help two zany gorilla princes return to their home in the snowy Rwenzori Mountains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 20:28:00" d="2019-08-21 20:30:00"><n>Disney Junior Music Nursery Rhymes</n><t>D</t>    <k>While digging holes in search of a bone Bingo buried, Bingo and Rolly discover a lot of buried treasures along the way!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 20:30:00" d="2019-08-21 20:55:00"><n>Sofia the First</n><t>D</t>    <k>After spending time learning to be royal, Sofia's ready to discover some of Enchancia's secrets as she releases a genie, finds a secret library and learns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 20:55:00" d="2019-08-21 21:25:00"><n>Sofia the First</n><t>D</t>    <k>After spending time learning to be royal, Sofia is ready to discover some of Enchancia's secrets as she releases a genie, finds a secret library and learns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 21:25:00" d="2019-08-21 21:30:00"><n>Elena of Avalor</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 21:30:00" d="2019-08-21 22:00:00"><n>Elena of Avalor</n><t>D</t>    <k>Isabel tries to prove she can babysit three baby jaquins by herself, but when the babies get loose it's a mad dash to find them before their parents get back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 22:00:00" d="2019-08-21 22:30:00"><n>Fancy Nancy Clancy</n><t>D</t>    <k>Nancy tries to prevent her old toy from being sold at the family yard sale without revealing that she still loves it. When Nancy produces Lionel's first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 22:30:00" d="2019-08-21 23:00:00"><n>Vampirina</n><t>D</t>    <k>Boris wants to sell some antiques. Gregoria gets mixed up with them. Edna is a dog show judge. Vee and Poppy decide to enter Wolfie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 23:00:00" d="2019-08-21 23:30:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>The PJ Masks face the newest villains in town: the Wolfies. Gekko's knowledge of dinosaurs helps the team get back prehistoric bones from the Wolfy Kids</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-21 23:30:00" d="2019-08-22 00:00:00"><n>Puppy Dog Pals</n><t>D</t>    <k>Snow monkeys help the pups to save Bob's ski trip. A.R.F. gets a robo-cold before an important demonstration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-22 00:00:00" d="2019-08-22 00:25:00"><n>The Lion Guard</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Guard must help two zany gorilla princes return to their home in the snowy Rwenzori Mountains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-22 00:25:00" d="2019-08-22 00:30:00"><n>Disney Junior Music Nursery Rhymes</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Muppet Babies learn their ABCs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-22 00:30:00" d="2019-08-22 01:00:00"><n>Trulli Tales</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-22 01:00:00" d="2019-08-22 01:25:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. Luna blames her moths for defeats and steals butterflies to replace them. Then, Luna Girl and Owlette compete to win the biggest, best toy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-22 01:25:00" d="2019-08-22 01:50:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cartoon adventures with Connor, Amaya and Greg, who by day are ordinary schoolkids, but by night are pyjama-wearing superheroes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-22 01:50:00" d="2019-08-22 02:00:00"><n>The Hive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mr Grasshopper helps Mamma Bee get back into shape and Mamma Bee learns to make healthier snacks after she eats too many cakes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-22 02:00:00" d="2019-08-22 02:15:00"><n>Zou</n><t>D</t>    <k>The zebra has a school project to do and borrows his father's camera to finish it. However, he misplaces the equipment and has to look for it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-22 02:15:00" d="2019-08-22 02:30:00"><n>Zou</n><t>D</t>    <k>Grandpa's vegetable patch has a visitor and Zou has to help him find a new home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-22 02:30:00" d="2019-08-22 02:55:00"><n>Henry Hugglemonster</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. Mama is to be Roarsville's official music maker so everyone must help at home. Then, Henry thinks Denzel is moving away, so plans a party for his best friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-22 02:55:00" d="2019-08-22 03:20:00"><n>Henry Hugglemonster</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. Unforeseen events threaten to make Henry late for his first day at Monsterschool. Then, Summer delivers singing Summergrams around Roarsville</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-22 03:20:00" d="2019-08-22 03:30:00"><n>The Hive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jasper is disappointed when worn-out batteries means they cannot play Buzzbee's computer game. Buzzbee suggests they play a real-life version</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-22 03:30:00" d="2019-08-22 03:40:00"><n>The Hive</n><t>D</t>    <k>When Buzzbee's record attempt takes a dramatic turn for the worse, he learns that winning isn't everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-22 03:40:00" d="2019-08-22 03:55:00"><n>Zou</n><t>D</t>    <k>When Uncle Zavier's car breaks, Zou is inspired to become a garage mechanic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-22 03:55:00" d="2019-08-22 04:10:00"><n>Zou</n><t>D</t>    <k>An army of ants causes problems for Zou when he tries to make the insects into pets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-22 04:10:00" d="2019-08-22 04:25:00"><n>Zou</n><t>D</t>    <k>Grandpa, Zou and Zak have to accept a big delivery in Uncle Zavier and Aunt Zelda's shop today</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-22 04:25:00" d="2019-08-22 04:35:00"><n>The Hive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Debee gets a brand new scooter, but Buzzbee finds it difficult to ride</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-22 04:35:00" d="2019-08-22 04:45:00"><n>The Hive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Pre-school series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-08-22 04:45:00" d="2019-08-22 07:45:00"><n>Henry Hugglemonster</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. Unforeseen events threaten to make Henry late for his first day at Monsterschool. Then, Summer delivers singing Summergrams around Roarsville</k>  </p>
</a>
