<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="67" t="2019-07-11 00:20:29"><p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 05:10:00" d="2019-07-15 05:35:00"><n>Henry Hugglemonster</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. Henry organises a spectacular finale for Summer's show, to make up for letting her down. Then, Cobby invents The Hugglebike to get the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 05:35:00" d="2019-07-15 05:45:00"><n>The Hive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Rubee and Debee decide they want to be grown up, just like Bobee, and find out how to make Debee's birthday party properly grown up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 05:45:00" d="2019-07-15 06:00:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Catboy falls prey to a Romeo remote, which rewinds all action, making the night last forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 06:00:00" d="2019-07-15 06:15:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cartoon adventures with Connor, Amaya and Greg, who by day are ordinary schoolkids, but by night are pyjama-wearing superheroes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 06:15:00" d="2019-07-15 06:30:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cartoon adventures with Connor, Amaya and Greg, who by day are ordinary schoolkids, but by night are pyjama-wearing superheroes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 06:30:00" d="2019-07-15 06:55:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Romeo turns people into babies. Gekko babysits his mates. Owlette must get back Luna Girl's board and magnet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 06:55:00" d="2019-07-15 07:00:00"><n>Minnie's Bow-Toons</n><t>D</t>    <k>Fun for children</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 07:00:00" d="2019-07-15 07:15:00"><n>Muppet Babies</n><t>D</t>    <k>Kermit becomes a Pirate Captain and leads his friends on a high-speed treasure hunt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 07:15:00" d="2019-07-15 07:30:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Catboy was turned into a cat by Romeo and Owlette and Gekko must deal with Catboy's feline behavior as well as stopping Romeo transform everyone into pets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 07:30:00" d="2019-07-15 08:00:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. Romeo's remote controls the PJ Masks. Then, Night Ninja breaks Owlette's statue, who gets revenge by destroying Night Ninja's masterpiece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 08:00:00" d="2019-07-15 08:30:00"><n>Vampirina</n><t>D</t>    <k>Vee invites friends Poopy and Vee for a sleepover, then realises it's a full moon. Vee becomes a bat while having her photo taken</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 08:30:00" d="2019-07-15 09:00:00"><n>Fancy Nancy Clancy</n><t>D</t>    <k>A neighbourhood climbing tree is declared off-limits, Nancy and friends protest. Nancy dreams of becoming a synchronized swimmer, but is afraid of water</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 09:00:00" d="2019-07-15 09:30:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Night Ninja made Armadylan believe the P J Masks stole all the new Flossy Flash comics in order to distract their attention from him stealing the city's food supplies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 09:30:00" d="2019-07-15 10:00:00"><n>Vampirina</n><t>D</t>    <k>Vee helps Bridget practise reading a poem for Poetry Day, but chaos ensues and they realise the book she was using contains spells, not poems!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 10:00:00" d="2019-07-15 10:30:00"><n>Sofia the First</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Princess Adventure Club sets out on an adventure to recover the Lost Pyramid of Kaldoun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 10:30:00" d="2019-07-15 11:00:00"><n>Sofia the First</n><t>D</t>    <k>When Sofia, Amber and James are left in charge of the castle for the day, they attempt to make peace between the River Elves and the Tree Elves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 11:00:00" d="2019-07-15 11:20:00"><n>Fancy Nancy Clancy</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 11:20:00" d="2019-07-15 11:40:00"><n>Fancy Nancy Clancy</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 11:40:00" d="2019-07-15 12:00:00"><n>Fancy Nancy Clancy</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 12:00:00" d="2019-07-15 12:20:00"><n>Puppy Dog Pals</n><t>D</t>    <k>Bob can't finish his jigsaw puzzle without the leopard picture that was on the torn box, so the Pugs go round the world in search of a leopard Bob can use as a reference</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 12:20:00" d="2019-07-15 12:40:00"><n>Puppy Dog Pals</n><t>D</t>    <k>Bob takes the pups and Hissy to an outdoor, pet-friendly symphony concert, but when they cause chaos they have to set things right so Bob can enjoy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 12:40:00" d="2019-07-15 13:00:00"><n>Puppy Dog Pals</n><t>D</t>    <k>Ol' Snapper . While on a fishing trip, Bob loses his favourite fishing pole and thinks his trip is ruined. To get it back, Bingo and Rolly must confront Ol</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 13:00:00" d="2019-07-15 13:20:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cartoon adventures with Connor, Amaya and Greg, who by day are ordinary schoolkids, but by night are pyjama-wearing superheroes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 13:20:00" d="2019-07-15 13:40:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cartoon adventures with Connor, Amaya and Greg, who by day are ordinary schoolkids, but by night are pyjama-wearing superheroes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 13:40:00" d="2019-07-15 14:00:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cartoon adventures with Connor, Amaya and Greg, who by day are ordinary schoolkids, but by night are pyjama-wearing superheroes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 14:00:00" d="2019-07-15 14:20:00"><n>Vampirina</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cartoon adventure about a vampire girl whose family run a guest house for ghouls and goblins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 14:20:00" d="2019-07-15 14:40:00"><n>Vampirina</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cartoon adventure about a vampire girl whose family run a guest house for ghouls and goblins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 14:40:00" d="2019-07-15 15:00:00"><n>Vampirina</n><t>D</t>    <k>When young female vampire Vee is stressed she gets the battys, and involuntarily flips from girl to vampire and back. This scares a new friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 15:00:00" d="2019-07-15 15:30:00"><n>Sofia the First</n><t>D</t>    <k>Amber and Sofia learn an important lesson about not spying on others after a magic telescope deceives them into thinking that their mother is in danger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 15:30:00" d="2019-07-15 16:00:00"><n>Sofia the First</n><t>D</t>    <k>Sofia's amulet summons her to help another princess, Princess Charlotte of Isleworth, who has been cursed by an enchantress and turned into a beast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 16:00:00" d="2019-07-15 16:30:00"><n>The Lion Guard</n><t>D</t>    <k>Ono grudgingly hatches and fosters a cuckoo egg left in his nest, then joins forces with the cuckoo mom when the baby is captured by vultures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 16:30:00" d="2019-07-15 17:00:00"><n>101 Dalmatian Street</n><t>D</t>    <k>There's a crime in the park and the evidence points to 101 Dalmatian Street, so Dylan turns detective. (S1 Ep8a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 17:00:00" d="2019-07-15 17:25:00"><n>Gigantosaurus</n><t>D</t>    <k>Timid Bill and brave Rocky end up stranded on an island, however Rocky suddenly becomes the scared one! Trey warns the little dinos about a cave monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 17:25:00" d="2019-07-15 17:30:00"><n>PJ Masks Shorts</n><t>D</t>    <k>Owlette uses her skills with her Owl Glider to turn Romeo's trap against his own lab</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 17:30:00" d="2019-07-15 18:00:00"><n>Mickey &amp; the Roadster Racers</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. Cuckoo Loca enters The Impossible Race. Then, the Happy Helpers help out on a cruise by organising a dance contest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 18:00:00" d="2019-07-15 18:30:00"><n>Fancy Nancy Clancy</n><t>D</t>    <k>A neighbourhood climbing tree is declared off-limits, Nancy and friends protest. Nancy dreams of becoming a synchronized swimmer, but is afraid of water</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 18:30:00" d="2019-07-15 19:00:00"><n>Vampirina</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cartoon adventure about a vampire girl whose family run a guest house for ghouls and goblins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 19:00:00" d="2019-07-15 19:30:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. Something is fishy when Catboy gets a gift of a scooter from an unknown aunt. Then, Gekko's got the sneezes and his friends want him to rest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 19:30:00" d="2019-07-15 20:00:00"><n>Puppy Dog Pals</n><t>D</t>    <k>Bingo and Rolly go on a mission to Hawaii in search of sand. Bob introduces the pups to A.R.F., a robotic dog programmed to clean up their mess</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 20:00:00" d="2019-07-15 20:25:00"><n>The Lion Guard</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 20:25:00" d="2019-07-15 20:30:00"><n>PJ Masks Shorts</n><t>D</t>    <k>Owlette uses her skills with her Owl Glider to turn Romeo's trap against his own lab</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 20:30:00" d="2019-07-15 20:55:00"><n>Sofia the First</n><t>D</t>    <k>The secret library sends Sofia on a mission to help the dragons of the Blazing Palisades defend their home against invading sea serpents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 20:55:00" d="2019-07-15 21:25:00"><n>Sofia the First</n><t>D</t>    <k>Sofia helps Clover plant a garden, but he has a hard time sharing with his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 21:25:00" d="2019-07-15 21:30:00"><n>Elena of Avalor</n><t>D</t>    <k>Isabel tries to prove she can babysit three baby jaquins by herself, but when the babies get loose it's a mad dash to find them before their parents get back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 21:30:00" d="2019-07-15 22:00:00"><n>Elena of Avalor</n><t>D</t>    <k>Elena discovers she has the ability to see ghosts and helps the spirit of a kind, elderly woman to mend the rift between her grandchildren and save the family restaurant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 22:00:00" d="2019-07-15 22:30:00"><n>Fancy Nancy Clancy</n><t>D</t>    <k>A neighbourhood climbing tree is declared off-limits, Nancy and friends protest. Nancy dreams of becoming a synchronized swimmer, but is afraid of water</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 22:30:00" d="2019-07-15 23:00:00"><n>Vampirina</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cartoon adventure about a vampire girl whose family run a guest house for ghouls and goblins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 23:00:00" d="2019-07-15 23:30:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. Something is fishy when Catboy gets a gift of a scooter from an unknown aunt. Then, Gekko's got the sneezes and his friends want him to rest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-15 23:30:00" d="2019-07-16 00:00:00"><n>Puppy Dog Pals</n><t>D</t>    <k>Bingo and Rolly go on a mission to Hawaii in search of sand. Bob introduces the pups to A.R.F., a robotic dog programmed to clean up their mess</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 00:00:00" d="2019-07-16 00:25:00"><n>The Lion Guard</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 00:25:00" d="2019-07-16 00:30:00"><n>Disney Junior Music Nursery Rhymes</n><t>D</t>    <k>Classic nursery rhymes re-imagined in a fun and playful way with the help of wildly popular Disney Junior characters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 00:30:00" d="2019-07-16 01:00:00"><n>Trulli Tales</n><t>D</t>    <k>Stella lets Zip take the blame when she breaks something. The kids reluctantly team up with Oscar for an assignment but his great sense of smell proves an asset</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 01:00:00" d="2019-07-16 01:25:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Double bill. The school instruments go missing. Then, Catboy and Gekko dream up an exciting new superhero move, but Owlette can't get it right</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 01:25:00" d="2019-07-16 01:50:00"><n>PJ Masks</n><t>D</t>    <k>Gekko's powers are increased by Power Pondweeds. Owlette breaks the ltelescope and tries to blame Luna Girl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 01:50:00" d="2019-07-16 02:00:00"><n>The Hive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Lord Bartlebee learns how to have fun with a little help from some of the younger residents of the Hive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 02:00:00" d="2019-07-16 02:15:00"><n>Zou</n><t>D</t>    <k>Zou runs out of paint and can't finish painting the garage. He meets two artist friends of Elzee's mum and ends up with a great picture to decorate the blank space</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 02:15:00" d="2019-07-16 02:30:00"><n>Zou</n><t>D</t>    <k>The little zebra and his friends go on a trip, but no one wants to visit the same place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 02:30:00" d="2019-07-16 02:55:00"><n>Henry Hugglemonster</n><t>D</t>    <k>Fun for children</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 02:55:00" d="2019-07-16 03:20:00"><n>Henry Hugglemonster</n><t>D</t>    <k>Henry chases Daddo's birthday cake that's caught on a balloon. Henry must save the monsterpets when they are swept into an airship on a windy day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 03:20:00" d="2019-07-16 03:30:00"><n>The Hive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Pappa Bee's reluctance to wear his new glasses causes problems until Buzzbee and Barnabee step in to help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 03:30:00" d="2019-07-16 03:40:00"><n>The Hive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buzzbee is inspired to make a window box when he sees the one that Rubee has grown. Katypillar gives him some seeds to plant but Buzzbee learns he must be patient</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 03:40:00" d="2019-07-16 03:55:00"><n>Zou</n><t>D</t>    <k>The zebra, Elzee and Grandpa make a huge dinosaur in the back garden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 03:55:00" d="2019-07-16 04:10:00"><n>Zou</n><t>D</t>    <k>Zou must make a big effort today to keep his visitor happy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 04:10:00" d="2019-07-16 04:25:00"><n>Zou</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dad, Zou and Zak try to share the gym with Zena, Elzee and Zinnia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 04:25:00" d="2019-07-16 04:35:00"><n>The Hive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buzzbee wants a little brother instead of a big bossy sister</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 04:35:00" d="2019-07-16 04:45:00"><n>The Hive</n><t>D</t>    <k>When Teddy Bee goes missing, it quickly becomes clear that there's been a bit of a mix-up at the school fair</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1104" o="2019-07-16 04:45:00" d="2019-07-16 05:10:00"><n>Henry Hugglemonster</n><t>D</t>    <k>Henry chases Daddo's birthday cake that's caught on a balloon. Henry must save the monsterpets when they are swept into an airship on a windy day</k>  </p>
</a>
