<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2021-07-09 07:10:30"><p id_tv="1106" o="2021-07-15 05:00:00" d="2021-07-15 09:00:00"><n>Lion Kingdom</n><t>D</t>    <k>A male lion resumes his former role as leader, while a younger animal is evicted from the pride and faces an uncertain future</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2021-07-15 09:00:00" d="2021-07-15 10:00:00"><n>Animals Gone Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>The documentary highlights astonishing animal antics, including the greatest escape acts, most unpredictable tricks and strangest natural instincts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2021-07-15 10:00:00" d="2021-07-15 11:00:00"><n>United Vets of America</n><t>D</t>    <k>Vets at zoos and clinics treat all kinds of felines, from everyday house cats to like tigers, leopards, lions and lynx</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2021-07-15 11:00:00" d="2021-07-15 12:00:00"><n>United Vets of America</n><t>D</t>    <k>Stories of vets taking care of orphaned wild animals, from bear cubs and baby deer, to a manatee that has been rescued, rehabilitated, and released into the wild</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2021-07-15 12:00:00" d="2021-07-15 13:00:00"><n>United Vets of America</n><t>D</t>    <k>Springtime brings a baby boom for vets at clinics and zoos across the US. In Alaska, it's all hands on deck when an injured baby fox is rushed into Dr Oakley's clinic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2021-07-15 13:00:00" d="2021-07-15 14:00:00"><n>Bizarre Animal Friends</n><t>D</t>    <k>Documentary exploring unusual friendships between humans and animals, including a deer that befriended two people and a cat, and a boy who bonded with a Cape buffalo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2021-07-15 14:00:00" d="2021-07-15 15:00:00"><n>Snakes in the City Compilations</n><t>D</t>    <k>Part two of a two-part special. More highlights from the series, including deadly black mambas in wardrobes and spitting cobras in factories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2021-07-15 15:00:00" d="2021-07-15 16:00:00"><n>Savage Kingdom</n><t>D</t>    <k>85% A lioness must choose between her pride's safety and her own freedom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2021-07-15 16:00:00" d="2021-07-15 17:00:00"><n>Savage Kingdom</n><t>D</t>    <k>85% The forest residents turn on orphaned leopard Motsidi. Meanwhile, the hyenas cause havoc, exploiting African wild dog Mogolo's weakening state</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2021-07-15 17:00:00" d="2021-07-15 18:00:00"><n>Savage Kingdom</n><t>D</t>    <k>85% Lioness Tsebe holds the Northern Brothers at bay until they prove worthy to father her new dynasty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2021-07-15 18:00:00" d="2021-07-15 19:00:00"><n>Bizarre Animal Friends</n><t>D</t>    <k>The programme exploring unlikely animal pairings returns, beginning with a two-legged Chihuahua that has befriended a silkie chicken, a mountaineer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2021-07-15 19:00:00" d="2021-07-15 20:00:00"><n>Africa's Hunters</n><t>D</t>    <k>83% A female hyena whose mother was a dominant member of the pack must assert her position in the fiercely competitive group</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2021-07-15 20:00:00" d="2021-07-15 21:00:00"><n>What The Shark?</n><t>D</t>    <k>Discover a side to sharks you've never seen before and take a deep dive, from the sunny beach to the 8000-foot abyss, to see how extreme adaptation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2021-07-15 21:00:00" d="2021-07-15 22:00:00"><n>The Croc that Ate Jaws</n><t>D</t>    <k>Wildlife experts Dr Mike Heithaus and Dr James Nifong draw on evidence from around the world to judge what would happen in a crocodile fought a shark</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2021-07-15 22:00:00" d="2021-07-15 23:00:00"><n>Shark Attack Files</n><t>D</t>    <k>Shark experts set out to uncover what exactly makes the powerful bites of great whites, tigers and bulls so deadly, and whether jaw strength or sharp teeth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2021-07-15 23:00:00" d="2021-07-16 00:00:00"><n>Sharks of Pirate Island</n><t>D</t>    <k>Divers embark on a mission to free sharks and turtles from illegal fishing lines off the coast of mainland Costa Rica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2021-07-16 00:00:00" d="2021-07-16 01:00:00"><n>Shark Gangs</n><t>D</t>    <k>Documentary exploring why species of sharks that have always been solitary predators have adapted to work in packs to catch their prey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2021-07-16 01:00:00" d="2021-07-16 02:00:00"><n>When Sharks Attack</n><t>D</t>    <k>A mysterious series of shark attacks off the New Jersey shore in 1916 in which five people were attacked and all but one died</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2021-07-16 02:00:00" d="2021-07-16 03:00:00"><n>When Sharks Attack</n><t>D</t>    <k>Experts investigate a series of attacks of the shore of Cape Cod in 2017 and 2018, including the first shark fatality in Massachusetts in more than 80 years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2021-07-16 03:00:00" d="2021-07-16 04:00:00"><n>Savage Kingdom</n><t>D</t>    <k>85% A lioness must choose between her pride's safety and her own freedom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2021-07-16 04:00:00" d="2021-07-16 07:00:00"><n>Savage Kingdom</n><t>D</t>    <k>85% The forest residents turn on orphaned leopard Motsidi. Meanwhile, the hyenas cause havoc, exploiting African wild dog Mogolo's weakening state</k>  </p>
</a>
