<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2019-08-13 02:21:36"><p id_tv="1106" o="2019-08-18 05:00:00" d="2019-08-18 09:00:00"><n>Animals Gone Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>Two swimmers get a surprise from a pair of whales. Plus, a circus lion proves highly unpredictable</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2019-08-18 09:00:00" d="2019-08-18 10:00:00"><n>Animals Gone Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>Documentary uncovering examples of strange behaviour in the natural world - with this episode focusing on disorderly conduct from locations across the globe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2019-08-18 10:00:00" d="2019-08-18 11:00:00"><n>Animals Gone Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>Featuring extraordinary feats of survival in the animal kingdom, including acts of bravery, heroic escapes and near-misses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2019-08-18 11:00:00" d="2019-08-18 12:00:00"><n>Animals Gone Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>Interesting behaviour in the natural world, including escape acts, unpredictable tricks and feats of survival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2019-08-18 12:00:00" d="2019-08-18 13:00:00"><n>Animals Gone Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>How creatures, including jaguars, pythons and monkeys manage to survive against the odds. Plus, the almost human quirks they can sometimes display</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2019-08-18 13:00:00" d="2019-08-18 14:00:00"><n>Animals Gone Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>Astonishing animal behaviour, including a trespassing bear and a quick-witted sea lion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2019-08-18 14:00:00" d="2019-08-18 15:00:00"><n>Animals Gone Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>A bear chews up a woman's kayak, despite her desperate protests, and a herd of elephants back a motorcyclist into a corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2019-08-18 15:00:00" d="2019-08-18 16:00:00"><n>Animals Gone Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>Astonishing animal behaviour, including a trespassing bear and a quick-witted sea lion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2019-08-18 16:00:00" d="2019-08-18 17:00:00"><n>Animals Gone Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>Documentary uncovering examples of unpredictable behaviour in the natural world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2019-08-18 17:00:00" d="2019-08-18 18:00:00"><n>Animals Gone Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>A French bull dog makes a bold move when it goes after three bears. Plus, a kitten gets stuck in heavy traffic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2019-08-18 18:00:00" d="2019-08-18 19:00:00"><n>Animals Gone Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>A diver suffers a close call with a great white shark, and a rabbit tries to outrun an avalanche</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2019-08-18 19:00:00" d="2019-08-18 20:00:00"><n>Animals Gone Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>Documentary uncovering examples of strange behaviour in the natural world, including a photo-bombing predator and a purse-snatching monkey. Plus, a parrot throws a tantrum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2019-08-18 20:00:00" d="2019-08-18 21:00:00"><n>Animals Gone Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>Documentary uncovering examples of strange behaviour in the natural world, including a herd of buffalo racing to save a calf from a lion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2019-08-18 21:00:00" d="2019-08-18 22:00:00"><n>Save This Rhino</n><t>D</t>    <k>Part one of two. Cricketers Kevin Pietersen and Graeme Smith head to Kruger National Park as they investigate efforts to save the critically-endangered</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2019-08-18 22:00:00" d="2019-08-18 23:00:00"><n>When Sharks Attack</n><t>D</t>    <k>A mysterious series of shark attacks off the New Jersey shore in 1916 in which five people were attacked and all but one died</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2019-08-18 23:00:00" d="2019-08-19 00:00:00"><n>Operation Sharklift</n><t>D</t>    <k>In a world-first, scientists catch, crane-lift and relocate huge bull sharks from a busy harbour in New Caledonia to a pristine coral reef far from people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2019-08-19 00:00:00" d="2019-08-19 01:00:00"><n>Eyewitness Shark Attack</n><t>D</t>    <k>Scientists analyse footage of a great white attacking a researcher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2019-08-19 01:00:00" d="2019-08-19 02:00:00"><n>When Sharks Attack</n><t>D</t>    <k>A mysterious series of shark attacks off the New Jersey shore in 1916 in which five people were attacked and all but one died</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2019-08-19 02:00:00" d="2019-08-19 03:00:00"><n>When Sharks Attack</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Bahamas is home to 40 species of shark, but attacks on humans are rare. However, in 2002, a spate of incidents occurred that left 36 people maimed or killed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2019-08-19 03:00:00" d="2019-08-19 04:00:00"><n>Animals Gone Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>A bear chews up a woman's kayak, despite her desperate protests, and a herd of elephants back a motorcyclist into a corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1106" o="2019-08-19 04:00:00" d="2019-08-19 07:00:00"><n>Animals Gone Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>A French bull dog makes a bold move when it goes after three bears. Plus, a kitten gets stuck in heavy traffic</k>  </p>
</a>
