<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="11" t="2020-05-15 04:58:23"><p id_tv="1111" o="2020-05-22 06:10:00" d="2020-05-22 08:10:00" c="1"><n>Enchanted</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Fairy tale princess Amy Adams is banished to real world New York by an evil queen. Will dashing lawyer Patrick Dempsey be her knight in pinstripe armour?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-05-22 08:10:00" d="2020-05-22 09:45:00" c="1"><n>Beauty And The Beast</n><t>F</t>    <k>A beautiful woman is imprisoned in the castle of a hideous beast in this enchanting retelling of the classic French fairy tale. Oscar-winning animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-05-22 09:45:00" d="2020-05-22 11:20:00" c="1"><n>Robin Hood</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% Brilliant animated fun as outlaw fox Robin Hood plans to outwit a greedy lion king who's leaving the animals of Sherwood Forest penniless. Oscar-nominated favourite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-05-22 11:20:00" d="2020-05-22 13:10:00" c="1"><n>A Bug's Life</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% An oddball ant unwittingly employs a creepy-crawly circus troupe to help him protect his colony from grasshoppers. Pixar animation with the voice of Julia Louis-Dreyfus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-05-22 13:10:00" d="2020-05-22 15:15:00" c="1"><n u="Incredibles">Incredibles 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% When a new villain emerges and hatches a dangerous plot, everyone's favourite super-powered family must come together to save the day. Oscar-nominated Pixar sequel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-05-22 15:15:00" d="2020-05-22 17:15:00" c="1"><n>The Game Plan</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% Dwayne 'The Rock' Johnson stars as the selfish NFL superstar whose world is turned upside down when he learns he has a daughter. Family comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-05-22 17:15:00" d="2020-05-22 19:00:00" c="1"><n>Meet The Robinsons</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% An orphaned boy genius learns a priceless lesson about family when he is whisked into the future by a time-travelling teen. Thrilling animated adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-05-22 19:00:00" d="2020-05-22 19:20:00" c="1"><n>Lava</n><t>F</t>    <k>Delightful Pixar short about a lonely volcano who just wants someone to love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-05-22 19:20:00" d="2020-05-22 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Mars Needs Moms</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% When his mum is kidnapped by Martians, young Milo must travel to the Red Planet to free her. Out of this world animated adventure with Seth Green and Joan Cusack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-05-22 21:00:00" d="2020-05-22 23:00:00" c="1"><n u="Incredibles">Incredibles 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% When a new villain emerges and hatches a dangerous plot, everyone's favourite super-powered family must come together to save the day. Oscar-nominated Pixar sequel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-05-22 23:00:00" d="2020-05-23 02:00:00" c="1"><n>Beauty And The Beast</n><t>F</t>    <k>A beautiful woman is imprisoned in the castle of a hideous beast in this enchanting retelling of the classic French fairy tale. Oscar-winning animation</k>  </p>
</a>
