<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-05-28 04:41:30"><p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-04 06:55:00" d="2020-06-04 08:20:00" c="1"><n>The Lion King 2: Simba's Pride</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Trouble brews when Simba's strong-willed daughter Kiara falls in love with a young lion raised by the exiled followers of Scar. Sequel to the smash-hit animated adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-04 08:20:00" d="2020-06-04 09:50:00" c="1"><n u="George Of The Jungle">George Of The Jungle 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>33% The lord of the japes swings into action to keep his family together - but there are no vines in Vegas! More monkey business among the treetops with John Cleese</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-04 09:50:00" d="2020-06-04 11:30:00" c="1"><n>A Bug's Life</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% An oddball ant unwittingly employs a creepy-crawly circus troupe to help him protect his colony from grasshoppers. Pixar animation with the voice of Julia Louis-Dreyfus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-04 11:30:00" d="2020-06-04 13:00:00" c="1"><n>The Little Mermaid</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% A teenage mermaid, who longs to track down a human prince, makes a deal with a ruthless sea-witch to trade her tail for legs. Classic animation from Disney</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-04 13:00:00" d="2020-06-04 14:20:00" c="1"><n>The Little Mermaid II: Return To The Sea</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% When her daughter sails away from home, Ariel must regain her mermaid's tail and scour the ocean to find her. Sweet sequel to the classic Disney animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-04 14:20:00" d="2020-06-04 16:20:00" c="1"><n>The Lion King</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Donald Glover, Seth Rogen and Beyoncé voice the Oscar-nominated remake of the Disney classic about a young lion prince hoping to follow in his father's footsteps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-04 16:20:00" d="2020-06-04 18:00:00" c="1"><n>A Bug's Life</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% An oddball ant unwittingly employs a creepy-crawly circus troupe to help him protect his colony from grasshoppers. Pixar animation with the voice of Julia Louis-Dreyfus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-04 18:00:00" d="2020-06-04 20:00:00" c="1"><n>Return To Oz</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% In this follow up to The Wizard of Oz, Dorothy returns to the magical land, where she discovers it's up to her to save it from the wicked Nome King</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-04 20:00:00" d="2020-06-04 22:00:00" c="1"><n>The Lion King</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Donald Glover, Seth Rogen and Beyoncé voice the Oscar-nominated remake of the Disney classic about a young lion prince hoping to follow in his father's footsteps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-04 22:00:00" d="2020-06-05 01:00:00" c="1"><n>The Haunted Mansion</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% Eddie Murphy and his family try to escape a ghostly house in this spooky family comedy. Co-starring Terence Stamp and Jennifer Tilly</k>  </p>
</a>
