<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="14" t="2019-08-15 22:51:47"><p id_tv="1111" o="2019-08-21 05:55:00" d="2019-08-21 07:20:00" c="1"><n>DuckTales The Movie: Treasure Of..</n><t>F</t>    <k>. The Lost Lamp: After an Egyptian treasure hunt, Scrooge McDuck and his mischievous nephews find a magic lamp, unaware a sorcerer is looking to claim it. Animated caper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-08-21 07:20:00" d="2019-08-21 09:05:00" c="1"><n>Bolt</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% A deluded canine TV star is forced to discover the true meaning of courage in this dazzling Disney animation. Featuring the voices of John Travolta and Miley Cyrus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-08-21 09:05:00" d="2019-08-21 11:05:00" c="1"><n>The Princess Diaries 2: Royal Engagement</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% Princess Anne Hathaway won't inherit the crown unless she marries. But do her suitors only want the throne? Royal romcom co-starring Julie Andrews</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-08-21 11:05:00" d="2019-08-21 12:50:00" c="1"><n>Up</n><t>F</t>    <k>83% An eager boy scout joins a crotchety OAP on an eventful quest to fulfil his late wife's last wish. Magnificent Oscar-winning animation from Pixar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-08-21 12:50:00" d="2019-08-21 14:30:00" c="1"><n>Monsters, Inc.</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% Two monsters break all the rules when a kid they're supposed to scare follows them back to their own world. Brilliant Pixar animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-08-21 14:30:00" d="2019-08-21 15:50:00" c="1"><n>Sleeping Beauty</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% In this classic Disney animation, wicked fairy Maleficent places a young princess under a curse that only true love can break</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-08-21 15:50:00" d="2019-08-21 17:35:00" c="1"><n>Bolt</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% A deluded canine TV star is forced to discover the true meaning of courage in this dazzling Disney animation. Featuring the voices of John Travolta and Miley Cyrus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-08-21 17:35:00" d="2019-08-21 19:20:00" c="1"><n>Up</n><t>F</t>    <k>83% An eager boy scout joins a crotchety OAP on an eventful quest to fulfil his late wife's last wish. Magnificent Oscar-winning animation from Pixar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-08-21 19:20:00" d="2019-08-21 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Monsters, Inc.</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% Two monsters break all the rules when a kid they're supposed to scare follows them back to their own world. Brilliant Pixar animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-08-21 21:00:00" d="2019-08-21 22:50:00" c="1"><n>Christopher Robin</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Ewan McGregor stars as a downtrodden Christopher Robin reunited with a cuddly childhood friend. Live action Disney fun with Hayley Atwell and the voice of Jim Cummings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-08-21 22:50:00" d="2019-08-22 00:25:00" c="1"><n>The Hunchback Of Notre Dame</n><t>F</t>    <k>Disney favourite following the efforts of deformed bell-ringer Quasimodo as he tries to escape the clutches of an evil justice minister in order to help a friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-08-22 00:25:00" d="2019-08-22 02:05:00" c="1"><n>Homeward Bound II: Lost In San Francisco</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% Family adventure about three pets who embark on a series of hair-raising escapades in San Francisco. With the voices of Michael J Fox and Sally Field</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-08-22 02:05:00" d="2019-08-22 04:00:00" c="1"><n>Tex</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Matt Dillon stars as a teen who, along with his brother, refuses to give up after his father's abandonment and the death of his mother. Coming-of-age drama with Jim Metzler</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-08-22 04:00:00" d="2019-08-22 05:55:00" c="1"><n>Christopher Robin</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Ewan McGregor stars as a downtrodden Christopher Robin reunited with a cuddly childhood friend. Live action Disney fun with Hayley Atwell and the voice of Jim Cummings</k>  </p>
</a>
