<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-05-29 04:36:21"><p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-05 05:55:00" d="2020-06-05 07:55:00" c="1"><n>Return To Oz</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% In this follow up to The Wizard of Oz, Dorothy returns to the magical land, where she discovers it's up to her to save it from the wicked Nome King</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-05 07:55:00" d="2020-06-05 09:25:00" c="1"><n>Brother Bear</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% A troubled youngster is transformed into a bear to teach him a priceless lesson about brotherhood. Disney animation with the voice of Joaquin Phoenix</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-05 09:25:00" d="2020-06-05 11:25:00" c="1"><n>Ralph Breaks The Internet</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% There's trouble ahead as video game villain Ralph bursts into the chaotic world of the internet with his best friend Vanellope in tow. With John C Reilly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-05 11:25:00" d="2020-06-05 13:40:00" c="1"><n>Mary Poppins Returns</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% The practically-perfect nanny returns, using her magical skills to dazzle the Banks family once again. Musical fantasy with Emily Blunt, Dick Van Dyke and Meryl Streep</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-05 13:40:00" d="2020-06-05 15:55:00" c="1"><n>National Treasure</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Nicolas Cage hunts for a legendary treasure that's been hidden for centuries. Unfortunately, villain Sean Bean is after the loot too. Breakneck adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-05 15:55:00" d="2020-06-05 18:05:00" c="1"><n>National Treasure: Book Of Secrets</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Adventurer Nicolas Cage is plunged into an adrenaline-fuelled quest to prove his ancestor was not an assassin. Spectacular popcorn fun with Helen Mirren</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-05 18:05:00" d="2020-06-05 20:00:00" c="1"><n>Enchanted</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Fairy tale princess Amy Adams is banished to real world New York by an evil queen. Will dashing lawyer Patrick Dempsey be her knight in pinstripe armour?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-05 20:00:00" d="2020-06-05 22:15:00" c="1"><n>Mary Poppins Returns</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% The practically-perfect nanny returns, using her magical skills to dazzle the Banks family once again. Musical fantasy with Emily Blunt, Dick Van Dyke and Meryl Streep</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-05 22:15:00" d="2020-06-06 01:15:00" c="1"><n>National Treasure</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Nicolas Cage hunts for a legendary treasure that's been hidden for centuries. Unfortunately, villain Sean Bean is after the loot too. Breakneck adventure</k>  </p>
</a>
