<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-04-15 04:36:18"><p id_tv="1111" o="2020-04-22 06:20:00" d="2020-04-22 07:55:00" c="1"><n>The Little Mermaid</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% A teenage mermaid, who longs to track down a human prince, makes a deal with a ruthless sea-witch to trade her tail for legs. Classic animation from Disney</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-04-22 07:55:00" d="2020-04-22 09:25:00" c="1"><n>Dinosaur</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% When a meteor hits earth, an orphaned dinosaur and the pack of lemurs who raised him embark upon an epic trek to safety. Animated adventure from Disney</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-04-22 09:25:00" d="2020-04-22 11:25:00" c="1"><n>Ratatouille</n><t>F</t>    <k>80% A rat helps a clumsy kitchen porter create culinary magic. But can Paris's newest sensation keep the secret ingredient under his hat? Pixar animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-04-22 11:25:00" d="2020-04-22 13:35:00" c="1"><n>Aladdin</n><t>F</t>    <k>Live-action re-imagining of the Disney classic about a street urchin who unleashes the power of a genie sparking a magical adventure. With Will Smith</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-04-22 13:35:00" d="2020-04-22 15:20:00" c="1"><n>Hocus Pocus</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% All hell breaks loose when witches Bette Midler, Sarah Jessica Parker and Kathy Najimy are resurrected in modern-day Salem. Family comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-04-22 15:20:00" d="2020-04-22 17:00:00" c="1"><n>Hercules</n><t>F</t>    <k>When the son of Greek God Zeus is robbed of his immortality by the evil god of the underworld, he must find his inner hero in order to reclaim it. Top Disney animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-04-22 17:00:00" d="2020-04-22 19:00:00" c="1"><n>Ralph Breaks The Internet</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% There's trouble ahead as video game villain Ralph bursts into the chaotic world of the internet with his best friend Vanellope in tow. With John C Reilly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-04-22 19:00:00" d="2020-04-22 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Ratatouille</n><t>F</t>    <k>80% A rat helps a clumsy kitchen porter create culinary magic. But can Paris's newest sensation keep the secret ingredient under his hat? Pixar animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-04-22 21:00:00" d="2020-04-23 00:00:00" c="1"><n>Aladdin</n><t>F</t>    <k>Live-action re-imagining of the Disney classic about a street urchin who unleashes the power of a genie sparking a magical adventure. With Will Smith</k>  </p>
</a>
