<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="11" t="2020-05-27 04:36:01"><p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-03 05:05:00" d="2020-06-03 06:45:00" c="1"><n>Old Dogs</n><t>F</t>    <k>Suddenly saddled with twins, businessmen John Travolta and Robin Williams must quickly develop their dad skills. Wacky Disney comedy with Bernie Mac and Seth Green</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-03 06:45:00" d="2020-06-03 08:15:00" c="1"><n>The Lion King 1 1/2</n><t>F</t>    <k>Timon and Pumbaa retell the The Lion King from their perspective, jumping back to before they met Simba and revealing how they learned about Hakuna Matata</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-03 08:15:00" d="2020-06-03 09:55:00" c="1"><n>Herbie Goes Bananas</n><t>F</t>    <k>49% The fourth adventure of the cute little VW sees Herbie journeying south of the Rio Grande for a cross country race. Family fun from Disney</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-03 09:55:00" d="2020-06-03 11:35:00" c="1"><n>Hercules</n><t>F</t>    <k>When the son of Greek God Zeus is robbed of his immortality by the evil god of the underworld, he must find his inner hero in order to reclaim it. Top Disney animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-03 11:35:00" d="2020-06-03 13:35:00" c="1"><n>Dumbo</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% Dumbo the elephant takes to the skies again in Tim Burton's live action remake of the 1941 Disney classic. Colin Farrell, Eva Green, Danny DeVito and Michael Keaton star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-03 13:35:00" d="2020-06-03 15:20:00" c="1"><n>Tangled</n><t>F</t>    <k>In Disney's dazzling animated twist on Rapunzel, the princess with the magical long, blonde hair is imprisoned by a villainess. Can dashing rogue Flynn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-03 15:20:00" d="2020-06-03 16:50:00" c="1"><n>The Lion King 2: Simba's Pride</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Trouble brews when Simba's strong-willed daughter Kiara falls in love with a young lion raised by the exiled followers of Scar. Sequel to the smash-hit animated adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-03 16:50:00" d="2020-06-03 18:30:00" c="1"><n>Herbie Goes Bananas</n><t>F</t>    <k>49% The fourth adventure of the cute little VW sees Herbie journeying south of the Rio Grande for a cross country race. Family fun from Disney</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-03 18:30:00" d="2020-06-03 20:00:00" c="1"><n>Underdog</n><t>F</t>    <k>49% Sniffer dog Shoeshine turns superhero after a lab accident, but the mad scientist behind it will stop at nothing to steal back the puppy's powers. Family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-03 20:00:00" d="2020-06-03 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Dumbo</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% Dumbo the elephant takes to the skies again in Tim Burton's live action remake of the 1941 Disney classic. Colin Farrell, Eva Green, Danny DeVito and Michael Keaton star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-06-03 22:00:00" d="2020-06-04 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Remember The Titans</n><t>F</t>    <k>78% Denzel Washington stars as the new coach of a high school American football team who are forced to battle racial prejudice. Top sports drama</k>  </p>
</a>
