<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="14" t="2019-07-11 00:21:00"><p id_tv="1111" o="2019-07-17 05:55:00" d="2019-07-17 07:40:00" c="1"><n>The Muppet Movie</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Kermit the Frog, Fozzie Bear, Miss Piggy, Gonzo and a motley crew of other Muppets go searching for fame and fortune in Hollywood. Family adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-07-17 07:40:00" d="2019-07-17 09:10:00" c="1"><n>Alexander And The Terrible Horrible, No Good, Very Bad Day</n><t>F</t>    <k>Chaos ensues when a family find themselves having the worst day ever! Family comedy starring Steve Carell and Jennifer Garner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-07-17 09:10:00" d="2019-07-17 10:45:00" c="1"><n>Homeward Bound: The Incredible Journey</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Three pets left behind by their holidaying owners go on an epic trek to find their masters. Animal adventure with the voices of Sally Field and Michael J Fox</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-07-17 10:45:00" d="2019-07-17 12:45:00" c="1"><n>A Wrinkle In Time</n><t>F</t>    <k>44% Sparkly sci-fi adventure following young heroine Storm Reid as she sets out across the cosmos to rescue her missing father. With Oprah Winfrey and Reese Witherspoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-07-17 12:45:00" d="2019-07-17 14:05:00" c="1"><n>The Lion King 1 1/2</n><t>F</t>    <k>Timon and Pumbaa retell the The Lion King from their perspective, jumping back to before they met Simba and revealing how they learned about Hakuna Matata</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-07-17 14:05:00" d="2019-07-17 15:35:00" c="1"><n>The Lion King 2: Simba's Pride</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Trouble brews when Simba's strong-willed daughter Kiara falls in love with a young lion raised by the exiled followers of Scar. Sequel to the smash-hit animated adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-07-17 15:35:00" d="2019-07-17 17:35:00" c="1"><n>The Incredibles</n><t>F</t>    <k>80% Mr Incredible and his superhero family may be semi-retired, but when duty calls they're ready for action. if they can still squeeze on the spandex. Super Pixar animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-07-17 17:35:00" d="2019-07-17 19:00:00" c="1"><n>Alexander And The Terrible Horrible, No Good, Very Bad Day</n><t>F</t>    <k>Chaos ensues when a family find themselves having the worst day ever! Family comedy starring Steve Carell and Jennifer Garner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-07-17 19:00:00" d="2019-07-17 21:00:00" c="1"><n>A Wrinkle In Time</n><t>F</t>    <k>44% Sparkly sci-fi adventure following young heroine Storm Reid as she sets out across the cosmos to rescue her missing father. With Oprah Winfrey and Reese Witherspoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-07-17 21:00:00" d="2019-07-17 23:00:00" c="1"><n>The Incredibles</n><t>F</t>    <k>80% Mr Incredible and his superhero family may be semi-retired, but when duty calls they're ready for action. if they can still squeeze on the spandex. Super Pixar animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-07-17 23:00:00" d="2019-07-18 00:35:00" c="1"><n>The Hunchback Of Notre Dame</n><t>F</t>    <k>Disney favourite following the efforts of deformed bell-ringer Quasimodo as he tries to escape the clutches of an evil justice minister in order to help a friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-07-18 00:35:00" d="2019-07-18 01:55:00" c="1"><n u="The Hunchback Of Notre Dame">The Hunchback Of Notre Dame II</n><t>F</t>    <k>48% Bell ringer Quasimodo needs all his determination to save his prized chimes from an evil magician. Animation with the voice of Jennifer Love Hewitt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-07-18 01:55:00" d="2019-07-18 04:10:00" c="1"><n>Swiss Family Robinson</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% A family is shipwrecked on an island and make a new home for themselves, but are soon under threat from a band of pirates. Classic. Distressing scenes/flashing images</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2019-07-18 04:10:00" d="2019-07-18 05:55:00" c="1"><n>Blank Cheque</n><t>F</t>    <k>A boy gets hold of a blank cheque and goes on a spending spree, but it's not long before the gangsters who lost it want their money back. Stereo sound</k>  </p>
</a>
