<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2020-05-14 04:53:53"><p id_tv="1111" o="2020-05-21 06:10:00" d="2020-05-21 08:10:00" c="1"><n>The Love Bug</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Luckless racing driver Dean Jones can't win a race, until he teams up with charismatic motorcar Herbie the Beetle. Family comedy directed by Mary Poppins' Robert Stevenson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-05-21 08:10:00" d="2020-05-21 10:10:00" c="1"><n>Bedknobs And Broomsticks</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Disney fun starring Angela Lansbury as an amateur witch whose plans to help the war effort take her and three young evacuees on a magical adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-05-21 10:10:00" d="2020-05-21 11:50:00" c="1"><n>Spooky Buddies</n><t>F</t>    <k>45% In this spooky family comedy, the adorable puppy pals must save their town from the villainous Wawrick Warlock and his partner in crime, the Halloween Hound</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-05-21 11:50:00" d="2020-05-21 13:30:00" c="1"><n>Hercules</n><t>F</t>    <k>When the son of Greek God Zeus is robbed of his immortality by the evil god of the underworld, he must find his inner hero in order to reclaim it. Top Disney animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-05-21 13:30:00" d="2020-05-21 15:40:00" c="1"><n>Aladdin</n><t>F</t>    <k>Live-action re-imagining of the Disney classic about a street urchin who unleashes the power of a genie sparking a magical adventure. With Will Smith</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-05-21 15:40:00" d="2020-05-21 17:05:00" c="1"><n>The Emperor's New Groove</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% A cocky young emperor is magically transformed into a llama in this hilarious animation. Can he learn some tough lessons and regain his throne?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-05-21 17:05:00" d="2020-05-21 19:00:00" c="1"><n>The Game Plan</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% Dwayne 'The Rock' Johnson stars as the selfish NFL superstar whose world is turned upside down when he learns he has a daughter. Family comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-05-21 19:00:00" d="2020-05-21 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Enchanted</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Fairy tale princess Amy Adams is banished to real world New York by an evil queen. Will dashing lawyer Patrick Dempsey be her knight in pinstripe armour?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-05-21 21:00:00" d="2020-05-21 23:10:00" c="1"><n>Aladdin</n><t>F</t>    <k>Live-action re-imagining of the Disney classic about a street urchin who unleashes the power of a genie sparking a magical adventure. With Will Smith</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1111" o="2020-05-21 23:10:00" d="2020-05-22 02:10:00" c="1"><n>The Emperor's New Groove</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% A cocky young emperor is magically transformed into a llama in this hilarious animation. Can he learn some tough lessons and regain his throne?</k>  </p>
</a>
