<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2019-07-11 00:20:51"><p id_tv="1113" o="2019-07-16 05:00:00" d="2019-07-16 09:00:00"><n>Drain the Oceans: Secrets Of D-Day</n><t>D</t>    <k>Sonar technology is used beneath Normandy's waves for a powerful look at the more than 100 ships wrecked during the largest amphibious invasion ever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-07-16 09:00:00" d="2019-07-16 10:00:00"><n>WWII's Greatest Raids</n><t>D</t>    <k>A look at how the British Commandos raided the crucial German port of St Nazaire in March 1942 in a ship disguised as a German destroyer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-07-16 10:00:00" d="2019-07-16 11:00:00"><n>WW2: Hell Under the Sea</n><t>D</t>    <k>A breakdown of the Cuban missile crisis, following Soviet submarines carrying nuclear torpedoes, and how a depth charge practice nearly started a nuclear war</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-07-16 11:00:00" d="2019-07-16 12:00:00"><n>Nazi Megastructures</n><t>D</t>    <k>The 600km Siegfried Line, considered one of the greatest fortifications in warfare history. The campaign to breach it cost 140,000 American casualties</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-07-16 12:00:00" d="2019-07-16 13:00:00"><n>Supercar Megabuild</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jodie Kidd asks mechanics Shane and Dan to convert a family saloon so it is capable of reaching 200mph, while also giving it a retro 1960s appearance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-07-16 13:00:00" d="2019-07-16 14:00:00"><n>Strippers: Cars for Cash</n><t>D</t>    <k>The teams bargain for an old Ford Transit and an ageing tractor to strip to a shell and compete to make the most profit in scrap value</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-07-16 14:00:00" d="2019-07-16 15:00:00"><n>Ice Road Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>Bjorn improvises to fill an engine with cooling water, while Thord and his new assistant Andrzej come to the aid of a Polish driver who is ill-equipped</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-07-16 15:00:00" d="2019-07-16 16:00:00"><n>Wicked Tuna</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tyler McLaughlin struggles to hold on to his position in third place as the leading two boats leap ahead, while the pressure takes its toll on Dave Marciano</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-07-16 16:00:00" d="2019-07-16 17:00:00"><n>Air Crash Investigation</n><t>D</t>    <k>Investigators trying to find the cause of a plane crash in Detroit make the discovery that the tragedy happened because of a danger that the industry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-07-16 17:00:00" d="2019-07-16 18:00:00"><n>Air Crash Investigation</n><t>D</t>    <k>A plane crash in Taiwan is initially blamed on a storm. However, when a second plane from the same airline crashes within six months, investigators become suspicious</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-07-16 18:00:00" d="2019-07-16 19:00:00"><n>Car SOS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Fuzz Townshend and Tim Shaw restore a Jaguar Mk2 that has been in its owner's family for 40 years, but which he has been unable to work on following an operation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-07-16 19:00:00" d="2019-07-16 20:00:00"><n>Car SOS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tim and Fuzz secretly fix up an Italian car enthusiast's rusty World Rally-winning pride and joy. But when tragedy strikes, the job takes on a very different meaning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-07-16 20:00:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00"><n>Drain the Oceans: Deep Dive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Experts use cutting-edge technology to drain the sites of lost civilisations as they investigate the powerful forces that caused these cities to vanish beneath the waves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 22:00:00"><n>Wicked Tuna</n><t>D</t>    <k>The quota drops from three fish per day to one. As the pressure mounts, the crews of Pinwheel and Falcon change their strategies and head for a different fishing ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-07-16 22:00:00" d="2019-07-16 23:00:00"><n>Battleground Brothers</n><t>D</t>    <k>With supplies running low, Golf company hunts for the Taliban command centre, a desperate search during which the biggest firefight of their operation erupts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-07-16 23:00:00" d="2019-07-17 00:00:00"><n>Breakout</n><t>D</t>    <k>Harold Laird discusses his escape from Stiles maximum security prison in Texas, revealing how everyday items such as dental floss and tissues helped him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-07-17 00:00:00" d="2019-07-17 01:00:00"><n>Banged Up Abroad</n><t>D</t>    <k>A marijuana smuggler arrested in Tijuana in the 1970s faced imprisonment in Mexico's infamous La Mesa prison, and set about finding a way to escape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-07-17 01:00:00" d="2019-07-17 02:00:00"><n>Explorer 2.0</n><t>D</t>    <k>The discovery of a dinosaur fossil in the Moab Desert. Plus, reports on declining sperm counts, smuggling in the Gaza Strip, and the potential medicinal benefits of dirt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-07-17 02:00:00" d="2019-07-17 03:00:00"><n>Underworld, Inc</n><t>D</t>    <k>The black market trade in stolen cargo, which involves thieves delivering illegal products around the globe and logistics companies arranging safe passage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-07-17 03:00:00" d="2019-07-17 04:00:00"><n>Nazi Megastructures</n><t>D</t>    <k>The 600km Siegfried Line, considered one of the greatest fortifications in warfare history. The campaign to breach it cost 140,000 American casualties</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-07-17 04:00:00" d="2019-07-17 07:00:00"><n>WW2: Hell Under the Sea</n><t>D</t>    <k>A breakdown of the Cuban missile crisis, following Soviet submarines carrying nuclear torpedoes, and how a depth charge practice nearly started a nuclear war</k>  </p>
</a>
