<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2019-08-13 02:21:30"><p id_tv="1113" o="2019-08-18 05:00:00" d="2019-08-18 09:00:00"><n>Seconds from Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>An investigation into the causes behind the commuter train crash that killed more than 100 people in Amagasaki, Japan, in April 2005</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-08-18 09:00:00" d="2019-08-18 10:00:00"><n>Seconds from Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>82% The 1988 crash of a train into a crowded Paris station platform. Minutes before the disaster the driver sent a warning that stated the locomotive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-08-18 10:00:00" d="2019-08-18 11:00:00"><n>Seconds from Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>82% An investigation into the collapse of a Singapore hotel in 1986 - the country's worst disaster since the Second World War. Rescue teams were forced</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-08-18 11:00:00" d="2019-08-18 12:00:00"><n>Seconds from Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>82% An investigation into a gas leak in Puerto Rico that caused an explosion and killed 33 people. The programme assesses whether the disaster was the result of negligence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-08-18 12:00:00" d="2019-08-18 13:00:00"><n>Seconds from Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>82% An investigation into the eruption of Mount St Helens in 1980, asking why scientists failed to predict the disaster. The volcano exploded in a cloud</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-08-18 13:00:00" d="2019-08-18 14:00:00"><n>Seconds from Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>82% How the British ferry Herald of Free Enterprise capsized in March 1987, killing more than 190 passengers. The bow doors were left open as</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-08-18 14:00:00" d="2019-08-18 15:00:00"><n>Seconds from Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>82% The story of space shuttle Columbia - hailed as the most complex craft ever built - which overcame technological challenges to become the first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-08-18 15:00:00" d="2019-08-18 16:00:00"><n>Seconds from Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>82% An investigation into the crash-landing of United Flight 232 at Iowa's Sioux City airport in July 1989. A failed engine sent the plane hurtling towards</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-08-18 16:00:00" d="2019-08-18 17:00:00"><n>Seconds from Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>82% How 19 tourists fell to their deaths at an Italian ski resort in 1998, when a military plane accidentally cut a cable supporting their gondola</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-08-18 17:00:00" d="2019-08-18 18:00:00"><n>Seconds from Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>82% The 1987 fire at King's Cross tube station, in which 31 people were killed when a match was discarded on a wooden escalator - despite a smoking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-08-18 18:00:00" d="2019-08-18 19:00:00"><n>Seconds from Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>82% An investigation into the 1999 Paddington train crash that killed 31 people, asking who was to blame and whether the accident could have been avoided</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-08-18 19:00:00" d="2019-08-18 20:00:00"><n>Seconds from Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>82% Examining how two aircraft came to collide in mid-air near the southern German town of Uberlingen in 2002, causing the deaths of 45 children</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-08-18 20:00:00" d="2019-08-18 21:00:00"><n>Seconds from Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>The events leading up to the crash of Japanese Airlines Flight 123 in 1985, which resulted in the deaths of 520 people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-08-18 21:00:00" d="2019-08-18 22:00:00"><n>Seconds from Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>82% A look at the cockpit fire that killed 229 people onboard Swiss Air 11 and how simple wear and tear caused the death of 520 passengers flying on Japan Airlines Flight 123</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-08-18 22:00:00" d="2019-08-18 23:00:00"><n>Genoa Bridge Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>The story of the collapse of Genoa's Morandi Bridge in which 43 people lost their lives. Testimony from survivors is examined to discover the cause of the disaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-08-18 23:00:00" d="2019-08-19 00:00:00"><n>Seconds from Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>82% Deconstruction of the chain of events leading to one of the world's most infamous disasters, revealing how freak incidents can cause catastrophe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-08-19 00:00:00" d="2019-08-19 01:00:00"><n>Seconds from Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>82% Deconstruction of the chain of events leading to the Mumbai terrorist attacks in 2008, when a string of bombings and shootings claimed 166 lives in the Indian city</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-08-19 01:00:00" d="2019-08-19 02:00:00"><n>Seconds from Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>82% The story of one of the world's worst industrial accidents, which affected the Indian city of Bhopal in December 1984. A broken valve at the Union Carbide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-08-19 02:00:00" d="2019-08-19 03:00:00"><n>Seconds from Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>The shocking 1995 bomb attack on a federal building in Oklahoma City, which saw a nine-storey tower collapse in seconds, killing 168 people and injuring many more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-08-19 03:00:00" d="2019-08-19 04:00:00"><n>Seconds from Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>82% The story behind the sinking of the HMS Coventry during the Falklands War, when on May 25, 1982, Argentinian jets attacked the vessel causing it to capsize within 20 minutes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2019-08-19 04:00:00" d="2019-08-19 07:00:00"><n>Seconds from Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>82% Deconstructing the events in Norway on 22 July, 2011, when mass murderer Anders Behring Breivik killed 77 people</k>  </p>
</a>
