<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="20" t="2021-07-09 07:10:07"><p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-14 05:00:00" d="2021-07-14 09:00:00"><n>Nazi Megastructures</n><t>D</t>    <k>Defensive lines built by the Nazis across Italy, which delayed the advance of Allied forces by almost two years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-14 09:00:00" d="2021-07-14 10:00:00"><n>Lost Cities with Albert Lin</n><t>D</t>    <k>National Geographic explorer Albert Lin uses his hi-tech 3D scans to uncover the truth behind the legends of El Dorado, Petra and Machu Picchu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-14 10:00:00" d="2021-07-14 11:00:00"><n>Lost Treasures of Egypt</n><t>D</t>    <k>Archaeologists search an underground labyrinth for the resting place of Egypt's most mysterious Queen, Nefertiti, and discover a coffin that dates back to her reign</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-14 11:00:00" d="2021-07-14 12:00:00"><n>Drain the Oceans</n><t>D</t>    <k>Metaphorically speaking, experts 'pull the plug' on the River Nile, looking at historical discoveries found at its bottom. The programme addresses issues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-14 12:00:00" d="2021-07-14 13:00:00"><n>Air Crash Investigation</n><t>D</t>    <k>A plane crashes just short of the runway in San Andres. While bad weather is thought to be the cause, investigators uncover something more troubling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-14 13:00:00" d="2021-07-14 14:00:00"><n>Air Crash Investigation</n><t>D</t>    <k>The investigation into the crash of a plane that nosedived into a remote desert in Patagonia. A microscopic filament provides the first tangible</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-14 14:00:00" d="2021-07-14 15:00:00"><n>Wicked Tuna</n><t>D</t>    <k>Stormy seas are on the horizon, and the crews face a tough choice between heading for the safety of port and braving the elements to bring home a big catch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-14 15:00:00" d="2021-07-14 16:00:00"><n>Car S.O.S.</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tim and Fuzz head to Lincolnshire where the embodiment of a once luxurious era awaits: a 1929 Rolls Royce Doctor's Coupe. When Emily's Dad recently</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-14 16:00:00" d="2021-07-14 17:00:00"><n>Car S.O.S.</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tim and Fuzz head to Norfolk where a once sporty French hot hatch awaits. The car belongs to 21-year-old student Senna who comes from a family of petrol heads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-14 17:00:00" d="2021-07-14 18:00:00"><n>Megafactories</n><t>D</t>    <k>74% Discovering how New York's R-160 subway car is made. Built to handle 1.6 billion riders per year, it weighs 39 tonnes and contains 24 miles of wiring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-14 18:00:00" d="2021-07-14 19:00:00"><n>Lawless Island</n><t>D</t>    <k>Matt Carlson tackles a new project with his sawmill as winter nears its end, and Sam Carlson helps to remedy an issue that impacts everyone's safety</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-14 19:00:00" d="2021-07-14 20:00:00"><n>Megastructures</n><t>D</t>    <k>World's Biggest Casino . The construction of a ?2.4billion casino in Macau, China, which includes a 3,000-suite hotel, an indoor canal, 350 shops</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-14 20:00:00" d="2021-07-14 21:00:00"><n>Seconds from Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>82% The story behind the sinking of the HMS Coventry during the Falklands War, when on May 25, 1982, Argentinian jets attacked the vessel causing it to capsize within 20 minutes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-14 21:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:00:00"><n>Mars: One Day on the Red Planet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Documentary capturing a single day on the surface of Mars from dawn to dusk, exploring giant volcanoes, ancient lakes, landscapes of ice, and spacecraft crash sites</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-14 23:00:00" d="2021-07-15 00:00:00"><n>Hubble's Cosmic Journey</n><t>D</t>    <k>Since the launch of the Hubble Space Telescope in 1990, it has captured thousands of stunning images of space and revolutionised the way the universe is understood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-15 00:00:00" d="2021-07-15 01:00:00"><n>Air Crash Investigation</n><t>D</t>    <k>The case of a plane that flew into a massive storm over Indonesia during the country's rainy season, but made a seemingly impossible emergency landing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-15 01:00:00" d="2021-07-15 02:00:00"><n>World War II: The Apocalypse</n><t>D</t>    <k>The story of the Second World War, featuring haunting images of Jewish persecution and footage of Hitler taken by his partner Eva Braun at his Alpine retreat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-15 02:00:00" d="2021-07-15 03:00:00"><n>Inside North Korea: Dangerous Games</n><t>D</t>    <k>The use of the Olympics in advancing North Korea's political ambitions, examining Kim Jong-un's decision to send a delegation to the winter games in Pyeongchang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-15 03:00:00" d="2021-07-15 04:00:00"><n>Banged Up Abroad Compilations</n><t>D</t>    <k>British student Lucy Wright decides to flee when she is busted for drug smuggling in Argentina. Robert Pringle has no hope of escape when he's thrown in jail in Peru</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-15 04:00:00" d="2021-07-15 05:00:00"><n>Drugs Inc</n><t>D</t>    <k>The trafficking of cocaine from Peru to Europe via Ghana and Nigeria, where the unguarded borders between West African countries make smuggling much easier</k>  </p>
</a>
