<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2021-07-08 05:03:31"><p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-13 05:00:00" d="2021-07-13 09:00:00"><n>Nazi Megastructures</n><t>D</t>    <k>How German forces were led into a trap on Sicily by false documents planted on a corpse, and had to make use of the island's rugged landscape to escape to Italy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-13 09:00:00" d="2021-07-13 10:00:00"><n>Lost Cities: The Great Flood</n><t>D</t>    <k>Albert Lin is on a global adventure, from icy Black Sea depths to the heights of the Peruvian Andes, searching for the origins of Great Flood stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-13 10:00:00" d="2021-07-13 11:00:00"><n>Lost Treasures of Egypt</n><t>D</t>    <k>Archaeologists unlock the mysteries of Egypt's most famous pharaoh, revealing surprising evidence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-13 11:00:00" d="2021-07-13 12:00:00"><n>Drain the Oceans</n><t>D</t>    <k>The China Seas are the site of one of the largest naval battles of all time, not to mention a 700-year-old mystery - and technological wonders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-13 12:00:00" d="2021-07-13 13:00:00"><n>Air Crash Investigation</n><t>D</t>    <k>After a routine landing, a Taiwanese commuter plane is rocked by an explosion. However, a team of investigators finds no evidence of a bomb on board</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-13 13:00:00" d="2021-07-13 14:00:00"><n>Air Crash Investigation</n><t>D</t>    <k>A plane ends up at the wrong end of a runway in heavy fog, leading to a collision that kills eight people - but it seems the pilots' personalities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-13 14:00:00" d="2021-07-13 15:00:00"><n>Wicked Tuna</n><t>D</t>    <k>A new strategy of boats forming alliances threatens to overturn the leaderboard - if trust can be maintained. Paul Hebert finds his fortunes changing for the better</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-13 15:00:00" d="2021-07-13 16:00:00"><n>Car S.O.S.</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tim and Fuzz come to the rescue of their first ever-custom car: a radically modified VW Beetle called a VW Wizard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-13 16:00:00" d="2021-07-13 17:00:00"><n>Car S.O.S.</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tim and Fuzz are off to Southampton to take on a car a 1969 Jensen Interceptor. Owner Nick cherished his dream car until he got extreme arthritis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-13 17:00:00" d="2021-07-13 18:00:00"><n>Megafactories</n><t>D</t>    <k>74% The Bentley factory, where 95 per cent of cars are custom-made, and engineers are beginning to remake the company's flagship Mulsanne</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-13 18:00:00" d="2021-07-13 18:30:00"><n>Food Factory</n><t>D</t>    <k>A look at the production of jumbo lollipops, Chinese hot and sour soup and hedgehog chocolate bars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-13 18:30:00" d="2021-07-13 19:00:00"><n>Food Factory</n><t>D</t>    <k>A look at the production of sugar-free mints, raspberry jellies and cranberry pecan clusters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-13 19:00:00" d="2021-07-13 20:00:00"><n>The World's Biggest Shredder</n><t>D</t>    <k>A visit to the site of the world's most powerful demolition machine, capable of pulverizing 450 vehicles within the space of an hour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-13 20:00:00" d="2021-07-13 21:00:00"><n>Seconds from Disaster</n><t>D</t>    <k>82% Charting the events that led to the crash of Swissair Flight 111 in 1998, when the aircraft plunged into the Atlantic Ocean off Canada, killing all 229 people on board</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-13 21:00:00" d="2021-07-13 22:00:00"><n>Britain's Underworld</n><t>D</t>    <k>Examining the infamous crime bosses, their activities and struggles with the police when they ruled Britain's toughest cities between the 1950s and 1990s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-13 22:00:00" d="2021-07-13 23:00:00"><n>Britain's Underworld</n><t>D</t>    <k>The life of Liverpool's Curtis 'Cocky' Warren, examining the way he made his money in drugs and how he came to be featured on the Sunday Times Rich List</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-13 23:00:00" d="2021-07-14 00:00:00"><n>Britain's Underworld</n><t>D</t>    <k>The notorious crime bosses who terrorised Manchester over five decades and the power struggles that have taken place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-14 00:00:00" d="2021-07-14 01:00:00"><n>Air Crash Investigation</n><t>D</t>    <k>The crash of a German plane flying over the French Alps, which inexplicably began losing altitude. The explanation for the disaster proves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-14 01:00:00" d="2021-07-14 02:00:00"><n>Apocalypse: The Second World War</n><t>D</t>    <k>Part two of two. Hitler becomes chancellor in 1933 after the German economy collapses and sets out to ensure the Nazi party's members dominate every aspect of society</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-14 02:00:00" d="2021-07-14 03:00:00"><n>Inside North Korea: Then and Now with Lisa Ling</n><t>D</t>    <k>A reporter who went undercover in the secretive nation in 2006 returns 11 years later to determine how much the country has changed since Kim Jong-un took power</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-14 03:00:00" d="2021-07-14 04:00:00"><n>Banged Up Abroad: Crime &amp; Punishment</n><t>D</t>    <k>Five prisoners dig a tunnel using rocks and a butter knife, and, a man mounts a daring escape from a brutal Soviet prison camp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1113" o="2021-07-14 04:00:00" d="2021-07-14 07:00:00"><n>Drugs Inc</n><t>D</t>    <k>A heroin kingpin tries to diversify his business in the face of competition from small-time dealers, but is not prepared for the intervention of a crack</k>  </p>
</a>
