<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2019-07-11 00:20:09"><p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-16 05:10:00" d="2019-07-16 06:00:00"><n>Tanked</n><t>D</t>    <k>67% Wayde and Brett make a tank for Hip Hop artist Tyga. To mark his hit single, Rack City, they seek to fill a tank with cash. Will Tyga feel like a million bucks?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-16 06:00:00" d="2019-07-16 07:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>In Denver, the vets treat a cat named Byron who has been mysteriously losing weight. Plus, Bear, the dog is treated for injuries after being hit by a car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-16 07:00:00" d="2019-07-16 08:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr Jeff examines a beloved Weimaraner who’s stopped eating and makes a surprising discovery. Plus, a servicewoman brings in her pit bull who has an injured leg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-16 08:00:00" d="2019-07-16 09:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>When SPCA Investigators are called to a remote property, they encounter one the worst causes of neglect. They find one horse dead and four more barely alive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-16 09:00:00" d="2019-07-16 10:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>The officers take control of 200 chickens that are being kept in inhumane temperatures exceeding 100 degrees. Plus, they uncover a house overrun by 50 rabbits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-16 10:00:00" d="2019-07-16 11:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia gets a call about a dog loose at a building site. Meanwhile, a family with an unusual lifestyle comes looking to adopt a new puppy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-16 11:00:00" d="2019-07-16 12:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mariah enlists a parolee's help to rescue a dangerously skinny dog. And, Tania and Perry struggle to plan their unconventional wedding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-16 12:00:00" d="2019-07-16 13:00:00"><n>Mekong: Soul Of A River</n><t>D</t>    <k>This fascinating journey up the Mekong River starts off the coast of Vietnam and continues into the Mekong Delta, in search of undiscovered species</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-16 13:00:00" d="2019-07-16 14:00:00"><n>Mekong: Soul Of A River</n><t>D</t>    <k>The journey along the Mekong continues into Cambodia in search of endangered species such as tigers, Siamese crocodiles and an array of primates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-16 14:00:00" d="2019-07-16 15:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>HSPCA worker Dana Moss is called to help a colt that is unable to stand, while Senior Investigator Kirstie rescues ferrets abandoned in a freezing house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-16 15:00:00" d="2019-07-16 16:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>The rescue team gets a call for help to assist a stray dog trying to deliver puppies. With two pups delivered alive and more to come, will she get help in time?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-16 16:00:00" d="2019-07-16 17:00:00"><n>Tanked</n><t>D</t>    <k>67% Donut Mania is Brett's newest business venture and they’re having a grand opening. Wayde and the team want to congratulate him with a surprise fish tank!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-16 17:00:00" d="2019-07-16 18:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>When a dog is rushed into the clinic foaming at the mouth, Dr Jeff must act fast. And when he meets Penelope the Pig, he faces a surgery he's never done before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-16 18:00:00" d="2019-07-16 19:00:00"><n>Spawn Of Jaws: The Birth</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Michael Domeier attempts to find the mating waters of the Great White and where it gives birth, which until now has perplexed the scientific community</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-16 19:00:00" d="2019-07-16 20:00:00"><n>Untamed China</n><t>D</t>    <k>Nigel travels on the highest altitude railway in the world in search of the rare and elusive Tibetan antelope. Plus, he finds a Tibetan fox and her cubs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-16 20:00:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00"><n>Alaskan Bush People</n><t>D</t>    <k>The boys meet some local girls and invite them back to their property for a unique style of bush dating. Plus, Billy strikes a barter for windows for their new home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 22:00:00"><n>Alaska Monsters</n><t>D</t>    <k>38% The team investigates reports of a massive wolf. Todd constructs a massive jail cell to hold this creature, while Levi implements laser technology</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-16 22:00:00" d="2019-07-16 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>When bears and tigers were found in a chicken shed, it was one of the most dramatic rescues ever. The team catch up with them as they enjoy new lives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-16 23:00:00" d="2019-07-17 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>A couple who recently lost their dog are looking for a new companion to join their family. Plus, the team take Hannah and Caleb to take part in the Puppy Bowl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 00:00:00" d="2019-07-17 01:00:00"><n>I'm Alive</n><t>D</t>    <k>69% Follow extraordinary tales of survival. After being bitten by a black widow, Mike fights for life. Can he be saved using an illegal antivenom smuggled into the US?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 01:00:00" d="2019-07-17 02:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>When bears and tigers were found in a chicken shed, it was one of the most dramatic rescues ever. The team catch up with them as they enjoy new lives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 02:00:00" d="2019-07-17 03:00:00"><n>Untamed China</n><t>D</t>    <k>Nigel travels on the highest altitude railway in the world in search of the rare and elusive Tibetan antelope. Plus, he finds a Tibetan fox and her cubs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 03:00:00" d="2019-07-17 03:50:00"><n>Alaskan Bush People</n><t>D</t>    <k>The boys meet some local girls and invite them back to their property for a unique style of bush dating. Plus, Billy strikes a barter for windows for their new home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 03:50:00" d="2019-07-17 04:40:00"><n>Alaska Monsters</n><t>D</t>    <k>38% The team investigates reports of a massive wolf. Todd constructs a massive jail cell to hold this creature, while Levi implements laser technology</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 04:40:00" d="2019-07-17 05:10:00"><n>Meet The Penguins</n><t>D</t>    <k>A large-scale leopard attack near Cape Town leaves thirty-three penguins dead. The sole survivor is picked up by rangers and rushed to Sanccob – but will he make it?</k>  </p>
</a>
