<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="28" t="2020-04-12 04:25:12"><p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 05:10:00" d="2020-04-19 06:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jackson travels to Portland to help Lee and Teresa, who called 911 on their cat Lux. After their son Jesse pulled on Lux's tail, he got clawed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 06:00:00" d="2020-04-19 07:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% When Justin gave his mum Bombadil, he had no idea the cat would be a gift from hell. Buddhists Tom and Pola lived in harmony until they adopted Percy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 07:00:00" d="2020-04-19 08:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Jeff, a photographer who lives and works out of his home, is at risk of losing his business and his assistant because of his blood-thirsty cat, Buster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 08:00:00" d="2020-04-19 09:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Maryam is a pet psychic, but she can't communicate with her vicious cat Lily. Plus, Khloe discovers an entire feral colony behind her parent's house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 09:00:00" d="2020-04-19 10:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Debbie is torn between her boyfriend and her peeing cat Blinkie. Krisi and Jason want to get married, but standing in their way is her crazy cat, Frankie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 10:00:00" d="2020-04-19 11:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Ambreen has been in an abusive relationship for the past 13 years, but her abuser is her cat, Calvin. Can Jackson Galaxy help Ambreen to get her life back?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 11:00:00" d="2020-04-19 12:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Sandy and Phil were happily married until they adopted their cat Woody. The couple is convinced that Woody is evil enough to kill their other cat, Pirate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 12:00:00" d="2020-04-19 13:00:00"><n>The Zoo</n><t>D</t>    <k>A markhor goat gives birth to Andre, the biggest baby of the year. And, confiscated lizards destined for the pet trade require urgent medical attention</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 13:00:00" d="2020-04-19 14:00:00"><n>The Zoo</n><t>D</t>    <k>Keepers introduce three gaur - a large, skittish species of cattle - to the rest of the herd. Plus, a sickly Sambar fawn is rushed to the health centre</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 14:00:00" d="2020-04-19 15:00:00"><n>The Zoo</n><t>D</t>    <k>Peaches, a two-month-old warthog, charms his keepers while training to become an animal ambassador. And Willow, a red panda, shows signs of being pregnant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 15:00:00" d="2020-04-19 16:00:00"><n>The Zoo</n><t>D</t>    <k>A trio of new penguin chicks are introduced to the pool for their first swim. Family dynamics change when the mandrill monkey troop welcomes a new baby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 16:00:00" d="2020-04-19 16:30:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why have a pair of giraffes turned white in Kenya? Plus, why are the world’s fastest land animal not always successful when hunting? Experts examine this and more!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 16:30:00" d="2020-04-19 17:00:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>Experts analyse and explain footage of 5,000 birds falling from the sky in Arkansas. Plus, why would a skunk ever do a handstand and what makes a frog flash?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 17:00:00" d="2020-04-19 17:30:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animals do the most incredible things, and some have super powers humans can only dream of. New science and amazing demonstrations reveal the secrets of the animal world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 17:30:00" d="2020-04-19 18:00:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animals can do extraordinary things – but how do they do it? Experts spill the secrets of the animal kingdom with amazing footage and surprising facts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 18:00:00" d="2020-04-19 18:30:00"><n>Coyote Peterson: Brave The Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animal expert Coyote Peterson navigates the turbulent waters of Australia’s tidepools at night to find and get close to the elusive wobbegong sharks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 18:30:00" d="2020-04-19 19:00:00"><n>Coyote Peterson: Brave The Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animal expert Coyote Peterson explores the inner tidepools along Australia’s Sunshine Coast to find and get close to its venomous marine creatures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 19:00:00" d="2020-04-19 20:00:00"><n>Alaska: The Last Frontier</n><t>D</t>    <k>Atz travels to Perl Island to build a homestead for a friend. Tempers flare as Otto, Eivin, and Levi move an old workshop cabin to Otto's property</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 20:00:00" d="2020-04-19 21:00:00"><n>Alaskan Bush People</n><t>D</t>    <k>Disaster strikes as floods plague the region, and the Browns must balance the fate of their new community with the success of their homestead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 21:00:00" d="2020-04-19 22:00:00"><n>Jeremy Wade's Dark Waters</n><t>D</t>    <k>Fisherman and adventurer, Jeremy Wade, travels to Lake Garda in northern Italy to investigate a 16th century monster fish. What secrets is the lake hiding?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 22:00:00" d="2020-04-19 23:00:00"><n>Expedition Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>Russell finds a structure he believes is a Bigfoot nest. Meanwhile, new team member Ronny joins Mireya in a race to the nest to collect DNA samples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 23:00:00" d="2020-04-20 00:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Marco and Aimee recently got married, but Marco's cat, Monty, is tearing them apart with his appetite for destruction – and will eat everything in sight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 00:00:00" d="2020-04-20 01:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Frankie the cat pees all over Daniel and Desiree's new multi-million dollar dream home. Plus, cat Sugar is hiding from newly adopted cat Dyna</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 01:00:00" d="2020-04-20 02:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Jay has one lady in his life and that's his ferocious attack cat, Marley. Marley will tear apart anyone who crosses her path - including Jay</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 02:00:00" d="2020-04-20 03:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Jackson has his hands full with two cats; one who likes to bully and another who poops excessively. Plus, there’s another who is doing its best to ruin a dream home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 03:00:00" d="2020-04-20 03:50:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Stanley and Shelby are ferocious when they are together, so who will their owners have guests around? Plus, Finn has a habit of jumping in the babies’ crib</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 03:50:00" d="2020-04-20 04:40:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jackson travels to Portland to help Lee and Teresa, who called 911 on their cat Lux. After their son Jesse pulled on Lux's tail, he got clawed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 04:40:00" d="2020-04-20 05:10:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animals can do extraordinary things – but how do they do it? Experts spill the secrets of the animal kingdom with amazing footage and surprising facts</k>  </p>
</a>
