<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="28" t="2020-04-09 04:26:16"><p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-16 05:10:00" d="2020-04-16 06:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Jackson Galaxy checks in with previous seasons cat owners, to recap on their story, and find out how they and their cats are doing since filming wrapped</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-16 06:00:00" d="2020-04-16 07:00:00"><n>Preposterous Pets</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the Czech Republic, the Lion Whisper’s oversized cats are threatening their owner. Plus meet the Texan cowboy who lets Buffalo roam in his own home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-16 07:00:00" d="2020-04-16 08:00:00"><n>Preposterous Pets</n><t>D</t>    <k>In Colorado, alligator-mad father and daughter duo wrestle with a few of their 350 ferocious reptiles. Plus, a family has an obsession for macaque monkeys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-16 08:00:00" d="2020-04-16 09:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>As temperatures soar in New Orleans, so do tempers. Tia calls out the parolees on their laziness, leading to an explosive confrontation with new parolee Randy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-16 09:00:00" d="2020-04-16 10:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia and the twins are devastated after they learn of Chong’s cancer diagnoses. Determined to make the most of a bad situation, Tia puts a plan into action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-16 10:00:00" d="2020-04-16 10:30:00"><n>Meet The Sloths</n><t>D</t>    <k>Sensitive sloth, Linus, hits a rocky patch when Claire has to leave the Sanctuary. Meanwhile, sloth scientist Becky reveals which of the sloth species</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-16 10:30:00" d="2020-04-16 11:00:00"><n>Meet The Sloths</n><t>D</t>    <k>Sloth Scientist Becky tries to find out what drives the females of the species wild. Meanwhile, young choloepus, Tigger, starts to display decidedly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-16 11:00:00" d="2020-04-16 11:30:00"><n>ACE: Animal Countdown Extraordinaire</n><t>D</t>    <k>From a spider with a home-made balloon to an aerodynamic snake, Jack and the Buccaneer countdown the best animal flyers on the planet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-16 11:30:00" d="2020-04-16 12:00:00"><n>ACE: Animal Countdown Extraordinaire</n><t>D</t>    <k>From brave new-born ducklings to hungry young sharks, Jack and Buck are calculating the top ten toughest baby animals on the planet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-16 12:00:00" d="2020-04-16 13:00:00"><n>Crikey! It's The Irwins</n><t>D</t>    <k>There’s huge excitement at Australia Zoo: Rosie the Giraffe is set to give birth! Robert has a bloody encounter with a wild python that entered an enclosure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-16 13:00:00" d="2020-04-16 14:00:00"><n>The Bronx Zoo</n><t>D</t>    <k>A young snow leopard cub is having difficulty walking and at risk of permanent disability. And, the zoo keepers prepare a new exhibit enclosure for gazelles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-16 14:00:00" d="2020-04-16 14:30:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That</n><t>D</t>    <k>How do caterpillars transform into magnificent butterflies in their cocoon? Plus, why are cats’ tongues the way they are? Experts answer these questions and more!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-16 14:30:00" d="2020-04-16 15:00:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>How can a dung beetle standing on its head roll a ball in a straight line? Do egrets ever regret hanging out next to hungry alligators? Experts explain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-16 15:00:00" d="2020-04-16 16:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>With thousands of animals in need, and vet care unaffordable to most, Dr Jeff heads to Mexico to run a mobile clinic and help as many people and pets as they can</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-16 16:00:00" d="2020-04-16 17:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr Jeff fights to save a bearded dragon which is having a seizure, and Dr Amy is put to the test when a routine cat neuter turns complicated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-16 17:00:00" d="2020-04-16 18:00:00"><n>Almost Human With Jane Goodall</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr Goodall explores the fascinating lives of chimpanzees as she searches for Gaia, the chimpanzee mother who has disappeared after tragically losing her baby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-16 18:00:00" d="2020-04-16 19:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>74% A three-day-old kitten with a badly twisted leg needs a series of splints to save her, and Female loggerhead turtles are in the midst of laying eggs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-16 19:00:00" d="2020-04-16 20:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Phoenix</n><t>D</t>    <k>A heat-exhausted domestic rabbit is abandoned in a car park. Plus, investigator Mark persuades the owner of six underfed dogs to give them more food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-16 20:00:00" d="2020-04-16 21:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Shelter volunteers drive from Kansas hoping the team can save a tiny rescue dog. Plus, Dr. Jeff’s cousin asks for the vets to visit Tennessee to provide free care</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-16 21:00:00" d="2020-04-16 22:00:00"><n>The Vet Life</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Lavigne thinks a cat is stressed because of a robot vacuum. Meanwhile, Dr. Blue quarantines a sick dog and a puppy requires emergency life-saving surgery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-16 22:00:00" d="2020-04-16 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>In a special edition of Animal Cops Houston, the investigators of the Houston SPCA look back on some of the most shocking cases of animal cruelty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-16 23:00:00" d="2020-04-17 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Villalobos prepares for Hurricane Barry with Tia and the crew urgently ensuring the animals’ safety. Later, a cancer survivor hopes to rescue an unwanted dog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 00:00:00" d="2020-04-17 01:00:00"><n>Mountain Monsters</n><t>D</t>    <k>After a shocking discovery Buck travels into the forest and encounters someone from his past. And, the team follows Jeff’s trail to the Three Rings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 01:00:00" d="2020-04-17 02:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Phoenix</n><t>D</t>    <k>A heat-exhausted domestic rabbit is abandoned in a car park. Plus, investigator Mark persuades the owner of six underfed dogs to give them more food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 02:00:00" d="2020-04-17 03:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Shelter volunteers drive from Kansas hoping the team can save a tiny rescue dog. Plus, Dr. Jeff’s cousin asks for the vets to visit Tennessee to provide free care</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 03:00:00" d="2020-04-17 03:50:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>In a special edition of Animal Cops Houston, the investigators of the Houston SPCA look back on some of the most shocking cases of animal cruelty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 03:50:00" d="2020-04-17 04:40:00"><n>Almost Human With Jane Goodall</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr Goodall explores the fascinating lives of chimpanzees as she searches for Gaia, the chimpanzee mother who has disappeared after tragically losing her baby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 04:40:00" d="2020-04-17 05:10:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animals can do extraordinary things – but how do they do it? Experts spill the secrets of the animal kingdom with amazing footage and surprising facts</k>  </p>
</a>
