<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2020-04-10 04:26:48"><p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 05:10:00" d="2020-04-17 06:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Jay has one lady in his life and that's his ferocious attack cat, Marley. Marley will tear apart anyone who crosses her path - including Jay</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 06:00:00" d="2020-04-17 07:00:00"><n>Preposterous Pets</n><t>D</t>    <k>On the West Coast of America, a young woman is living the night life with a pair of tamandua anteaters. Elsewhere, a family shares their home with hippos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 07:00:00" d="2020-04-17 08:00:00"><n>Preposterous Pets</n><t>D</t>    <k>The latest pet craze in the US? Owners pimp out their poodles to compete in grooming contests. Plus, in Kenya, a family owns domesticated Giraffes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 08:00:00" d="2020-04-17 09:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia is contacted by NBA star Zach Randolph regarding a dog rescued from a drainpipe. Later, Mariah and Earl prepare a puppy rescued from the 9th Ward for adoption</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 09:00:00" d="2020-04-17 10:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>The team find themselves in a dangerous situation when they attempt to rescue dogs involved in a dog-fighting ring. And, for one lucky pit bull, a new home awaits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 10:00:00" d="2020-04-17 10:30:00"><n>Meet The Sloths</n><t>D</t>    <k>It's touch-and-go when sanctuary lothario, Randy, succumbs to an infection, a new arrival gets a presidential welcome and Becky unravels the secrets of sloth attraction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 10:30:00" d="2020-04-17 11:00:00"><n>Meet The Sloths</n><t>D</t>    <k>The sanctuary team try to save a poisoned sloth, Claire turns sloth sleuth to find a much-loved missing toy, and Becky tries to pin down the secret of sloth manliness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 11:00:00" d="2020-04-17 12:00:00"><n>Preposterous Pets</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the Czech Republic, the Lion Whisper’s oversized cats are threatening their owner. Plus meet the Texan cowboy who lets Buffalo roam in his own home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 12:00:00" d="2020-04-17 13:00:00"><n>Crikey! It's The Irwins</n><t>D</t>    <k>While Bindi and the keepers ready Sophie the baby Giraffe for her first steps into her enclosure, Robert helps to raise another baby: Melman the Kangaroo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 13:00:00" d="2020-04-17 14:00:00"><n>The Bronx Zoo</n><t>D</t>    <k>26-year old polar bear, Tundra, is one of the zoo’s favourite inhabitants. But, after his behaviour changes, keepers are worried about signs of disease</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 14:00:00" d="2020-04-17 14:30:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why are some cats cross-eyed? How do meerkats eat poisonous scorpions and how can hippos sleep whilst holding their breath? Experts answer these questions and more!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 14:30:00" d="2020-04-17 15:00:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>Experts examine incredible natural phenomena. Which animals get the giggles? Why do San Francisco’s sea lions mysteriously swim away - all at once?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 15:00:00" d="2020-04-17 16:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Jeff must act fast to save a kitten with head trauma. Dr. Amy treats a dog with a weak heart. And a Good Samaritan helps a family when their dog is hit by a car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 16:00:00" d="2020-04-17 17:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Jeff and his team helps two Chihuahuas found abandoned in a storm drain. Then Dr. Jeff makes a discovery when a cat's odd eating habits put its life in danger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 17:00:00" d="2020-04-17 18:00:00"><n>Wild Mexico</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mexico is an ancient land, full of diversity and mystery. It is home to a vast wilderness of oceans, deserts, jungle, and unique creatures that are found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 18:00:00" d="2020-04-17 19:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>74% It’s the turn of the Cook Islands to provide the cases today, as Chris handles a hit-and run victim, a wolfhound with an eye problem and very mischievous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 19:00:00" d="2020-04-17 20:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Phoenix</n><t>D</t>    <k>Investigator Mark rescues a dog with open wounds from a crate and the Phoenix Fire Department try to reach a cat stuck 40ft up a palm tree in fierce winds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 20:00:00" d="2020-04-17 21:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>After a string of bad luck with some of the parolees, Tia hopes newbie Richard will prove to be a valuable asset. Plus, the team rushes to save a mutilated pup</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 21:00:00" d="2020-04-17 22:00:00"><n>Amanda To The Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>Returning from Puerto Rico, Amanda sets out to acclimatize her rescues to life on the mainland. First, a trip to the vet to make sure the dogs are in good health</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 22:00:00" d="2020-04-17 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Chief Investigator Boller leads the rescue of a deer that was badly injured after running through an office glass window. And, an angry owner wants to keep his six dogs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-17 23:00:00" d="2020-04-18 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>When a litter of puppies are dropped off at Villalobos, Tia and M2 turn to social media to get them adopted. Plus, Mariah and Lizzy struggle to catch a stray</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 00:00:00" d="2020-04-18 01:00:00"><n>Mountain Monsters</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buck is forced to reveal his actions to the rest of the AIMS team. Later, he searches for the Little Girl who seems to be the key to the mystery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 01:00:00" d="2020-04-18 02:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Phoenix</n><t>D</t>    <k>Investigator Mark rescues a dog with open wounds from a crate and the Phoenix Fire Department try to reach a cat stuck 40ft up a palm tree in fierce winds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 02:00:00" d="2020-04-18 03:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>After a string of bad luck with some of the parolees, Tia hopes newbie Richard will prove to be a valuable asset. Plus, the team rushes to save a mutilated pup</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 03:00:00" d="2020-04-18 03:50:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Chief Investigator Boller leads the rescue of a deer that was badly injured after running through an office glass window. And, an angry owner wants to keep his six dogs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 03:50:00" d="2020-04-18 04:40:00"><n>Wild Mexico</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mexico is an ancient land, full of diversity and mystery. It is home to a vast wilderness of oceans, deserts, jungle, and unique creatures that are found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 04:40:00" d="2020-04-18 06:00:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animals can do extraordinary things – but how do they do it? Experts spill the secrets of the animal kingdom with amazing footage and surprising facts</k>  </p>
</a>
