<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2020-04-14 04:24:58"><p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 05:10:00" d="2020-04-21 06:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Frankie the cat pees all over Daniel and Desiree's new multi-million dollar dream home. Plus, cat Sugar is hiding from newly adopted cat Dyna</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 06:00:00" d="2020-04-21 07:00:00"><n>America's Cutest Pets</n><t>D</t>    <k>How do cats squeeze into tight spaces, why do they make odd friends, what is the secret to their agility, and which is the cutest of them all?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 07:00:00" d="2020-04-21 08:00:00"><n>America's Cutest Pets</n><t>D</t>    <k>Can kittens mimic their human friends, why do felines get stuck in sticky situations, do cats like babies, and which is the cutest cat of all?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 08:00:00" d="2020-04-21 09:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Hurricane season is approaching and Tia prepares for the worst. Later, Villalobos employee Rico steps up to the plate when his grandparents adopt a shy dog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 09:00:00" d="2020-04-21 10:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Hurricane Isaac tears through New Orleans, flooding Villalobos’ evacuation location and leaving Tia and her team cut off from the rest of the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 10:00:00" d="2020-04-21 10:30:00"><n>Meet The Penguins</n><t>D</t>    <k>The staff at the Sanccob Seabird Rescue Centre in Cape Town race against time to help a penguin contaminated by oil, and wannabe dad Winston takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 10:30:00" d="2020-04-21 11:00:00"><n>Meet The Penguins</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Centre’s grumpiest resident, Crabby, greets a new arrival that melts his icy heart, and Princess – queen of the resident penguins – faces the biggest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 11:00:00" d="2020-04-21 12:00:00"><n>Preposterous Pets</n><t>D</t>    <k>On the West Coast of America, a young woman is living the night life with a pair of tamandua anteaters. Elsewhere, a family shares their home with hippos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 12:00:00" d="2020-04-21 13:00:00"><n>Crikey! It's The Irwins</n><t>D</t>    <k>Love is in the air at Australia Zoo! Terri helps determine if Caballe the Rhino is pregnant, while Robert matchmakes the zoo's Aldabra giant tortoises</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 13:00:00" d="2020-04-21 14:00:00"><n>The Bronx Zoo</n><t>D</t>    <k>Keepers help out 14-year-old Dave, a kangaroo suffering with arthritis. Plus, the keepers struggle to keep critically endangered Indian gharial from fighting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 14:00:00" d="2020-04-21 14:30:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That</n><t>D</t>    <k>Do parrots really know what they’re talking about? How do electric eels not electrocute themselves? Plus, why are panda’s black and white? Experts answer these questions!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 14:30:00" d="2020-04-21 15:00:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>Experts examine footage of crows leaving gifts in Seattle. Plus, could a shark really be older than America? And, what is making crop circles in the sea?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 15:00:00" d="2020-04-21 16:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>After 25 years in a tiny clinic, the team is moving to a new clinic with twice the space. When Dr. Jeff repairs a dog's knee, he makes a special connection with her owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 16:00:00" d="2020-04-21 17:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Jeff heads out to a wild animal sanctuary to help an injured tiger. Meanwhile, Dr. Amy tackles exploratory surgery on a cat with a strange appetite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 17:00:00" d="2020-04-21 18:00:00"><n>Orphans Of A Fading Forest</n><t>D</t>    <k>Liza Gadsby and Peter Jenkins have dedicated their lives to save six species of monkeys - all of whom pushed close to extinction by the pressure of the 'bushmeat trade'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 18:00:00" d="2020-04-21 19:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>74% Chris heads to Victoria to try and trim the tusks of 220 kilo pig called Burpy, tries to keep a three-legged cow on its feet, and treats a very dizzy doggy called Bello</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 19:00:00" d="2020-04-21 20:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Phoenix</n><t>D</t>    <k>The AHS Field Dispatch Team gets 200 calls daily for animals needing help. A dog and her nine puppies need rescuing from a storm drain before the rain arrives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 20:00:00" d="2020-04-21 21:00:00"><n>The Zoo: San Diego</n><t>D</t>    <k>Two influential zoos in San Diego provide a unique look at their animals, keepers and veterinarians and explain the unique projects that help fund the organisations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 21:00:00" d="2020-04-21 22:00:00"><n>The Aquarium</n><t>D</t>    <k>Nandi, the aquarium’s smallest manta ray, is due her annual checkup and some young ruddy ducks arrive at the aquarium and are introduced to their new habitat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 22:00:00" d="2020-04-21 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>SPCA investigators seize a horse with a horrific leg injury. Emotions run high as they fight to save the animal and bring the owner to justice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 23:00:00" d="2020-04-22 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>When an aggressive dog is in danger of being put down, Tia heads to South Carolina to save him. Plus, parolee Toney Converse takes on more responsibility</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-22 00:00:00" d="2020-04-22 01:00:00"><n>Mountain Monsters</n><t>D</t>    <k>The AIMS team hunts down a monstrous wolf-like creature that is lurking in the cornfields of Jackson County, West Virginia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-22 01:00:00" d="2020-04-22 02:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Phoenix</n><t>D</t>    <k>The AHS Field Dispatch Team gets 200 calls daily for animals needing help. A dog and her nine puppies need rescuing from a storm drain before the rain arrives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-22 02:00:00" d="2020-04-22 03:00:00"><n>The Zoo: San Diego</n><t>D</t>    <k>Two influential zoos in San Diego provide a unique look at their animals, keepers and veterinarians and explain the unique projects that help fund the organisations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-22 03:00:00" d="2020-04-22 03:50:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>SPCA investigators seize a horse with a horrific leg injury. Emotions run high as they fight to save the animal and bring the owner to justice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-22 03:50:00" d="2020-04-22 04:40:00"><n>Orphans Of A Fading Forest</n><t>D</t>    <k>Liza Gadsby and Peter Jenkins have dedicated their lives to save six species of monkeys - all of whom pushed close to extinction by the pressure of the 'bushmeat trade'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-22 04:40:00" d="2020-04-22 05:10:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why are cows always chewing? Do rhinos have a sensitive side and what’s the loudest animal on earth? Plus, why do rattlesnakes release their prey?</k>  </p>
</a>
