<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2020-04-11 04:26:02"><p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 06:00:00" d="2020-04-18 06:30:00"><n>Meet The Orangutans</n><t>D</t>    <k>Follow the lives of orphaned orangutan babies as they are brought to the world’s oldest orangutan sanctuary in Borneo. Toddlers are wheel-barrowed in for lessons in life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 06:30:00" d="2020-04-18 07:00:00"><n>Meet The Orangutans</n><t>D</t>    <k>One orphan is new on the scene, and needs another, more experienced one to help them bed in. The babies are at high risk from parasites ingested from the ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 07:00:00" d="2020-04-18 07:30:00"><n>Meet The Orangutans</n><t>D</t>    <k>The orphaned orangutan Peanut is one of the newest and youngest arrivals at the sanctuary. He has made friends with Beryl, but he is not feeling very well</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 07:30:00" d="2020-04-18 08:00:00"><n>ACE: Animal Countdown Extraordinaire</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jack Yabsley and the HMS Buccaneer count down the ten stinkiest animal on the planet. With their ‘Stinkometer-4000’ they’ll analyse animal aromas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 08:00:00" d="2020-04-18 08:30:00"><n>ACE: Animal Countdown Extraordinaire</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jack and the Buccaneer count down the top ten ‘bites’ of the animal world. They’ll calculate each animals jaw strength to rank the best</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 08:30:00" d="2020-04-18 09:00:00"><n>ACE: Animal Countdown Extraordinaire</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jack and Buck compare the world’s top ten wackiest animal racers with human sprinters. Could a monkey outrun the world’s fastest man?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 09:00:00" d="2020-04-18 10:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Phoenix</n><t>D</t>    <k>As temperatures reach over 110 degrees, medical technician Stacie Dabolt is called in to rescue two dogs trapped in the glare of the midday sun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 10:00:00" d="2020-04-18 11:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Phoenix</n><t>D</t>    <k>The team makes a dramatic rescue when a spaniel gets trapped underground. Plus, a challenging situation arises when a dog and her pups are attacked by bees</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 11:00:00" d="2020-04-18 12:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Phoenix</n><t>D</t>    <k>It's a race against time as an AHS team battle to save a kitten trapped in a maze of underground pipes. A dog with a fatal injury is the centre of a shocking case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 12:00:00" d="2020-04-18 13:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>A puppy is rescued from a kill shelter in Oklahoma. And a dog eats a box of toxic chocolates infused with marijuana, and is rushed to the clinic for treatment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 13:00:00" d="2020-04-18 14:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr Jeff races to save the legs of a puppy who has been hit by a car. And newly hired exotic pet vet, Dr Baier, treats a Burmese python that is losing weight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 14:00:00" d="2020-04-18 15:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>With thousands of animals in need, and vet care unaffordable to most, Dr Jeff heads to Mexico to run a mobile clinic and help as many people and pets as they can</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 15:00:00" d="2020-04-18 16:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr Jeff fights to save a bearded dragon which is having a seizure, and Dr Amy is put to the test when a routine cat neuter turns complicated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 16:00:00" d="2020-04-18 17:00:00"><n>Coyote Peterson: Return To The Wilderness</n><t>D</t>    <k>Coyote Peterson and his crew plunge deep on a dangerous journey into the Costa Rican rainforest where they find Central America’s most lethal pit viper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 17:00:00" d="2020-04-18 18:00:00"><n>Coyote Peterson: Brave The Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>Coyote heads to Texas in search of a rumoured giant snapping turtle. He is determined to prove that this turtle is the largest living creature of his kind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 18:00:00" d="2020-04-18 18:30:00"><n>Coyote Peterson: Brave The Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>Coyote heads to Brazil to encounter the Yacare Caiman. As he swims alongside them in piranha-infested waterways, he studies their perfect-predator personality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 18:30:00" d="2020-04-18 19:00:00"><n>Coyote Peterson: Brave The Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>Capturing big cats on film is a near-impossible task, but Coyote demonstrates how with technology nature enthusiasts can see predators like jaguars up close</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 19:00:00" d="2020-04-18 19:30:00"><n>Coyote Peterson: Brave The Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animal expert Coyote Peterson navigates the turbulent waters of Australia’s tidepools at night to find and get close to the elusive wobbegong sharks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 19:30:00" d="2020-04-18 20:00:00"><n>Coyote Peterson: Brave The Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animal expert Coyote Peterson explores the inner tidepools along Australia’s Sunshine Coast to find and get close to its venomous marine creatures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 20:00:00" d="2020-04-18 21:00:00"><n>Big Cat Tales</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jackson observes a group of five cheetahs cooperatively hunting. Meanwhile, Jonathan witnesses a spectacular river crossing of thousands of wildebeest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 21:00:00" d="2020-04-18 22:00:00"><n>Wildest Islands Of Indonesia</n><t>D</t>    <k>Indonesia is home to more active volcanoes than any other country on earth. How has the wildlife here uniquely adapted to the specific demands of life in the furnace?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 22:00:00" d="2020-04-18 23:00:00"><n>In Search Of Monsters</n><t>D</t>    <k>New evidence reveals a Vietnam War pilot may have returned home with a secret cargo. Experts use this to try and find the missing link in human evolution</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-18 23:00:00" d="2020-04-19 00:00:00"><n>Finding Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>40% The team is back to Louisiana to investigate a photo of a possible Sasquatch. With the help of a local drum line, they hope to lure the beast of the bayou</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 00:00:00" d="2020-04-19 01:00:00"><n>Finding Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>40% The team travels to the Blue Mountains to meet with local anthropologist Professor Jeff Meldrum who discovered the tracks of a possible Bigfoot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 01:00:00" d="2020-04-19 02:00:00"><n>Finding Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>40% The team travels to Bobo's backyard to investigate photos of a possible Bigfoot among the Redwoods. Will using heavy metal vocals work as bait?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 02:00:00" d="2020-04-19 03:00:00"><n>Finding Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>40% Four eccentric but passionate Bigfoot enthusiasts embark on one single-minded mission: to find the elusive &quot;creature&quot; known as Bigfoot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 03:00:00" d="2020-04-19 03:50:00"><n>Finding Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>40% The team travels to Nepal in search of the infamous Yeti. They visit monasteries to examine relics and travel into the dense forests of the Himalayas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 03:50:00" d="2020-04-19 04:40:00"><n>Finding Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>40% The team travels to Idaho, and after sending a scout team of researchers ahead of the group, they split into teams and disperse across the state</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-19 04:40:00" d="2020-04-19 05:10:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animals can do extraordinary things – but how do they do it? Experts spill the secrets of the animal kingdom with amazing footage and surprising facts</k>  </p>
</a>
