<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2020-05-12 04:28:16"><p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-19 05:10:00" d="2020-05-19 06:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Jackson enters Ellen's world, one that's crawling with neighbourhood feral cats, who she's been feeding and trying to contain virtually by herself for 20 years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-19 06:00:00" d="2020-05-19 07:00:00"><n>Must Love Cats</n><t>D</t>    <k>John is on the prowl to find the coolest cats on the US west coast. While in LA, he samples a cuppa made from coffee beans scooped out of cat poo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-19 07:00:00" d="2020-05-19 08:00:00"><n>Must Love Cats</n><t>D</t>    <k>Host John Fulton heads to America's southwest to meet felines with frontier flair. Plus, he learns everything is bigger in Texas, even the cats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-19 08:00:00" d="2020-05-19 09:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>A vicious swarm of bees returns to the dog sanctuary with a vengeance. Plus, will Tia manage to house an old and arthritic mastiff, abandoned by his owners?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-19 09:00:00" d="2020-05-19 10:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>In Tuscaloosa a young boy has to give up his pit bull after a tornado destroys his home, and Tia is inspired to help local rescuers rebuild their kennels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-19 10:00:00" d="2020-05-19 11:00:00"><n u="Dogs">Dogs 101</n><t>D</t>    <k>A dog encyclopaedia, with the Australian Cattle Dog, Saluki, Norwich Terrier, Boykin Spaniel, Wonder Dog, Bull Terrier, and Cardigan Welsh Corgi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-19 11:00:00" d="2020-05-19 12:00:00"><n u="Dogs">Dogs 101</n><t>D</t>    <k>Learn which pets are best for urban living and which ones are family friendly through a mix of experts, live-action footage and photography</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-19 12:00:00" d="2020-05-19 13:00:00"><n>Safari Park Adventure</n><t>D</t>    <k>Pregnant elephant Damini undergoes a scan to check on the health of her calf. Plus bull rhino Kei is finally let loose onto the African plain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-19 13:00:00" d="2020-05-19 14:00:00"><n>The Zoo</n><t>D</t>    <k>Willow, a young red panda, is having mysterious foot problems. And, the bird department anxiously awaits the gender reveal of two new adjutant stork chicks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-19 14:00:00" d="2020-05-19 14:30:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>Experts explain why some spiders dance and what is the weird, bubbling foam engulfing a whole town? Plus, what mysterious creature is preying on Europe’s sheep?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-19 14:30:00" d="2020-05-19 15:00:00"><n>Little Giants</n><t>D</t>    <k>The team is in Madagascar to study the recently-discovered Goodman's mouse lemur. One of the world’s smallest primates, it’s incredible agile and ferocious</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-19 15:00:00" d="2020-05-19 16:00:00"><n>Amanda To The Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>Amanda Giese and her family and friends tackle and treat the most hopeless cases within her in-home animal rehab and rescue in rural Washington</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-19 16:00:00" d="2020-05-19 17:00:00"><n>Amanda To The Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>Amanda Giese and her family and friends tackle and treat the most hopeless cases within her in-home animal rehab and rescue in rural Washington</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-19 17:00:00" d="2020-05-19 18:00:00"><n>Finding Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>40% The team travel to Rhode Island to examine video of a roadside sighting of a Bigfoot. Could this small state turn out to be a prime location for Sasquatch activity?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-19 18:00:00" d="2020-05-19 19:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet: Coast To Coast</n><t>D</t>    <k>74% Dr. Kate investigates why a rabbit has stopped eating. Plus, a sausage dog receives experimental treatment and Dr. Peter helps a monkey with suspected tuberculosis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-19 19:00:00" d="2020-05-19 20:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>A woman is forced to face the facts about the high number of cats that she shares her residence with. Meanwhile, a dog owner is turning a blind eye to his pet’s suffering</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-19 20:00:00" d="2020-05-19 21:00:00"><n>The Zoo</n><t>D</t>    <k>A trio of abandoned puma cubs arrives at the zoo. Meanwhile, a Caribbean flamingo is born at the zoo after nearly 20 years, and Otto the stallion makes his debut</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-19 21:00:00" d="2020-05-19 22:00:00"><n>Crikey! It's The Irwins</n><t>D</t>    <k>Hunter the tiger is being sedated for his annual eye check, allowing Terri to get close. Bindi puts on a birthday party for Minibus - the Zoo's oldest Wombat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-19 22:00:00" d="2020-05-19 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Investigators seize seven horses from a negligent owner who's left them in a filthy, waterlogged field. However, the horses show no inclination to leave peacefully</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-19 23:00:00" d="2020-05-20 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia heads to a dangerous part of New Orleans to rescue a mama dog left to die. And, a tropical storm threatens to disrupt Tania and Perry's wedding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-20 00:00:00" d="2020-05-20 01:00:00"><n>I'm Alive</n><t>D</t>    <k>67% Follow extraordinary tales of survival. After being bitten by a black widow, Mike fights for life. Can he be saved using an illegal antivenom smuggled into the US?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-20 01:00:00" d="2020-05-20 02:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>A woman is forced to face the facts about the high number of cats that she shares her residence with. Meanwhile, a dog owner is turning a blind eye to his pet’s suffering</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-20 02:00:00" d="2020-05-20 03:00:00"><n>The Zoo</n><t>D</t>    <k>A trio of abandoned puma cubs arrives at the zoo. Meanwhile, a Caribbean flamingo is born at the zoo after nearly 20 years, and Otto the stallion makes his debut</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-20 03:00:00" d="2020-05-20 03:50:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Investigators seize seven horses from a negligent owner who's left them in a filthy, waterlogged field. However, the horses show no inclination to leave peacefully</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-20 03:50:00" d="2020-05-20 04:40:00"><n>Finding Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>40% The team travel to Rhode Island to examine video of a roadside sighting of a Bigfoot. Could this small state turn out to be a prime location for Sasquatch activity?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-20 04:40:00" d="2020-05-20 05:10:00"><n>Escape To Chimp Eden</n><t>D</t>    <k>85% Chimp Eden director Eugene must act as the alpha male to teach the new chimps how to forage, climb and interact after a lifetime in captivity</k>  </p>
</a>
