<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2020-04-16 04:26:38"><p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-23 05:10:00" d="2020-04-23 06:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Stanley and Shelby are ferocious when they are together, so who will their owners have guests around? Plus, Finn has a habit of jumping in the babies’ crib</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-23 06:00:00" d="2020-04-23 07:00:00"><n>America's Cutest Pets</n><t>D</t>    <k>How do dogs guard human babies, what makes mutts so athletic, why do some pooches bark more than others, and which is the cutest dog of all?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-23 07:00:00" d="2020-04-23 08:00:00"><n>America's Cutest Pets</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why do dogs make great friends, which puppies make the most playful pets, what breeds are the most mischievous, and which is the cutest dog of all?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-23 08:00:00" d="2020-04-23 09:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Earl returns from rehab, hoping to rebuild his life working with the dogs. Plus, Lizzy rescues a dog after a confrontation with the owner who abandoned it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-23 09:00:00" d="2020-04-23 10:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>A woman travels from San Diego to offer one of Villalobos' senior dogs a home. Meanwhile, Lizzy and Marcel search for a mama dog's lost puppies out in the country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-23 10:00:00" d="2020-04-23 10:30:00"><n>Meet The Penguins</n><t>D</t>    <k>Amputee Cedric’s happy marriage to wife Robin faces its biggest challenge, Squeaker the juvenile tests people’s patience and a wild penguin comes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-23 10:30:00" d="2020-04-23 11:00:00"><n>Meet The Penguins</n><t>D</t>    <k>A wild penguin receives treatment for a life-or-death wound, two home-pen inhabitants get into a nasty fight and one of the long-term residents celebrates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-23 11:00:00" d="2020-04-23 12:00:00"><n>Preposterous Pets</n><t>D</t>    <k>Meet the lizard obsessive who changed his name to Mr Lizard Lover and found fame taking photos of his scaly friends posing as humans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-23 12:00:00" d="2020-04-23 13:00:00"><n>Crikey! It's The Irwins</n><t>D</t>    <k>Terri attends the exam of Charlie the tiger to see if his tumours were successfully treated. And, Bindi helps develop a vaccine for Eden the Tasmanian Devil</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-23 13:00:00" d="2020-04-23 14:00:00"><n>The Bronx Zoo</n><t>D</t>    <k>A female slow loris has weight problems that stop her from becoming pregnant. Keepers take the penguin colony for a CT scan and an ocopy has pain in his hooves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-23 14:00:00" d="2020-04-23 14:30:00"><n>Coyote Peterson: Brave The Wild</n><t>D</t>    <k>Coyote heads to Australia and reveals the history behind the critically endangered Tasmanian devil. He discovers the manpower needed to conserve this species</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-23 14:30:00" d="2020-04-23 15:00:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animals can do extraordinary things – but how do they do it? Experts spill the secrets of the animal kingdom with amazing footage and surprising facts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-23 15:00:00" d="2020-04-23 16:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>When an Eskimo dog arrives with a broken jaw Dr Jeff must uncover the cause. Plus, Dr Nichols and Dr Jeff have their hands full treating some uncooperative yaks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-23 16:00:00" d="2020-04-23 17:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr Jeff and Dr Petra work together to save a beloved pet husky’s leg. Meanwhile, specialist Dr Baier has a scare during a routine treatment of pet pig Strawberry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-23 17:00:00" d="2020-04-23 18:00:00"><n>The Zoo: San Diego</n><t>D</t>    <k>A baby klipspringer is born on one of the coldest nights of the season and needs to be nursed back to health. Plus, gorilla Joanne turns five years old</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-23 18:00:00" d="2020-04-23 19:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>74% Chris is called to Cairns Rainforest Station Nature Park to check on the broken jaw of Agro the crocodile, who has managed to kill all nine of the other crocs in his pond</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-23 19:00:00" d="2020-04-23 20:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Phoenix</n><t>D</t>    <k>Investigators Andy and Jeana help a skunk and cat trapped together in a storm drain. Officer Kelley finds a snake dumped on a golf course – with a horrific injury</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-23 20:00:00" d="2020-04-23 21:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Jeff has been helping pets around the world for 30 years. He remembers some of the most special, inspiring and important cases he has taken on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-23 21:00:00" d="2020-04-23 22:00:00"><n>The Vet Life</n><t>D</t>    <k>The vets make a house call to a llama that's causing some drama. Dr. Ross extracts 14 teeth from a mini poodle, and Dr. Blue introduces his baby girl to the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-23 22:00:00" d="2020-04-23 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Investigator Deborah Turner battles to save puppies trapped in a church drain. Sadly in a different case Houston SPCA inspectors arrive too late to save another dog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-23 23:00:00" d="2020-04-24 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Moe and Lizzy reveal they are expecting a child and the family band together to host a gender party. Plus, Lizzy goes the extra mile for her favourite dog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-24 00:00:00" d="2020-04-24 01:00:00"><n>Mountain Monsters</n><t>D</t>    <k>AIMS looks for a big bear-like creature known as the Silver Giant and build their largest trap ever. Plus, they learn about other beasts there too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-24 01:00:00" d="2020-04-24 02:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Phoenix</n><t>D</t>    <k>Investigators Andy and Jeana help a skunk and cat trapped together in a storm drain. Officer Kelley finds a snake dumped on a golf course – with a horrific injury</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-24 02:00:00" d="2020-04-24 03:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Jeff has been helping pets around the world for 30 years. He remembers some of the most special, inspiring and important cases he has taken on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-24 03:00:00" d="2020-04-24 03:50:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Investigator Deborah Turner battles to save puppies trapped in a church drain. Sadly in a different case Houston SPCA inspectors arrive too late to save another dog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-24 03:50:00" d="2020-04-24 04:40:00"><n>The Zoo: San Diego</n><t>D</t>    <k>A baby klipspringer is born on one of the coldest nights of the season and needs to be nursed back to health. Plus, gorilla Joanne turns five years old</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-24 04:40:00" d="2020-04-24 05:10:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why do sloths turn green? How do sea turtles navigate their way home? Plus, how do diving beetles spend so long underwater?</k>  </p>
</a>
