<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2019-08-15 22:22:40"><p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 05:10:00" d="2019-08-20 06:00:00"><n>Tanked</n><t>D</t>    <k>67% World champion boxer, Fernando Vargas, asks ATM to make a boxing glove-shaped tank for his boxing gym in Las Vegas. Can they deliver a knockout?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 06:00:00" d="2019-08-20 06:30:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% A tiny terrier is savaged by a bigger dog, and a police Alsatian is struck down by a mystery fever. Plus, will a Shar Pei’s eyelid operation be successful?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 06:30:00" d="2019-08-20 07:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% A Puggle who hates his paws being petted has his claws clipped, and a breeding mare gives birth to a foal. Plus, can Buddy the boxer survive an acute allergic reaction?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 07:00:00" d="2019-08-20 07:30:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% Chris has a traumatic night when Bella the pug is rushed into the Bondi clinic. She's in labour and needs an emergency caesarean. Can the team save her and the babies?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 07:30:00" d="2019-08-20 08:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% When Bruno the terrier is accidentally run over by his remorseful owner, his shattered back leg needs surgery. But things look bleak when he is diagnosed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 08:00:00" d="2019-08-20 09:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Houston SPCA's Chief Investigator Charles Jantzen joins his team on an emergency mission in Galveston to try to save hundreds of trapped and abandoned pets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 09:00:00" d="2019-08-20 10:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Chief Investigator Charles Jantzen and Investigator Debbie Michielson rescue a pack of dogs on the brink of turning feral from a deceased owner's property</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 10:00:00" d="2019-08-20 11:00:00"><n>Crocodile Hunter</n><t>D</t>    <k>This is a thought-provoking look at why many animals have escaped into the bush to become environmental menaces and, worse still, killers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 11:00:00" d="2019-08-20 12:00:00"><n>Alaska: The Last Frontier</n><t>D</t>    <k>Otto must move the outhouse due to frozen soil. Eivin takes Eve on her first deer-hunt on Afognak Island and Atz and sons gather trees for a big new project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 12:00:00" d="2019-08-20 13:00:00"><n>Wild Mexico</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mexico is an ancient land, full of diversity and mystery. It is home to a vast wilderness of oceans, deserts, jungle, and unique creatures that are found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 13:00:00" d="2019-08-20 13:30:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% A tiny terrier is savaged by a bigger dog, and a police Alsatian is struck down by a mystery fever. Plus, will a Shar Pei’s eyelid operation be successful?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 13:30:00" d="2019-08-20 14:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% A Puggle who hates his paws being petted has his claws clipped, and a breeding mare gives birth to a foal. Plus, can Buddy the boxer survive an acute allergic reaction?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 14:00:00" d="2019-08-20 14:30:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% Chris has a traumatic night when Bella the pug is rushed into the Bondi clinic. She's in labour and needs an emergency caesarean. Can the team save her and the babies?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 14:30:00" d="2019-08-20 15:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% When Bruno the terrier is accidentally run over by his remorseful owner, his shattered back leg needs surgery. But things look bleak when he is diagnosed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 15:00:00" d="2019-08-20 16:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>80% Tia must deal with a wayward pit bull, leaving the owner grappling with a heart wrenching life or death decision. Plus, a straight forward adoption turns nasty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 16:00:00" d="2019-08-20 17:00:00"><n>Treehouse Masters</n><t>D</t>    <k>Treehouse visionary Alain Laurens joins Pete on his travels through France, where he shares his fantastical structures that redefine what a treehouse can be!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 17:00:00" d="2019-08-20 18:00:00"><n>Amanda To The Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>Amanda rescues three dogs with special needs from the California wildfires, including a very pregnant Chihuahua that could give birth at any moment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 18:00:00" d="2019-08-20 19:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% Chris makes a discovery on a miniature goat that horrifies its owner. Later, Chris takes a daring dive to save an endangered shark species while Lisa tries to save a dog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 19:00:00" d="2019-08-20 20:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>When Tia is touched by a heartfelt adoption application from a former prisoner turned martial arts fighter, she sends Tania and Mariah on an adoption road trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 20:00:00" d="2019-08-20 21:00:00"><n>The Aquarium</n><t>D</t>    <k>A curious and active box turtle goes for his daily walk and two wobbegong sharks are due for a check-up. Plus, the staff prepare for puffin breeding season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 21:00:00" d="2019-08-20 22:00:00"><n>Alaska: The Last Frontier</n><t>D</t>    <k>Otto pulls porcupine quills out of a colt's face. Eve has conflicting thoughts about deer hunting and Atz gives Jane a lesson in rabbit skinning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 22:00:00" d="2019-08-20 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animal control officers have been removing cats from an apartment where a woman has recently been evicted. Some of the animals are in bad shape and need help urgently</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-20 23:00:00" d="2019-08-21 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>80% Tia hopes she has found a home for Latwanda, a badly abused dog, but is this pit bull ready to leave? Plus, funny-man Brian annoys everyone when he slacks off</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 00:00:00" d="2019-08-21 01:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>80% Mariah rescues kittens, and a mother with puppies, from a fetid abandoned home. Plus, it’s time to take a tough decision when Sloth’s health deteriorates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 01:00:00" d="2019-08-21 02:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animal control officers have been removing cats from an apartment where a woman has recently been evicted. Some of the animals are in bad shape and need help urgently</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 02:00:00" d="2019-08-21 03:00:00"><n>Wildest Europe</n><t>D</t>    <k>Explores the wildlife of Northern Europe’s frozen frontier, from the golden eagle in Scotland’s Cairngorms to the polar bears of Norway’s Svalbard Archipelago</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 03:00:00" d="2019-08-21 03:50:00"><n>Alaska: The Last Frontier</n><t>D</t>    <k>Otto pulls porcupine quills out of a colt's face. Eve has conflicting thoughts about deer hunting and Atz gives Jane a lesson in rabbit skinning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 03:50:00" d="2019-08-21 04:40:00"><n>Alaska Monsters</n><t>D</t>    <k>38% The team heads deep into the Alaskan Interior outside of Fairbanks to investigate reports of a gigantic bear-like creature known as the Northern Giant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 04:40:00" d="2019-08-21 05:10:00"><n>Orangutan Island</n><t>D</t>    <k>81% Illness is raging on the island, and as a result Donald has to be attended by staff. If the contagion continues it threatens the future of the project</k>  </p>
</a>
