<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2020-05-15 04:34:36"><p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 05:10:00" d="2020-05-22 06:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% In a show first, Jackson helps a cat - who can't get along in its rescue home - to move in with a foster family who he’s hopeful will adopt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 06:00:00" d="2020-05-22 07:00:00"><n>Bad Dog!</n><t>D</t>    <k>From a beagle that irritates a family by digging under the house, to a cat burglar that steals fish from the freezer, how far can pets push their owners?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 07:00:00" d="2020-05-22 08:00:00"><n>Bad Dog!</n><t>D</t>    <k>More misbehaving pets including a cat that swats alligators back into the swamp, a dog that steals coffee and a monkey that rides the family dog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 08:00:00" d="2020-05-22 09:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>80% Mariah rescues kittens, and a mother with puppies, from a fetid abandoned home. Plus, it’s time to take a tough decision when Sloth’s health deteriorates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 09:00:00" d="2020-05-22 10:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>80% Tia heads to Georgia to evaluate a prison dog program, and joins their team on a shocking rescue mission. Plus, could a surprise inspection close Villalobos down?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 10:00:00" d="2020-05-22 11:00:00"><n u="Cats">Cats 101</n><t>D</t>    <k>80% Meet the cat that can help those who suffer from cat allergens and the world's rarest breed of feline. Plus, which cat's personality depends on their fur colour?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 11:00:00" d="2020-05-22 12:00:00"><n>Cat Vs Dog</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jackson and Zoe meet Tami. Her three dogs terrorise her cats, Esmeralda Beyonce and Cozy Cosette, so she built a rooftop cat sanctuary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 12:00:00" d="2020-05-22 12:30:00"><n>ACE: Animal Countdown Extraordinaire</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jack and Buck serve up foul feasts in their search for the top ten animals with the most disgusting diets. Which food is most foul?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 12:30:00" d="2020-05-22 13:00:00"><n>ACE: Animal Countdown Extraordinaire</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jack and the Buccaneer strap in for danger as they count down the world’s top ten animal thrill-seekers. Featuring a bird that juggles fire with its beak!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 13:00:00" d="2020-05-22 14:00:00"><n>The Zoo: San Diego</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Safari Park team release a group of burrowing owls into the wild. Plus, a hamadryas baboon searches for a mate, but the keepers may need to help him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 14:00:00" d="2020-05-22 14:30:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>Experts explain where to find an enchanted underwater forest. Plus, why have some rattlesnakes on a remote Mexican island lost their rattle?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 14:30:00" d="2020-05-22 15:00:00"><n>Little Giants</n><t>D</t>    <k>In Thailand, the team track down one of the few venomous mammals in the world. With incredible agility, the Thai musk shrew is a force to be reckoned with</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 15:00:00" d="2020-05-22 16:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Jeff helps a dog with a serious illness. Mel and her daughter rescue a baby squirrel, while Dr. Jeff and Dr. Petra team up to save a beloved cat hit by a car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 16:00:00" d="2020-05-22 17:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Jeff treats a skittish Savannah cat with an unusual condition. And, the team races to save a stray dog as it runs toward the freeway</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 17:00:00" d="2020-05-22 18:00:00"><n>Finding Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>The team travels to Kentucky to investigate footage of glowing eyes that could belong to a Bigfoot. Can they lure the mysterious beast out of hiding?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 18:00:00" d="2020-05-22 19:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet: Coast To Coast</n><t>D</t>    <k>74% Dr. Lewis tries to solve a mysterious condition on a dog. Plus, at Perth Zoo Dr. Peter looks after an elephant and Dr. Danni helps a dog with a suspected twisted stomach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 19:00:00" d="2020-05-22 20:00:00"><n>Animal Cops San Francisco</n><t>D</t>    <k>Lieutenant Scott uncovers an illegal cache of constrictor snakes; is their owner trading these deadly predators? Plus, an abused dog fights for life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 20:00:00" d="2020-05-22 21:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>The rescue team begin Operation Rhino, hoping to place a long-term shelter resident in a fantastic home. Plus, two dogs need rescuing in the French Quarter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 21:00:00" d="2020-05-22 22:00:00"><n>Amanda To The Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>A miniature schnauzer with a suspected liver shunt needs complicated and costly surgery. Plus, Amanda prepares a blind puppy for his new home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 22:00:00" d="2020-05-22 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Rescuers are called in when cat hoarding brings mayhem to a million-dollar mansion. Plus, a shocking case of neglect is reported</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 23:00:00" d="2020-05-23 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Pit bull trainer Tia Maria Torres continues on her quest to challenge the misconceptions associated with pit bulls at her Villalobos Rescue Centre</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-23 00:00:00" d="2020-05-23 01:00:00"><n>I'm Alive</n><t>D</t>    <k>67% Deep in the woods a sheriff is bitten by a rattlesnake and in Hawaii a diver is impaled by crocodile needlefish in the chest. Both are miles from help, will they survive?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-23 01:00:00" d="2020-05-23 02:00:00"><n>Animal Cops San Francisco</n><t>D</t>    <k>Lieutenant Scott uncovers an illegal cache of constrictor snakes; is their owner trading these deadly predators? Plus, an abused dog fights for life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-23 02:00:00" d="2020-05-23 03:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>The rescue team begin Operation Rhino, hoping to place a long-term shelter resident in a fantastic home. Plus, two dogs need rescuing in the French Quarter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-23 03:00:00" d="2020-05-23 03:50:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Rescuers are called in when cat hoarding brings mayhem to a million-dollar mansion. Plus, a shocking case of neglect is reported</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-23 03:50:00" d="2020-05-23 04:40:00"><n>Finding Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>The team travels to Kentucky to investigate footage of glowing eyes that could belong to a Bigfoot. Can they lure the mysterious beast out of hiding?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-23 04:40:00" d="2020-05-23 06:00:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>Experts analyse and explain home footage of a racoon that scales a skyscraper in Minnesota. Then, they answer why a duck has so many ducklings?</k>  </p>
</a>
