<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2021-07-09 06:28:08"><p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 05:00:00" d="2021-07-15 05:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 05:30:00" d="2021-07-15 06:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 06:00:00" d="2021-07-15 06:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 06:30:00" d="2021-07-15 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 07:00:00" d="2021-07-15 07:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 07:30:00" d="2021-07-15 08:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 08:00:00" d="2021-07-15 08:30:00"><n>Meet The Sloths</n><t>D</t>    <k>Meet The Sloths follows a year in the life of five slow-moving residents of the Aviarios Sloth Sanctuary, a sanctuary dedicated to saving orphaned or injured sloths</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 08:30:00" d="2021-07-15 09:00:00"><n>Meet The Sloths</n><t>D</t>    <k>An emergency rescue puts sanctuary vet, Marcello, on the spot, a love triangle leaves Bradypus, Samantha, in the doghouse and Becky puts sloth speed to the test</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 09:00:00" d="2021-07-15 10:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Reality star and retired model Adrianne Curry and her boyfriend, Todd, are living with Adrianne’s menacing Siamese cat, Billy Shears</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 10:00:00" d="2021-07-15 11:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Steev and Laura have been dating for seven years, but Steev’s cat Darkness is tearing them apart. Can Jackson ease their woes?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 11:00:00" d="2021-07-15 12:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>When a sinkhole threatens to swallow a nearby neighbourhood, Tia teams up with cat expert Jackson Galaxy to rescue dozens of cats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 12:00:00" d="2021-07-15 13:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>A family contacts Tia after seeing their dog rescued on a previous episode. Tia confronts Earl about his erratic behaviour, and Matt makes a life-changing decision</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 13:00:00" d="2021-07-15 14:00:00"><n>Scaled</n><t>D</t>    <k>The team must create a samurai-themed enclosure for two boa constrictors for the grand opening of Serpent Tattoo. Plus, Rachel faces her fear of snakes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 14:00:00" d="2021-07-15 15:00:00"><n>Crikey! It's The Irwins</n><t>D</t>    <k>Robert wrangles Western Diamondback rattlesnakes in Arizona for the first time using his dad’s techniques. Terri helps save some baby feathertail gliders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 15:00:00" d="2021-07-15 16:00:00"><n>Crikey! It's The Irwins</n><t>D</t>    <k>Bindi swims alongside whale sharks, assisting with research efforts on the world's largest fish. Robert works to save an echidna that's trapped under a fridge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 16:00:00" d="2021-07-15 17:00:00"><n>Homestead Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>74% There’s a nightmare in North Carolina. A couple’s ramshackle cabin has exposed wires in the shower livestock decimated by predators. Can the Raneys help?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 17:00:00" d="2021-07-15 18:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Investigators are called out after disturbing reports of a large number of dogs held captive in make-shift pens. Plus, Octavio Gonzales receives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 18:00:00" d="2021-07-15 19:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animal cruelty investigators join forces with Texas police officers in an attempt to smash one of the biggest dog fighting rings in US history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 19:00:00" d="2021-07-15 20:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>When investigators from the Houston SPCA respond to a call at a livery stable they find themselves in a life or death battle to save a severely neglected horse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 20:00:00" d="2021-07-15 21:00:00"><n>Dodo Heroes</n><t>D</t>    <k>Derrick Campana fits Jabu, an elephant with a life-threatening injury, the world’s first elephant orthotic leg brace in the hopes it will save his life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 21:00:00" d="2021-07-15 22:00:00"><n>Homestead Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>74% The Raneys arrives at a homestead threatened by heat, coyotes and even cows. Disaster strikes when Marty attempts to protect livestock with a massive build</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 22:00:00" d="2021-07-15 23:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Peggy is a ‘Real Housewife of Orange County’. Being a housewife, she's used to catfights, except she's now dealing with one involving her real cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 23:00:00" d="2021-07-16 00:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% When Justin gave his mum Bombadil, he had no idea the cat would be a gift from hell. Buddhists Tom and Pola lived in harmony until they adopted Percy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 00:00:00" d="2021-07-16 01:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia surprises her family, the parolees and every dog at the rescue with an extraordinary Christmas gift – but how can this giant present be something Villalobos can use?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 01:00:00" d="2021-07-16 02:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia gets a devastating injury, so her kids must help keep Villalobos running, and everyone must help catch an elusive dog in the middle of the night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 02:00:00" d="2021-07-16 03:00:00"><n>Monster Hammerhead</n><t>D</t>    <k>A team of shark experts head out on a dangerous trip to the Florida Keys to capture evidence of Old Hitler, a monster hammerhead shark rumoured to be up to 25 feet long</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 03:00:00" d="2021-07-16 03:50:00"><n>Monsters Inside Me</n><t>D</t>    <k>76% The lives of three families are turned upside down, a couples’ dream home is a living nightmare, and an insidious creature takes a man's spleen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 03:50:00" d="2021-07-16 04:40:00"><n>The Aquarium</n><t>D</t>    <k>Aquariums play a vital role in sea life conservation across the globe. Now, Georgia Aquarium is sharing the remarkable stories that unfold there every day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 04:40:00" d="2021-07-16 05:00:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That?</n><t>D</t>    <k>What are lions saying when they roar? Plus, what are leaf cutter ants doing with all the leaves they collect? Experts answer these questions and more!</k>  </p>
</a>
