<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2020-05-14 04:42:27"><p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-21 05:10:00" d="2020-05-21 06:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Jackson visits New York City to meet a father and son who’ve been taking care of a feral cat colony in their backyard and are desperately in need of help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-21 06:00:00" d="2020-05-21 07:00:00"><n>Must Love Cats</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% John heads to the birth place of the domestic shorthair cat. Plus, how many different breeds compete at CFA sponsored cat shows?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-21 07:00:00" d="2020-05-21 08:00:00"><n>Bad Dog!</n><t>D</t>    <k>Meet misbehaving pets, from a dog that latches onto his owner's clothing when she leaves for work, to three goats that use their owner's car as a rock climbing trail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-21 08:00:00" d="2020-05-21 09:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>80% It’s a race against time as Tia and the crew search for a mother pit bull and her puppies that have been dumped in the sweltering Mojave Desert; will they find them?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-21 09:00:00" d="2020-05-21 10:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>80% Tia hopes she has found a home for Latwanda, a badly abused dog, but is this pit bull ready to leave? Plus, funny-man Brian annoys everyone when he slacks off</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-21 10:00:00" d="2020-05-21 11:00:00"><n u="Cats">Cats 101</n><t>D</t>    <k>80% Meet the feline co-host of a popular talk radio show and discover which native island cat may have been the first to be domesticated by man</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-21 11:00:00" d="2020-05-21 12:00:00"><n u="Cats">Cats 101</n><t>D</t>    <k>80% Meet the cat with a sixth finger on each paw, find out which feline originates from a 125-degree desert and discover which breed was Julius Cesar's favourite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-21 12:00:00" d="2020-05-21 12:30:00"><n>ACE: Animal Countdown Extraordinaire</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jack and Buck compare the world’s top ten wackiest animal racers with human sprinters. Could a monkey outrun the world’s fastest man?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-21 12:30:00" d="2020-05-21 13:00:00"><n>ACE: Animal Countdown Extraordinaire</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jack and the HMS Buccaneer dive under the sea to discover the top ten most daring animal divers. The deeper the dive, the greater the danger!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-21 13:00:00" d="2020-05-21 14:00:00"><n>The Zoo: San Diego</n><t>D</t>    <k>A baby klipspringer is born on one of the coldest nights of the season and needs to be nursed back to health. Plus, gorilla Joanne turns five years old</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-21 14:00:00" d="2020-05-21 14:30:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>Narwhals are the unicorns of the sea, but what do they use their extraordinary tusks for? What animal has transformed Yellowstone? Experts explain it all!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-21 14:30:00" d="2020-05-21 15:00:00"><n>Little Giants</n><t>D</t>    <k>The rhinoceros beetle has one of the highest strength to bodyweight ratios on the planet. The team is in Thailand to test this beefy beetle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-21 15:00:00" d="2020-05-21 16:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Jeff treats a dog with a mysterious injury, while a neglected turtle needs a new home. Plus, the team falls in love with a litter of stray kittens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-21 16:00:00" d="2020-05-21 17:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Jeff and his team help a dog lost during a windstorm. Dr. Baier treats a small bird with a big personality. Susan rescues an abandoned paralysed dog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-21 17:00:00" d="2020-05-21 18:00:00"><n>Finding Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>40% The team visit Virginia to check out footage of a creature the locals have dubbed ‘The Beast of Gumhill’. Can they prove this elusive beast is real?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-21 18:00:00" d="2020-05-21 19:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet: Coast To Coast</n><t>D</t>    <k>74% Dr. Kate anxiously awaits her dog’s test results. Plus, Dr. Danni volunteers at a pop-up clinic and Dr. Alex has a house call check-up with a pig and her piglets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-21 19:00:00" d="2020-05-21 20:00:00"><n>Animal Cops San Francisco</n><t>D</t>    <k>Scott rescues a dehydrated pit bull puppy that has been left, muzzled and chained, in the back of a hot car. Will its owners be allowed to redeem their dog?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-21 20:00:00" d="2020-05-21 21:00:00"><n>Dr. Dee: Alaska Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Dee investigates a possible neurological problem in her own dog. A horse castration turns dangerous, and a potential case of animal neglect is not what it seems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-21 21:00:00" d="2020-05-21 22:00:00"><n>The Vet Life</n><t>D</t>    <k>The vets are faced with a pug who is struggling to breathe through narrowed nostrils and struggle as they deal with a small dog who seems to have a failing heart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-21 22:00:00" d="2020-05-21 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>The officers take control of 200 chickens that are being kept in inhumane temperatures exceeding 100 degrees. Plus, they uncover a house overrun by 50 rabbits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-21 23:00:00" d="2020-05-22 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Join the team for a very special holiday gathering to re-live the most surprising rescues and the most poignant adoptions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 00:00:00" d="2020-05-22 01:00:00"><n>I'm Alive</n><t>D</t>    <k>67% Follow extraordinary tales of survival. A mother watches helplessly as her teenager is mauled by three lions, and in Iraq, a soldier is stung by a scorpion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 01:00:00" d="2020-05-22 02:00:00"><n>Animal Cops San Francisco</n><t>D</t>    <k>Scott rescues a dehydrated pit bull puppy that has been left, muzzled and chained, in the back of a hot car. Will its owners be allowed to redeem their dog?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 02:00:00" d="2020-05-22 03:00:00"><n>Dr. Dee: Alaska Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Dee investigates a possible neurological problem in her own dog. A horse castration turns dangerous, and a potential case of animal neglect is not what it seems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 03:00:00" d="2020-05-22 03:50:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>The officers take control of 200 chickens that are being kept in inhumane temperatures exceeding 100 degrees. Plus, they uncover a house overrun by 50 rabbits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 03:50:00" d="2020-05-22 04:40:00"><n>Finding Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>40% The team visit Virginia to check out footage of a creature the locals have dubbed ‘The Beast of Gumhill’. Can they prove this elusive beast is real?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-05-22 04:40:00" d="2020-05-22 05:10:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>Experts analyse and explain home footage of a spider that sparkles. Then, they look at what animal could have killed the ocean’s best and most feared predator?</k>  </p>
</a>
