<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="28" t="2021-07-08 04:54:12"><p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-13 05:00:00" d="2021-07-13 05:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-13 05:30:00" d="2021-07-13 06:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-13 06:00:00" d="2021-07-13 06:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-13 06:30:00" d="2021-07-13 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-13 07:00:00" d="2021-07-13 07:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-13 07:30:00" d="2021-07-13 08:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-13 08:00:00" d="2021-07-13 09:00:00"><n>The Aquarium</n><t>D</t>    <k>A curious and active box turtle goes for his daily walk and two wobbegong sharks are due for a check-up. Plus, the staff prepare for puffin breeding season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-13 09:00:00" d="2021-07-13 10:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Jay has one lady in his life and that's his ferocious attack cat, Marley. Marley will tear apart anyone who crosses her path - including Jay</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-13 10:00:00" d="2021-07-13 11:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Jackson has his hands full with two cats; one who likes to bully and another who poops excessively. Plus, there’s another who is doing its best to ruin a dream home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-13 11:00:00" d="2021-07-13 12:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia and the team try nursing a severely malnourished dog back to health and a Hurricane Katrina survivor finally has a chance at a forever home, 10 years on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-13 12:00:00" d="2021-07-13 13:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>When a reputed dognapper dumps a dog at Villalobos, Mariah scrambles to find the owner. Plus, a new parolee realises he is in over his head</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-13 13:00:00" d="2021-07-13 14:00:00"><n>Scaled</n><t>D</t>    <k>In Washington State, Greg and Lucas meet the Dasch family, who are looking to create a grand Mayan inspired terrarium for their Poisonous Dart Frogs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-13 14:00:00" d="2021-07-13 15:00:00"><n>Crikey! It's The Irwins</n><t>D</t>    <k>Terri returns to her hometown in Oregon to help Brady, a cougar in need of a health check. At the zoo, Bindi bathes an echidna with bad skin allergies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-13 15:00:00" d="2021-07-13 16:00:00"><n>Crikey! It's The Irwins</n><t>D</t>    <k>Terri helps prepare the zoo's new baby rhino for a life-saving vaccine. Meanwhile, Robert is on a rescue mission to save two black swans in bad shape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-13 16:00:00" d="2021-07-13 17:00:00"><n>Homestead Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>74% In Hawaii the Raneys attempt to save two homesteaders whose dream homestead lays a flash-flood zone. As the weather closes in, can they save the property from the water?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-13 17:00:00" d="2021-07-13 18:00:00"><n>Saved By The Barn</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dan travels to Chicago to give cockfighting roosters a second chance. Meanwhile, the crew worry whether an unruly cow will be welcomed by the rest of the herd</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-13 18:00:00" d="2021-07-13 19:00:00"><n>Saved By The Barn</n><t>D</t>    <k>As summer arrives, the team host a car wash to raise money for cows and donkeys. Meanwhile, Dan goes on a covert mission to save an injured goat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-13 19:00:00" d="2021-07-13 20:00:00"><n>Saved By The Barn</n><t>D</t>    <k>The barn joins forces with a charity to find homes for four neglected calves. Meanwhile, a litter of piglets are born and Chris builds a playground for the goats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-13 20:00:00" d="2021-07-13 21:00:00"><n>The Zoo</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Central Park Zoo welcomes its first Atlantic puffin chick. Meanwhile, an endangered species of gecko welcomes her first hatchling and Penny the rhino undergoes tests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-13 21:00:00" d="2021-07-13 22:00:00"><n>The Aquarium</n><t>D</t>    <k>Technology from California is brought to the aquarium to monitor beluga whale activity. And, a sea star undergoes a check-up after suspicious growths form</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-13 22:00:00" d="2021-07-13 23:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Stanley and Shelby are ferocious when they are together, so who will their owners have guests around? Plus, Finn has a habit of jumping in the babies’ crib</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-13 23:00:00" d="2021-07-14 00:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jackson travels to Portland to help Lee and Teresa, who called 911 on their cat Lux. After their son Jesse pulled on Lux's tail, he got clawed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 00:00:00" d="2021-07-14 01:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>An outbreak of disease in the swamps threatens the dogs. And after years of waiting for a forever home, Jackson finally gets his shot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 01:00:00" d="2021-07-14 02:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia is short-staffed, but finding a parolee who is prepared for the demands of the job is proving difficult. Then, the team races to an overwhelmed owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 02:00:00" d="2021-07-14 03:00:00"><n>Monster Island</n><t>D</t>    <k>In order to attain legendary status in the world of bow hunting, four hunters must track and kill wild boar on the deadly outpost of Isla Mona in the Atlantic Ocean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 03:00:00" d="2021-07-14 03:50:00"><n>Extinct Or Alive</n><t>D</t>    <k>In Indonesia, Forrest seeks the Millers Grizzled Langur, or Dracula monkey. When he hears of an illegal pet market, his search becomes a rescue mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 03:50:00" d="2021-07-14 04:40:00"><n>The Aquarium</n><t>D</t>    <k>Nandi, the aquarium’s smallest manta ray, is due her annual checkup and some young ruddy ducks arrive at the aquarium and are introduced to their new habitat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 04:40:00" d="2021-07-14 05:00:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That?</n><t>D</t>    <k>Experts test to see how anteaters eat so quickly. Plus, male humpback whales can sing for several days, but how do they do it with no vocal cords and why do they do it?</k>  </p>
</a>
