<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="30" t="2021-07-09 06:28:19"><p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 05:00:00" d="2021-07-16 05:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 05:30:00" d="2021-07-16 06:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 06:00:00" d="2021-07-16 06:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 06:30:00" d="2021-07-16 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 07:00:00" d="2021-07-16 07:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 07:30:00" d="2021-07-16 08:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 08:00:00" d="2021-07-16 08:30:00"><n>Meet The Sloths</n><t>D</t>    <k>Sensitive sloth, Linus, hits a rocky patch when Claire has to leave the Sanctuary. Scientist Becky reveals which of the sloth species is a natural-born swimmer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 08:30:00" d="2021-07-16 09:00:00"><n>Meet The Sloths</n><t>D</t>    <k>Becky tries to find out what drives the females of the species wild. Meanwhile, young choloepus, Tigger, starts to display decidedly un-slothlike tendencies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 09:00:00" d="2021-07-16 10:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Peggy is a ‘Real Housewife of Orange County’. Being a housewife, she's used to catfights, except she's now dealing with one involving her real cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 10:00:00" d="2021-07-16 11:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% When Justin gave his mum Bombadil, he had no idea the cat would be a gift from hell. Buddhists Tom and Pola lived in harmony until they adopted Percy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 11:00:00" d="2021-07-16 12:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia surprises her family, the parolees and every dog at the rescue with an extraordinary Christmas gift – but how can this giant present be something Villalobos can use?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 12:00:00" d="2021-07-16 13:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia gets a devastating injury, so her kids must help keep Villalobos running, and everyone must help catch an elusive dog in the middle of the night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 13:00:00" d="2021-07-16 14:00:00"><n>Scaled</n><t>D</t>    <k>The team creates a gangster-themed enclosure for a collection of seven snakes. Greg gets a surprise when he takes his bearded dragon, Kevin, to the vet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 14:00:00" d="2021-07-16 15:00:00"><n>Crikey! It's The Irwins</n><t>D</t>    <k>Robert feeds 44 hungry alligators, all at the same time. Terri helps examine Kaitlyn the tiger and makes a thrilling discovery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 15:00:00" d="2021-07-16 16:00:00"><n>Crikey! It's The Irwins</n><t>D</t>    <k>Robert and Terri take to the skies to release some sea turtles near the Great Barrier Reef. Bindi eagerly awaits the birth of the zoo's first tiger cub in years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 16:00:00" d="2021-07-16 17:00:00"><n>Homestead Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>74% Arctic temperatures and a hungry grizzly wreak havoc on a struggling homestead. The Raneys take action with big builds including a blacksmith shop - but tragedy strikes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 17:00:00" d="2021-07-16 18:00:00"><n>The Bronx Zoo</n><t>D</t>    <k>Zoo director Jim Breheny is excited to meet a king penguin chick. Keepers move a dangerous king cobra to a bigger exhibit, and the kiwis begin mating</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 18:00:00" d="2021-07-16 19:00:00"><n>The Bronx Zoo</n><t>D</t>    <k>Keeper Lauren tries to train some stubborn Rothschild’s giraffes. Meanwhile, staff help some Kihansi spray toads make a historic return to Tanzania</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 19:00:00" d="2021-07-16 20:00:00"><n>The Bronx Zoo</n><t>D</t>    <k>A young snow leopard cub is having difficulty walking and at risk of permanent disability. And, the zoo keepers prepare a new exhibit enclosure for gazelles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 20:00:00" d="2021-07-16 21:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Freak weather hits Texas and the team fight to save eight horses swimming in a flooded pasture. The rescue is successful but a horse is left with potentially fatal wounds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 21:00:00" d="2021-07-16 22:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Jeff treats a cherished Bloodhound puppy that won’t eat. Plus, Dr. Petra comes to the rescue of a cat after it swallowed a handful of hair ties</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 22:00:00" d="2021-07-16 23:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Jeff, a photographer who lives and works out of his home, is at risk of losing his business and his assistant because of his blood-thirsty cat, Buster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-16 23:00:00" d="2021-07-17 00:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Maryam is a pet psychic, but she can't communicate with her vicious cat Lily. Plus, Khloe discovers an entire feral colony behind her parent's house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 00:00:00" d="2021-07-17 01:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Earl returns from rehab, hoping to rebuild his life working with the dogs. Plus, Lizzy rescues a dog after a confrontation with the owner who abandoned it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 01:00:00" d="2021-07-17 02:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>A woman travels from San Diego to offer one of Villalobos' senior dogs a home. Meanwhile, Lizzy and Marcel search for a mama dog's lost puppies out in the country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 02:00:00" d="2021-07-17 03:00:00"><n>Shark Vortex</n><t>D</t>    <k>Each summer the Gulf Stream pushes north into the waters of southern New England, bringing with it thirty species of shark. Greg Skomal and Joe Remeiro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 03:00:00" d="2021-07-17 03:50:00"><n>Monsters Inside Me</n><t>D</t>    <k>76% The lives of three families are jolted - one infection rips a man's leg apart, and a rare brain infection pushes a seven year old girl toward suicide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 03:50:00" d="2021-07-17 04:15:00"><n>Meet The Sloths</n><t>D</t>    <k>Meet The Sloths follows a year in the life of five slow-moving residents of the Aviarios Sloth Sanctuary, a sanctuary dedicated to saving orphaned or injured sloths</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 04:15:00" d="2021-07-17 04:40:00"><n>Meet The Sloths</n><t>D</t>    <k>An emergency rescue puts sanctuary vet, Marcello, on the spot, a love triangle leaves Bradypus, Samantha, in the doghouse and Becky puts sloth speed to the test</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 04:40:00" d="2021-07-17 06:00:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That?</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why do domestic cats find it so hard to get down from trees, and how have two jungle cats evolved? Plus, why do kiwi birds lay monster-sized eggs compared to their size?</k>  </p>
</a>
