<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2020-05-28 04:30:41"><p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-04 05:10:00" d="2020-06-04 06:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Jackson helps cat Good Kitty stand up to her two feline attackers. He also meets a couple fed up with their cats, Tiki and Marley, eating everything in sight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-04 06:00:00" d="2020-06-04 07:00:00"><n>Bad Dog!</n><t>D</t>    <k>A pug is obsessed with pizza, and a dog tears up the house and the backyard. Plus, a horse keeps escaping its stall and releases the other horses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-04 07:00:00" d="2020-06-04 08:00:00"><n>Safari Park Adventure</n><t>D</t>    <k>When disaster strikes in the deer park, a pride of lions enjoys the gory benefits. Plus, find out how Otzee, the chief of the rhinos, will react</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-04 08:00:00" d="2020-06-04 09:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>A midnight rescue finds Tia, Tania and new worker Perry scrambling after an injured dog. Then, a puppy’s chance at a forever home is threatened by an unexpected danger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-04 09:00:00" d="2020-06-04 10:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tania oversees the rescue of ten dogs left to die in deplorable conditions. Tia helps a family find the perfect companion for their special needs teenager</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-04 10:00:00" d="2020-06-04 11:00:00"><n>Crikey! It's The Irwins</n><t>D</t>    <k>Steve Irwin’s son Robert follows in his footsteps. After months of training, it's time for him to solo feed the most notorious croc at the Australia Zoo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-04 11:00:00" d="2020-06-04 12:00:00"><n>Crikey! It's The Irwins</n><t>D</t>    <k>Hunter the tiger is being sedated for his annual eye check, allowing Terri to get close. Bindi puts on a birthday party for Minibus - the Zoo's oldest Wombat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-04 12:00:00" d="2020-06-04 13:00:00"><n>Extinct Or Alive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Forrest is in the Faroe Islands looking for a trace of the great auk, a large flightless seabird that was declared extinct over 175 years ago</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-04 13:00:00" d="2020-06-04 14:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Steev and Laura have been dating for seven years, but Steev’s cat Darkness is tearing them apart. Can Jackson ease their woes?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-04 14:00:00" d="2020-06-04 14:30:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>How do bats avoid bumping into each other in the middle of the night? Why did a bottlenose dolphin seek out a diver’s help? Experts examine this and more!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-04 14:30:00" d="2020-06-04 15:00:00"><n>ACE: Animal Countdown Extraordinaire</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jack and the HMS Buccaneer dive under the sea to discover the top ten most daring animal divers. The deeper the dive, the greater the danger!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-04 15:00:00" d="2020-06-04 16:00:00"><n>Animal ER</n><t>D</t>    <k>Boxer dog Logan has a cancerous lump removed from his jaw by his own vet, but is referred to the hospital to check if the cancer has spread</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-04 16:00:00" d="2020-06-04 17:00:00"><n>Animal ER</n><t>D</t>    <k>Owners Lisa and Callu are worried about Merlin, a Great Dane who goes over on his front toes when he walks. Neurologist Annette Wessman suspects a problem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-04 17:00:00" d="2020-06-04 18:00:00"><n>Finding Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>40% The team head to Michigan to answer a call from a woman who claims a Bigfoot threw a log at her moving car. Could this be their most successful mission yet?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-04 18:00:00" d="2020-06-04 19:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>74% Chris attempts to help a lady who runs a shelter for abandoned donkeys. Lisa takes on a six-year-old apprentice who has arrived at SASH with her sick dog, Jelly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-04 19:00:00" d="2020-06-04 20:00:00"><n>Animal Cops San Francisco</n><t>D</t>    <k>Lieutenant Scott tracks down a dog on the run from a major explosion and Officer Forester races to save the life of a critically ill cat. Plus, can 77 collies be saved?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-04 20:00:00" d="2020-06-04 21:00:00"><n>Dr. Dee: Alaska Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Dee takes care of her mum while manning the clinic, where the vet performs emergency surgery on a puppy. Plus, Dr. Terry fights to save one of Santa’s reindeer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-04 21:00:00" d="2020-06-04 22:00:00"><n>The Vet Life</n><t>D</t>    <k>Three veterinarians who became friends at university and dreamed of starting their own practice run a veterinary hospital together in Houston, Texas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-04 22:00:00" d="2020-06-04 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>A violent clash between two warring stallions presents the SPCA team with a massive challenge. And, a dog and her puppies are found dumped on a street</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-04 23:00:00" d="2020-06-05 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>After rescuing a scared pit bull, Tia finds herself battling with a shelter over the dog's fate. And a dog rescued from the brink of death finally has a shot at a home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 00:00:00" d="2020-06-05 01:00:00"><n>I'm Alive</n><t>D</t>    <k>A teenager bitten by an unidentified animal while surfing in Costa Rica, and a man attacked by a grizzly bear share their extraordinary tales of survival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 01:00:00" d="2020-06-05 02:00:00"><n>Animal Cops San Francisco</n><t>D</t>    <k>Lieutenant Scott tracks down a dog on the run from a major explosion and Officer Forester races to save the life of a critically ill cat. Plus, can 77 collies be saved?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 02:00:00" d="2020-06-05 03:00:00"><n>Dr. Dee: Alaska Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Dee takes care of her mum while manning the clinic, where the vet performs emergency surgery on a puppy. Plus, Dr. Terry fights to save one of Santa’s reindeer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 03:00:00" d="2020-06-05 03:50:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>A violent clash between two warring stallions presents the SPCA team with a massive challenge. And, a dog and her puppies are found dumped on a street</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 03:50:00" d="2020-06-05 04:40:00"><n>Finding Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>40% The team head to Michigan to answer a call from a woman who claims a Bigfoot threw a log at her moving car. Could this be their most successful mission yet?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 04:40:00" d="2020-06-05 05:10:00"><n>Meet The Orangutans</n><t>D</t>    <k>The orphans are learning how to make important relationships. Mui Mui and Anne have become inseparable, but now Anne is pregnant, and she needs to be separated</k>  </p>
</a>
