<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="30" t="2021-07-10 04:53:37"><p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 06:00:00" d="2021-07-17 06:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 06:30:00" d="2021-07-17 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 07:00:00" d="2021-07-17 07:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 07:30:00" d="2021-07-17 08:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 08:00:00" d="2021-07-17 08:30:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That?</n><t>D</t>    <k>How can elephants hear something hundreds of miles away? What goes on inside a chicken’s egg? How has an incredible snake learnt how to fly?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 08:30:00" d="2021-07-17 09:00:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That?</n><t>D</t>    <k>How can a fish fly the length of three football fields? Can a spider be adorable? What’s the real story behind a flamingo’s colour?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 09:00:00" d="2021-07-17 10:00:00"><n>My Fat Pet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travis’ pet expertise is put to the test when he's called to help out a 24-pound cat who acts out unless he has round-the-clock access to food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 10:00:00" d="2021-07-17 10:30:00"><n>Meet The Penguins</n><t>D</t>    <k>The staff at the Sanccob Seabird Rescue Centre in Cape Town race against time to help a penguin contaminated by oil, and wannabe dad Winston takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 10:30:00" d="2021-07-17 11:00:00"><n>Meet The Penguins</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Centre’s grumpiest resident, Crabby, greets a new arrival that melts his icy heart, and Princess – queen of the resident penguins – faces the biggest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 11:00:00" d="2021-07-17 12:00:00"><n>Saved By The Barn</n><t>D</t>    <k>As summer arrives, the team host a car wash to raise money for cows and donkeys. Meanwhile, Dan goes on a covert mission to save an injured goat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 12:00:00" d="2021-07-17 13:00:00"><n>Animal Cribs</n><t>D</t>    <k>Antonio helps working dog with messy habits and turns the laundry room into a fully operational spa. The team creates a football-themed doggy paradise!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 13:00:00" d="2021-07-17 14:00:00"><n>Animal Cribs</n><t>D</t>    <k>Antonio transforms a cluttered basement housing more than 20 rescued reptiles, mammals and birds. The team build exotic enclosures and an entertainment space</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 14:00:00" d="2021-07-17 15:00:00"><n>Animal Cribs</n><t>D</t>    <k>Antonio and the team build make a mountain cabin safer for Chickie, a blind senior dog. Plus, they build a Japanese-inspired indoor dog lounge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 15:00:00" d="2021-07-17 16:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia and the team try nursing a severely malnourished dog back to health and a Hurricane Katrina survivor finally has a chance at a forever home, 10 years on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 16:00:00" d="2021-07-17 17:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>When a reputed dognapper dumps a dog at Villalobos, Mariah scrambles to find the owner. Plus, a new parolee realises he is in over his head</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 17:00:00" d="2021-07-17 17:30:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>Who or what stole a cow’s carcass that was being used for a science experiment. Plus, what natural event caused a gathering of orcas in Norway?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 17:30:00" d="2021-07-17 18:00:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>Experts try to answer some of nature’s strangest mysteries like, can fish really predict when an earthquake is coming? And, why are eggs shaped like that?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 18:00:00" d="2021-07-17 19:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Stanley and Shelby are ferocious when they are together, so who will their owners have guests around? Plus, Finn has a habit of jumping in the babies’ crib</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 19:00:00" d="2021-07-17 20:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jackson travels to Portland to help Lee and Teresa, who called 911 on their cat Lux. After their son Jesse pulled on Lux's tail, he got clawed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 20:00:00" d="2021-07-17 21:00:00"><n>Alaskan Bush People</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Browns embark on a quest to discover new land that steers them into unfamiliar terrain. There, they pledge to rebuild a life of independence in the bush</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 21:00:00" d="2021-07-17 22:00:00"><n>Shark Vortex</n><t>D</t>    <k>Each summer the Gulf Stream pushes north into the waters of southern New England, bringing with it thirty species of shark. Greg Skomal and Joe Remeiro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 22:00:00" d="2021-07-17 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Investigators are called out after disturbing reports of a large number of dogs held captive in make-shift pens. Plus, Octavio Gonzales receives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-17 23:00:00" d="2021-07-18 00:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animal cruelty investigators join forces with Texas police officers in an attempt to smash one of the biggest dog fighting rings in US history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-18 00:00:00" d="2021-07-18 01:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>When investigators from the Houston SPCA respond to a call at a livery stable they find themselves in a life or death battle to save a severely neglected horse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-18 01:00:00" d="2021-07-18 02:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tigger the cat is monitored closely for unusual eating habits. Plus, Dr. Jeff cautions an owner of the perils of buying online when she brings in her unwell puppy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-18 02:00:00" d="2021-07-18 03:00:00"><n>Homestead Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>74% In Oregon, the Raneys are called in to help snowbound homesteaders. Exposed to local predators, they worry about the region’s forest fires</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-18 03:00:00" d="2021-07-18 03:25:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That?</n><t>D</t>    <k>How can elephants hear something hundreds of miles away? What goes on inside a chicken’s egg? How has an incredible snake learnt how to fly?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-18 03:25:00" d="2021-07-18 03:50:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That?</n><t>D</t>    <k>How can a fish fly the length of three football fields? Can a spider be adorable? What’s the real story behind a flamingo’s colour?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-18 03:50:00" d="2021-07-18 04:40:00"><n>My Fat Pet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travis’ pet expertise is put to the test when he's called to help out a 24-pound cat who acts out unless he has round-the-clock access to food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-18 04:40:00" d="2021-07-18 05:00:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That?</n><t>D</t>    <k>How do caterpillars transform into magnificent butterflies in their cocoon? Plus, why are cats’ tongues the way they are? Experts answer these questions and more!</k>  </p>
</a>
