<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2020-05-25 04:34:25"><p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-01 05:10:00" d="2020-06-01 06:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jackson works with hyperactive Persian cat Mr. Weasley, but when he collapses mid-play, the story takes a different turn. Plus, can he bring exiled cat Max back indoors?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-01 06:00:00" d="2020-06-01 07:00:00"><n>Bad Dog!</n><t>D</t>    <k>Owners wonder about their dog's intelligence, a balloon-popping bulldog thinks everything belongs to her and a cat steals from everyone in its neighbourhood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-01 07:00:00" d="2020-06-01 08:00:00"><n>Bad Dog!</n><t>D</t>    <k>A dog loves all things ice cream and another dog keeps getting his head stuck in things. Plus, a parrot has a habit of rapping and swearing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-01 08:00:00" d="2020-06-01 09:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>80% Mariah rescues kittens, and a mother with puppies, from a fetid abandoned home. Plus, it’s time to take a tough decision when Sloth’s health deteriorates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-01 09:00:00" d="2020-06-01 10:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>80% Tia heads to Georgia to evaluate a prison dog program, and joins their team on a shocking rescue mission. Plus, could a surprise inspection close Villalobos down?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-01 10:00:00" d="2020-06-01 11:00:00"><n>America's Cutest Pets</n><t>D</t>    <k>How do cats squeeze into tight spaces, why do they make odd friends, what is the secret to their agility, and which is the cutest of them all?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-01 11:00:00" d="2020-06-01 12:00:00"><n>America's Cutest Pets</n><t>D</t>    <k>Can kittens mimic their human friends, why do felines get stuck in sticky situations, do cats like babies, and which is the cutest cat of all?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-01 12:00:00" d="2020-06-01 13:00:00"><n>Extinct Or Alive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Forrest tracks clues and eyewitness accounts that suggest the Formosan Clouded Leopard, which was declared extinct only recently, could still be alive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-01 13:00:00" d="2020-06-01 14:00:00"><n>The Zoo: San Diego</n><t>D</t>    <k>The youngest elephant at the park learns how to use her trunk. Plus, an Andean bear is ready to mate and Jeff searches for the elusive coast patch-nosed snake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-01 14:00:00" d="2020-06-01 14:30:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>Experts examine footage of crows leaving gifts in Seattle. Plus, could a shark really be older than America? And, what is making crop circles in the sea?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-01 14:30:00" d="2020-06-01 15:00:00"><n>ACE: Animal Countdown Extraordinaire</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jack Yabsley and the HMS Buccaneer count down the ten stinkiest animal on the planet. With their ‘Stinkometer-4000’ they’ll analyse animal aromas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-01 15:00:00" d="2020-06-01 16:00:00"><n>Animal ER</n><t>D</t>    <k>When equine vet David Sutton helps Tilly, a ten year old mare, who has grass sickness and hasn't eaten for a fortnight, her owners are faced with a heart breaking decision</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-01 16:00:00" d="2020-06-01 17:00:00"><n>Animal ER</n><t>D</t>    <k>When Theodore a four year old Maltese Terrier is brought into the vet hospital with a mystery illness, the vets struggle for a diagnosis as his condition gets worse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-01 17:00:00" d="2020-06-01 18:00:00"><n>Finding Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>40% The forests of Arizona's Mogollon Rim are believed to be the perfect habitat for young Sasquatches. Can the local Apache Indian tribe help the team to find them?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-01 18:00:00" d="2020-06-01 19:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>74% Join Dr. Chris Brown at his commercial veterinary clinic in a suburb of Sydney. Today he treats Gizmo the shaking cavoodle, a baby cheetah and a machine-gun pig</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-01 19:00:00" d="2020-06-01 20:00:00"><n>Animal Cops San Francisco</n><t>D</t>    <k>Officer Sadler saves a dog from a fire and Officer Johnson takes urgent action against a cruel pet owner. Plus, can the team break up an illegal cockfighting ring?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-01 20:00:00" d="2020-06-01 21:00:00"><n>River Of No Return</n><t>D</t>    <k>Father and son jetboat captains take on Deadman's Rapids. And, felling a huge dead tree puts Ron and Wes at risk from crashing widow makers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-01 21:00:00" d="2020-06-01 22:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Investigators take on one of their most dangerous operations to save a group of bears and tigers held captive in a chicken shed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-01 22:00:00" d="2020-06-01 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Houston SPCA investigators act quickly when a panicked dog struggles between life and death, and the team rescue cats living in cockroach-infested squalor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-01 23:00:00" d="2020-06-02 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>A veteran makes a plea for help being reunited with his dogs. Plus, a shelter overwhelmed by dogs rescued from shocking conditions seeks Tia's assistance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 00:00:00" d="2020-06-02 01:00:00"><n>I'm Alive</n><t>D</t>    <k>67% When a black bear attacks her family, a mother puts her life on the line to save her children and a man is bitten by a deadly taipan on 9/11. Will they survive?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 01:00:00" d="2020-06-02 02:00:00"><n>Animal Cops San Francisco</n><t>D</t>    <k>Officer Sadler saves a dog from a fire and Officer Johnson takes urgent action against a cruel pet owner. Plus, can the team break up an illegal cockfighting ring?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 02:00:00" d="2020-06-02 03:00:00"><n>River Of No Return</n><t>D</t>    <k>Father and son jetboat captains take on Deadman's Rapids. And, felling a huge dead tree puts Ron and Wes at risk from crashing widow makers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 03:00:00" d="2020-06-02 03:50:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Houston SPCA investigators act quickly when a panicked dog struggles between life and death, and the team rescue cats living in cockroach-infested squalor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 03:50:00" d="2020-06-02 04:40:00"><n>Finding Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>40% The forests of Arizona's Mogollon Rim are believed to be the perfect habitat for young Sasquatches. Can the local Apache Indian tribe help the team to find them?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 04:40:00" d="2020-06-02 05:10:00"><n>Meet The Orangutans</n><t>D</t>    <k>Follow the lives of orphaned orangutan babies as they are brought to the world’s oldest orangutan sanctuary in Borneo. Toddlers are wheel-barrowed in for lessons in life</k>  </p>
</a>
