<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2020-05-29 04:29:21"><p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 05:10:00" d="2020-06-05 06:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Jackson visits a house divided, with four cats always fighting. Plus, he’s at a cattery where territorial issues forced two cats to live in isolation for years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 06:00:00" d="2020-06-05 07:00:00"><n>Safari Park Adventure</n><t>D</t>    <k>Emergency vets are called in as illness strikes zebras, primates, and a rare Siberian tiger - are other animals at risk? Plus, find out just how clever an elephant can be</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 07:00:00" d="2020-06-05 08:00:00"><n>Safari Park Adventure</n><t>D</t>    <k>Keepers resort to desperate measures to stop conflict amongst the lions and keep a close eye on a newborn litter of wolves. Plus, an old lemur faces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 08:00:00" d="2020-06-05 09:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Two stray pit bulls hiding beneath a two-ton stack of lumber lure Tia into a dramatic and potentially deadly rescue. Then a colourful Bayou couple visit Villalobos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 09:00:00" d="2020-06-05 10:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>A rescue mission brings Tia and daughter Mariah face to face with a protective mama dog and her litter of seven puppies, but Villalobos is overrun with puppies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 10:00:00" d="2020-06-05 11:00:00"><n>Crikey! It's The Irwins</n><t>D</t>    <k>Terri, Bindi and Robert prepare Croc One, Steve Irwin's research ship, for a special mission to release an endangered sea turtle back into the wild</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 11:00:00" d="2020-06-05 12:00:00"><n>Crikey! It's The Irwins</n><t>D</t>    <k>Robert follows in Steve's steps wrangling Utah, a highly venomous King Cobra. A vet from the zoo’s hospital, Dr. Amber, visits Tandora to treat wild Koalas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 12:00:00" d="2020-06-05 13:00:00"><n>Extinct Or Alive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Madagascar's Pachylemurs were red, furry giants, nearly the size of great apes. Forrest scales the jungle canopy to prove the giant species still lives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 13:00:00" d="2020-06-05 14:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Peggy is a ‘Real Housewife of Orange County’. Being a housewife, she's used to catfights, except she's now dealing with one involving her real cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 14:00:00" d="2020-06-05 14:30:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why would 25,000 honeybees swarm a hot dog stand in the middle of Times Square? Why would a bat hunker down in the snow? Experts examine this and more!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 14:30:00" d="2020-06-05 15:00:00"><n>ACE: Animal Countdown Extraordinaire</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jack and Buck serve up foul feasts in their search for the top ten animals with the most disgusting diets. Which food is most foul?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 15:00:00" d="2020-06-05 16:00:00"><n>Hanging With The Hendersons</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Henderson brothers and their dad are all veterinarians. Fox Animal Hospital sees dogs and cats who need help. But, can the vets fix them?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 16:00:00" d="2020-06-05 17:00:00"><n>Hanging With The Hendersons</n><t>D</t>    <k>A stoned dog is rushed to the clinic after eating a bag of marijuana. A pot-bellied pig rescue has plus-sized problems, and Natalia’s mum meets the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 17:00:00" d="2020-06-05 18:00:00"><n>Finding Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>40% The team travels to Vermont to investigate a photo of what may be a Sasquatch carrying her baby. They take to the forest in hopes of finding evidence themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 18:00:00" d="2020-06-05 19:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>74% Join Dr Chris Brown in his veterinary exploits in beautiful Bondi, Australia. Chris pays a visit to the Kyabram Vet Clinic in country Victoria to help out an old friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 19:00:00" d="2020-06-05 20:00:00"><n>Animal Cops San Francisco</n><t>D</t>    <k>Officer Sadler discovers what she thinks are fighting cocks in the back of a pickup truck and Lieutenant Scott is faced with a daring bridge rescue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 20:00:00" d="2020-06-05 21:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Overwhelmed by work, Tia hires three new parolees to help out – but soon things take a turn for the worse. And the shelter is swamped by a group of new dogs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 21:00:00" d="2020-06-05 22:00:00"><n>Amanda To The Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>Amanda finds forever homes for her Hawaiian rescues. Super Scootie has malformed legs amongst an array of other health issues and needs help fast!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 22:00:00" d="2020-06-05 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>The team try to help a tiny dog with a coat so matted and filthy, they need to sedate him to remove it. It is a case Investigator Dana Moss will never forget</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-05 23:00:00" d="2020-06-06 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Earl rallies the parolees' festive spirits and enlists their help to decorate the Tahyo Tavern and prepare a very special Christmas feast for the Villalobos family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-06 00:00:00" d="2020-06-06 01:00:00"><n>I'm Alive</n><t>D</t>    <k>A wildlife specialist clings to life after being pinned under his truck by a charging elephant and boy battles to save his father after he is bitten by a rattlesnake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-06 01:00:00" d="2020-06-06 02:00:00"><n>Animal Cops San Francisco</n><t>D</t>    <k>Officer Sadler discovers what she thinks are fighting cocks in the back of a pickup truck and Lieutenant Scott is faced with a daring bridge rescue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-06 02:00:00" d="2020-06-06 03:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Overwhelmed by work, Tia hires three new parolees to help out – but soon things take a turn for the worse. And the shelter is swamped by a group of new dogs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-06 03:00:00" d="2020-06-06 03:50:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>The team try to help a tiny dog with a coat so matted and filthy, they need to sedate him to remove it. It is a case Investigator Dana Moss will never forget</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-06 03:50:00" d="2020-06-06 04:40:00"><n>Finding Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>40% The team travels to Vermont to investigate a photo of what may be a Sasquatch carrying her baby. They take to the forest in hopes of finding evidence themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-06 04:40:00" d="2020-06-06 06:00:00"><n>Meet The Orangutans</n><t>D</t>    <k>Gelison arrived at Sepilok at just one year old, and was traumatised from losing his mother. While settling in better, his skiving antics and bully-boy</k>  </p>
</a>
