<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2019-08-09 01:29:22"><p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-15 05:10:00" d="2019-08-15 06:00:00"><n>Tanked</n><t>D</t>    <k>67% CEO of Zappos thinks his employees deserve a nap room! Wayde and Brett accept the challenge to create a 24 ft long tank with individual sleeping pods</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-15 06:00:00" d="2019-08-15 07:00:00"><n>Dr. Dee: Alaska Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Dee performs a three-hour surgery to save a dog's life. And, Dr. Dee visits a giant Tegu lizard and several snakes for a wellness check</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-15 07:00:00" d="2019-08-15 08:00:00"><n>Dr. Dee: Alaska Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Dee treats a border collie puppy with a congenital issue and a rescued cat who may have an incurable disease called feline immunodeficiency virus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-15 08:00:00" d="2019-08-15 09:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Kristie Franks has a difficult job trying to herd up 20 cats in the overrun house of a hoarder, while Debbie Michielson rescues a horse with an injury to its leg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-15 09:00:00" d="2019-08-15 10:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Chief investigator Charles Jantzen leads his team in the biggest horse seizure of the year, while investigator Trischa Price rescues a dog left home alone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-15 10:00:00" d="2019-08-15 11:00:00"><n>Crocodile Hunter</n><t>D</t>    <k>Candid interviews reveal Steve Irwin's most private and innermost thoughts, from what drives him to the success of his first feature film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-15 11:00:00" d="2019-08-15 12:00:00"><n>Alaska: The Last Frontier</n><t>D</t>    <k>Atz Lee and Eivin travel 160 miles and brave the bears of &quot;Terrible Island&quot; to hunt deer. Meanwhile, Eve helps Charlotte solve a swarming bee problem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-15 12:00:00" d="2019-08-15 13:00:00"><n>Wildest Islands</n><t>D</t>    <k>A third of the world’s penguin species make the Falklands their annual breeding ground; why do penguins and their sea lion predators thrive here?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-15 13:00:00" d="2019-08-15 14:00:00"><n>Dr. Dee: Alaska Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Dee performs a three-hour surgery to save a dog's life. And, Dr. Dee visits a giant Tegu lizard and several snakes for a wellness check</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-15 14:00:00" d="2019-08-15 15:00:00"><n>Dr. Dee: Alaska Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Dee treats a border collie puppy with a congenital issue and a rescued cat who may have an incurable disease called feline immunodeficiency virus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-15 15:00:00" d="2019-08-15 16:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>80% After a teenager is attacked by a group of pit bulls, Tia finds herself thrust into a rescue mission to save an innocent pit bull caught up in the media storm</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-15 16:00:00" d="2019-08-15 17:00:00"><n>Treehouse Masters</n><t>D</t>    <k>Pete builds a citadel fortress for a couple who loves all things medieval. A high tower will hold a round table and thrones, as well as a glass floor loft</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-15 17:00:00" d="2019-08-15 18:00:00"><n>Project Grizzly</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jeff’s unconventional hunting lessons fail to prepare Bob and Screech to hunt game in the wild, but he discovers they may be learning on their own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-15 18:00:00" d="2019-08-15 19:00:00"><n>Living Dinosaur Of Liberia: Expedition Mungo</n><t>D</t>    <k>A huge crocodilian creature known as the Gbahali is killing people in Liberia. Mungo wonders if it is a species more akin to a dinosaur than anything known today?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-15 19:00:00" d="2019-08-15 20:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>With husband AJ heading to trial, Tia struggles to keep control at Villalobos. Things worsen when she gets an emotional phone call putting AJ's fate in her hands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-15 20:00:00" d="2019-08-15 21:00:00"><n>The Vet Life</n><t>D</t>    <k>A beloved basset hound has a condition that could complicate surgery for Dr. Ross. Plus, Dr. Lavigne doesn’t want a vet tech to assist in an operation on her own dog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-15 21:00:00" d="2019-08-15 22:00:00"><n>Alaska: The Last Frontier</n><t>D</t>    <k>Autumn arrives and the Kilchers scramble to finish their winter preparations in time. Meanwhile, Eivin uses a samurai sword to prepare Thanksgiving dinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-15 22:00:00" d="2019-08-15 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Investigators find themselves tackling one of their biggest ever hoarding cases when they uncover over 120 cats living inside a house in terrible conditions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-15 23:00:00" d="2019-08-16 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>With husband AJ heading to trial, Tia struggles to keep control at Villalobos. Things worsen when she gets an emotional phone call putting AJ's fate in her hands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-16 00:00:00" d="2019-08-16 01:00:00"><n>Extinct Or Alive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Forrest teams up with an expert in Newfoundland seeking the white wolf, which was declared extinct in 1930. They meet a hunter convinced he shot one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-16 01:00:00" d="2019-08-16 02:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Investigators find themselves tackling one of their biggest ever hoarding cases when they uncover over 120 cats living inside a house in terrible conditions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-16 02:00:00" d="2019-08-16 03:00:00"><n>Wildest Islands Of Indonesia</n><t>D</t>    <k>From deep below the ocean surface, to the vaulted canopies of Borneo’s tallest trees, discover the hidden worlds of some of the planet’s most fascinating creatures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-16 03:00:00" d="2019-08-16 03:50:00"><n>Alaska: The Last Frontier</n><t>D</t>    <k>Autumn arrives and the Kilchers scramble to finish their winter preparations in time. Meanwhile, Eivin uses a samurai sword to prepare Thanksgiving dinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-16 03:50:00" d="2019-08-16 04:40:00"><n>Alaska Monsters</n><t>D</t>    <k>38% The team investigates reports of a massive wolf. Todd constructs a massive jail cell to hold this creature, while Levi implements laser technology</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-16 04:40:00" d="2019-08-16 05:10:00"><n>Orangutan Island</n><t>D</t>    <k>82% As the orangutans settle into their new home, the first signs of a fledgling society begin to emerge as well as signs of a pack mentality</k>  </p>
</a>
