<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2019-08-13 01:53:40"><p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 05:10:00" d="2019-08-18 06:00:00"><n>Tanked</n><t>D</t>    <k>67% Donut Mania is Brett's newest business venture and they’re having a grand opening. Wayde and the team want to congratulate him with a surprise fish tank!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 06:00:00" d="2019-08-18 07:00:00"><n>The Bronx Zoo</n><t>D</t>    <k>When two tigers are introduced as potential mates, it doesn’t go as smoothly as keepers had hoped. Meanwhile, a pair of African porcupines arrive at the zoo!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 07:00:00" d="2019-08-18 08:00:00"><n>Tanked</n><t>D</t>    <k>67% NBA superstar Anthony Davis brings Wayde and Brett on board to transform an entire room into an aquarium! Will they be able to deliver a winning tank?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 08:00:00" d="2019-08-18 09:00:00"><n>Animal Cribs</n><t>D</t>    <k>A family’s two Nigerian dwarf goats wreak havoc in their backyard! So, designer Antonio transforms it into a fun goat playground, including a climbing tower</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 09:00:00" d="2019-08-18 10:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Naja has been at the sanctuary since she was a puppy, so it's a big day when she's adopted. And two feral pit bulls have had a run in with a porcupine - can Tia help?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 10:00:00" d="2019-08-18 11:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>A vicious swarm of bees returns to the dog sanctuary with a vengeance. Plus, will Tia manage to house an old and arthritic mastiff, abandoned by his owners?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 11:00:00" d="2019-08-18 12:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>In Tuscaloosa a young boy has to give up his pit bull after a tornado destroys his home, and Tia is inspired to help local rescuers rebuild their kennels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 12:00:00" d="2019-08-18 13:00:00"><n>Alaska: The Last Frontier</n><t>D</t>    <k>Spring finally arrives on the homestead. Eivin mills lumber, builds a large chicken house from scratch and helps his wife Eve take out a rogue cannibal hen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 13:00:00" d="2019-08-18 14:00:00"><n>Alaska: The Last Frontier</n><t>D</t>    <k>Otto and his family battle the elements and predators to drive their cattle to the summer pasture. Atz Lee and Jane build a makeshift greenhouse from cast off supplies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 14:00:00" d="2019-08-18 15:00:00"><n>Alaska: The Last Frontier</n><t>D</t>    <k>Eivin and Eve's cannibal hen strikes again. Meanwhile, Atz begins his summer range riding season to protect Otto's cattle herd, but will he keep the predators at bay?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 15:00:00" d="2019-08-18 16:00:00"><n>Alaska: The Last Frontier</n><t>D</t>    <k>The clan have 48 hours to build a cattle fence and rebuild a cabin, or the hazardous river's tide will trap their barge full of critical equipment for another month</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 16:00:00" d="2019-08-18 17:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>The team cares for abandoned kittens. Plus, Dr. Jeff gives hope to a concerned owner when their beloved dog is diagnosed with cancer and a rescue tiger finds love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 17:00:00" d="2019-08-18 18:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Extra Dose</n><t>D</t>    <k>New to the crew, Dr Amy helps a family’s cat whose jaw is badly injured. Plus, an owner brings in Spike, his dog who has been shot with buckshot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 18:00:00" d="2019-08-18 19:00:00"><n>The Aquarium</n><t>D</t>    <k>Nandi, the aquarium’s smallest manta ray, is due her annual check up and some young ruddy ducks arrive at the aquarium and are introduced to their new habitat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 19:00:00" d="2019-08-18 20:00:00"><n>Jaws Comes Home: Return Of The Great Whites</n><t>D</t>    <k>Shark expert and scientist, Greg Skomal, follows five Great White sharks on a six month journey as he attempts to understand all he can about these much-maligned hunters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 20:00:00" d="2019-08-18 21:00:00"><n>Homestead Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>Marty embarks on an ambitious, off-grid hydropower system following a storm. Matt creates a meat smoker, but a surprise accident leads to a construction site injury</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 21:00:00" d="2019-08-18 22:00:00"><n>Alaska: The Last Frontier</n><t>D</t>    <k>The extended Kilcher family struggle through a record-breaking harsh winter. Desperate for food, Atz Lee and Jane venture into the brutal elements in search of food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 22:00:00" d="2019-08-18 23:00:00"><n>Alaska: The Last Frontier</n><t>D</t>    <k>Spring finally arrives on the homestead. Eivin mills lumber, builds a large chicken house from scratch and helps his wife Eve take out a rogue cannibal hen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 23:00:00" d="2019-08-19 00:00:00"><n>Alaska: The Last Frontier</n><t>D</t>    <k>Otto and his family battle the elements and predators to drive their cattle to the summer pasture. Atz Lee and Jane build a makeshift greenhouse from cast off supplies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-19 00:00:00" d="2019-08-19 01:00:00"><n>Alaska: The Last Frontier</n><t>D</t>    <k>Eivin and Eve's cannibal hen strikes again. Meanwhile, Atz begins his summer range riding season to protect Otto's cattle herd, but will he keep the predators at bay?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-19 01:00:00" d="2019-08-19 02:00:00"><n>Alaska: The Last Frontier</n><t>D</t>    <k>The clan have 48 hours to build a cattle fence and rebuild a cabin, or the hazardous river's tide will trap their barge full of critical equipment for another month</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-19 02:00:00" d="2019-08-19 03:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Naja has been at the sanctuary since she was a puppy, so it's a big day when she's adopted. And two feral pit bulls have had a run in with a porcupine - can Tia help?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-19 03:00:00" d="2019-08-19 03:50:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>A vicious swarm of bees returns to the dog sanctuary with a vengeance. Plus, will Tia manage to house an old and arthritic mastiff, abandoned by his owners?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-19 03:50:00" d="2019-08-19 04:40:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>In Tuscaloosa a young boy has to give up his pit bull after a tornado destroys his home, and Tia is inspired to help local rescuers rebuild their kennels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-19 04:40:00" d="2019-08-19 05:10:00"><n>Orangutan Island</n><t>D</t>    <k>82% Chen Chen asserts his dominance by brutally attacking Cha Cha. Despite rescue attempts, Cha Cha flees. Nowhere to be found, Cha Cha is isolated from the community</k>  </p>
</a>
