<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2019-08-11 01:28:06"><p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-17 06:00:00" d="2019-08-17 07:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>A cruelty investigator is responding to a call from the sheriff’s department. A pony has been dragged down a road, leaving it crippled with pain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-17 07:00:00" d="2019-08-17 08:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animal control officers have been removing cats from an apartment where a woman has recently been evicted. Some of the animals are in bad shape and need help urgently</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-17 08:00:00" d="2019-08-17 09:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animal Cruelty Investigators arrive at a property to rescue some horses, but have a surprise in store when they discover a litter of puppies trapped inside a storm drain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-17 09:00:00" d="2019-08-17 10:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animal Cruelty Investigators from the Houston SPCA discover an elderly family overrun with cats all living under one roof dangerously close to collapse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-17 10:00:00" d="2019-08-17 11:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>In a special edition of Animal Cops Houston Investigators look back at the most shocking cases of the series, reliving stories of despair, neglect, rescue and hope</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-17 11:00:00" d="2019-08-17 12:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>In a special episode we go behind the closed doors of Hoarder homes and find out how the Houston SPCA is fighting this most shocking act of an animal cruelty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-17 12:00:00" d="2019-08-17 13:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>It’s a race against time as Tia and the crew search for a mother pit bull and her puppies that have been dumped in the sweltering Mojave Desert; will they find them?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-17 13:00:00" d="2019-08-17 14:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>80% Tia hopes she has found a home for Latwanda, a badly abused dog, but is this pit bull ready to leave? Plus, funny-man Brian annoys everyone when he slacks off</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-17 14:00:00" d="2019-08-17 15:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>80% Mariah rescues kittens, and a mother with puppies, from a fetid abandoned home. Plus, it’s time to take a tough decision when Sloth’s health deteriorates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-17 15:00:00" d="2019-08-17 16:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>80% Tia heads to Georgia to evaluate a prison dog program, and joins their team on a shocking rescue mission. Plus, could a surprise inspection close Villalobos down?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-17 16:00:00" d="2019-08-17 17:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Jeff faces surgery first on a Rottweiler with a broken shoulder and Dr. Baier sees to a limping pig. Plus, the team head to the mountains to treat some wolves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-17 17:00:00" d="2019-08-17 18:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Jeff conducts tricky surgery to remove a large mass from a Doberman's side. Dr. Baier treats a 10-year old cockatiel having trouble breathing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-17 18:00:00" d="2019-08-17 19:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>A beloved poodle is rushed to surgery. Four turtles, unable to eat, get their first vet visit in 43 years and Dr. Jeff and the team head out to operate on an alligator</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-17 19:00:00" d="2019-08-17 20:00:00"><n>The Bronx Zoo</n><t>D</t>    <k>When two tigers are introduced as potential mates, it doesn’t go as smoothly as keepers had hoped. Meanwhile, a pair of African porcupines arrive at the zoo!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-17 20:00:00" d="2019-08-17 21:00:00"><n>The Aquarium</n><t>D</t>    <k>Nandi, the aquarium’s smallest manta ray, is due her annual check up and some young ruddy ducks arrive at the aquarium and are introduced to their new habitat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-17 21:00:00" d="2019-08-17 22:00:00"><n>Homestead Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Raneys create their first-ever self-automated homestead in the fierce Alaskan wilderness while firefighters Kim and Casey Boespflug are away on duty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-17 22:00:00" d="2019-08-17 23:00:00"><n>After The Attack</n><t>D</t>    <k>Stories of bravery as survivors of animal attacks recount their experiences. This time, an entire family is attacked by a lone wolf and a bison hurls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-17 23:00:00" d="2019-08-18 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>A rescue mission brings Tia and daughter Mariah face to face with a protective mama dog and her litter of seven puppies, but Villalobos is overrun with puppies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 00:00:00" d="2019-08-18 01:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>A frightening rescue sends the Villalobos team racing into the city in search of a dog reportedly hit by a car. And with kennels at peak capacity, adoption is needed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 01:00:00" d="2019-08-18 02:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia receives a call about a puppy stuck in a pipe and enlists the help of the twins to rescue the dog. Later, it’s up to Perry to help build up a shy puppy’s confidence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 02:00:00" d="2019-08-18 03:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>When it becomes apparent that a group of cats are in peril, the investigators from the Houston Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals swoop into action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 03:00:00" d="2019-08-18 03:50:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Follow the work of the Houston Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals as they tackle cases of cruelty and neglect, and promote animal welfare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 03:50:00" d="2019-08-18 04:40:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animal cruelty investigators join forces with Texas police officers in an attempt to smash one of the biggest dog fighting rings in US history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-18 04:40:00" d="2019-08-18 05:10:00"><n>Orangutan Island</n><t>D</t>    <k>82% The orangutans are still learning new skills. However, Cha Cha ignores vital lessons and curiosity leads her into the path of a deadly snake</k>  </p>
</a>
