<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="28" t="2021-07-09 06:27:59"><p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 05:00:00" d="2021-07-14 05:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 05:30:00" d="2021-07-14 06:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 06:00:00" d="2021-07-14 06:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 06:30:00" d="2021-07-14 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 07:00:00" d="2021-07-14 07:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 07:30:00" d="2021-07-14 08:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 08:00:00" d="2021-07-14 09:00:00"><n>The Aquarium</n><t>D</t>    <k>Aquariums play a vital role in sea life conservation across the globe. Now, Georgia Aquarium is sharing the remarkable stories that unfold there every day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 09:00:00" d="2021-07-14 10:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Stanley and Shelby are ferocious when they are together, so who will their owners have guests around? Plus, Finn has a habit of jumping in the babies’ crib</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 10:00:00" d="2021-07-14 11:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jackson travels to Portland to help Lee and Teresa, who called 911 on their cat Lux. After their son Jesse pulled on Lux's tail, he got clawed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 11:00:00" d="2021-07-14 12:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>An outbreak of disease in the swamps threatens the dogs. And after years of waiting for a forever home, Jackson finally gets his shot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 12:00:00" d="2021-07-14 13:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia is short-staffed, but finding a parolee who is prepared for the demands of the job is proving difficult. Then, the team races to an overwhelmed owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 13:00:00" d="2021-07-14 14:00:00"><n>Scaled</n><t>D</t>    <k>Stevie and the team design a sci-fi fantasy-themed enclosure for her Basilisk lizard. The guys add some princess magic to a showpiece for three Ball Pythons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 14:00:00" d="2021-07-14 15:00:00"><n>Crikey! It's The Irwins</n><t>D</t>    <k>It's moving day for Acco, the zoo's biggest crocodile. But his mate Cassie goes into hiding as the team races to reunite the pair in their new enclosure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 15:00:00" d="2021-07-14 16:00:00"><n>Crikey! It's The Irwins</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Irwins caravan into the Outback to release baby kangaroos and an emu onto their wildlife conservation area. But they find more animals in need of rescue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 16:00:00" d="2021-07-14 17:00:00"><n>Homestead Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>74% In Oregon, the Raneys are called in to help snowbound homesteaders. Exposed to local predators, they worry about the region’s forest fires</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 17:00:00" d="2021-07-14 18:00:00"><n>Animal Cribs</n><t>D</t>    <k>Antonio helps working dog with messy habits and turns the laundry room into a fully operational spa. The team creates a football-themed doggy paradise!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 18:00:00" d="2021-07-14 19:00:00"><n>Animal Cribs</n><t>D</t>    <k>Antonio transforms a cluttered basement housing more than 20 rescued reptiles, mammals and birds. The team build exotic enclosures and an entertainment space</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 19:00:00" d="2021-07-14 20:00:00"><n>Animal Cribs</n><t>D</t>    <k>Antonio and the team build make a mountain cabin safer for Chickie, a blind senior dog. Plus, they build a Japanese-inspired indoor dog lounge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 20:00:00" d="2021-07-14 21:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia takes in a pit bull that was rescued from awful conditions in Kuwait. Meanwhile, when a stray dog arrives at Villalobos, Earl is determined to find the owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 21:00:00" d="2021-07-14 22:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Steev and Laura have been dating for seven years, but Steev’s cat Darkness is tearing them apart. Can Jackson ease their woes?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 22:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Reality star and retired model Adrianne Curry and her boyfriend, Todd, are living with Adrianne’s menacing Siamese cat, Billy Shears</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-14 23:00:00" d="2021-07-15 00:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Steev and Laura have been dating for seven years, but Steev’s cat Darkness is tearing them apart. Can Jackson ease their woes?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 00:00:00" d="2021-07-15 01:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>When a sinkhole threatens to swallow a nearby neighbourhood, Tia teams up with cat expert Jackson Galaxy to rescue dozens of cats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 01:00:00" d="2021-07-15 02:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>A family contacts Tia after seeing their dog rescued on a previous episode. Tia confronts Earl about his erratic behaviour, and Matt makes a life-changing decision</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 02:00:00" d="2021-07-15 03:00:00"><n>Return Of The Great White Serial Killer</n><t>D</t>    <k>Seeks to find answers for a series of Great White shark attacks that have occurred with clocklike precision at the same beach, in the same month, every two years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 03:00:00" d="2021-07-15 03:50:00"><n>Extinct Or Alive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Forrest sets off on a dangerous, shark-infested search for the extinct Caribbean monk seal. He and the crew come face-to-face with a giant tiger shark</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 03:50:00" d="2021-07-15 04:40:00"><n>The Aquarium</n><t>D</t>    <k>A curious and active box turtle goes for his daily walk and two wobbegong sharks are due for a check-up. Plus, the staff prepare for puffin breeding season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2021-07-15 04:40:00" d="2021-07-15 05:00:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That?</n><t>D</t>    <k>Experts test how impressive dogs’ noses are at picking up scents even under water. Plus, how and why do fireflies glow? And, how do ostriches run so fast?</k>  </p>
</a>
