<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2020-06-01 04:28:09"><p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-08 05:10:00" d="2020-06-08 06:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Jackson works with a mother daughter duo whose lovable cats are having a territorial spraying match. Plus, he meets with troublemaking cat Bowie who’s on his last chance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-08 06:00:00" d="2020-06-08 07:00:00"><n>Safari Park Adventure</n><t>D</t>    <k>Young giraffe males risk injury to themselves and others in the herd as they begin to spar, and two different species of monkey go head to head in a puzzle-box showdown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-08 07:00:00" d="2020-06-08 08:00:00"><n>Safari Park Adventure</n><t>D</t>    <k>Two male giraffes prepare to leave the park but their departure is fraught with difficulties. Plus, how will bull rhino Kei react when he is introduced</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-08 08:00:00" d="2020-06-08 09:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>A frightening rescue sends the Villalobos team racing into the city in search of a dog reportedly hit by a car. And with kennels at peak capacity, adoption is needed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-08 09:00:00" d="2020-06-08 10:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia receives a call about a puppy stuck in a pipe and enlists the help of the twins to rescue the dog. Later, it’s up to Perry to help build up a shy puppy’s confidence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-08 10:00:00" d="2020-06-08 11:00:00"><n>Crikey! It's The Irwins</n><t>D</t>    <k>Robert helps out with a health check for the zoo's unusual-looking alligator snapping turtles. Terri and Bindi welcome seven new Lemurs from the US</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-08 11:00:00" d="2020-06-08 12:00:00"><n>Crikey! It's The Irwins</n><t>D</t>    <k>Following Steve's global conservation dream, the Irwins go to South Africa. Terri helps release a wild leopard. Bindi meets an all-female anti-poaching team</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-08 12:00:00" d="2020-06-08 13:00:00"><n>Extinct Or Alive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Forrest delves into the island of Java in Indonesia, seeking the Javan tiger. It was declared extinct in 2003, but there have been recent reported sightings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-08 13:00:00" d="2020-06-08 14:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% When Justin gave his mum Bombadil, he had no idea the cat would be a gift from hell. Buddhists Tom and Pola lived in harmony until they adopted Percy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-08 14:00:00" d="2020-06-08 14:30:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That</n><t>D</t>    <k>What are cats trying to communicate to humans? Why have some of the world’s cleverest monkeys turned to a life of crime? Experts answer these questions and more!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-08 14:30:00" d="2020-06-08 15:00:00"><n>ACE: Animal Countdown Extraordinaire</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jack and the Buccaneer strap in for danger as they count down the world’s top ten animal thrill-seekers. Featuring a bird that juggles fire with its beak!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-08 15:00:00" d="2020-06-08 16:00:00"><n>Hanging With The Hendersons</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr Ryan and Dr Tony tag team on a rare double knee surgery. A rescued cat melts hearts with his big hugs, and the family gathers at their cabin for off-road racing!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-08 16:00:00" d="2020-06-08 17:00:00"><n>Hanging With The Hendersons</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr Ross visits a donkey rescue centre to learn more about equine care. Back at the clinic, Dr Tony helps an injured puppy and Dr Ryan performs a delicate surgery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-08 17:00:00" d="2020-06-08 18:00:00"><n>Finding Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>40% The team heads to Sumatra in search of the elusive orang pendek. They venture into the jungle, in hopes of proving this mythical creature is in fact real</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-08 18:00:00" d="2020-06-08 19:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>74% Chris' work at the Kyabram Veterinary Clinic continues. Harriet, the Bearded Dragon, has a lump on her leg that her keeper is concerned about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-08 19:00:00" d="2020-06-08 20:00:00"><n>Animal Cops San Francisco</n><t>D</t>    <k>Officer Sadler fights to save a dog's life after he finds two others left to starve to death, and a woman loses her cats during a fire at her apartment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-08 20:00:00" d="2020-06-08 21:00:00"><n>River Of No Return</n><t>D</t>    <k>With dangerous rocks exposed by low water, Buck must hit high speeds to keep his jetboat safe from harm. Landing solo on a narrow airstrip tests Katie as a pilot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-08 21:00:00" d="2020-06-08 22:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>The team try to help a tiny dog with a coat so matted and filthy, they need to sedate him to remove it. It is a case Investigator Dana Moss will never forget</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-08 22:00:00" d="2020-06-08 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>It's an emotional case for Houston SPCA's animal cruelty investigators when they find a puppy that's been badly beaten and has 13 broken bones. Vets fight to save him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-08 23:00:00" d="2020-06-09 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Sui is ready for more responsibility and tests himself by taking the lead in a rescue. Later, Tia rescues a pit bull with scars that reveal a painful past</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-09 00:00:00" d="2020-06-09 01:00:00"><n>I'm Alive</n><t>D</t>    <k>67% Two friends fight for survival after they are bitten by a supposedly harmless class pet, and a family vacation becomes a nightmare when a father is mauled by a hippo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-09 01:00:00" d="2020-06-09 02:00:00"><n>Animal Cops San Francisco</n><t>D</t>    <k>Officer Sadler fights to save a dog's life after he finds two others left to starve to death, and a woman loses her cats during a fire at her apartment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-09 02:00:00" d="2020-06-09 03:00:00"><n>River Of No Return</n><t>D</t>    <k>With dangerous rocks exposed by low water, Buck must hit high speeds to keep his jetboat safe from harm. Landing solo on a narrow airstrip tests Katie as a pilot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-09 03:00:00" d="2020-06-09 03:50:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>It's an emotional case for Houston SPCA's animal cruelty investigators when they find a puppy that's been badly beaten and has 13 broken bones. Vets fight to save him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-09 03:50:00" d="2020-06-09 04:40:00"><n>Finding Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>40% The team heads to Sumatra in search of the elusive orang pendek. They venture into the jungle, in hopes of proving this mythical creature is in fact real</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-09 04:40:00" d="2020-06-09 05:10:00"><n>Meet The Orangutans</n><t>D</t>    <k>There’s a baby boom at the sanctuary as new arrivals mix with news of more on the way. The dominant male known as C.I.D is thought to be father</k>  </p>
</a>
