<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2019-08-15 22:22:48"><p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 05:10:00" d="2019-08-21 06:00:00"><n>Tanked</n><t>D</t>    <k>67% Howie Mandel wants ATM to build another tank! This time it's a surprise for his manager's company - and their an existing tank needs a major upgrade</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 06:00:00" d="2019-08-21 06:30:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% When a mother duck decides to hatch her nine babies on a high rise balcony, vet Chris, has to round them up. But their lives are in danger when the release goes wrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 06:30:00" d="2019-08-21 07:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% Chris heads to the bush when a 16-month-old Dachshund with a crazy obsession needs help - Schnitzel won't leave the new born calves alone and is putting his life in danger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 07:00:00" d="2019-08-21 07:30:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% Chris gets an emergency night call when a dog is rushed in after being hit by a taxi. The accident victim is traumatized and suffering from a punctured lung</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 07:30:00" d="2019-08-21 08:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% When Alfie, the American alligator, swallows a plastic bottle, the reptile must be caught so Chris can put his hand down the alligator's throat and check</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 08:00:00" d="2019-08-21 09:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Chief investigator Charles Jantzen gets more than he bargained for when he helps out with the removal of a rather grumpy - and obese - pot-bellied pig</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 09:00:00" d="2019-08-21 10:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Investigator Trischa Price is called out on an animal cruelty case with sinister undertones. She finds a sick horse, and nearby, some needles. What is going on?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 10:00:00" d="2019-08-21 11:00:00"><n>Crocodile Hunter</n><t>D</t>    <k>Featuring out-takes, this is a behind-the-scenes look at the scariest moments from the Crocodile Hunter series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 11:00:00" d="2019-08-21 12:00:00"><n>Alaska: The Last Frontier</n><t>D</t>    <k>Otto pulls porcupine quills out of a colt's face. Eve has conflicting thoughts about deer hunting and Atz gives Jane a lesson in rabbit skinning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 12:00:00" d="2019-08-21 13:00:00"><n>Wildest Europe</n><t>D</t>    <k>Discovers the wildlife of Europe’s waterways, including the world’s only underwater spider, the European river otter, and the Danube delta’s golden jackal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 13:00:00" d="2019-08-21 13:30:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% When a mother duck decides to hatch her nine babies on a high rise balcony, vet Chris, has to round them up. But their lives are in danger when the release goes wrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 13:30:00" d="2019-08-21 14:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% Chris heads to the bush when a 16-month-old Dachshund with a crazy obsession needs help - Schnitzel won't leave the new born calves alone and is putting his life in danger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 14:00:00" d="2019-08-21 14:30:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% Chris gets an emergency night call when a dog is rushed in after being hit by a taxi. The accident victim is traumatized and suffering from a punctured lung</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 14:30:00" d="2019-08-21 15:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% When Alfie, the American alligator, swallows a plastic bottle, the reptile must be caught so Chris can put his hand down the alligator's throat and check</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 15:00:00" d="2019-08-21 16:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>When Tia is touched by a heartfelt adoption application from a former prisoner turned martial arts fighter, she sends Tania and Mariah on an adoption road trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 16:00:00" d="2019-08-21 17:00:00"><n>Treehouse Masters</n><t>D</t>    <k>Pete heads to Alabama's Appalachia to build a super spy treehouse, featuring talking gadgets, hidden passageways, secret rooms and more!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 17:00:00" d="2019-08-21 18:00:00"><n>Amanda To The Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>Amanda and her friend go on a road trip to rescue Jedi, a boxer whose blindness doesn’t affect his energy. At the crowded shelter, she takes in 32 dogs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 18:00:00" d="2019-08-21 19:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% Chris is called out to give miniature rescue horse Charley an urgent examination, but the tiny neglected horse refuses to be caught. Plus, Lisa is worried</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 19:00:00" d="2019-08-21 20:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tempers flare at Villalobos as Tia learns that parolee Billy isn't pulling his weight. His fate is in the parolees' hands, but when things escalate, Tia intervenes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 20:00:00" d="2019-08-21 21:00:00"><n>Extinct Or Alive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Forrest delves into the island of Java in Indonesia, seeking the Javan tiger. It was declared extinct in 2003, but there have been recent reported sightings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 21:00:00" d="2019-08-21 22:00:00"><n>Alaska: The Last Frontier</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Kilchers race through the last few days of fall, prepping the cabins, winterising the bee hive, sorting the cellar, bottling raspberry mead and creating a new field</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 22:00:00" d="2019-08-21 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animal Cruelty Investigators arrive at a property to rescue some horses, but have a surprise in store when they discover a litter of puppies trapped inside a storm drain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-21 23:00:00" d="2019-08-22 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>80% Tia heads to Georgia to evaluate a prison dog program, and joins their team on a shocking rescue mission. Plus, could a surprise inspection close Villalobos down?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 00:00:00" d="2019-08-22 01:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>80% The new site is at risk when locals appeal against having a dangerous dog sanctuary in the neighbourhood. And a puppy needs help, but is it too tiny to save?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 01:00:00" d="2019-08-22 02:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animal Cruelty Investigators arrive at a property to rescue some horses, but have a surprise in store when they discover a litter of puppies trapped inside a storm drain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 02:00:00" d="2019-08-22 03:00:00"><n>Wildest Europe</n><t>D</t>    <k>Discovers the wildlife of Europe’s waterways, including the world’s only underwater spider, the European river otter, and the Danube delta’s golden jackal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 03:00:00" d="2019-08-22 03:50:00"><n>Alaska: The Last Frontier</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Kilchers race through the last few days of fall, prepping the cabins, winterising the bee hive, sorting the cellar, bottling raspberry mead and creating a new field</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 03:50:00" d="2019-08-22 04:40:00"><n>Alaska Monsters</n><t>D</t>    <k>Hot on the trail of a huge feline who has been reported in the town of Paxson, Todd devises a trap, while Levi figures out a way to wirelessly trigger it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 04:40:00" d="2019-08-22 05:10:00"><n>Orangutan Island</n><t>D</t>    <k>81% The island vets are working around the clock to unravel the mystery orangutan illness. But when Bertha finds abscesses, further confusion halts progress</k>  </p>
</a>
