<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2019-08-15 22:22:55"><p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 05:10:00" d="2019-08-22 06:00:00"><n>Tanked</n><t>D</t>    <k>Pianoworks in New York wants Wayde and Brett to build them their own piano-shaped tank made from acrylic. Will the guys hit the right note?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 06:00:00" d="2019-08-22 06:30:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% When young Labrador Cino suffers bad seizures and uncontrollable shakes, Lisa thinks the dog has swallowed a toxin that is attacking her system</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 06:30:00" d="2019-08-22 07:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% A tiny terrier is brought in as an emergency after being savaged by a pit bull terrier. Despite his terrible wounds, the dog turns out to be one of Lisa's bravest patients</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 07:00:00" d="2019-08-22 07:30:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% When a King Charles cavalier spaniel raids a lingerie drawer and eats a G-string, will they have to operate or can Lisa find another solution for the cheeky spaniel?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 07:30:00" d="2019-08-22 08:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% When Chris leads an Australian vet team overseas to help the animal victims of Fiji's devastating cyclone, their first patient is a badly injured horse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 08:00:00" d="2019-08-22 09:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>SPCA investigators are called out on a shocking case – to rescue a 25-year-old chimpanzee that has been found living alone in a cage at his owner's house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 09:00:00" d="2019-08-22 10:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Investigator Jennifer Francis helps police seize four emaciated horses and a calf following a heated exchange with the owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 10:00:00" d="2019-08-22 11:00:00"><n>Crocodile Hunter</n><t>D</t>    <k>Fraser Island is the largest sand island in the world. The late Steve Irwin meets dingoes, goannas and underwater life in the freshwater lakes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 11:00:00" d="2019-08-22 12:00:00"><n>Alaska: The Last Frontier</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Kilchers race through the last few days of fall, prepping the cabins, winterising the bee hive, sorting the cellar, bottling raspberry mead and creating a new field</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 12:00:00" d="2019-08-22 13:00:00"><n>Wildest Europe</n><t>D</t>    <k>Explores the wildlife of Europe’s astonishing woodland and forested habitats, including Europe’s third largest predator, the Eurasian lynx</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 13:00:00" d="2019-08-22 13:30:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% When young Labrador Cino suffers bad seizures and uncontrollable shakes, Lisa thinks the dog has swallowed a toxin that is attacking her system</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 13:30:00" d="2019-08-22 14:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% A tiny terrier is brought in as an emergency after being savaged by a pit bull terrier. Despite his terrible wounds, the dog turns out to be one of Lisa's bravest patients</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 14:00:00" d="2019-08-22 14:30:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% When a King Charles cavalier spaniel raids a lingerie drawer and eats a G-string, will they have to operate or can Lisa find another solution for the cheeky spaniel?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 14:30:00" d="2019-08-22 15:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% When Chris leads an Australian vet team overseas to help the animal victims of Fiji's devastating cyclone, their first patient is a badly injured horse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 15:00:00" d="2019-08-22 16:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tempers flare at Villalobos as Tia learns that parolee Billy isn't pulling his weight. His fate is in the parolees' hands, but when things escalate, Tia intervenes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 16:00:00" d="2019-08-22 17:00:00"><n>Treehouse Masters</n><t>D</t>    <k>The crew is at an alpaca farm to build a lodge inspired by US National Parks. They create a structure with mountain views and cable bridge entrance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 17:00:00" d="2019-08-22 18:00:00"><n>Amanda To The Rescue</n><t>D</t>    <k>A new mum Chihuahua and her eight puppies are ready to go to their homes. Amanda takes Splat, a special needs bulldog puppy with swimmers’ syndrome, into her care</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 18:00:00" d="2019-08-22 19:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>72% While Dr Lisa is confronted with a dog that suffers from a bizarre eye problem, it is time for an emotional goodbye for one of Dr Chris’s favourite patient</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 19:00:00" d="2019-08-22 20:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia sends Tania and Mariah to New Orleans to rescue a pit bull left tied to a metal post; but the girls are forced into their most unusual rescue to date</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 20:00:00" d="2019-08-22 21:00:00"><n>The Vet Life</n><t>D</t>    <k>Yuki the bulldog ate something she shouldn’t have, now Dr. Blue needs to find it. And, the rescue cat Dr. Lavigne adopted needs care after its double amputation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 21:00:00" d="2019-08-22 22:00:00"><n>Alaska: The Last Frontier</n><t>D</t>    <k>After a long winter, cabin fever is setting in. Eivin and Atz get caught overnight in the backcountry and Otto gets an orphan calf to connect with an unwilling mother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 22:00:00" d="2019-08-22 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animal Cruelty Investigators from the Houston SPCA discover an elderly family overrun with cats all living under one roof dangerously close to collapse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-22 23:00:00" d="2019-08-23 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia puts out the word that she is looking for more parolees - but will she like the guys who show up for work? And an abandoned pit bull is found chained in a field</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-23 00:00:00" d="2019-08-23 01:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls And Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>An urgent call about a starving pit bull leads to a long-distance rescue, and the race is on to save an injured stray. Meanwhile, rats freak out some parolees</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-23 01:00:00" d="2019-08-23 02:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animal Cruelty Investigators from the Houston SPCA discover an elderly family overrun with cats all living under one roof dangerously close to collapse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-23 02:00:00" d="2019-08-23 03:00:00"><n>Wildest Europe</n><t>D</t>    <k>Discovers Europe’s highest mountain range and one of its largest intact ecological ranges, home to specialised animal species including the alpine ibex and the grey wolf</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-23 03:00:00" d="2019-08-23 03:50:00"><n>Alaska: The Last Frontier</n><t>D</t>    <k>After a long winter, cabin fever is setting in. Eivin and Atz get caught overnight in the backcountry and Otto gets an orphan calf to connect with an unwilling mother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-23 03:50:00" d="2019-08-23 04:40:00"><n>Alaska Monsters</n><t>D</t>    <k>38% The team heads to southern Alaska to investigate sightings of a highly temperamental Bigfoot. Todd and Rhett build a huge, electrified tepee to catch it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-08-23 04:40:00" d="2019-08-23 05:10:00"><n>Orangutan Island</n><t>D</t>    <k>81% Nine months have passed on the island - is the group's hierarchy beginning to shift? Although Hamlet continues to lead, the others are being distracted by romance!</k>  </p>
</a>
