<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2020-04-13 04:24:36"><p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 05:10:00" d="2020-04-20 06:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>78% Andy loves girlfriend Alyssa, but hates her ‘demon cat’, Tosh, who turned after he moved in with her. Eric and Kaotar's problem cat, Vincent, tries anything to escape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 06:00:00" d="2020-04-20 07:00:00"><n>Preposterous Pets</n><t>D</t>    <k>Meet the lizard obsessive who changed his name to Mr Lizard Lover and found fame taking photos of his scaly friends posing as humans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 07:00:00" d="2020-04-20 08:00:00"><n>Preposterous Pets</n><t>D</t>    <k>An Oklahoma woman cares for a kangaroo, a man walks his pet jaguar in Mexico City and a Buddhist cover himself in a 1000 scorpions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 08:00:00" d="2020-04-20 09:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>A dangerously ill dog is rescued by Tania and Tia from the streets of New Orleans. Later, Chong takes a turn for the worse as his cancerous tumour grows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 09:00:00" d="2020-04-20 10:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mariah is devastated when she learns that a friend has passed away. Later, a couple from Tia’s past is interested in adopting four dogs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 10:00:00" d="2020-04-20 10:30:00"><n>Meet The Sloths</n><t>D</t>    <k>Two rehabilitated sloths are released back into the wild, Claire reveals the athletic secrets of the jungle gym and Sloth Scientist Becky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 10:30:00" d="2020-04-20 11:00:00"><n>Meet The Sloths</n><t>D</t>    <k>Sanctuary favourite, Sidwiggy, puts a new tracking system to the test, Claire becomes a sloth anger management counsellor and Becky reveals the secret life of sloth fur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 11:00:00" d="2020-04-20 12:00:00"><n>Preposterous Pets</n><t>D</t>    <k>In Colorado, alligator-mad father and daughter duo wrestle with a few of their 350 ferocious reptiles. Plus, a family has an obsession for macaque monkeys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 12:00:00" d="2020-04-20 13:00:00"><n>Crikey! It's The Irwins</n><t>D</t>    <k>Terri welcomes Mballa, a new cheetah cub from South Africa, to the Australia Zoo family. Meanwhile, Robert sets out to save a stranded platypus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 13:00:00" d="2020-04-20 14:00:00"><n>The Bronx Zoo</n><t>D</t>    <k>Armani the Aardvark suffers from a mouth infection which seems to only get worse every day. Plus, the brown bears keep digging up and destroying their exhibit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 14:00:00" d="2020-04-20 14:30:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That</n><t>D</t>    <k>How does a squirrel take on a dangerous rattle snake? What makes eagles’ eyes so powerful? Plus, why is the planet overrun with bugs? Experts answer these questions!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 14:30:00" d="2020-04-20 15:00:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>Experts examine incredible footage of a lone dolphin that gets muddy. Plus, why is it possible that a snake could exist totally undetected by predators?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 15:00:00" d="2020-04-20 16:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>When a beloved dog needs knee surgery, Dr Jeff may be his only hope. Then Dr Nichols and Dr Petra team up to fix a cat’s broken elbow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 16:00:00" d="2020-04-20 17:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr Jeff battles to save a puppy with broken ribs and internal bleeding. And Dr Baier attempts surgery he’s never done before to treat a family’s beloved rat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 17:00:00" d="2020-04-20 18:00:00"><n>Wild Hawaii</n><t>D</t>    <k>Explore the sublime nature of the Hawaiian Islands and discover of the islands' contrasting ecosystems accommodate many endangered species</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 18:00:00" d="2020-04-20 19:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>74% More creatures from the Cook Islands are treated by Chris and his team, including a cat called ‘Small One’ who is missing part of his nose, and a massive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 19:00:00" d="2020-04-20 20:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Phoenix</n><t>D</t>    <k>As summer arrives, temperatures exceed 100F. Mark rescues a skinny Rottweiler chained out in the hot sun, and investigators seek out kittens trapped under roof tiles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 20:00:00" d="2020-04-20 21:00:00"><n>Wild Australia</n><t>D</t>    <k>Australia is one of the largest and most extreme wildernesses on earth. Here, the indigenous Aborigines have survived by observing and learning from nature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 21:00:00" d="2020-04-20 22:00:00"><n>Alaska Monsters</n><t>D</t>    <k>38% The team investigates the Otterman who is believed to have the ability to shape-shift. Todd builds a Ring of Fire trap, while the rest of the team utilises an airboat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 22:00:00" d="2020-04-20 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>A senior investigator is rushed to the ER during a raid at the home of an elderly cat collector. Plus, the SPCA rescue a wounded Doberman on the side of the road</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-20 23:00:00" d="2020-04-21 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia comes to the rescue of five injured dogs who have been used for fighting. Plus, parolee Spencer is released from jail and returns to Villalobos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 00:00:00" d="2020-04-21 01:00:00"><n>Mountain Monsters</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buck makes a shocking discovery that leads him to a secret garden. Meanwhile the rest of the team help Jeff make a daring escape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 01:00:00" d="2020-04-21 02:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Phoenix</n><t>D</t>    <k>As summer arrives, temperatures exceed 100F. Mark rescues a skinny Rottweiler chained out in the hot sun, and investigators seek out kittens trapped under roof tiles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 02:00:00" d="2020-04-21 03:00:00"><n>Wild Australia</n><t>D</t>    <k>Australia is one of the largest and most extreme wildernesses on earth. Here, the indigenous Aborigines have survived by observing and learning from nature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 03:00:00" d="2020-04-21 03:50:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>A senior investigator is rushed to the ER during a raid at the home of an elderly cat collector. Plus, the SPCA rescue a wounded Doberman on the side of the road</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 03:50:00" d="2020-04-21 04:40:00"><n>Wild Hawaii</n><t>D</t>    <k>Explore the sublime nature of the Hawaiian Islands and discover of the islands' contrasting ecosystems accommodate many endangered species</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-04-21 04:40:00" d="2020-04-21 05:10:00"><n>How Do Animals Do That</n><t>D</t>    <k>How do cats always land on their feet? How do hummingbirds fly when it is raining? Plus, does a subterranean mammal on the secret to longevity?</k>  </p>
</a>
