<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2020-05-26 04:29:19"><p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 05:10:00" d="2020-06-02 06:00:00"><n>My Cat From Hell</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jackson visits a blind cat suffering in a chaotic living environment. He then meets cat, Jude, who is a darling during the day - but a nightmare at night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 06:00:00" d="2020-06-02 07:00:00"><n>Bad Dog!</n><t>D</t>    <k>Monkey Boo has free reign of the house and his owner's heart and Duke, a Labradoodle, is obsessed with getting into anything that might contain food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 07:00:00" d="2020-06-02 08:00:00"><n>Bad Dog!</n><t>D</t>    <k>Chocolate lab Max has his own private wing of the house and cool cat Didga rides her skateboard to the beach. Plus, a micro-pig keeps rummaging bins for food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 08:00:00" d="2020-06-02 09:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mariah is devastated when she learns that a friend has passed away. Later, a couple from Tia’s past is interested in adopting four dogs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 09:00:00" d="2020-06-02 10:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Hurricane season is approaching and Tia prepares for the worst. Later, Villalobos employee Rico steps up to the plate when his grandparents adopt a shy dog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 10:00:00" d="2020-06-02 11:00:00"><n>America's Cutest Pets</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why are some cats really fluffy, what is the secret of feline stealth, what makes some cats fussy about their food, and which is the cutest cat of all?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 11:00:00" d="2020-06-02 12:00:00"><n>America's Cutest Pets</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why do dogs make great friends, how can you tell when a dog feels guilty, how do dogs have fun, and which is the cutest dog in the world?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 12:00:00" d="2020-06-02 13:00:00"><n>Extinct Or Alive</n><t>D</t>    <k>Forrest teams up with an expert in Newfoundland seeking the white wolf, which was declared extinct in 1930. They meet a hunter convinced he shot one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 13:00:00" d="2020-06-02 14:00:00"><n>The Zoo: San Diego</n><t>D</t>    <k>Two influential zoos in San Diego provide a unique look at their animals, keepers and veterinarians and explain the unique projects that help fund the organisations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 14:00:00" d="2020-06-02 14:30:00"><n>Nature's Strangest Mysteries: Solved</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why would goats risk their lives to climb an almost vertical wall? Plus, what happens when a zebra has no stripes? Experts explain this and more!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 14:30:00" d="2020-06-02 15:00:00"><n>ACE: Animal Countdown Extraordinaire</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jack and the Buccaneer count down the top ten ‘bites’ of the animal world. They’ll calculate each animals jaw strength to rank the best</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 15:00:00" d="2020-06-02 16:00:00"><n>Animal ER</n><t>D</t>    <k>Oncologist Jenny Helm is faced with much-loved family cat Misha, who has a worrying lump in her chest and a stray pup called Ellie who is brought</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 16:00:00" d="2020-06-02 17:00:00"><n>Animal ER</n><t>D</t>    <k>Oorla, an Alaskan Malamute is brought into the hospital after having a cancerous lump removed. But when vets find the cancer has spread, can a course</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 17:00:00" d="2020-06-02 18:00:00"><n>Finding Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>40% The researchers make a major breakthrough whilst investigating several Sasquatch sightings in central Oklahoma. Have they finally found Bigfoot DNA?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 18:00:00" d="2020-06-02 19:00:00"><n>Bondi Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>74% Join Dr. Chris Brown at his commercial veterinary clinic in the Sydney suburb of Bondi. Today he treats Splodge the escape artist, a randy rabbit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 19:00:00" d="2020-06-02 20:00:00"><n>Animal Cops San Francisco</n><t>D</t>    <k>A dead puppy is found chained up in an abandoned house; will its wicked owner be brought to justice? Plus, a cat hoarder is encouraged to give up some pets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 20:00:00" d="2020-06-02 21:00:00"><n>The Zoo</n><t>D</t>    <k>The zoo awaits the arrival of a snow leopard's fourth cub. A pair of Andean condors embrace their new enclosure, and a squirmy binturong fights his annual vaccination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 21:00:00" d="2020-06-02 22:00:00"><n>Crikey! It's The Irwins</n><t>D</t>    <k>Robert follows in Steve's steps wrangling Utah, a highly venomous King Cobra. A vet from the zoo’s hospital, Dr. Amber, visits Tandora to treat wild Koalas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 22:00:00" d="2020-06-02 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Boris the boar has been abandoned without food or water in disgusting conditions. The race is on to free him and give him a better life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-02 23:00:00" d="2020-06-03 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>After her beloved dog passes away, an adopter comes to VRC hoping to fill the void in her heart. Meanwhile, Louise and Matt rescue a dog that was hit by a car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-03 00:00:00" d="2020-06-03 01:00:00"><n>I'm Alive</n><t>D</t>    <k>67% Follow extraordinary tales of survival. A farmer is bitten by a cobra hidden under his pillow and a teenager on a rafting trip is mauled by a black bear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-03 01:00:00" d="2020-06-03 02:00:00"><n>Animal Cops San Francisco</n><t>D</t>    <k>A dead puppy is found chained up in an abandoned house; will its wicked owner be brought to justice? Plus, a cat hoarder is encouraged to give up some pets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-03 02:00:00" d="2020-06-03 03:00:00"><n>The Zoo</n><t>D</t>    <k>The zoo awaits the arrival of a snow leopard's fourth cub. A pair of Andean condors embrace their new enclosure, and a squirmy binturong fights his annual vaccination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-03 03:00:00" d="2020-06-03 03:50:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Boris the boar has been abandoned without food or water in disgusting conditions. The race is on to free him and give him a better life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-03 03:50:00" d="2020-06-03 04:40:00"><n>Finding Bigfoot</n><t>D</t>    <k>40% The researchers make a major breakthrough whilst investigating several Sasquatch sightings in central Oklahoma. Have they finally found Bigfoot DNA?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2020-06-03 04:40:00" d="2020-06-03 05:10:00"><n>Meet The Orangutans</n><t>D</t>    <k>One orphan is new on the scene, and needs another, more experienced one to help them bed in. The babies are at high risk from parasites ingested from the ground</k>  </p>
</a>
