<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2019-07-11 00:20:09"><p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 05:10:00" d="2019-07-17 06:00:00"><n>Tanked</n><t>D</t>    <k>67% World-famous DJ Steve Aoki wants a custom-made, three-headed dragon on the verge of escape inside his tank! The guys must ensure this job is as outrageous as the DJ!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 06:00:00" d="2019-07-17 07:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jeff and his team head to a remote town where they encounter an unexpected animal. In Denver, Dr Amy treats a kitten with a mysterious injury</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 07:00:00" d="2019-07-17 08:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr Jeff helps a remote town which has become overwhelmed with feral cats. Plus, a staff member’s dog needs emergency surgery and Jeff rushes to save a Chihuahua</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 08:00:00" d="2019-07-17 09:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Investigators rescue an abandoned mare and her newly born foal. The baby is in serious condition, but the Houston SPCA team pulls out all the stops to save him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 09:00:00" d="2019-07-17 10:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>Stormy weather brings a flurry of emergency calls into the shelter. After heavy overnight rain, cruelty Investigator Barbra Christiansen is called to rescue a horse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 10:00:00" d="2019-07-17 11:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia heads to a dangerous part of New Orleans to rescue a mama dog left to die. And, a tropical storm threatens to disrupt Tania and Perry's wedding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 11:00:00" d="2019-07-17 12:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>A look back at the most memorable moments of the season. Including never-before-seen moments, a look behind the scenes, and a chance to catch up with past favourites</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 12:00:00" d="2019-07-17 13:00:00"><n>Mekong: Soul Of A River</n><t>D</t>    <k>The story of the mighty Mekong river continues through Laos and Thailand, illuminating the ancient cultures that embraced the river and how the river has changed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 13:00:00" d="2019-07-17 14:00:00"><n>Mekong: Soul Of A River</n><t>D</t>    <k>The journey along the Mekong reaches China, where steep canyons fall from the Tibetan plateau. Diverse species roam, such as the elusive snow leopard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 14:00:00" d="2019-07-17 15:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dr. Jeff treats a puppy suffering from a deadly virus. And, he must gain the trust of rescued wolves to help an ailing member of the pack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 15:00:00" d="2019-07-17 16:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>The crew race the clock as they undergo a tough rescue mission. With animal control ready to take over, Tia must save the group of dogs before it’s too late</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 16:00:00" d="2019-07-17 17:00:00"><n>Tanked</n><t>D</t>    <k>67% Businessman Brad Jennings wants to complete his new office with three tanks. The guys work on three complementary interiors which include a working fireplace!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 17:00:00" d="2019-07-17 18:00:00"><n>Dr. Jeff: Rocky Mountain Vet</n><t>D</t>    <k>A puppy is rescued from a kill shelter in Oklahoma. And a dog eats a box of toxic chocolates infused with marijuana, and is rushed to the clinic for treatment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 18:00:00" d="2019-07-17 19:00:00"><n>Air Jaws: Fin Of Fury</n><t>D</t>    <k>In 2011, a great white shark called Colossus swam off never to be seen again. Now, a team of shark experts has assembled to bring this Giant up from the deep</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 19:00:00" d="2019-07-17 20:00:00"><n>Wild Hawaii</n><t>D</t>    <k>Explore the sublime nature of the Hawaiian Islands and discover of the islands' contrasting ecosystems accommodate many endangered species</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 20:00:00" d="2019-07-17 21:00:00"><n>Alaskan Bush People</n><t>D</t>    <k>Billy falls seriously ill and is forced to seek medical help. Meanwhile, the kids are left to fend for themselves and build a large raft to help move lumber</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 21:00:00" d="2019-07-17 22:00:00"><n>Alaska Monsters</n><t>D</t>    <k>38% The team investigates the Otterman who is believed to have the ability to shape-shift. Todd builds a Ring of Fire trap, while the rest of the team utilises an airboat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 22:00:00" d="2019-07-17 23:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>When Barney, a dog with an embedded collar, is spotted in the Houston countryside Investigator Kristi Franks is called into action and a desperate chase ensues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-17 23:00:00" d="2019-07-18 00:00:00"><n>Pit Bulls &amp; Parolees</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tia, Tania and Mariah take a look back at the most adorable moments – from surprising rescues and teary reunions to parolee antics and heart-warming adoptions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-18 00:00:00" d="2019-07-18 01:00:00"><n>I'm Alive</n><t>D</t>    <k>69% Follow extraordinary tales of survival. Craig is attacked by a bull shark in Florida and Piet by a leopard at his daughter's wedding. Will they make it?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-18 01:00:00" d="2019-07-18 02:00:00"><n>Animal Cops Houston</n><t>D</t>    <k>When Barney, a dog with an embedded collar, is spotted in the Houston countryside Investigator Kristi Franks is called into action and a desperate chase ensues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-18 02:00:00" d="2019-07-18 03:00:00"><n>Wild Hawaii</n><t>D</t>    <k>Explore the sublime nature of the Hawaiian Islands and discover of the islands' contrasting ecosystems accommodate many endangered species</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-18 03:00:00" d="2019-07-18 03:50:00"><n>Alaskan Bush People</n><t>D</t>    <k>Billy falls seriously ill and is forced to seek medical help. Meanwhile, the kids are left to fend for themselves and build a large raft to help move lumber</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-18 03:50:00" d="2019-07-18 04:40:00"><n>Alaska Monsters</n><t>D</t>    <k>38% The team investigates the Otterman who is believed to have the ability to shape-shift. Todd builds a Ring of Fire trap, while the rest of the team utilises an airboat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1117" o="2019-07-18 04:40:00" d="2019-07-18 05:10:00"><n>E-Vets: The Interns</n><t>D</t>    <k>Meet three of the seven new doctors at Alameda East Veterinary Hospital. It's the beginning of their year-long internship and it's no easy start</k>  </p>
</a>
