<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-08-15 22:52:26"><p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-22 06:00:00" d="2019-08-22 07:45:00" c="1"><n>A Wizard's Tale</n><t>F</t>    <k>Family animation about a normal kid whisked away to a magical kingdom robbed of laughter and happiness by a grumpy wizard. With the voices of Lily Collins and Toby Kebbell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-22 07:45:00" d="2019-08-22 09:25:00" c="1"><n>The Female Brain</n><t>F</t>    <k>Rom-com conventions get a brain scan as neuroscientist Whitney Cummings looks into the biochemistry of the female brain. With Sofia Vergara and Westworld's James Marsden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-22 09:25:00" d="2019-08-22 11:05:00" c="1"><n>Ingrid Goes West</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% It's Single White Female for the smartphone era as troubled Aubrey Plaza latches onto LA influencer Elizabeth Olsen. and won't let go. Dark comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-22 11:05:00" d="2019-08-22 13:35:00" c="1"><n>Avengers: Infinity War</n><t>F</t>    <k>84% The Avengers assemble once more, coming together to stop the universe-destroying plans of mighty villain Thanos. Breakneck superhero adventure with Robert Downey Jr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-22 13:35:00" d="2019-08-22 15:35:00" c="1"><n>Prince Of Persia: The Sands Of Time</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Jake Gyllenhaal is the muscle-bound monarch out to save his kingdom from being destroyed by a magical artefact. Spectacular action with Gemma Arterton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-22 15:35:00" d="2019-08-22 17:35:00" c="1"><n>Patti Cake$</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Feelgood underdog tale following an unlikely New Jersey rapper desperate to escape her humdrum life and make it big. Danielle Macdonald stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-22 17:35:00" d="2019-08-22 19:30:00" c="1"><n>The Senator</n><t>F</t>    <k>Senator Ted Kennedy (Jason Clarke) struggles to save his political career and maintain his family's legacy after a tragic accident. Historical drama with Kate Mara</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-22 19:30:00" d="2019-08-22 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Avengers: Infinity War</n><t>F</t>    <k>84% The Avengers assemble once more, coming together to stop the universe-destroying plans of mighty villain Thanos. Breakneck superhero adventure with Robert Downey Jr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-22 22:00:00" d="2019-08-23 00:00:00" c="1"><n>Prince Of Persia: The Sands Of Time</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Jake Gyllenhaal is the muscle-bound monarch out to save his kingdom from being destroyed by a magical artefact. Spectacular action with Gemma Arterton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-23 00:00:00" d="2019-08-23 01:35:00" c="1"><n>A Quiet Place</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% Survival thriller following a family living in constant fear of giant, reptile-like creatures who hunt by sound. John Krasinski and Emily Blunt star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-23 01:35:00" d="2019-08-23 03:30:00" c="1"><n>Searching</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% When his daughter goes missing, a widowed dad trawls her social media in a desperate attempt to find her. But can he handle what he uncovers? Thriller starring Jon Cho</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-23 03:30:00" d="2019-08-23 05:10:00" c="1"><n>Lucky</n><t>F</t>    <k>The late Harry Dean Stanton stars as Lucky, a 90-year-old atheist who embarks on a spiritual journey in a bid to find enlightenment as he faces his own mortality</k>  </p>
</a>
