<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-04-15 04:36:30"><p id_tv="1118" o="2020-04-22 05:45:00" d="2020-04-22 07:30:00" c="1"><n>Bedtime Stories</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% From the Old West to ancient Greece, hotel handyman Adam Sandler finds his bedtime stories become reality after lights out. Vibrant fantasy adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-04-22 07:30:00" d="2020-04-22 10:45:00" c="1"><n>King Kong</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Oscar-winning adventure, with Jack Black as an ambitious filmmaker whose star Naomi Watts is snatched by a terrifying giant ape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-04-22 10:45:00" d="2020-04-22 12:35:00" c="1"><n>The Nutcracker And The Four Realms</n><t>F</t>    <k>56% Disney twist on a classic tale, as heroine Clara (Mackenzie Foy) discovers a magical land beset by conflict. Fantasy with Keira Knightley and Helen Mirren</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-04-22 12:35:00" d="2020-04-22 14:10:00" c="1"><n u="Men In Black">Men In Black II</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% With the scum of the universe menacing Earth again, agent Will Smith brings back Tommy Lee Jones to kick alien backside. Comic sequel. Mild fantasy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-04-22 14:10:00" d="2020-04-22 16:15:00" c="1"><n>Instant Family</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% A couple decide to adopt, but get more than they bargained for when they take in a rebellious teen and her two siblings. Comedy-drama with Mark Wahlberg and Rose Byrne</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-04-22 16:15:00" d="2020-04-22 18:15:00" c="1"><n u="Aftermath, The">Aftermath, The (2019)</n><t>F</t>    <k>In post-war Hamburg, tensions arise for a British colonel and his wife after they move into a house with a German widower. Drama starring Keira Knightley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-04-22 18:15:00" d="2020-04-22 20:25:00" c="1"><n>Godzilla</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% As the legendary monster resurfaces, will he prove to be humanity's unlikely saviour? Dazzling action blockbuster with Bryan Cranston and Aaron Taylor-Johnson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-04-22 20:25:00" d="2020-04-22 23:25:00" c="1"><n u="Men In Black">Men In Black II</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% With the scum of the universe menacing Earth again, agent Will Smith brings back Tommy Lee Jones to kick alien backside. Comic sequel. Mild fantasy</k>  </p>
</a>
