<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-08-15 22:52:23"><p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-21 05:10:00" d="2019-08-21 07:00:00" c="1"><n>Monster Family</n><t>F</t>    <k>The first Sky Cinema Original Film sees a young family cursed by a witch and transformed into monsters. Animated comedy with the voices of Emily Watson and Jason Isaacs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-21 07:00:00" d="2019-08-21 09:20:00" c="1"><n>Call Me By Your Name</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% Oscar-winning drama charting the summer romance between precocious teen Timothee Chalamet and grad student Armie Hammer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-21 09:20:00" d="2019-08-21 11:20:00" c="1"><n>The Exception</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Jai Courtney stars as a German soldier who falls for maid Lily James while keeping a watchful eye over the exiled Kaiser Wilhelm II. WWII drama with Christopher Plummer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-21 11:20:00" d="2019-08-21 13:15:00" c="1"><n>Juliet, Naked</n><t>F</t>    <k>A relationship is turned upside down by a woman's chance encounter with an obscure rocker who has an obsessive fan - her boyfriend. Charming rom-com with Ethan Hawke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-21 13:15:00" d="2019-08-21 15:50:00" c="1"><n>First Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Damien Chazelle's biographical drama stars Ryan Gosling as American astronaut Neil Armstrong in the years leading up to the Apollo 11 mission to the moon. With Claire Foy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-21 15:50:00" d="2019-08-21 17:50:00" c="1"><n>Total Recall</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% Philip K Dick adaptation, with Colin Farrell as a future-world factory worker on the run and struggling to know what's real</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-21 17:50:00" d="2019-08-21 20:05:00" c="1"><n>John Carter</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% US civil war veteran Taylor Kitsch is thrown into an alien conflict when he is transported to Mars. Epic fantasy with Willem Dafoe and Mark Strong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-21 20:05:00" d="2019-08-21 22:00:00" c="1"><n>The Darkest Minds</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% It's kids vs adults when a mysterious pandemic wipes out most of the children, leaving those who survive with superpowers. Dystopian thriller starring Amandla Stenberg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-21 22:00:00" d="2019-08-22 00:25:00" c="1"><n>First Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Damien Chazelle's biographical drama stars Ryan Gosling as American astronaut Neil Armstrong in the years leading up to the Apollo 11 mission to the moon. With Claire Foy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-22 00:25:00" d="2019-08-22 02:30:00" c="1"><n>Ant-Man And The Wasp</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Ant-Man suits up once more, teaming with The Wasp on an urgent mission to uncover secrets from the past. Playful superhero sequel starring Paul Rudd and Evangeline Lilly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-22 02:30:00" d="2019-08-22 04:15:00" c="1"><n>The Nun</n><t>F</t>    <k>54% A priest and a novice nun uncover the order's terrible secret and battle a malevolent force while investigating the apparent suicide of a Romanian nun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-22 04:15:00" d="2019-08-22 06:00:00" c="1"><n>Unfriended: Dark Web</n><t>F</t>    <k>Spine-chilling horror starring Colin Woodell as a teenager who makes a series of disturbing discoveries when he boots up a second-hand laptop</k>  </p>
</a>
