<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-08-09 01:42:09"><p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-15 06:30:00" d="2019-08-15 08:30:00" c="1"><n>Just Go With It</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% When Adam Sandler's dream date mistakenly thinks he's married, assistant Jennifer Aniston steps in to play the wife he's pretending to divorce. Romcom with Nicole Kidman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-15 08:30:00" d="2019-08-15 11:00:00" c="1"><n>Avengers: Infinity War</n><t>F</t>    <k>84% The Avengers assemble once more, coming together to stop the universe-destroying plans of mighty villain Thanos. Breakneck superhero adventure with Robert Downey Jr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-15 11:00:00" d="2019-08-15 12:45:00" c="1"><n>Upgrade</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% A mugging victim left widowed and quadriplegic is offered an AI implant cure. With his new mobility comes superhuman strength and a thirst for revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-15 12:45:00" d="2019-08-15 14:35:00" c="1"><n>Life Of The Party</n><t>F</t>    <k>57% Back-to-school comedy starring Melissa McCarthy as a down-on-her-luck fortysomething who decides to finally finish her degree - at the same college as her daughter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-15 14:35:00" d="2019-08-15 16:35:00" c="1"><n>The International</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Interpol agent Clive Owen and attorney Naomi Watts travel the globe to bring down a corrupt bank suspected of arms trading. Stylish spy thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-15 16:35:00" d="2019-08-15 18:30:00" c="1"><n u="Daddy's Home">Daddy's Home 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% Tensions boil over when the dad-stepdad double team of Will Ferrell and Mark Wahlberg invite their fathers over for Christmas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-15 18:30:00" d="2019-08-15 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Avengers: Infinity War</n><t>F</t>    <k>84% The Avengers assemble once more, coming together to stop the universe-destroying plans of mighty villain Thanos. Breakneck superhero adventure with Robert Downey Jr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-15 21:00:00" d="2019-08-15 22:45:00" c="1"><n>Upgrade</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% A mugging victim left widowed and quadriplegic is offered an AI implant cure. With his new mobility comes superhuman strength and a thirst for revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-15 22:45:00" d="2019-08-16 00:55:00" c="1"><n u="The Equalizer">The Equalizer 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% Denzel Washington reprises his role as retired CIA agent Robert McCall in this fast-paced thriller. The murder of an old friend triggers a relentless quest for revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-16 00:55:00" d="2019-08-16 03:00:00" c="1"><n>SuperFly</n><t>F</t>    <k>51% A drug lord decides it's time to bow out of the game - but not before one last deal. Unfortunately for him, it looks like it's going to be the toughest one yet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-16 03:00:00" d="2019-08-16 04:35:00" c="1"><n>Slender Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>33% Four girls come to the horrifying realisation that the creepy legend 'Slender Man' may be all too real, after they try to summon him, and one of them vanishes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-16 04:35:00" d="2019-08-16 06:30:00" c="1"><n>Flatliners</n><t>F</t>    <k>53% Sci-fi horror remake about a group of young medical students whose experiments with near-death experiences take a sinister turn</k>  </p>
</a>
