<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2019-08-10 01:39:29"><p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-16 06:30:00" d="2019-08-16 08:15:00" c="1"><n>Ali &amp; Nino</n><t>F</t>    <k>As Azerbaijan fights for its independence, a young Muslim man attempts to build a life with his Christian lover. Romantic drama from Senna and Amy director Asif Kapadia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-16 08:15:00" d="2019-08-16 09:55:00" c="1"><n>Peter Rabbit</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Beatrix Potter adaptation with James Corden voicing the mischievous rabbit whose feud with the McGregors reaches new heights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-16 09:55:00" d="2019-08-16 11:55:00" c="1"><n>Slaughterhouse Rulez</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% Chaos descends on an esteemed British boarding school when a mysterious sinkhole appears and unleashes pure terror. Comedy horror with Simon Pegg and Asa Butterfield</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-16 11:55:00" d="2019-08-16 14:00:00" c="1"><n>Jumanji: Welcome To The Jungle</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Four teens in detention discover an old video game that sucks them into the dangerous world of Jumanji. Dwayne Johnson stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-16 14:00:00" d="2019-08-16 16:05:00" c="1"><n>Same Kind Of Different As Me</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Wealthy married couple Greg Kinnear and Renee Zellweger discover a renewed sense of purpose when they befriend homeless drifter Djimon Hounsou</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-16 16:05:00" d="2019-08-16 18:20:00" c="1"><n>Fantastic Beasts: The Crimes Of Grindelwald</n><t>F</t>    <k>83% Newt Scamander and Albus Dumbledore try to take down the dark wizard Gellert Grindelwald in the second instalment of the series written by JK Rowling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-16 18:20:00" d="2019-08-16 20:00:00" c="1"><n>Peter Rabbit</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% Beatrix Potter adaptation with James Corden voicing the mischievous rabbit whose feud with the McGregors reaches new heights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-16 20:00:00" d="2019-08-16 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Slaughterhouse Rulez</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% Chaos descends on an esteemed British boarding school when a mysterious sinkhole appears and unleashes pure terror. Comedy horror with Simon Pegg and Asa Butterfield</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-16 22:00:00" d="2019-08-17 00:00:00" c="1"><n>Jumanji: Welcome To The Jungle</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Four teens in detention discover an old video game that sucks them into the dangerous world of Jumanji. Dwayne Johnson stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-17 00:00:00" d="2019-08-17 01:50:00" c="1"><n>Searching</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% When his daughter goes missing, a widowed dad trawls her social media in a desperate attempt to find her. But can he handle what he uncovers? Thriller starring Jon Cho</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-17 01:50:00" d="2019-08-17 03:40:00" c="1"><n u="Super Troopers">Super Troopers 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>60% An unexpected border dispute between the US and Canada gives a group of disgraced state troopers a second chance. Comedy sequel with Rob Lowe and Brian Cox</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-17 03:40:00" d="2019-08-17 05:35:00" c="1"><n>Final Score</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% An ex-soldier (Dave Bautista) is forced into action when terrorists take control of a football stadium. Sky Cinema Original Film with Pierce Brosnan</k>  </p>
</a>
