<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="13" t="2019-08-13 02:27:39"><p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-18 06:25:00" d="2019-08-18 08:10:00" c="1"><n>The Muppet Movie</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Kermit the Frog, Fozzie Bear, Miss Piggy, Gonzo and a motley crew of other Muppets go searching for fame and fortune in Hollywood. Family adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-18 08:10:00" d="2019-08-18 08:40:00"><n>Black Panther: Special</n>    <k>Sky Cinema takes a special look at Marvel's superhero adventure, starring Chadwick Boseman (Captain America: Civil War) and Creed's Michael B Jordan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-18 08:40:00" d="2019-08-18 10:15:00" c="1"><n>Johnny English Strikes Again</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Rowan Atkinson returns for a third time as secret service agent Johnny English. This time, a sinister cyber attack sees him sent on an adventure in the South of France</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-18 10:15:00" d="2019-08-18 12:15:00" c="1"><n>The Girl In The Spider's Web</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% Claire Foy plays a savvy hacker on a frantic hunt for a stolen computer programme that could spark a global disaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-18 12:15:00" d="2019-08-18 14:05:00" c="1"><n>Isle Of Dogs</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% In a dystopian Japan a young boy goes searching for his beloved mutt on the bleak island where all dogs have been quarantined. From Wes Anderson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-18 14:05:00" d="2019-08-18 16:05:00" c="1"><n>The Darkest Minds</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% It's kids vs adults when a mysterious pandemic wipes out most of the children, leaving those who survive with superpowers. Dystopian thriller starring Amandla Stenberg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-18 16:05:00" d="2019-08-18 18:20:00" c="1"><n>Fantastic Beasts: The Crimes Of Grindelwald</n><t>F</t>    <k>83% Newt Scamander and Albus Dumbledore try to take down the dark wizard Gellert Grindelwald in the second instalment of the series written by JK Rowling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-18 18:20:00" d="2019-08-18 20:15:00" c="1"><n>Juliet, Naked</n><t>F</t>    <k>A relationship is turned upside down by a woman's chance encounter with an obscure rocker who has an obsessive fan - her boyfriend. Charming rom-com with Ethan Hawke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-18 20:15:00" d="2019-08-18 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Johnny English Strikes Again</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% Rowan Atkinson returns for a third time as secret service agent Johnny English. This time, a sinister cyber attack sees him sent on an adventure in the South of France</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-18 22:00:00" d="2019-08-19 00:00:00" c="1"><n>The Girl In The Spider's Web</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% Claire Foy plays a savvy hacker on a frantic hunt for a stolen computer programme that could spark a global disaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-19 00:00:00" d="2019-08-19 01:55:00" c="1"><n>Extremely Wicked, Shockingly...</n><t>F</t>    <k>Sky Cinema original exploring the horrific crimes of Ted Bundy (Zac Efron) as told from the perspective of his girlfriend Elizabeth Kloepfer (Lily Collins)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-19 01:55:00" d="2019-08-19 03:40:00" c="1"><n>Hotel Artemis</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% Sci-fi thriller starring Jodie Foster as the operator of a secret, criminals-only safe house in a dystopian, near-future LA. With Jeff Goldblum and Dave Bautista</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-19 03:40:00" d="2019-08-19 05:30:00" c="1"><n>Brigsby Bear</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Oddball comedy-drama about an isolated young man obsessed with a children's TV show which is suddenly revealed to be a fake. Starring Mark Hamill and SNL's Kyle Mooney</k>  </p>
</a>
