<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="8" t="2020-05-16 04:57:11"><p id_tv="1118" o="2020-05-23 06:30:00" d="2020-05-23 08:30:00" c="1"><n>Christopher Robin</n><t>F</t>    <k>73% Ewan McGregor stars as a downtrodden Christopher Robin reunited with a cuddly childhood friend. Live action Disney fun with Hayley Atwell and the voice of Jim Cummings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-05-23 08:30:00" d="2020-05-23 10:45:00" c="1"><n>Captain America: The First Avenger</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% When a secret experiment turns frail kid Chris Evans into a rippling, spandex-clad superhero, the fate of WWII rests in his all-American hands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-05-23 10:45:00" d="2020-05-23 13:00:00" c="1"><n>Iron Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>Robert Downey Jr has a blast as the cocky weapons designer turned peacemaker in this slick action adventure. With Jeff Bridges and Gwyneth Paltrow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-05-23 13:00:00" d="2020-05-23 15:15:00" c="1"><n u="Iron Man">Iron Man 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Robert Downey Jr steels the show as his metal-clad hero takes on Mickey Rourke's vengeful villain. Superb sequel with Don Cheadle, Scarlett Johansson and Sam Rockwell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-05-23 15:15:00" d="2020-05-23 18:00:00" c="1"><n>Harry Potter and the Philosopher's Stone</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% Harry Potter discovers that he is the son of two powerful wizards and has magical powers of his own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-05-23 18:00:00" d="2020-05-23 20:00:00" c="1"><n>Thor</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Exiled to Earth, Norse god Chris Hemsworth seeks the help of scientist Natalie Portman to get back home. Action-packed Marvel Comics adventure with Anthony Hopkins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-05-23 20:00:00" d="2020-05-23 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Thor: The Dark World</n><t>F</t>    <k>70% Chris Hemsworth returns as the Mighty Avenger, who must battle a race of Dark Elves to save the world. Marvel action with Tom Hiddleston</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-05-23 22:00:00" d="2020-05-24 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Avengers: Age Of Ultron</n><t>F</t>    <k>The Avengers reassemble in order to take down terrifying new enemy Ultron. Spectacular superhero fun with Robert Downey Jr, Chris Hemsworth and Scarlett Johansson</k>  </p>
</a>
