<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-05-12 04:38:33"><p id_tv="1118" o="2020-05-19 05:35:00" d="2020-05-19 07:15:00" c="1"><n>Evan Almighty</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% Hapless Evan (Steve Carrell) is tasked with building an ark when God (Morgan Freeman) and a menagerie of animals appear on his doorstep. Comedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-05-19 07:15:00" d="2020-05-19 09:30:00" c="1"><n>Mary Poppins Returns</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% The practically-perfect nanny returns, using her magical skills to dazzle the Banks family once again. Musical fantasy with Emily Blunt, Dick Van Dyke and Meryl Streep</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-05-19 09:30:00" d="2020-05-19 11:05:00" c="1"><n>Zombieland</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% With America in the grip of a zombie apocalypse, Woody Harrelson and Jesse Eisenberg team up to survive. With Emma Stone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-05-19 11:05:00" d="2020-05-19 13:30:00" c="1"><n>Avengers: Age Of Ultron</n><t>F</t>    <k>The Avengers reassemble in order to take down terrifying new enemy Ultron. Spectacular superhero fun with Robert Downey Jr, Chris Hemsworth and Scarlett Johansson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-05-19 13:30:00" d="2020-05-19 15:30:00" c="1"><n>Ant-Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>Paul Rudd stars as a cat burglar given the ability to shrink to the size of an ant. Subatomic superhero fun with Michael Douglas and Evangeline Lilly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-05-19 15:30:00" d="2020-05-19 17:30:00" c="1"><n>Ant-Man And The Wasp</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Ant-Man suits up once more, teaming with The Wasp on an urgent mission to uncover secrets from the past. Playful superhero sequel starring Paul Rudd and Evangeline Lilly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-05-19 17:30:00" d="2020-05-19 19:45:00" c="1"><n>Mary Poppins Returns</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% The practically-perfect nanny returns, using her magical skills to dazzle the Banks family once again. Musical fantasy with Emily Blunt, Dick Van Dyke and Meryl Streep</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-05-19 19:45:00" d="2020-05-19 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Glass</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% David Dunn hunts a dangerous superhuman with 24 personalities in M Night Shyamalan's final instalment of the Unbreakable trilogy. With Bruce Willis and James McAvoy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-05-19 22:00:00" d="2020-05-20 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Ant-Man</n><t>F</t>    <k>Paul Rudd stars as a cat burglar given the ability to shrink to the size of an ant. Subatomic superhero fun with Michael Douglas and Evangeline Lilly</k>  </p>
</a>
