<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="13" t="2019-08-13 02:27:42"><p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-19 05:30:00" d="2019-08-19 07:20:00" c="1"><n>Isle Of Dogs</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% In a dystopian Japan a young boy goes searching for his beloved mutt on the bleak island where all dogs have been quarantined. From Wes Anderson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-19 07:20:00" d="2019-08-19 09:15:00" c="1"><n>Anon</n><t>F</t>    <k>60% Stylish sci-fi thriller starring Clive Owen as a troubled near-future detective investigating a series of mysterious murders. Sky Cinema Original Film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-19 09:15:00" d="2019-08-19 11:10:00" c="1"><n>Smallfoot</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% An epic journey ensues when a Yeti named Migo stumbles across a real human being - but is banished from his snowy home when no-one believes him. With Channing Tatum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-19 11:10:00" d="2019-08-19 13:15:00" c="1"><n>Jumanji: Welcome To The Jungle</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Four teens in detention discover an old video game that sucks them into the dangerous world of Jumanji. Dwayne Johnson stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-19 13:15:00" d="2019-08-19 15:15:00" c="1"><n>Night School</n><t>F</t>    <k>56% Comedy about a group of troublesome adults who are forced to attend night classes in a bid to finish high school. Starring Kevin Hart and Tiffany Haddish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-19 15:15:00" d="2019-08-19 17:15:00" c="1"><n>The Little Stranger</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% A young doctor (Domhnall Gleeson) makes a house-call to a dilapidated mansion with a dark secret. Gothic horror from Room's Lenny Abrahamson. Ruth Wilson stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-19 17:15:00" d="2019-08-19 19:10:00" c="1"><n>Game Night</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% A group of friends wind up in over their heads when their weekly game night spirals completely out of control. Jason Bateman and Rachel McAdams star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-19 19:10:00" d="2019-08-19 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Smallfoot</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% An epic journey ensues when a Yeti named Migo stumbles across a real human being - but is banished from his snowy home when no-one believes him. With Channing Tatum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-19 21:00:00" d="2019-08-19 23:00:00" c="1"><n>Jumanji: Welcome To The Jungle</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% Four teens in detention discover an old video game that sucks them into the dangerous world of Jumanji. Dwayne Johnson stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-19 23:00:00" d="2019-08-20 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Night School</n><t>F</t>    <k>56% Comedy about a group of troublesome adults who are forced to attend night classes in a bid to finish high school. Starring Kevin Hart and Tiffany Haddish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-20 01:00:00" d="2019-08-20 02:35:00" c="1"><n>The Possession Of Hannah Grace</n><t>F</t>    <k>Shay Mitchell stars as an ex-cop who finds herself facing a terrifying series of bizarre events when a disfigured corpse is brought into the hospital morgue she works at</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-20 02:35:00" d="2019-08-20 04:05:00" c="1"><n>Mom And Dad</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% Blackly comic horror with Selma Blair and Nicolas Cage as parents out to kill their own kids when a mysterious disorder sweeps through their community. Distressing themes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2019-08-20 04:05:00" d="2019-08-20 06:05:00" c="1"><n>Same Kind Of Different As Me</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Wealthy married couple Greg Kinnear and Renee Zellweger discover a renewed sense of purpose when they befriend homeless drifter Djimon Hounsou</k>  </p>
</a>
