<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2021-07-10 05:03:23"><p id_tv="1118" o="2021-07-17 05:10:00" d="2021-07-17 07:00:00" c="1"><n>The Secret Garden</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% Unlock your imagination as a young orphan discovers a magical garden when she's sent to live on her uncle's estate. Colin Firth stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2021-07-17 07:00:00" d="2021-07-17 08:35:00" c="1"><n>Dragon Rider</n><t>F</t>    <k>53% An adventure ensues for a young silver dragon as he sets out to find a mysterious haven for his kind. With the voice of Sir Patrick Stewart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2021-07-17 08:35:00" d="2021-07-17 10:55:00" c="1"><n>Little Women</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Greta Gerwig's acclaimed adaptation of Louisa May Alcott's novel about four sisters' coming-of-age in the shadow of the American Civil War</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2021-07-17 10:55:00" d="2021-07-17 13:00:00" c="1"><n>Joker</n><t>F</t>    <k>83% The chilling standalone story of the iconic villain, played by the Oscar-winning Joaquin Phoenix. Psychological thriller with Robert De Niro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2021-07-17 13:00:00" d="2021-07-17 15:10:00" c="1"><n>Oblivion</n><t>F</t>    <k>One of the last people on an evacuated Earth finds himself battling to save mankind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2021-07-17 15:10:00" d="2021-07-17 17:45:00" c="1"><n u="Le Mans">Le Mans 66</n><t>F</t>    <k>Car designer Carroll Shelby and driver Ken Miles battle to build a revolutionary race car for Ford. Oscar-winning drama starring Matt Damon and Christian Bale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2021-07-17 17:45:00" d="2021-07-17 19:20:00" c="1"><n>Vantage Point</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% When the president is shot, agent Dennis Quaid races to find the assassin. Eight witnesses hold the clues, but who's telling the truth?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2021-07-17 19:20:00" d="2021-07-17 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Jungleland</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% When a devastating loss in the ring leaves Lion and his manager and brother Stan in debt to a local crime boss, the pair must fight for a better life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2021-07-17 21:00:00" d="2021-07-17 23:10:00" c="1"><n>Oblivion</n><t>F</t>    <k>One of the last people on an evacuated Earth finds himself battling to save mankind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2021-07-17 23:10:00" d="2021-07-18 02:10:00" c="1"><n u="Le Mans">Le Mans 66</n><t>F</t>    <k>Car designer Carroll Shelby and driver Ken Miles battle to build a revolutionary race car for Ford. Oscar-winning drama starring Matt Damon and Christian Bale</k>  </p>
</a>
