<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-05-27 04:36:03"><p id_tv="1118" o="2020-06-03 06:00:00" d="2020-06-03 07:40:00" c="1"><n>Monster Family</n><t>F</t>    <k>The first Sky Cinema Original Film sees a young family cursed by a witch and transformed into monsters. Animated comedy with the voices of Emily Watson and Jason Isaacs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-06-03 07:40:00" d="2020-06-03 09:15:00" c="1"><n>The Grinch</n><t>F</t>    <k>The grumpy old Grinch hatches a dastardly scheme to ruin Christmas in Whoville. Animated Dr Seuss adaptation with the voices of Benedict Cumberbatch and Pharrell Williams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-06-03 09:15:00" d="2020-06-03 11:25:00" c="1"><n>Eclipse</n><t>F</t>    <k>53% In the dramatic third chapter of the fantasy saga, Bella is torn between Edward and Jacob. Starring Kristen Stewart and Robert Pattinson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-06-03 11:25:00" d="2020-06-03 13:30:00" c="1"><n>Rocketman</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% Dazzling musical biopic detailing Sir Elton John's breakthrough years. Taron Egerton, Jamie Bell and Richard Madden star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-06-03 13:30:00" d="2020-06-03 15:30:00" c="1"><n>Prince Of Persia: The Sands Of Time</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Jake Gyllenhaal is the muscle-bound monarch out to save his kingdom from being destroyed by a magical artefact. Spectacular action with Gemma Arterton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-06-03 15:30:00" d="2020-06-03 17:35:00" c="1"><n>Godzilla</n><t>F</t>    <k>64% As the legendary monster resurfaces, will he prove to be humanity's unlikely saviour? Dazzling action blockbuster with Bryan Cranston and Aaron Taylor-Johnson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-06-03 17:35:00" d="2020-06-03 19:50:00" c="1"><n>Godzilla: King Of The Monsters</n><t>F</t>    <k>Godzilla battles a host of giant monsters - including his nemesis, the three-headed King Ghidorah. Action-packed sequel with Millie Bobby Brown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-06-03 19:50:00" d="2020-06-03 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Eclipse</n><t>F</t>    <k>53% In the dramatic third chapter of the fantasy saga, Bella is torn between Edward and Jacob. Starring Kristen Stewart and Robert Pattinson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1118" o="2020-06-03 22:00:00" d="2020-06-04 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Rocketman</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% Dazzling musical biopic detailing Sir Elton John's breakthrough years. Taron Egerton, Jamie Bell and Richard Madden star</k>  </p>
</a>
