<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-04-09 04:36:03"><p id_tv="1119" o="2020-04-16 06:00:00" d="2020-04-16 07:25:00" c="1"><n>Lego Batman The Movie DC Super Heroes Unite</n><t>F</t>    <k>Batman and Superman join forces with the rest of the Justice League to stop Lex Luthor and the Joker from bringing down Gotham. Animated action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-04-16 07:25:00" d="2020-04-16 09:25:00" c="1"><n>Total Recall</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% Philip K Dick adaptation, with Colin Farrell as a future-world factory worker on the run and struggling to know what's real</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-04-16 09:25:00" d="2020-04-16 11:10:00" c="1"><n>Happy Death Day 2U</n><t>F</t>    <k>62% College student Tree Gelbman is again stuck in a murderous time-loop and has to face up to a new killer. Horror sequel to the smash-hit 2017 film, with Jessica Rothe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-04-16 11:10:00" d="2020-04-16 12:40:00" c="1"><n>Lifechanger</n><t>F</t>    <k>Spine-chilling horror following the story of Drew, a murderous shapeshifter who's killing spree takes a complex turn when he falls in love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-04-16 12:40:00" d="2020-04-16 14:20:00" c="1"><n>The Party Crasher</n><t>F</t>    <k>A group of college kids throw a Hawaiian-themed luau party in a bid to banish the winter blues, but it isn't long before an evil entity makes itself at home. Horror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-04-16 14:20:00" d="2020-04-16 16:00:00" c="1"><n>Brightburn</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% An extra-terrestrial child mysteriously crash-lands on Earth. His powers are unlike anything ever seen - but can they be harnessed for good? Elizabeth Banks stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-04-16 16:00:00" d="2020-04-16 18:00:00" c="1"><n>Mad Max: Beyond Thunderdome</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% Mel Gibson plays the lone road warrior forced to fight in the gladiatorial arena of Bartertown, under the rule of queen Tina Turner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-04-16 18:00:00" d="2020-04-16 19:35:00" c="1"><n>I'll Take Your Dead</n><t>F</t>    <k>A man who gets rid of corpses for gangsters runs into trouble when it turns out one of the 'dead' bodies is still alive. Horror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-04-16 19:35:00" d="2020-04-16 22:35:00" c="1"><n>Minority Report</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% Future cop Tom Cruise goes on the run for a murder he's yet to commit in Spielberg's dazzling sci-fi thriller. With Colin Farrell</k>  </p>
</a>
