<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="11" t="2021-07-13 05:04:29"><p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-20 05:25:00" d="2021-07-20 07:05:00" c="1"><n>Volition</n><t>F</t>    <k>Sci-fi thriller about a man with psychic abilities who battles to change his fate when a series of events leads to a vision of his own murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-20 07:05:00" d="2021-07-20 08:40:00" c="1"><n u="Men In Black">Men In Black II</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% With the scum of the universe menacing Earth again, agent Will Smith brings back Tommy Lee Jones to kick alien backside. Comic sequel. Mild fantasy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-20 08:40:00" d="2021-07-20 11:00:00" c="1"><n>V For Vendetta</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% In a Britain crushed by a cruel dictator, a masked avenger enlists Natalie Portman in a fight for freedom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-20 11:00:00" d="2021-07-20 13:15:00" c="1"><n>The Birds</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Unflappable socialite Tippi Hedren follows a handsome lawyer back to his coastal home, but becomes terrorized by flocks of angry birds. Legendary Hitchcock horror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-20 13:15:00" d="2021-07-20 14:55:00" c="1"><n>The Final Wish</n><t>F</t>    <k>A man returns home to help his grief-stricken mother following his father's sudden death, and discovers a darkly mysterious object in his possessions. Mystery-horror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-20 14:55:00" d="2021-07-20 16:10:00" c="1"><n>Justice League: Throne Of Atlantis</n><t>F</t>    <k>66% The newly formed Justice League must rally together when Cyborg discovers an imminent and powerful threat in the depths of the oceans. Action-packed animation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-20 16:10:00" d="2021-07-20 17:45:00" c="1"><n>We Summon The Darkness</n><t>F</t>    <k>A fun night at a festival turns deadly when three friends head to a band's afterparty. Horror starring Alexandra Daddario and Johnny Knoxville</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-20 17:45:00" d="2021-07-20 19:25:00" c="1"><n>Villains</n><t>F</t>    <k>Two amateur robbers get way more than they bargained for when they break into a large house looking for fuel and wind up trapped by the home owners. Comedy horror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-20 19:25:00" d="2021-07-20 21:00:00" c="1"><n u="Men In Black">Men In Black II</n><t>F</t>    <k>63% With the scum of the universe menacing Earth again, agent Will Smith brings back Tommy Lee Jones to kick alien backside. Comic sequel. Mild fantasy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-20 21:00:00" d="2021-07-20 23:15:00" c="1"><n>V For Vendetta</n><t>F</t>    <k>81% In a Britain crushed by a cruel dictator, a masked avenger enlists Natalie Portman in a fight for freedom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-20 23:15:00" d="2021-07-21 02:15:00" c="1"><n>Blade</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% Stylish action with Wesley Snipes as a half-human half-vampire hero on a mission to destroy the vampire underworld</k>  </p>
</a>
