<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="11" t="2021-07-08 05:05:39"><p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-13 05:40:00" d="2021-07-13 07:30:00" c="1"><n>The Others</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Skin-crawling supernatural tale starring Nicole Kidman as a mother desperate to keep her allergic children out of the light. With Christopher Eccleston</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-13 07:30:00" d="2021-07-13 10:20:00" c="1"><n>Interstellar</n><t>F</t>    <k>86% Christopher Nolan's awe-inspiring sci-fi epic stars Matthew McConaughey and Anne Hathaway as explorers tasked with securing humanity's survival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-13 10:20:00" d="2021-07-13 12:25:00" c="1"><n>Mad Max: Fury Road</n><t>F</t>    <k>80% Tom Hardy and Charlize Theron star in George Miller's action adventure about a rebel and a drifter who team up in post-apocalyptic Australia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-13 12:25:00" d="2021-07-13 14:00:00" c="1"><n>Cosmic Sin</n><t>F</t>    <k>A team of soldiers launch a pre-emptive strike against a newly discovered alien civilisation. Sci-fi action with Bruce Willis and Frank Grillo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-13 14:00:00" d="2021-07-13 15:50:00" c="1"><n>The Lighthouse</n><t>F</t>    <k>72% Two lighthouse keepers try to stay sane while living on a remote and mysterious island in New England. Psychological thriller starring Robert Pattinson and Willem Dafoe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-13 15:50:00" d="2021-07-13 17:30:00" c="1"><n>Sea Fever</n><t>F</t>    <k>A trawler crew have the fight of their lives when they're marooned at sea and have to tackle a parasite in their water supply. Sci-fi horror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-13 17:30:00" d="2021-07-13 19:10:00" c="1"><n>Minor Premise</n><t>F</t>    <k>Attempting to surpass his father's legacy, a reclusive neuroscientist becomes entangled in his own experiment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-13 19:10:00" d="2021-07-13 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Interstellar</n><t>F</t>    <k>86% Christopher Nolan's awe-inspiring sci-fi epic stars Matthew McConaughey and Anne Hathaway as explorers tasked with securing humanity's survival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-13 22:00:00" d="2021-07-14 00:05:00" c="1"><n>Mad Max: Fury Road</n><t>F</t>    <k>80% Tom Hardy and Charlize Theron star in George Miller's action adventure about a rebel and a drifter who team up in post-apocalyptic Australia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-14 00:05:00" d="2021-07-14 03:05:00" c="1"><n>IT: Chapter Two</n><t>F</t>    <k>Twenty-seven years after their first encounter with Pennywise the Clown, it returns to Derry again. Terrifying horror sequel with James McAvoy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-14 03:05:00" d="2021-07-14 05:20:00" c="1"><n>The Exorcist</n><t>F</t>    <k>William Friedkin's Oscar-winning horror classic follows a priest battling to save the soul of a young girl</k>  </p>
</a>
