<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-05-26 04:39:53"><p id_tv="1119" o="2020-06-02 06:20:00" d="2020-06-02 07:00:00"><n>Sky Cinema Preview</n>    <k>Previews of the great films now playing on Sky Cinema plus other highlights showing on Sky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-06-02 07:00:00" d="2020-06-02 09:25:00" c="1"><n>Star Wars: Attack Of The Clones</n><t>F</t>    <k>A Jedi Knight (Ewan McGregor) and his young apprentice (Hayden Christensen) battle to protect the Republic from separatist leader Count Dooku</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-06-02 09:25:00" d="2020-06-02 11:40:00" c="1"><n>Star Trek: The Motion Picture</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Admiral James T Kirk and the USS Enterprise are called on to intercept an alien craft heading for Earth. Sci-fi action with the late Leonard Nimoy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-06-02 11:40:00" d="2020-06-02 13:40:00" c="1"><n>Star Trek II: The Wrath Of Khan</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Captain Kirk leads his crew in a desperate battle against ruthless arch-nemesis Khan. Sci-fi adventure with the late Leonard Nimoy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-06-02 13:40:00" d="2020-06-02 15:40:00" c="1"><n>Star Trek III: The Search For Spock</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% The crew of the Starship Enterprise steal their old ship and set out to free the trapped soul of Spock (the late Leonard Nimoy)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-06-02 15:40:00" d="2020-06-02 17:40:00" c="1"><n>Star Trek IV: The Voyage Home</n><t>F</t>    <k>74% Eco-friendly sci-fi with Kirk (William Shatner) and the crew of the Enterprise travelling back to 1980s San Francisco to save a pair of whales, and thus, the planet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-06-02 17:40:00" d="2020-06-02 19:35:00" c="1"><n>Star Trek V: The Final Frontier</n><t>F</t>    <k>57% Captain Kirk and his crew are kidnapped by a renegade Vulcan in this sci-fi sequel, directed by William Shatner. With the late Leonard Nimoy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-06-02 19:35:00" d="2020-06-02 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Star Wars: Attack Of The Clones</n><t>F</t>    <k>A Jedi Knight (Ewan McGregor) and his young apprentice (Hayden Christensen) battle to protect the Republic from separatist leader Count Dooku</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-06-02 22:00:00" d="2020-06-03 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Edge Of Tomorrow: Live</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% Die. Repeat: When aliens invade Earth, army officer Tom Cruise gets stuck in a time-loop that sees him doing battle with them again and again. Sci-fi action</k>  </p>
</a>
