<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-05-27 04:36:05"><p id_tv="1119" o="2020-06-03 05:05:00" d="2020-06-03 07:20:00" c="1"><n>Star Trek: The Motion Picture</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Admiral James T Kirk and the USS Enterprise are called on to intercept an alien craft heading for Earth. Sci-fi action with the late Leonard Nimoy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-06-03 07:20:00" d="2020-06-03 09:15:00" c="1"><n>The Omen</n><t>F</t>    <k>76% Gregory Peck switches kids after his wife delivers a stillborn baby, little realising that he's adopting the Antichrist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-06-03 09:15:00" d="2020-06-03 11:10:00" c="1"><n>Upgrade</n><t>F</t>    <k>75% A mugging victim left widowed and quadriplegic is offered an AI implant cure. With his new mobility comes superhuman strength and a thirst for revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-06-03 11:10:00" d="2020-06-03 13:25:00" c="1"><n>Glass</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% David Dunn hunts a dangerous superhuman with 24 personalities in M Night Shyamalan's final instalment of the Unbreakable trilogy. With Bruce Willis and James McAvoy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-06-03 13:25:00" d="2020-06-03 15:50:00" c="1"><n>Star Wars: Revenge Of The Sith</n><t>F</t>    <k>Anakin Skywalker becomes closer with Chancellor Palpatine and begins to succumb to the temptations of the dark side. Epic sci-fi adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-06-03 15:50:00" d="2020-06-03 17:45:00" c="1"><n>Escape Room</n><t>F</t>    <k>A group of college students are unwittingly lured into escape room scenarios, leading to a terrifying battle for their lives. Psychological thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-06-03 17:45:00" d="2020-06-03 19:45:00" c="1"><n>Us</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% A family holiday becomes a nightmare when it's interrupted by unexpected visitors. Eerie horror from Get Out's Jordan Peele starring Oscar winner Lupita Nyong'o</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-06-03 19:45:00" d="2020-06-03 22:00:00" c="1"><n>Glass</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% David Dunn hunts a dangerous superhuman with 24 personalities in M Night Shyamalan's final instalment of the Unbreakable trilogy. With Bruce Willis and James McAvoy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2020-06-03 22:00:00" d="2020-06-04 01:00:00" c="1"><n>Star Wars: Revenge Of The Sith</n><t>F</t>    <k>Anakin Skywalker becomes closer with Chancellor Palpatine and begins to succumb to the temptations of the dark side. Epic sci-fi adventure</k>  </p>
</a>
