<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="10" t="2021-07-10 05:03:37"><p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-17 05:30:00" d="2021-07-17 07:15:00" c="1"><n>Daniel Isn't Real</n><t>F</t>    <k>A troubled young man resurrects his imaginary childhood friend to help him cope with a trauma, without realising that 'Daniel' has deadly intentions. Psychological horror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-17 07:15:00" d="2021-07-17 09:15:00" c="1"><n>Bloodshot</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% Action-packed superhero film starring Vin Diesel as Ray Garrison, a soldier killed in action and brought back to life as the super-human Bloodshot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-17 09:15:00" d="2021-07-17 11:20:00" c="1"><n>Edge Of Tomorrow: Live</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% Die. Repeat: When aliens invade Earth, army officer Tom Cruise gets stuck in a time-loop that sees him doing battle with them again and again. Sci-fi action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-17 11:20:00" d="2021-07-17 13:05:00" c="1"><n>The Dark</n><t>F</t>    <k>54% A couple mourning the loss of their daughter are visited by a young girl who bears a resemblance to her. Fantasy horror with Sean Bean and Maria Bello</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-17 13:05:00" d="2021-07-17 15:05:00" c="1"><n>The Others</n><t>F</t>    <k>77% Skin-crawling supernatural tale starring Nicole Kidman as a mother desperate to keep her allergic children out of the light. With Christopher Eccleston</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-17 15:05:00" d="2021-07-17 16:55:00" c="1"><n>The Wretched</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% A teenage boy gets embroiled in a battle with an old witch who has possessed his next door neighbour. Supernatural horror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-17 16:55:00" d="2021-07-17 19:00:00" c="1"><n>I, Robot</n><t>F</t>    <k>71% In 2035, robots are built to help humans. But when there's a murder, cop Will Smith is convinced that the machines have gone bad. Sci-fi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-17 19:00:00" d="2021-07-17 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Bloodshot</n><t>F</t>    <k>58% Action-packed superhero film starring Vin Diesel as Ray Garrison, a soldier killed in action and brought back to life as the super-human Bloodshot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-17 21:00:00" d="2021-07-17 23:00:00" c="1"><n>Edge Of Tomorrow: Live</n><t>F</t>    <k>79% Die. Repeat: When aliens invade Earth, army officer Tom Cruise gets stuck in a time-loop that sees him doing battle with them again and again. Sci-fi action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1119" o="2021-07-17 23:00:00" d="2021-07-18 02:00:00" c="1"><n>The New Mutants</n><t>F</t>    <k>Five teenage mutants fight for their lives as they try to escape from a dangerous secret facility and their own pasts. Starring Anya Taylor-Joy and Maisie Williams</k>  </p>
</a>
