<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2019-08-11 01:29:08"><p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 07:00:00" d="2019-08-17 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria I (105)</n><t>M</t>    <k>81% Daria's economics class takes a field trip to an enormous new mall. Daria is sickened by the teeming masses. After discovering Quinn playing hooky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 07:20:00" d="2019-08-17 07:45:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills V (515)</n><t>M</t>    <k>36% Justin plays hard to get with Kristin, but his plan backfires. Holly's drinking leads to an intervention. Brody and Jayde get into a fight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 07:45:00" d="2019-08-17 08:10:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills V (516)</n><t>M</t>    <k>36% Justin finds himself in hot water after Kristin and Audrina finally meet face to face. All Heidi wants for her birthday is a baby, but Spencer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 08:10:00" d="2019-08-17 08:35:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills V (517)</n><t>M</t>    <k>36% Kristin and Brody consider dating again, but a run-in with Jayde proves it may be easier said than done. Audrina and Justin discuss their future</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 08:35:00" d="2019-08-17 09:00:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills V (518)</n><t>M</t>    <k>36% Kristin clashes with Jayde when she comes back to reclaim Brody. Heidi hatches a plan to get pregnant, and Audrina copes with the fact that Justin still</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 09:00:00" d="2019-08-17 09:30:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills V (519)</n><t>M</t>    <k>36% A wild weekend in Vegas makes Kristin unsure if she has real feelings for Justin. Spencer comes up with a plan to find out if Heidi has stopped taking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 09:30:00" d="2019-08-17 10:00:00"><n u="The Hills">The Hills V (520)</n><t>M</t>    <k>36% Kristin decides she doesn't want to be with Justin. Brody gets cold feet when Jayde wants to move in with him. Spencer worries that Heidi might be pregnant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 10:00:00" d="2019-08-17 11:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs Priciest Pads">MTV Cribs Priciest Pads I (101)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Take a peek into the most expensive homes of the rich and famous. In this episode: Paulina Rubio, Nelly, Russell &amp; Kimora in New York, Tommy Lee, Rasheed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 11:00:00" d="2019-08-17 12:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs Priciest Pads">MTV Cribs Priciest Pads I (102)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Take a peek into the most expensive homes of the rich and famous. In this episode: Pamela Anderson, Penny Hardaway, Joey Fatone, Gene Simmons, Usher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 12:00:00" d="2019-08-17 13:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs Priciest Pads">MTV Cribs Priciest Pads I (103)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Take a peek into the most expensive homes of the rich and famous. In this episode: Ice-T, Robbie Williams, The Osbournes, Mariah Carey, Master P and Babyface! (S1, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 13:00:00" d="2019-08-17 14:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs Priciest Pads">MTV Cribs Priciest Pads I (104)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Come see the most expensive homes of the rich and famous. In this episode: Russell and Kimora, Brody and Brandon Jenner, Kimberly Stewart, The Playboy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 14:00:00" d="2019-08-17 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Love At First Swipe">Catfish: Love At First Swipe V (503)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Since Leuh saw surfer Justin it's been insta-love. But after two failed attempts to meet up, she wants to know if he's the man of her dreams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 15:00:00" d="2019-08-17 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Love At First Swipe">Catfish: Love At First Swipe VI (614)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Southern sweetheart Kelsie is madly in love with her online Romeo, Brandon. But after years of endless excuses about not meet up, Kelsie recruits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 16:00:00" d="2019-08-17 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Love At First Swipe">Catfish: Love At First Swipe VII (706)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>When Zak met Garret online he fell hard, but curious disappearances have Zak worried about who he really fell in love with. Will Nev and Max find Garret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 17:00:00" d="2019-08-17 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Love At First Swipe">Catfish: Love At First Swipe VII (710)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dylan's fallen for a beautiful model with an elusive secret. With all the standard red flags, Nev and Max assume it's an open and shut case, but the truth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 18:00:00" d="2019-08-17 20:00:00"><n>Bring It On: In It To Win It</n><t>M</t>    <k>A high-school senior (Ashley Benson) falls for a fellow cheerleader (Michael Copon), not realising that he is on a rival squad. (2007)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 20:00:00" d="2019-08-17 22:00:00"><n>Bring It On: All Or Nothing</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Hayden Panettiere stars as a cheerleader who transfers to a rough high school and joins the cheerleading squad, where she has to fight against her former</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 22:00:00" d="2019-08-17 23:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (404)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The king of Essex, Joey Essex co-hosts with Charlotte. Geordie Shore lovebirds Chloe and Sam face a trust test, and Frenemies Becky and Zoe tell each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 23:00:00" d="2019-08-18 00:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (405)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Ex On The Beach star Natalie Harris is taught a lesson by her mum and Love Island hunks Tom and Rykard try to get one over on each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-18 00:00:00" d="2019-08-18 01:00:00"><n u="RuPaul's Drag Race Season 6 Boxset">RuPaul's Drag Race Season 6 Boxset VI (609)</n><t>M</t>    <k>For the main challenge, the queens host a talk show and interview special guests. They hit the runway in their own &quot;animal kingdom couture.&quot; (S6, ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-18 01:00:00" d="2019-08-18 02:00:00"><n u="RuPaul's Drag Race Season 6 Boxset">RuPaul's Drag Race Season 6 Boxset VI (610)</n><t>M</t>    <k>For this weeks main challenge, the queens transform grooms into brides for a wedding. (S6, ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-18 02:00:00" d="2019-08-18 03:00:00"><n u="RuPaul's Drag Race Season 6 Boxset">RuPaul's Drag Race Season 6 Boxset VI (611)</n><t>M</t>    <k>For this weeks main challenge, the queens create three looks (banjee girl bling, executive realness, &amp; dripping in jewels eleganza) for a fabulous glitter ball! (S6, ep11)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-18 03:00:00" d="2019-08-18 04:00:00"><n u="New: Yo! Rates">New: Yo! Rates I (113)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Presenters Snoochie Shy and Poet, plus special guests, take you through the hottest new rap videos. This episode features UK Rapper 'Mist' and an exclusive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-18 04:00:00" d="2019-08-18 04:25:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XI (1128)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob Dyrdek hosts an internet video clip show with celebrity guests and co-hosts Sterling &quot;Steelo&quot; Brim and Chanel West Coast. (S11, ep 28)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-18 04:25:00" d="2019-08-18 04:40:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XI (1129)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob Dyrdek hosts an internet video clip show with celebrity guests and co-hosts Sterling &quot;Steelo&quot; Brim and Chanel West Coast. (S11, ep29)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-18 04:40:00" d="2019-08-18 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness X (1028)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Steelo, and Chanel are joined by country musician Wheeler Walker Jr. to discuss his &quot;banned mates&quot;, analyze grooming techniques and explore</k>  </p>
</a>
