<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2020-04-11 04:34:31"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-18 07:00:00" d="2020-04-18 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria IV (403)</n><t>M</t>    <k>80% Daria talks Kevin into buying a motorcycle when she sees him buying a leather jacket to impress Brittany, but he settles for a moped. (S4, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-18 07:20:00" d="2020-04-18 08:10:00"><n u="Young and Married">Young and Married I (108)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>In Pennsylvania, Christian couple Lindsey and Stephen got married two years ago but Lindsey's worried she is turning into a 1950s housewife and wants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-18 08:10:00" d="2020-04-18 09:00:00"><n u="Young and Married">Young and Married I (109)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Ashley and Preston have been together since school and eloped three years ago after discovering Ashley was pregnant. Shannon and Cory are planning their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-18 09:00:00" d="2020-04-18 10:00:00"><n u="Young and Married">Young and Married I (110)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Rebecca and Mohammed are getting married in just a few weeks and they haven't got anything arranged. Moe's family are Muslim and Rebecca's are Catholic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-18 10:00:00" d="2020-04-18 11:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (401)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Charlotte's boyfriend Josh joins her as co-host and her mum and dad put their marriage to the test. While business partners Scott and Stefan's friendship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-18 11:00:00" d="2020-04-18 11:30:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (402)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Friends Saffron and Sheniya send each other a message, mother and son Mary and Lewis test their family bond while lovebirds Emily and Chris</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-18 11:30:00" d="2020-04-18 12:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (403)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Geordie Shore star Chloe Ferry co-hosts the show, best mates Josh and Warren push banter to its limits, and Charlotte Crosby gets her revenge by inking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-18 12:00:00" d="2020-04-18 13:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (404)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The king of Essex, Joey Essex co-hosts with Charlotte. Geordie Shore lovebirds Chloe and Sam face a trust test, and Frenemies Becky and Zoe tell each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-18 13:00:00" d="2020-04-18 14:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (405)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Ex On The Beach star Natalie Harris is taught a lesson by her mum and Love Island hunks Tom and Rykard try to get one over on each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-18 14:00:00" d="2020-04-18 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Betrayals">Catfish: Betrayals II (201)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Cassie was on a downward spiral until she got a friend request from a rapper named Steve. Two and a half years later, Cassie and Steve are engaged</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-18 15:00:00" d="2020-04-18 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Betrayals">Catfish: Betrayals VI (602)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Alante has been planning a life with his online love. She’s perfect but her disappearances have Alante worried. Nev and Max help uncover a truth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-18 16:00:00" d="2020-04-18 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Betrayals">Catfish: Betrayals VII (711)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Kiaira and Cortney had a baby despite Kiaira never meeting Cortney or the baby! Nev and Max try to bring the family together, but is this the greatest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-18 17:00:00" d="2020-04-18 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Betrayals">Catfish: Betrayals V (516)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After months of intimate texts with Titus, a man she met online, Candice has decided to tell to her husband. But before she does, she asks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-18 18:00:00" d="2020-04-18 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Betrayals">Catfish: Betrayals VII (730)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>When Kristina met Faith in a chatroom, she didn't intend to fall in love and betray her IRL fiancé. Now Nev and co-host Tallulah Willis navigate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-18 19:00:00" d="2020-04-18 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Betrayals">Catfish: Betrayals VII (715)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Max agree to help Chelsea finally meet Charles in person. While Chelsea has only spoken to Charles once on the phone, the guys soon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-18 20:00:00" d="2020-04-18 21:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Betrayals">Catfish: Betrayals VII (732)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and co-host Elle King help Angel find her online love Remy. But the closest Angel has ever gotten to Remy was when he was creepily watching</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-18 21:00:00" d="2020-04-18 23:00:00"><n u="MTV EMA">MTV EMA 2019 (105)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Watch the biggest stars take the stage for the annual MTV EMAs, live from Seville, Spain. Hosted by Becky G with performances by Rosalia, Halsey, Niall</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-18 23:00:00" d="2020-04-19 00:00:00"><n u="True Life Crime">True Life Crime I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>True Life Crime investigates the case of Kenneka Jenkins who vanished from a party at a hotel in Chicago, after going live on Facebook. 24 hours later</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 00:00:00" d="2020-04-19 01:00:00"><n u="True Life Crime">True Life Crime I (102)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Sarah Stern's car is discovered, the keys still in the ignition, but she is nowhere to be found. Police initially suspected suicide, but why would</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 01:00:00" d="2020-04-19 02:00:00"><n u="True Life Crime">True Life Crime I (103)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>16-year-old Kedarie Johnson, a gender fluid teen, begins walking home from a friend's house. Later that night, shots ring out and Kedarie's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 02:00:00" d="2020-04-19 03:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs Priciest Pads">MTV Cribs Priciest Pads I (101)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Take a peek into the most expensive homes of the rich and famous. In this episode: Paulina Rubio, Nelly, Russell &amp; Kimora in New York, Tommy Lee, Rasheed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 03:00:00" d="2020-04-19 03:50:00"><n u="MTV Cribs Priciest Pads">MTV Cribs Priciest Pads I (102)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Take a peek into the most expensive homes of the rich and famous. In this episode: Pamela Anderson, Penny Hardaway, Joey Fatone, Gene Simmons, Usher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 03:50:00" d="2020-04-19 04:40:00"><n u="MTV Cribs Priciest Pads">MTV Cribs Priciest Pads I (103)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Take a peek into the most expensive homes of the rich and famous. In this episode: Ice-T, Robbie Williams, The Osbournes, Mariah Carey, Master P and Babyface! (S1, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 04:40:00" d="2020-04-19 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XIV (1431)</n><t>M</t>    <k>62% Lil Jon joins Rob, Chanel, and Steelo to end the party in Turn Down For This, have the hardest Christmas ever in Merry Crunk-mas, and to</k>  </p>
</a>
