<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="30" t="2021-07-10 05:02:00"><p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 05:00:00" d="2021-07-17 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 07:00:00" d="2021-07-17 07:20:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (23)</n><t>M</t>    <k>See Dylan &amp; Lyris' New York City apartment in the sky with views of the Empire State Building and Central Park. Then see Kipling, Rio &amp; Selkirk's Idaho</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 07:20:00" d="2021-07-17 07:45:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson plays cupid to help sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight heartbroken heartthrob Christian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 07:45:00" d="2021-07-17 08:10:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (102)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson plays cupid to help sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight single mum Charlotte and her Blackpool</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 08:10:00" d="2021-07-17 08:35:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (103)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson plays cupid to help sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight feisty fly girl Felicia and her London</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 08:35:00" d="2021-07-17 09:00:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (104)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson ditches the dating apps and helps sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight Tanya calls in her Love Squad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 09:00:00" d="2021-07-17 10:00:00"><n u="Ghosted: Love Gone Missing">Ghosted: Love Gone Missing II (201)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>47% Joanna never expected to meet the man of her dreams in her rideshare driver, Aaron. After a lovely ride through their hometown a blossoming relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 10:00:00" d="2021-07-17 10:55:00"><n u="Catfish UK">Catfish UK I (105)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Alex has been chatting to Matt for a year and thinks he could be the one. But after several failed attempts to meet, Alex wants Julie and Oobah to track him down. (S1, ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 10:55:00" d="2021-07-17 11:00:00"><n u="New: Fresh Out Live">New: Fresh Out Live II (226)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Fresh Out Live delivers the most important music and pop culture news of the week and beyond with artist interviews, in-studio performances, album drops</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 11:00:00" d="2021-07-17 12:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom">Teen Mom 2 X (1030)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Jade recovers at Briana's house, but has to make a decision about her family. Leah tries to balance Ali and Aleeah's unique needs. Kail juggles three</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 12:00:00" d="2021-07-17 13:00:00"><n u="The Hills: New Beginnings">The Hills: New Beginnings II (208)</n><t>M</t>    <k>36% Brody and Audrina's flirtation heats up. The war between the Pratts and Wahlers finally reaches boiling point. Brandon is left out in the cold by Dani's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 13:00:00" d="2021-07-17 14:00:00"><n u="16 &amp; Pregnant">16 &amp; Pregnant VI (609)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Kyla has always had a complicated relationship with her mum, and things got worse when she fell pregnant. Kyla moved out to live with her aunt, while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 14:00:00" d="2021-07-17 15:00:00"><n u="It's Your Fault I'm Fat">It's Your Fault I'm Fat II (206)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Reality series following teenagers and their families as they work together to shift the pounds. Since moving to the UK, Kaspars has been tempted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 15:00:00" d="2021-07-17 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Meltdowns">Catfish: Meltdowns II (202)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Anthony is a war veteran who wears his heart on his sleeve. Over a year ago, he bonded online with a caring man named Marq. Today, they're head over heels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 16:00:00" d="2021-07-17 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Meltdowns">Catfish: Meltdowns IV (405)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Chitara took a big leap and came out to her family when she met Priscilla online, but Priscilla ended their relationship unexpectedly. Now Chitara</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 17:00:00" d="2021-07-17 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Meltdowns">Catfish: Meltdowns VII (723)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Fashion designer Truth is hot for his online crush despite the fact he's in a relationship IRL. The drama deepens when Nev and co-host Zeke Thomas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 18:00:00" d="2021-07-17 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Meltdowns">Catfish: Meltdowns V (519)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Luis has fallen for a single mum, and now he's ready to take their online relationship to the next level. But first Nev and Max must</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 19:00:00" d="2021-07-17 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Meltdowns">Catfish: Meltdowns VII (734)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Taylor needs help after falling for a guy claiming to have gone to her school. Nev and co-host Tallulah dig into Taylor's tale only to uncover secrets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 20:00:00" d="2021-07-17 21:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Meltdowns">Catfish: Meltdowns VI (607)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>When Sandra learns that her granddaughter, Yasmine, sent money to an online boyfriend, she asks Nev and Max for help. And they soon discover there's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 21:00:00" d="2021-07-17 22:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Meltdowns">Catfish: Meltdowns II (206)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After being bullied in her past, Jen relies on online communities to establish relationships. After meeting Skylar online, they immediately hit it off</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 22:00:00" d="2021-07-17 23:00:00"><n u="True Life Crime">True Life Crime I (104)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>24-year-old Jerika Binks vanished while out on a Sunday morning run in American Fork, Utah. Her family and authorities searched for a year, but found no trace. (S1, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 23:00:00" d="2021-07-18 00:00:00"><n u="True Life Crime">True Life Crime I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>True Life Crime investigates the case of Kenneka Jenkins who vanished from a party at a hotel in Chicago, after going live on Facebook. 24 hours later</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-18 00:00:00" d="2021-07-18 01:00:00"><n u="True Life Crime">True Life Crime I (105)</n><t>M</t>    <k>16-year-old Mujey Dumbuya left her home and vanished. Mujey was classified as a runaway by authorities. Days later, her body was found in a wooded</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-18 01:00:00" d="2021-07-18 02:00:00"><n u="True Life Crime">True Life Crime I (108)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Hanna Harris, a 21-year-old young mother, went out to celebrate the Fourth of July, but she never made it home. In order to find Hanna her family mounted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-18 02:00:00" d="2021-07-18 03:00:00"><n>Geordie Shore: Why Aye Love You</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>This Geordie Shore special takes a look back across five crazy years of break-ups and make-ups, getting mortal and travelling the world to highlight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-18 03:00:00" d="2021-07-18 03:25:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XV (1507)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>63% Rob, Steelo and Chanel catch a few 'Buzzard Beaters', take some 'Hats Off', and discover the true meaning of the term 'Doorbusters'. (S15, ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-18 03:25:00" d="2021-07-18 03:50:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XV (1508)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>63% Rob, Chanel, and Steelo try and decide when's the right time to 'Buzz The Fuzz', and reveal the hidden powers of ski masks in 'Invincibility Cloaks'. (S15, ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-18 03:50:00" d="2021-07-18 04:15:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XV (1509)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>63% Rob, Chanel and Steelo earn a gold medal in 'Ginastics', study some beasts that are 'Wildly Intelligent', and learn what trends are 'Hot In China'. (S15, ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-18 04:15:00" d="2021-07-18 04:40:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XV (1510)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>63% Rob, Chanel, and Steelo get sprung from some 'Rejector Seats', put friends to the test in 'Friend-terns', and steal the spotlight in 'Shine Suckers'. (S15, ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-18 04:40:00" d="2021-07-18 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XV (1511)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>63% Rob, Steelo and Chanel learn 'Practical Karate', bond with 'Grizzly Bros', and witness displays of 'Odd Dominance'. (S15, ep11)</k>  </p>
</a>
