<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2020-06-01 04:35:40"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 05:00:00" d="2020-06-08 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 07:00:00" d="2020-06-08 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria II (204)</n><t>M</t>    <k>80% Daria and her family participate in a strange and frightening ritual known as a family wedding. (S2, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 07:20:00" d="2020-06-08 07:45:00"><n u="Vidiots">Vidiots I (118)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The Vidiots get &quot;Cold&quot; with Maroon 5, pop bottles with &quot;Congratulations&quot;, shatter records with Paramore's &quot;Ain't It Fun&quot;, and are Rick Rolled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 07:45:00" d="2020-06-08 08:10:00"><n u="Say It In Song">Say It In Song I (112)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Shani and Nay were close friends on their high school step dance team, but things have been frosty between them ever since Shani dated Nay's ex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 08:10:00" d="2020-06-08 10:00:00"><n u="New: Lady Gaga Official Top">New: Lady Gaga Official Top 20 I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>We use exclusive official charts stats to count down the biggest-selling songs from Lady Gaga. But which of her tracks will be Number 1? Tune in to find out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 10:00:00" d="2020-06-08 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant">Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant II (212)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Kayla and Luke sit down with Stephan and Madison. Brianna gets Braeson his first tricycle. Ashley is shocked when Bar asks for a paternity test</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 11:00:00" d="2020-06-08 12:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant">Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant II (213)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Kayla is hopeful that Stephan will start showing up for Izaiah. Ashley resolves to co-parent with Bar. Rachel takes a pregnancy test. Kiaya asks Teazha</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 12:00:00" d="2020-06-08 13:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant">Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant II (214)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The guy Brianna's been talking to online makes a move. Ashley reaches a big milestone. Rachel wants her dad to meet her baby. Kayla's mom makes a decision</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 13:00:00" d="2020-06-08 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Backstabbers">Catfish: Backstabbers VII (730)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>When Kristina met Faith in a chatroom, she didn't intend to fall in love and betray her IRL fiancé. Now Nev and co-host Tallulah Willis navigate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 14:00:00" d="2020-06-08 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Backstabbers">Catfish: Backstabbers VII (732)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and co-host Elle King help Angel find her online love Remy. But the closest Angel has ever gotten to Remy was when he was creepily watching</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 15:00:00" d="2020-06-08 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Backstabbers">Catfish: Backstabbers V (506)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Chanelle is the light Michael needed in his life, but out of the blue she's disappeared, leaving only Nev and Max to help him find his missing love. (S5, ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 16:00:00" d="2020-06-08 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Backstabbers">Catfish: Backstabbers VII (726)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and co-host Slick Woods help 19-year-old Aubri find her Snapchat love, Brian. Brian says he lives at Aubri's college but has shady excuses not to meet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 17:00:00" d="2020-06-08 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Backstabbers">Catfish: Backstabbers I (107)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Joe was sceptical when Miss Teen USA, Kari, sent him a friend request. Now, after months of communication, Joe thinks it might be the real deal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 18:00:00" d="2020-06-08 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Backstabbers">Catfish: Backstabbers VII (715)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Max agree to help Chelsea finally meet Charles in person. While Chelsea has only spoken to Charles once on the phone, the guys soon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 19:00:00" d="2020-06-08 20:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom UK">Teen Mom UK VII (705)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Chloe argues with Sue over getting back with Jordan. Emma defends Nasseh. Amber's finding motherhood harder the second time round while Megan throws</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 20:00:00" d="2020-06-08 21:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (820)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Amber's new boyfriend comes to visit. Maci contemplates sending Bentley to a private school. Cheyenne enrolls Ryder in a preschool prep class while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 21:00:00" d="2020-06-08 21:30:00"><n u="New: Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown..">New: Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown.. I (105)</n><t>M</t>    <k>. Luaghs. Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs features the funniest clips from across the world. This week we've got toilet roll workouts, bin night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 21:30:00" d="2020-06-08 22:00:00"><n u="New: MTV Cribs: Footballers Stay..">New: MTV Cribs: Footballers Stay.. I (102)</n><t>M</t>    <k>. Home. Premier League Golden Boot winner Pierre-Emerick Aubameyang displays his trophy collection and Borussia Dortmund favourite Axel Witsel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 22:00:00" d="2020-06-08 23:00:00"><n u="One Night With My Ex">One Night With My Ex I (105)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>A communication breakdown caused Emma and Scott's break-up. Sophy and Sam never properly ended their love affair. Aiden learns the reason Brendon broke up with him. (S1, ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 23:00:00" d="2020-06-09 00:00:00"><n u="Young, Dumb &amp; Banged Up In The Sun">Young, Dumb &amp; Banged Up In The Sun I (105)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Waleed found himself framed for attempted robbery by a Thai market-keeper. Addy allowed herself to be used as a drug mule only to end up in a notorious Jamaica jail. (S1, ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-09 00:00:00" d="2020-06-09 01:00:00"><n u="Murdered By: Killed On Camera">Murdered By: Killed On Camera I (102)</n><t>M</t>    <k>17-year-old Georgia Williams, a policeman's daughter, was tortured on camera by her friend Jamie Reynolds, who was already known to the police</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-09 01:00:00" d="2020-06-09 01:30:00"><n u="New: Ridiculousness">New: Ridiculousness XVI (1616)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo celebrate Glass-Eatin, run from some Street Cows and go into retail with the Ridic Shopping Network. (S16, ep16)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-09 01:30:00" d="2020-06-09 02:00:00"><n u="New: Ridiculousness">New: Ridiculousness XVI (1617)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo get in touch with their softer sides in Tough and Tender, watch some baby thieves in Tiny, Sticky Fingers, and experience</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-09 02:00:00" d="2020-06-09 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! IX (902)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Holly has a house party but there's a massive kick-off between the lads when Marnie tries to make Aaron jealous by necking on with Kyle. (S9, ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-09 03:00:00" d="2020-06-09 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! IX (903)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The Geordies head to Paris for a Tash-on Tours job. Vicky gets unprofessionally mortal at work, and, on returning to the Toon, Charlotte leaves for crisis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-09 03:50:00" d="2020-06-09 04:40:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! IX (904)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Charlotte and Gary find themselves gravitating together after she returns from a showdown with her boyfriend. Vicky struggles to convince Marnie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-09 04:40:00" d="2020-06-09 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XVI (1603)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel, and Steelo get bent out of shape in 'Hinge Cringe', get trapped in a 'Giggle Prison' and take a visit to the angriest place on earth. (S16, ep3)</k>  </p>
</a>
