<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2020-05-29 04:36:08"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-05 05:00:00" d="2020-06-05 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-05 07:00:00" d="2020-06-05 07:20:00"><n u="Vidiots">Vidiots I (117)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The Vidiots shout they &quot;Ain't Your Mama&quot; with JLo, split up with Charlie Puth's &quot;We Don't Talk Anymore&quot;, and get freaky with Tov Lo's &quot;Cool Girl&quot;. (S1, ep17)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-05 07:20:00" d="2020-06-05 07:45:00"><n u="Crash Karaoke">Crash Karaoke I (110)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Hosts Hannah and Dylan wreak havoc at a supermarket, bust into a dog park, and make waves on a commuter ferry. Last in season. (S1, ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-05 07:45:00" d="2020-06-05 08:10:00"><n u="Say It In Song">Say It In Song I (110)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Redfoo and the song squad cook up a special visit to the park involving dancing yogis choreographed to Zedd's &quot;I Want You To Know&quot; to help convince Tara's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-05 08:10:00" d="2020-06-05 10:00:00"><n u="The Official UK Top">The Official UK Top 20 XIII (1322)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Exclusive first look at the biggest-selling songs of the week as we reveal the winners and losers of the race to the Official UK Number One spot!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-05 10:00:00" d="2020-06-05 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant">Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant II (209)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Rachel deals with consequences of not knowing who Hazelee's biological father is. Kiaya visits X'Zayveon in prison for the first time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-05 11:00:00" d="2020-06-05 12:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant">Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant II (210)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Ashley and Bar each take steps to move on. Kayla reaches a breaking point with Stephan. Rachel struggles to fit Drew into Hazelee's life. Brianna wrestles with a decision. (S2, ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-05 12:00:00" d="2020-06-05 13:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant">Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant II (211)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Kayla changes Izaiah's last name. Ashley meets up with a friend she's been talking to on social media. Rachel considers birth control. Kiaya agrees</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-05 13:00:00" d="2020-06-05 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Troublemakers">Catfish: Troublemakers II (209)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Five months ago Artis met Jess online. Artis and Jess each were in relationships, but believed they'd found true love. But is Jess everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-05 14:00:00" d="2020-06-05 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Troublemakers">Catfish: Troublemakers VI (617)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Robin is desperate to meet her hunky, long-distance love in person. Nev and Max agree to help her hunt him down, but what they uncover turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-05 15:00:00" d="2020-06-05 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Troublemakers">Catfish: Troublemakers III (307)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>John is ready to leave Detroit but one thing holds him back: Kelsey. The two have never spoken outside of online chats but John is sure she's the one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-05 16:00:00" d="2020-06-05 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Troublemakers">Catfish: Troublemakers II (211)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Aaliyah has been able to share her life struggles with Alicia. However, despite living only 70 blocks away, Alicia refuses to meet her as she hasn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-05 17:00:00" d="2020-06-05 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Troublemakers">Catfish: Troublemakers VII (713)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>A Tinder match ignited a fire for Jordan that caused Angel to end a real relationship to pursue him. Nev and his wife Laura uncover dark truths that could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-05 18:00:00" d="2020-06-05 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Troublemakers">Catfish: Troublemakers IV (415)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>David is the only love Andria has ever known. Love letters and voice messages make Andria stay. But having never met after 10 years, she needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-05 19:00:00" d="2020-06-05 19:30:00"><n u="Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs">Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs I (104)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs features the funniest lockdown clips from across the world. This week it's the 'trick shot lockdown showdown'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-05 19:30:00" d="2020-06-05 19:55:00"><n u="MTV Cribs: Footballers Stay Home">MTV Cribs: Footballers Stay Home I (101)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Manchester United star Jesse Lingard shows off his hard-earned England caps, and former FIFA Women's Player of the Year Lieke Martens reveals what she's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-05 19:55:00" d="2020-06-05 20:00:00"><n>The Official UK Number One</n><t>M</t>    <k>Check out this week's ultimate chart champion as we present The Official UK Number 1!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-05 20:00:00" d="2020-06-05 21:00:00"><n u="New: Post Malone: Official Top">New: Post Malone: Official Top 10</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>We use official chart stats to count down 10 of the biggest tracks from US superstar Post Malone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-05 21:00:00" d="2020-06-05 22:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (820)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Amber's new boyfriend comes to visit. Maci contemplates sending Bentley to a private school. Cheyenne enrolls Ryder in a preschool prep class while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-05 22:00:00" d="2020-06-05 23:00:00"><n u="New: Meghan: From Rags To Riches">New: Meghan: From Rags To Riches I (102)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Light-hearted look at Meghan Markle's journey from the streets of LA to her very own Prince Charming. The Hollywood starlet charmed the Queen, Harry's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-05 23:00:00" d="2020-06-06 02:00:00"><n>All New Most Shocking Celebrity...</n><t>M</t>    <k>. Moments. From Megan and Harry's turbulent time, to Wagatha Christie, we take a look at all new most shocking celebrity moments!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 02:00:00" d="2020-06-06 02:30:00"><n u="Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs">Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs I (104)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs features the funniest lockdown clips from across the world. This week it's the 'trick shot lockdown showdown'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 02:30:00" d="2020-06-06 03:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs: Footballers Stay Home">MTV Cribs: Footballers Stay Home I (101)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Manchester United star Jesse Lingard shows off his hard-earned England caps, and former FIFA Women's Player of the Year Lieke Martens reveals what she's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 03:00:00" d="2020-06-06 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! VIII (802)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Gary gets jealous when Marnie flirts with new boy Aaron. Vicky returns to the house, and there's the first ever Tash-On Tours as the Geordies put their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 03:50:00" d="2020-06-06 04:40:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! VIII (803)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Charlotte's back! And her arrival couldn't have come at a worse time. New lad Aaron wins a date with Holly after her challenge, but he reveals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 04:40:00" d="2020-06-06 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XV (1539)</n><t>M</t>    <k>62% Tommy Lee joins Rob, Steelo, and Chanel as they enter 'Total Mayhem', get blown away by 'Industrial Size Fans' and roll around 'In The Dirt'. (S15, ep39)</k>  </p>
</a>
