<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2020-05-13 04:36:00"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 05:00:00" d="2020-05-20 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 07:00:00" d="2020-05-20 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria I (109)</n><t>M</t>    <k>80% Quinn decides she needs cosmetic surgery, and drags Daria to the doctor with her. The surgeon is very interested in Daria, whom she views as a long-term</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 07:20:00" d="2020-05-20 08:10:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant V (511)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Pregnant Courtney has decided to reclaim her abstinence - which leaves her boyfriend Scott feeling frustrated and alone. Will their relationship survive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 08:10:00" d="2020-05-20 09:00:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant V (512)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Savannah had a difficult upbringing and relied on her boyfriend Stone for support. But after finding out she was pregnant, they soon split! Will they be able to co-parent as friends? (S5, ep12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 09:00:00" d="2020-05-20 10:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant">Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant I (101)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Kayla finds out news about Stephen. Cheerleader Lexi has to face the crowd with her pregnant belly. Brianna and Danae try to persuade Brianna's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 10:00:00" d="2020-05-20 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant UK">Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant UK I (108)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Charlotte throws a party for the twins. Charlie and Brett get back together. Alisha moves into a new house. Laura and Morgan celebrate their first mother's day! (S1, ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 11:00:00" d="2020-05-20 12:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us V (511)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Tattoo virgin Kieran trusts his best friend Dan. Jess and Paige reveal some hard truths. Squabbling siblings Tanya and Gemma try to mend their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 12:00:00" d="2020-05-20 13:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us V (512)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Lateysha Grace joins Charlotte to wrap up the series. Irish twins Simone and Olivia brew up some trouble. Will brothers-in-law Brandon and Ryan start a family feud? (S5, ep12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 13:00:00" d="2020-05-20 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Liars">Catfish: Liars VII (734)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Taylor needs help after falling for a guy claiming to have gone to her school. Nev and co-host Tallulah dig into Taylor's tale only to uncover secrets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 14:00:00" d="2020-05-20 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Liars">Catfish: Liars VI (601)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Divorcee Shawny calls Nev and Max to help uncover the shadowy identity of her attempt at new love. But things get interesting as they discover that Shawny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 15:00:00" d="2020-05-20 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Liars">Catfish: Liars IV (407)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Whitney met Brenell on a LGBT website four years ago and is head-over-heels in love. Brenell refuses to video chat with her, and Whitney is desperate to know why</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 16:00:00" d="2020-05-20 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Liars">Catfish: Liars IV (417)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Hundra never planned on falling in love with a girl and is risking coming out on national TV to learn if her love is for real. Nev investigates to reveal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 17:00:00" d="2020-05-20 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Liars">Catfish: Liars V (512)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Max travel across the country to discover the truth behind online romantic relationships</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 18:00:00" d="2020-05-20 19:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant UK">Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant UK I (108)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Charlotte throws a party for the twins. Charlie and Brett get back together. Alisha moves into a new house. Laura and Morgan celebrate their first mother's day! (S1, ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 19:00:00" d="2020-05-20 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show VII (752)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The Young and the Catfished. Nev and Max count down the Top Ten crazy &quot;Teenage Episodes&quot;, as well as share hilarious and embarrassing stories from their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 20:00:00" d="2020-05-20 21:00:00"><n u="New: Teen Mom OG">New: Teen Mom OG VIII (818)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Amber is shocked when security footage leaks from the night she was arrested. Andrew decides to share his side of the story. Catelynn confronts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 21:00:00" d="2020-05-20 22:00:00"><n u="New: Teen Mom UK">New: Teen Mom UK VII (708)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Chloe takes to the stage. Amber and Ste do some straight talking. Megan gets whisked away to Venice by new boyfriend Tel and Nasseh wants to prove</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 22:00:00" d="2020-05-20 23:00:00"><n u="New: Kids In Drag: We're Fabulous">New: Kids In Drag: We're Fabulous I (102)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Leo and his mother visit Dragutante, one of the only events designed for drag kids. Fabian and Nemis explore Montreal's gay village. Stephen and family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 23:00:00" d="2020-05-21 00:00:00"><n u="New: Body In The Bathroom: The...">New: Body In The Bathroom: The... II (201)</n><t>M</t>    <k>. Murder Of Naomi Hersi. Naomi Hersi met Jesse McDonald on a dating website. Jesse stabbed Naomi, left her body in the bathroom, and enlisted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 00:00:00" d="2020-05-21 01:00:00"><n u="True Life Crime">True Life Crime I (102)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Sarah Stern's car is discovered, the keys still in the ignition, but she is nowhere to be found. Police initially suspected suicide, but why would</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 01:00:00" d="2020-05-21 02:00:00"><n u="Young, Dumb &amp; Banged Up In The Sun">Young, Dumb &amp; Banged Up In The Sun I (102)</n><t>M</t>    <k>A champagne brunch in Dubai ends badly for Rebecca when she is accused of having sex in a taxi. Daniel is chasing the high life in Miami</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 02:00:00" d="2020-05-21 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! II (202)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Charlotte is pushed to breaking point as lothario Gaz continues to pull anything in a skirt. Rebecca's feistiness intensifies as she faces competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 03:00:00" d="2020-05-21 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! II (203)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>There's no time to mourn Charlotte's departure as Vicky and Ricci's nocturnal spooning is interrupted by an unexpected visitor. Meanwhile, Gary and James</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 03:50:00" d="2020-05-21 04:40:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! II (204)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>James continues his lucky streak with the ladies. Unlucky in love Sophie is played for a mug. Gary persuades Charlotte to return. but has she managed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 04:40:00" d="2020-05-21 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XV (1523)</n><t>M</t>    <k>62% Rob, Steelo and Chanel welcome Grammy-winning artist Anderson .Paak to check out some 'Social Slams', celebrate people with 'Signature Smiles', and party</k>  </p>
</a>
