<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2020-05-10 04:34:51"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-17 05:00:00" d="2020-05-17 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-17 07:00:00" d="2020-05-17 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria I (106)</n><t>M</t>    <k>80% Lawndale High has a couple of visitors, claiming to be modeling scouts looking for the next Christy Turlington. Quinn and Brittany have high hopes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-17 07:20:00" d="2020-05-17 08:10:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (810)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Catelynn and Tyler celebrate Carly's birthday without her, Maci sees Ryan at Bentley's baseball game, and Mackenzie suspects her husband may have cheated on her. (S8, ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-17 08:10:00" d="2020-05-17 09:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (811)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Amber feels she's at breaking point with Andrew. Cheyenne takes a trip to wine country with Matt and Ryder, and as Mackenzie tries to prepare for a fitness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-17 09:00:00" d="2020-05-17 10:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (812)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Maci takes Bentley to a counselor, Catelynn and Tyler reunite with Carly, Mackenzie gets devastating news, Cheyenne addresses Taylor's racist tweets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-17 10:00:00" d="2020-05-17 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom UK">Teen Mom UK VII (705)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Chloe argues with Sue over getting back with Jordan. Emma defends Nasseh. Amber's finding motherhood harder the second time round while Megan throws</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-17 11:00:00" d="2020-05-17 12:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom UK">Teen Mom UK VII (706)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Chloe lets her hair down on a weekend away but reality bites when she gets home. Emma gets an offer from Nasseh she can't resist. Dylan and Tel come to blows. (S7, ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-17 12:00:00" d="2020-05-17 13:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom UK">Teen Mom UK VII (707)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Megan is left speechless with a big surprise from new boyfriend Tel. Poor Amber ends up back in hospital. Chloe starts singing lessons and Emma's wish comes true. (S7, ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-17 13:00:00" d="2020-05-17 13:30:00"><n u="Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs">Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs I (101)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs features the funniest lockdown clips alongside specially designed celebrity challenges. This week famous faces compete</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-17 13:30:00" d="2020-05-17 14:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs UK">MTV Cribs UK I (103)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>This cult show is your access all areas pass to nosey around the pads of the famous. This week featuring Love Island love birds Alex &amp; Olivia Bowen &amp; Towie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-17 14:00:00" d="2020-05-17 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The Friend">Catfish: The Friend II (201)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Cassie was on a downward spiral until she got a friend request from a rapper named Steve. Two and a half years later, Cassie and Steve are engaged</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-17 15:00:00" d="2020-05-17 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The Friend">Catfish: The Friend VII (717)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>A mystery leads Nev and Laura to help Derek track down his online love. They uncover a Snapchat scandal, betrayal, and a conclusion that hits closer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-17 16:00:00" d="2020-05-17 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The Friend">Catfish: The Friend VII (709)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Infiniti is a 19-year-old dancer who is certain that her online romance is the real deal. But when Nev and Max dive deep, they find Infiniti's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-17 17:00:00" d="2020-05-17 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The Friend">Catfish: The Friend V (508)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Joanna was about to meet her online love in the flesh, but a crazy night in Vegas caused the whole relationship to go sour. Now she's enlisted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-17 18:00:00" d="2020-05-17 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The Friend">Catfish: The Friend VII (726)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and co-host Slick Woods help 19-year-old Aubri find her Snapchat love, Brian. Brian says he lives at Aubri's college but has shady excuses not to meet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-17 19:00:00" d="2020-05-17 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The Friend">Catfish: The Friend VII (715)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Max agree to help Chelsea finally meet Charles in person. While Chelsea has only spoken to Charles once on the phone, the guys soon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-17 20:00:00" d="2020-05-17 21:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The Friend">Catfish: The Friend VII (713)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>A Tinder match ignited a fire for Jordan that caused Angel to end a real relationship to pursue him. Nev and his wife Laura uncover dark truths that could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-17 21:00:00" d="2020-05-17 22:00:00"><n u="Rich Kids Go Skint">Rich Kids Go Skint I (104)</n><t>M</t>    <k>When Angelina moves in with a teenage mum with a three-year-old child, she struggles with housework, shopping on a budget and even walking the dog. (S1, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-17 22:00:00" d="2020-05-17 23:00:00"><n u="New: Undercover Twins">New: Undercover Twins I (104)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After both girls have gone on a date with likely lad Sam, they decide that it is time to reveal their subterfuge to all of the boys. (S1, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-17 23:00:00" d="2020-05-18 00:00:00"><n u="One Night With My Ex">One Night With My Ex I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Former couples are reunited for 24 hours and asked to delve deep into the heart of their broken romance. Will they move on and find closure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-18 00:00:00" d="2020-05-18 01:00:00"><n u="Ex On The Beach USA: Peak Of Love">Ex On The Beach USA: Peak Of Love IV (412)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Adore is pushed to choose between her ex and her next, pushing one of them into a jealous fit. A Hot Date is rewarded that causes tensions to flare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-18 01:00:00" d="2020-05-18 02:00:00"><n u="Jersey Shore Family Vacation">Jersey Shore Family Vacation III (350)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>It's been 10 years since The Guidos took over Seaside and the world! We're celebrating their 10th anniversary by looking back at all of the memorable</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-18 02:00:00" d="2020-05-18 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore">Geordie Shore I (104)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>With Holly gone, the atmosphere in the house takes a turn for the worse. Vicky and Jay fall out, Gaz plays away from home, and someone else tries to leave. (S1, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-18 03:00:00" d="2020-05-18 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore">Geordie Shore I (105)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Holly makes a surprise return to the Geordie Shore house, but not before Jay and Gaz face their toughest work assignment at a working man's club</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-18 03:50:00" d="2020-05-18 04:40:00"><n u="Geordie Shore">Geordie Shore I (106)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>There's no fairytale ending in the Geordie Shore finale. Gaz gives Charlotte some serious news, Jay and Vicky's relationship erupts in a shocking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-18 04:40:00" d="2020-05-18 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XV (1520)</n><t>M</t>    <k>62% Rob, Steelo and Chanel find out what makes you Call The Health Inspector, celebrate with some officers who've won the Cop Lottery, and air grievances</k>  </p>
</a>
