<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2021-07-12 04:59:30"><p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-19 05:00:00" d="2021-07-19 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-19 07:00:00" d="2021-07-19 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria IV (409)</n><t>M</t>    <k>81% The new discount store in Lawndale has opened. Daria, Jane and many others are forced to brave the soul-crushing horror of discount shopping when Daria</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-19 07:20:00" d="2021-07-19 08:10:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show I (108)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After a year and a half of chatting with her online, Tyler thinks he may have a future with Amanda. But are Tyler's friends correct because they suspect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-19 08:10:00" d="2021-07-19 09:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show I (109)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Rod met Ebony on a dating web site four years ago, now it's time for the two to meet in person. Is Ebony who she says she is? What will happen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-19 09:00:00" d="2021-07-19 09:30:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (105)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson ditches the dating apps and helps sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight Jake calls in his Love Squad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-19 09:30:00" d="2021-07-19 10:00:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (106)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson ditches the dating apps and helps sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight Fay calls in her Love Squad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-19 10:00:00" d="2021-07-19 10:30:00"><n u="Awkward">Awkward II (209)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Haunted by her break-up and make-up with the boys, Jenna privately struggles with how to untangle her twisted love life until an unexpected text brings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-19 10:30:00" d="2021-07-19 11:00:00"><n u="Awkward">Awkward II (210)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>In the aftermath of releasing her blog, everyone seems to have an opinion about Jenna's life. But while everyone else is in it for the entertainment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-19 11:00:00" d="2021-07-19 12:00:00"><n u="16 &amp; Pregnant">16 &amp; Pregnant II (217)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Christinna and Isiah have had to change their college plans as they prepare for their baby. His family is furious when he gives up his scholarship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-19 12:00:00" d="2021-07-19 13:00:00"><n u="16 &amp; Pregnant">16 &amp; Pregnant II (218)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Kayla is a southern belle. Now that she's pregnant, she has to start making her own tough decisions about marriage and her ability to make it without</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-19 13:00:00" d="2021-07-19 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Betrayals">Catfish: Betrayals VIII (8017)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Zay has gotten herself entangled with beautiful Jayda, causing strain on her already struggling marriage. But the lies are so deep, it's hard to uncover the truth. (S8, ep17)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-19 14:00:00" d="2021-07-19 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Betrayals">Catfish: Betrayals VII (713)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>A Tinder match ignited a fire for Jordan that caused Angel to end a real relationship to pursue him. Nev and his wife Laura uncover dark truths that could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-19 15:00:00" d="2021-07-19 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Betrayals">Catfish: Betrayals VII (732)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and co-host Elle King help Angel find her online love Remy. But the closest Angel has ever gotten to Remy was when he was creepily watching</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-19 16:00:00" d="2021-07-19 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Betrayals">Catfish: Betrayals V (506)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Chanelle is the light Michael needed in his life, but out of the blue she's disappeared, leaving only Nev and Max to help him find his missing love. (S5, ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-19 17:00:00" d="2021-07-19 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Betrayals">Catfish: Betrayals V (516)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After months of intimate texts with Titus, a man she met online, Candice has decided to tell to her husband. But before she does, she asks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-19 18:00:00" d="2021-07-19 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Betrayals">Catfish: Betrayals VI (602)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Alante has been planning a life with his online love. She's perfect but her disappearances have Alante worried. Nev and Max help uncover a truth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-19 19:00:00" d="2021-07-19 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Betrayals">Catfish: Betrayals VIII (8013)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Kamie receive a request to help Dre finally meet elusive Casey. But the request is unconventional and the situation becomes so intense, the hosts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-19 20:00:00" d="2021-07-19 21:00:00"><n u="Rich Kids Go Skint">Rich Kids Go Skint II (203)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rich kids share homes with families living on the breadline. (S2, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-19 21:00:00" d="2021-07-19 22:00:00"><n u="New: It's Your Fault I'm Fat">New: It's Your Fault I'm Fat II (207)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Reality series following teenagers and their families as they work together to shift the pounds. Dominique loves food, but her problem is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-19 22:00:00" d="2021-07-19 23:00:00"><n u="Catfish UK">Catfish UK I (105)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Alex has been chatting to Matt for a year and thinks he could be the one. But after several failed attempts to meet, Alex wants Julie and Oobah to track him down. (S1, ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-19 23:00:00" d="2021-07-20 00:00:00"><n u="True Life Crime UK">True Life Crime UK I (104)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>When James Brindley, 26, is knifed to death on his way home from a night out it devastates his close-knit family. Linda Adey looks to unravel the truth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 00:00:00" d="2021-07-20 01:00:00"><n u="Tattoo Disasters">Tattoo Disasters III (302)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Documentary series about people with now-regretted tattoos. Shaun's brother teases him about his incorrectly spelled football club tattoo. (S3, ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 01:00:00" d="2021-07-20 01:30:00"><n u="New: Ridiculousness">New: Ridiculousness XX (2022)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo check out dangerous butts in &quot;rear-ended&quot;, enter a dimension of beer and bad jokes in &quot;the dad zone&quot;, and lost almost all their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 01:30:00" d="2021-07-20 02:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XX (2021)</n><t>M</t>    <k>63% Rob, Chanel, and Steelo see what happens when families have &quot;no boundaries&quot;, look for a little more in some &quot;underreactions&quot; and check</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 02:00:00" d="2021-07-20 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Series">Geordie Shore: Series 18 XVIII (1801)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The Geordies are back on home turf and ready to cause more mayhem. This time, they'll be joined by old faces, new faces, friends and family as they prepare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 03:00:00" d="2021-07-20 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Series">Geordie Shore: Series 18 XVIII (1802)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Chloe and Sam show off their new home with a housewarming party. Nathan's buzzing when he realises he has to work on Scott's first job</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 03:50:00" d="2021-07-20 04:15:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (17)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Hole up in Morgan's house that has it all, from a private petting zoo to indoor spas and an outdoor oasis. (S2, ep17)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 04:15:00" d="2021-07-20 04:40:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (18)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Meet Bradley, the son of an entrepreneur, who dreams of being in the NBA. Next we check out the crib of brothers, Josh and Tucker, who live in a custom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 04:40:00" d="2021-07-20 05:00:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (19)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Brichon shows us her crib, complete with two movie theatres, and Aishah takes us on a tour of her haunted hotel! (S2, ep19)</k>  </p>
</a>
