<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="28" t="2020-04-12 04:33:00"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 05:00:00" d="2020-04-19 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 07:00:00" d="2020-04-19 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria IV (404)</n><t>M</t>    <k>80% A cheating scandal in Mr. DeMartino's class is fodder for Daria's nightmares, where she dreams that she's accused of killing Kevin, the suspected ringleader. (S4, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 07:20:00" d="2020-04-19 08:10:00"><n u="Young and Married">Young and Married I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>In this episode of 'Young and Married' we meet the couple 21-year-old Ben and 20-year-old Kirsten, from Atlanta. The couple married in secret without</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 08:10:00" d="2020-04-19 09:00:00"><n u="Young and Married">Young and Married I (102)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Engaged couple 19-year-old Oscar and 21-year-old Jordan live in Texas where same sex marriage is illegal. They're planning a commitment ceremony</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 09:00:00" d="2020-04-19 10:00:00"><n u="Young and Married">Young and Married I (103)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Engaged couple 19-year-old Missy and 20-year-old Matt announce they have set a date for their wedding to their family and friends but their family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 10:00:00" d="2020-04-19 11:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (407)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Chloe Ferry is back as a guest host. Benny &amp; Scott test their bromance. Bobby Norris &amp; Charlie find out how well they know each other. Kobi &amp; Macauley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 11:00:00" d="2020-04-19 12:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (408)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Joey Essex co-hosts and couple Cameron and Shereece confess all. Christian and Megan teach each other a lesson, Jordan and Zoe test their relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 12:00:00" d="2020-04-19 13:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (409)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The Valleys star Lateysha co-hosts the show and Big Brother star Aisleyne and her BFF Amy cement their friendship. Father and son Darren and Dean don't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 13:00:00" d="2020-04-19 14:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (410)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Charlotte's boyfriend Josh co-hosts and her BFFs Lauren and Melissa put their friendship to the test. DJ Tom Zanetti and his brother get competitive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 14:00:00" d="2020-04-19 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Shockers">Catfish: Shockers VII (704)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After a number of near-death experiences, Lawrence survived through it all with the assurance of Cierra's online love. But with Cierra blowing Lawrence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 15:00:00" d="2020-04-19 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Shockers">Catfish: Shockers VII (735)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Kimiko Glenn joins Nev in helping Matthew find his elusive Instagram love, Chance. But as they search for answers, they run into unsurpassable roadblocks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 16:00:00" d="2020-04-19 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Shockers">Catfish: Shockers VIII (806)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Akirra contacts Catfish for help to stop her bae's online ex, Jamie, from harassing her and her boyfriend William. But the script is flipped</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 17:00:00" d="2020-04-19 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Shockers">Catfish: Shockers VI (617)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Robin is desperate to meet her hunky, long-distance love in person. Nev and Max agree to help her hunt him down, but what they uncover turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 18:00:00" d="2020-04-19 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Shockers">Catfish: Shockers IV (411)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After a three-year online relationship, Tiana moved across the country to be with love-of-her-life James, and reveal her secret. Now in the same state</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 19:00:00" d="2020-04-19 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Shockers">Catfish: Shockers VIII (804)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Kamie receive an anonymous email from a whistleblower reporting a catfishing! But when our hosts arrive to help the named victim, they uncover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 20:00:00" d="2020-04-19 21:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Shockers">Catfish: Shockers VI (610)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dylan receives an anonymous text warning him that his online love, Ally, is not who she says she is. After the mystery texter is revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 21:00:00" d="2020-04-19 22:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (813)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After her arrest, Amber is released from jail. Mackenzie finds out Josh cheated on her. Maci's son can't go to Jagger's first birthday party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 22:00:00" d="2020-04-19 23:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom UK">Teen Mom UK VII (703)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Heartbroken Chloe gets some advice she doesn't want to hear. Amber and Ste come to blows. The honeymoon period is over for Megan and new mum Emma tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-19 23:00:00" d="2020-04-20 00:00:00"><n u="Celebrity Ex On The Beach">Celebrity Ex On The Beach I (113)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>One of the boys get sent home leaving the girls in tears. It all gets too much for one of the original eight. Sophie may have finally met</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 00:00:00" d="2020-04-20 01:00:00"><n u="True Life Crime">True Life Crime I (108)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Hanna Harris, a 21-year-old young mother, went out to celebrate the Fourth of July, but she never made it home. In order to find Hanna her family mounted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 01:00:00" d="2020-04-20 02:00:00"><n u="Ex On The Beach USA: Peak Of Love">Ex On The Beach USA: Peak Of Love IV (408)</n><t>M</t>    <k>A perfect date turns into a perfect nightmare for one couple. Niall is met with serious competition for Allie's affection. Marlon and La Demi struggle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 02:00:00" d="2020-04-20 02:30:00"><n u="Jackass">Jackass II (201)</n><t>M</t>    <k>68% Johnny Knoxville puts a sport cup through the ultimate in self-defence testing, and Chris Pontius gets attacked by a guard dog. Also features the human</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 02:30:00" d="2020-04-20 03:00:00"><n u="Jackass">Jackass II (202)</n><t>M</t>    <k>68% Johnny Knoxville and Steve-O engage in a dangerous game with professional Jai Alai players, and Ryan Dunn pays homage to Evel Knievel with an attempt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 03:00:00" d="2020-04-20 03:25:00"><n u="Jackass">Jackass I (105)</n><t>M</t>    <k>68% Chris Pontius terrorizes the late night denizens of LA, Johnny Knoxville creates the world's first &quot;Beekini&quot; and Ryan Dunn attempts to immerse himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 03:25:00" d="2020-04-20 03:50:00"><n u="Jackass">Jackass I (107)</n><t>M</t>    <k>68% Chris Pontius puts on his best leopard print G-string to wrestle some alligators in Florida, and Johnny Knoxville lets the winds of peace rush through</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 03:50:00" d="2020-04-20 04:15:00"><n u="Jackass">Jackass II (211)</n><t>M</t>    <k>68% Bam Margera and Brandon Dicamillo get double-crossed by the Jackass producers during a prank and &quot;arrested&quot; by a fake police officer. Also features beard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 04:15:00" d="2020-04-20 04:40:00"><n u="Jackass">Jackass II (212)</n><t>M</t>    <k>68% Johnny Knoxville, Chris Pontius, Mike Kassak and Rick Kossick go to the Sunset ranch for an old-style western shoot out. Also features snow surfing and spermathon! (S2, ep12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 04:40:00" d="2020-04-20 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XIV (1432)</n><t>M</t>    <k>62% Austin Mahone joins Rob, Steelo, and Chanel to talk about grandparents who are Grandpositive, the experience of Lake Aches, and things that happen Only In Japan. (S14, ep32)</k>  </p>
</a>
