<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="30" t="2021-07-09 07:09:52"><p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 05:00:00" d="2021-07-16 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 07:00:00" d="2021-07-16 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria IV (408)</n><t>M</t>    <k>81% The Morgendorffers attend a weekend retreat at the Quiet Ivy mental-health spa to be evaluated, as Helen is being considered for promotion. (S4, ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 07:20:00" d="2021-07-16 08:10:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show I (106)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>In this episode we meet Kya and Alyx, who fell in love quickly after meeting online. Are they being honest with each other? Hosts Nev Schulman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 08:10:00" d="2021-07-16 09:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show I (107)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Joe was sceptical when Miss Teen USA, Kari, sent him a friend request. Now, after months of communication, Joe thinks it might be the real deal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 09:00:00" d="2021-07-16 10:00:00"><n u="Rich Kids Go Skint">Rich Kids Go Skint II (202)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rich kids share homes with families living on the breadline. (S2, ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 10:00:00" d="2021-07-16 10:30:00"><n u="Awkward">Awkward II (207)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Now clear on her feelings for Jake, Jenna is to do the deed. Her determination however is met with obstacles in the form of Aunt Ally's wedding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 10:30:00" d="2021-07-16 11:00:00"><n u="Awkward">Awkward II (208)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>A series of revelations and bad timing leaves Jenna and Jake both devastated. (S2, ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 11:00:00" d="2021-07-16 12:00:00"><n u="16 &amp; Pregnant">16 &amp; Pregnant II (215)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Pregnant Markai and her boyfriend James may be kicked out of her house when her mum has had enough. So will Markai finish school and can their relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 12:00:00" d="2021-07-16 13:00:00"><n u="16 &amp; Pregnant">16 &amp; Pregnant II (216)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Aubrey and Brandon must find a home and start over in a new town, all while she tries to get her GED. They get married, but will their fresh start cause</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 13:00:00" d="2021-07-16 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Love At First Swipe">Catfish: Love At First Swipe III (309)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After a string of bad luck with women, Jeff believes he has finally found his dream girl in Megan. However, Megan is starting to sound off Catfish alarms. (S3, ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 14:00:00" d="2021-07-16 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Love At First Swipe">Catfish: Love At First Swipe IV (407)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Whitney met Brenell on a LGBT website four years ago and is head-over-heels in love. Brenell refuses to video chat with her, and Whitney is desperate to know why</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 15:00:00" d="2021-07-16 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Love At First Swipe">Catfish: Love At First Swipe V (503)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Since Leuh saw surfer Justin it's been insta-love. But after two failed attempts to meet up, she wants to know if he's the man of her dreams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 16:00:00" d="2021-07-16 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Love At First Swipe">Catfish: Love At First Swipe VII (722)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and co-host Tallulah Willis help Chelsea, a young woman who's fallen for a reality TV star. But digging for the truth only reveals Chelsea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 17:00:00" d="2021-07-16 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Love At First Swipe">Catfish: Love At First Swipe VIII (8009)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Aaliyah is saving herself for model Jaquan, a guy she's dating exclusively but has never met. As Nev and Kamie dig into his story, they become alarmed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 18:00:00" d="2021-07-16 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Love At First Swipe">Catfish: Love At First Swipe VIII (8028)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Michael is a reality TV star that has fallen in love with his online dream girl. When Nev and Kamie try to make a love connection, Michael gets a reality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 19:00:00" d="2021-07-16 19:55:00"><n u="Catfish: Love At First Swipe">Catfish: Love At First Swipe VII (717)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>A mystery leads Nev and Laura to help Derek track down his online love. They uncover a Snapchat scandal, betrayal, and a conclusion that hits closer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 19:55:00" d="2021-07-16 20:00:00"><n>The Official UK Number One</n><t>M</t>    <k>Check out this week's ultimate chart champion as we present The Official UK Number 1!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 20:00:00" d="2021-07-16 20:30:00"><n u="New: My Life On MTV">New: My Life On MTV I (109)</n><t>M</t>    <k>No one saw the late 90's pop explosion coming but once these two future legends stepped on the TRL stage they quickly became family, and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 20:30:00" d="2021-07-16 21:00:00"><n u="My Life On MTV">My Life On MTV I (108)</n><t>M</t>    <k>This is the true story about the evolution of two of the world's greatest rock bands, with MTV global archival footage dating back to our first broadcast year. 981! (S1, ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 21:00:00" d="2021-07-16 22:00:00"><n u="Catfish UK">Catfish UK I (105)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Alex has been chatting to Matt for a year and thinks he could be the one. But after several failed attempts to meet, Alex wants Julie and Oobah to track him down. (S1, ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 22:00:00" d="2021-07-16 23:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs: Ultimate Party Pads">MTV Cribs: Ultimate Party Pads I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>AJ Odudu has found the crčme de la crčme of MTV Cribs party pads, from Castle Bam to the notorious Playboy mansion, no one throws a house party like these guys. (S1, ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 23:00:00" d="2021-07-17 00:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs: Beautiful Beach Houses">MTV Cribs: Beautiful Beach Houses I (102)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Join AJ Odudu for a tour of the most beautiful celebrity beach houses on the planet. From Pamela Anderson's Malibu mansion to Naomi Campbell's Caribbean hideout. (S1, ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 00:00:00" d="2021-07-17 01:00:00"><n u="New: Teen Mom 2 Uncut">New: Teen Mom 2 Uncut X (1030)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>In Teen Mom 2 Uncut, Jade recovers at Briana's house, but has to make a decision about her family. Kail juggles three different co-parenting relationships. (S10, ep30)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 01:00:00" d="2021-07-17 01:30:00"><n u="MTV Cribs">MTV Cribs I (103)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Get ready to snoop around the homes of some of the biggest names in the business! This week featuring triple threat Jojo Siwa and Brit comedy genius Tom Allen. (S2, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 01:30:00" d="2021-07-17 02:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs">MTV Cribs I (104)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Get ready to snoop around the homes of some of the biggest names in the business! This week featuring Drag queen superstar Alyssa Edwards</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 02:00:00" d="2021-07-17 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Series">Geordie Shore: Series 17 XVII (1711)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The gang celebrate Pride as only the Geordies can with a mother of a house party. The course of true love doesn't run smooth for Sophie and Alex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 03:00:00" d="2021-07-17 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Series">Geordie Shore: Series 17 XVII (1712)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The Geordies' time down under is at an end, but not before they hit the seas for a boat party. Sam and Chloe make a decision about their relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 03:50:00" d="2021-07-17 04:15:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (14)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Kayden's Utah crib is so massive, it fills up an entire episode! There's a room of Harry Potter memorabilia, an Indiana Jones themed theatre</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 04:15:00" d="2021-07-17 04:40:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (15)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Twins Alan &amp; Andy's Austin home proves that everything is bigger in Texas. Then the elevator in Katie's killer Michigan crib ensures that we</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-17 04:40:00" d="2021-07-17 05:00:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (16)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Climb up treehouses, hang out in blissed-out bedrooms and trek across acres of adventureland at Rita and Will's Cribs. (S2, ep16)</k>  </p>
</a>
