<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2021-07-09 07:09:32"><p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 05:00:00" d="2021-07-14 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 07:00:00" d="2021-07-14 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria IV (406)</n><t>M</t>    <k>81% On an errand for her father, Daria runs into her school's annual parade where she encounters a lost child and strange feelings on a chance meeting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 07:20:00" d="2021-07-14 08:10:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show I (102)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Trina is a dancer who always had trouble meeting trustworthy guys, until she met Scorpio, a fellow dancer, online. Will Trina finally get to rendezvous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 08:10:00" d="2021-07-14 09:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show I (103)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Kim's been pouring her heart out to Matt for over 10 years. Now, Kim's facing a life-changing decision - should she marry her current boyfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 09:00:00" d="2021-07-14 09:30:00"><n u="MTV Cribs UK">MTV Cribs UK I (105)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>This cult show is your access all areas pass to nosey around the pads of the famous. This week featuring the homes of Essex queen Gemma Collins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 09:30:00" d="2021-07-14 10:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs UK">MTV Cribs UK I (106)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>This cult show is your access all areas pass to nosey around the pads of the famous. This week featuring the homes of Eyal Booker, Jess Wright and Chris Eubank Jnr. (S1, ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 10:00:00" d="2021-07-14 10:30:00"><n u="Awkward">Awkward II (203)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>While trying to make nice with Matty and please Jake, Jenna struggles to ignore Matty's on-going flirtatious efforts and clingy behaviour. (S2, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 10:30:00" d="2021-07-14 11:00:00"><n u="Awkward">Awkward II (204)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Still reeling from her parents separation, Jenna feels responsible. In an impulsive effort to absolve herself, she seeks refuge from her problems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 11:00:00" d="2021-07-14 12:00:00"><n u="16 &amp; Pregnant">16 &amp; Pregnant II (209)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Lizzie's pregnancy forces her to drop out of high school and the marching band. She looks to her boyfriend Skylar for support. until she discovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 12:00:00" d="2021-07-14 13:00:00"><n u="16 &amp; Pregnant">16 &amp; Pregnant II (210)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Kailyn's mum moved in with her new boyfriend, forcing Kailyn to live with her young boyfriend's family while she attempts to go to college. (S2, ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 13:00:00" d="2021-07-14 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Catastrophes">Catfish: Catastrophes VIII (8002)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Alfred's thirsty to find Adonis, the man of his dreams. But as they dig for answers, word that Nev and Kamie are in town leads to the most explosive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 14:00:00" d="2021-07-14 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Catastrophes">Catfish: Catastrophes VII (735)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Kimiko Glenn joins Nev in helping Matthew find his elusive Instagram love, Chance. But as they search for answers, they run into unsurpassable roadblocks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 15:00:00" d="2021-07-14 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Catastrophes">Catfish: Catastrophes VIII (8029)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>California preacher Jason thought Mar was the one when they matched but Mar would never meet up! When Nev and Kamie find out Mar could be a girl, Jason</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 16:00:00" d="2021-07-14 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Catastrophes">Catfish: Catastrophes I (104)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Jasmine has been texting with Mike for two years and thinks he could be the perfect step-father for her son. Although they live only 15 minutes apart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 17:00:00" d="2021-07-14 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Catastrophes">Catfish: Catastrophes VIII (8017)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Zay has gotten herself entangled with beautiful Jayda, causing strain on her already struggling marriage. But the lies are so deep, it's hard to uncover the truth. (S8, ep17)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 18:00:00" d="2021-07-14 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Catastrophes">Catfish: Catastrophes II (209)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Five months ago Artis met Jess online. Artis and Jess each were in relationships, but believed they'd found true love. But is Jess everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 19:00:00" d="2021-07-14 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Catastrophes">Catfish: Catastrophes V (501)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Max discover that Dejay and Malik are being played by the same guy. Sparks fly as they discover just how explosive a love triangle can be. (S5, ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 20:00:00" d="2021-07-14 21:00:00"><n u="New: Teen Mom">New: Teen Mom 2 X (1030)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Jade recovers at Briana's house, but has to make a decision about her family. Leah tries to balance Ali and Aleeah's unique needs. Kail juggles three</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 21:00:00" d="2021-07-14 22:00:00"><n u="New: The Hills: New Beginnings">New: The Hills: New Beginnings II (208)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Brody and Audrina's flirtation heats up. The war between the Pratts and Wahlers finally reaches boiling point. Brandon is left out in the cold by Dani's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 22:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom UK: Chloe's Story">Teen Mom UK: Chloe's Story I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Step inside the world of Chloe Patton. Chloe talks about falling pregnant at 16, walking out of a termination appointment, standing by her man, embracing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 23:00:00" d="2021-07-15 00:00:00"><n u="New: Catfish UK">New: Catfish UK I (105)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Alex has been chatting to Matt for a year and thinks he could be the one. But after several failed attempts to meet, Alex wants Julie and Oobah to track him down. (S1, ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 00:00:00" d="2021-07-15 01:00:00"><n u="Geordie OGs">Geordie OGs IV (401)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The OGs are back but will Aaron and Talia's relationship survive a new baby? Will Marnie and Casey stay strong after a recent split? Will Holly and Jacob</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 01:00:00" d="2021-07-15 01:30:00"><n u="New: Ridiculousness">New: Ridiculousness XX (2021)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo see what happens when families have &quot;no boundaries&quot;, look for a little more in some &quot;underreactions&quot; and check</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 01:30:00" d="2021-07-15 02:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XX (2020)</n><t>M</t>    <k>63% Rob, Chanel, and Steelo check out some mangled mouths in &quot;dentally ill&quot;, hit the skies in &quot;flying cars&quot;, and call out bald people attempting &quot;hair trickery&quot;. (S20, ep20)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 02:00:00" d="2021-07-15 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Series">Geordie Shore: Series 17 XVII (1707)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Holly arrives with a blast from the past. Nathan brings his inner Peter Andre to the club while Sophie brings her flirting skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 03:00:00" d="2021-07-15 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Series">Geordie Shore: Series 17 XVII (1708)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Holly is concerned for Chloe but Chloe just wants to teach Sam a lesson. Nathan's birthday calls for a trip to the outback, but what will the locals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 03:50:00" d="2021-07-15 04:15:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (8)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Get the tour of Harleigh's fun and colourful Florida home. Then join us as we head to Jesse's Virginia pad, and from there it's just a short</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 04:15:00" d="2021-07-15 04:40:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (9)</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this episode of Teen Cribs our first stop is Samantha's Pennsylvania princess palace, then we get to check out Dylan's Colorado mountain mansion. (S2, ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 04:40:00" d="2021-07-15 05:00:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (10)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Don't miss Nicole's tour of her amazing New Jersey home, complete with twenty-one cars! Then down in Virginia we check out Cody's crib, where</k>  </p>
</a>
