<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2019-08-13 02:21:17"><p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-19 05:00:00" d="2019-08-19 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-19 07:00:00" d="2019-08-19 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria I (107)</n><t>M</t>    <k>81% Daria and Kevin are forced to work as partners in science class. Daria does all the work, of course, while Kevin watches football on TV and flirts with Quinn. (S1, ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-19 07:20:00" d="2019-08-19 08:35:00"><n u="16 And Pregnant">16 And Pregnant II (208)</n><t>M</t>    <k>West Virginia cheerleader Leah is having twins with a boy she was dating for one month. If that wasn't hard enough, she develops health issues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-19 08:35:00" d="2019-08-19 10:00:00"><n u="16 And Pregnant">16 And Pregnant II (219)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Ashley is a pregnant high school senior from Texas with no baby daddy weighing in, and a family encouraging her to choose adoption</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-19 10:00:00" d="2019-08-19 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VII (725)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>All of the mums fly to New York for press week and it's the first time Amber, Maci and Catelynn meet Cheyenne and Bristol. Meanwhile, Tyler visits Butch in Austin. (S7, ep25)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-19 11:00:00" d="2019-08-19 12:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VII (726)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Amber travels to LA for a charity boxing event and Andrew motivates her to step in the ring. Maci takes all the kids to Texas. Catelynn takes steps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-19 12:00:00" d="2019-08-19 13:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VII (727)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Catelynn and Tyler celebrate the gender reveal of their new baby but are still planning to live separately. Amber continues to struggle with her depression</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-19 13:00:00" d="2019-08-19 14:00:00"><n u="The Hills: New Beginnings">The Hills: New Beginnings I (107)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>36% It's a new beginning for this iconic group of friends, as they return to the Hills and reconnect for the first time in years. While facing new challenges</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-19 14:00:00" d="2019-08-19 15:00:00"><n u="The Hills: New Beginnings">The Hills: New Beginnings I (108)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>36% It's a new beginning for this iconic group, as they return to the Hills and reconnect for the first time in years. Old rivalries and romances collide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-19 15:00:00" d="2019-08-19 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Most Shocking Reveals">Catfish: Most Shocking Reveals IV (407)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Whitney met Brenell on a LGBT website four years ago and is head-over-heels in love. Brenell refuses to video chat with her, and Whitney is desperate to know why</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-19 16:00:00" d="2019-08-19 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Most Shocking Reveals">Catfish: Most Shocking Reveals VII (705)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>A former Catfish turns to Nev and Max for help when they fall hard in love online. Could this Catfish be playing Nev and Max? Or will the Catfish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-19 17:00:00" d="2019-08-19 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Most Shocking Reveals">Catfish: Most Shocking Reveals V (516)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After months of intimate texts with Titus, a man she met online, Candice has decided to tell to her husband. But before she does, she asks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-19 18:00:00" d="2019-08-19 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Most Shocking Reveals">Catfish: Most Shocking Reveals III (304)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Lucille led a simple life until she was asked to work for music producer Kidd Cole. Companies were never paid and one day Kidd couldn't be found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-19 19:00:00" d="2019-08-19 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Most Shocking Reveals">Catfish: Most Shocking Reveals VI (617)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Robin is desperate to meet her hunky, long-distance love in person. Nev and Max agree to help her hunt him down, but what they uncover turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-19 20:00:00" d="2019-08-19 21:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant">Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant I (121)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Brianna focuses on Braeson's first birthday instead of her issues with Robert. Lexi's parents confront her about their problems with Kyler</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-19 21:00:00" d="2019-08-19 21:30:00"><n u="New: MTV Cribs UK">New: MTV Cribs UK I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>This cult show is your access all areas pass to nosey around the pads of the famous. This week featuring the homes of reality king Joey Essex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-19 21:30:00" d="2019-08-19 22:00:00"><n u="The Charlotte Show">The Charlotte Show III (308)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Charlotte comes out of surgery after having her breast implants removed, but it looks like recovery will be slow and painful. It's Charlotte's birthday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-19 22:00:00" d="2019-08-19 23:00:00"><n u="Geordie OGs">Geordie OGs I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Aaron misses his train to a press conference announcing his big fight, will he make it in time? Holly gets a tattoo removed and Marnie has her baby scan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-19 23:00:00" d="2019-08-20 00:00:00"><n u="New: Are You The One?">New: Are You The One? VIII (807)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Jonathan tries to make amends with Basit. One couple grows closer while others struggle to overcome toxic dating behaviours. (S8, ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 00:00:00" d="2019-08-20 00:30:00"><n u="New: Just Tattoo Of Us USA">New: Just Tattoo Of Us USA II (211)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>A couple come to the studio with opposite intentions, leaving a cheating boyfriend to face an ultimatum. Rage gets the better of two brothers. (S2, ep11)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 00:30:00" d="2019-08-20 01:00:00"><n u="New: Ridiculousness">New: Ridiculousness XII (1207)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo welcome &quot;Too Stupid To Die&quot; star Zach Holmes so they can spy on some Freaky Farmers! (S12, ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 01:00:00" d="2019-08-20 02:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits">Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits VIII (801)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The Geordies are back in the Toon for more partying, necking on and getting mortal. Everyone's buzzin' as a new lad arrives to join the crew and Marnie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 02:00:00" d="2019-08-20 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits">Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits VIII (803)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Charlotte's back! And her arrival couldn't have come at a worse time. New lad Aaron wins a date with Holly after her challenge, but he reveals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 03:00:00" d="2019-08-20 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits">Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits VIII (807)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After checking out the local guys, girls and geysers in Iceland, the Geordies head back to the Toon, where it all kicks off as Aaron and Scott</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 03:50:00" d="2019-08-20 04:40:00"><n u="MTV Cribs Priciest Pads">MTV Cribs Priciest Pads I (101)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Take a peek into the most expensive homes of the rich and famous. In this episode: Paulina Rubio, Nelly, Russell &amp; Kimora in New York, Tommy Lee, Rasheed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 04:40:00" d="2019-08-20 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness X (1030)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Steelo and Chanel are joined by actor Matt Shively to experience some &quot;paranorm-ish activity&quot;, and meet some animals that are &quot;milk ready&quot;. (S10, ep30)</k>  </p>
</a>
