<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2020-05-27 04:35:49"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 05:00:00" d="2020-06-03 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 07:00:00" d="2020-06-03 07:20:00"><n u="Vidiots">Vidiots I (115)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The Vidiots hit the couch and groove to &quot;Uptown Funk&quot; by Bruno Mars, &quot;Grow Up&quot; with Olly Murs, win with Panic! At The Disco's &quot;Victorious&quot; and go viral</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 07:20:00" d="2020-06-03 07:45:00"><n u="Crash Karaoke">Crash Karaoke I (108)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>On MTV's new ambush game show, hosts Hannah and Dylan get locked in a storage unit, shake up a pinball arcade, and bust into a tattoo parlour. (S1, ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 07:45:00" d="2020-06-03 08:10:00"><n u="Say It In Song">Say It In Song I (108)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Leah's friends Kelsey &amp; Sarah are getting married. Unfortunately, she can't make it to the wedding. Instead, she wants to surprise them, so she turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 08:10:00" d="2020-06-03 09:00:00"><n u="New: Bruno Mars: Official Top">New: Bruno Mars: Official Top 10 I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>We use exclusive official charts data to count down the best-selling singles from Bruno Mars. What will be his biggest-selling single? Tune in to find out!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 09:00:00" d="2020-06-03 10:00:00"><n>New: Nicole Scherzinger...</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>. Official Top 10. What's the biggest selling Nicole Scherzinger song ever? Find out right now with this official countdown packed full of the her hits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 10:00:00" d="2020-06-03 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant">Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant II (203)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Kayla starts to deal with her second pregnancy. Rachel is due any day but her family is forced to worry about her sister instead. Kiaya questions Teazha's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 11:00:00" d="2020-06-03 12:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant">Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant II (204)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Brianna gets a paternity test for Braeson. Kayla finally tells her mum the news about her pregnancy. Rachel gives birth and makes a decision about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 12:00:00" d="2020-06-03 13:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant">Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant II (205)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Brianna gets the results of Braeson's paternity test. Ashley reaches her breaking point with Bar. Kayla tries to give Stephan another chance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 13:00:00" d="2020-06-03 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Awkward Meetups">Catfish: Awkward Meetups VIII (808)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>DeJohn is so in love with online beauty Cashay that he's ready to propose, but his younger brother Adonis is convinced Cashay is a lie. Can Nev and Kamie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 14:00:00" d="2020-06-03 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Awkward Meetups">Catfish: Awkward Meetups IV (403)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Harold found his match with a beautiful fellow jock named Armani. Although they live in the same area, they've never met. Nev is joined by Angel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 15:00:00" d="2020-06-03 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Awkward Meetups">Catfish: Awkward Meetups VII (740)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Laura joins Nev to help Angel find her online love, Antonio. He claims to live in Angel's small town, yet is never able to meet her! It's clear Antonio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 16:00:00" d="2020-06-03 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Awkward Meetups">Catfish: Awkward Meetups VII (703)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After five years of talking to Matt, Kim is ready to meet up. As Max and Nev try to bring the two together, they uncover buried secrets that threaten</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 17:00:00" d="2020-06-03 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Awkward Meetups">Catfish: Awkward Meetups VII (728)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and NFL star Rashad Jennings help Deven find his mysterious online love James. James won't videochat yet he invites Deven to fly across the country to meet him! Deven needs answers. (S7, ep28)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 18:00:00" d="2020-06-03 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Awkward Meetups">Catfish: Awkward Meetups IV (412)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Falesha's name and pictures were stolen by a fake profile that nearly ruined her life. She thought her troubles were behind her, but four years later</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 19:00:00" d="2020-06-03 20:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom UK">Teen Mom UK VII (703)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Heartbroken Chloe gets some advice she doesn't want to hear. Amber and Ste come to blows. The honeymoon period is over for Megan and new mum Emma tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 20:00:00" d="2020-06-03 21:00:00"><n u="New: Billionaire Babies">New: Billionaire Babies I (102)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Reality series following super-rich parents who only provide the best for their offspring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 21:00:00" d="2020-06-03 22:00:00"><n u="New: Teen Mom OG">New: Teen Mom OG VIII (820)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Amber's new boyfriend comes to visit. Maci contemplates sending Bentley to a private school. Cheyenne enrolls Ryder in a preschool prep class while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 22:00:00" d="2020-06-03 23:00:00"><n>When Mum Becomes Dad &amp; Son...</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>. Becomes Daughter. Three people who are transitioning from their birth gender let cameras in on the many challenges that they face on the road to becoming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 23:00:00" d="2020-06-04 00:00:00"><n u="New: Murdered By: Killed On Camera">New: Murdered By: Killed On Camera I (102)</n><t>M</t>    <k>17-year-old Georgia Williams, a policeman's daughter, was tortured on camera by her friend Jamie Reynolds, who was already known to the police</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-04 00:00:00" d="2020-06-04 01:00:00"><n u="True Life Crime">True Life Crime I (104)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>24-year-old Jerika Binks vanished while out on a Sunday morning run in American Fork, Utah. Her family and authorities searched for a year, but found no trace. (S1, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-04 01:00:00" d="2020-06-04 02:00:00"><n u="Young, Dumb &amp; Banged Up In The Sun">Young, Dumb &amp; Banged Up In The Sun I (104)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Dale got caught up in Ibiza's party drug scene and was arrested as part of an island-wide sting. Charlie got stabbed in a Magaluf beach brawl and ended</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-04 02:00:00" d="2020-06-04 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! VII (702)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The Geordies are reeling from an explosive fallout following new girl Marnie's arrival. A night out ends with Scott completely losing his cool and trying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-04 03:00:00" d="2020-06-04 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! VII (703)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>It is Holly's birthday, the Geordies celebrate as only they know how - with a mint house party. Meanwhile there's a tiny tragedy in the house, leading</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-04 03:50:00" d="2020-06-04 04:40:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! VII (704)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The house is rocked to the core as Charlotte and Holly have an explosive falling out with new girl Marnie. Scott and Gary's friendship is pushed to the limit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-04 04:40:00" d="2020-06-04 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XV (1537)</n><t>M</t>    <k>62% Rob, Steelo and Chanel welcome singer and rapper DaniLeigh as they question the thinking behind 'Bad Plans', and celebrate the kings of the jungle in 'Lion Vibes'. (S15, ep37)</k>  </p>
</a>
