<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2020-05-26 04:38:07"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-02 05:00:00" d="2020-06-02 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-02 07:00:00" d="2020-06-02 07:20:00"><n u="Vidiots">Vidiots I (114)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The Vidiots party at &quot;My House&quot; with Flo Rida, call up Lady Gaga and Beyoncé's &quot;Telephone&quot;, and get colourful with Gotye's &quot;Somebody That I Used To Know&quot;. (S1, ep14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-02 07:20:00" d="2020-06-02 07:45:00"><n u="Crash Karaoke">Crash Karaoke I (107)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>On MTV's ambush game show, hosts Hannah and Dylan pose as hibachi chefs at a Japanese restaurant, bust up a bachelorette party, and sneak aboard an airline flight. (S1, ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-02 07:45:00" d="2020-06-02 08:10:00"><n u="Say It In Song">Say It In Song I (107)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Mike's parents are frustrated that he works long hours and they don't get to see him often. With Vampire Weekend's &quot;Holiday&quot; playing, he surprises</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-02 08:10:00" d="2020-06-02 10:00:00"><n u="New: The Official UK Top">New: The Official UK Top 20 XIII (1322)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Exclusive first look at the biggest-selling songs of the week as we reveal the winners and losers of the race to the Official UK Number One spot!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-02 10:00:00" d="2020-06-02 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant">Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant I (126)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Ashley disappoints her mum and sister. Jade re-evaluates her life after her grandmother's cancer scare. Brianna tries to heal old wounds. Kayla navigates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-02 11:00:00" d="2020-06-02 12:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant">Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant II (201)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Ashley gets back on track with school. Kayla understands she may have to drop out of school to take care of Izaiah. Brianna struggles to balance multiple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-02 12:00:00" d="2020-06-02 13:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant">Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant II (202)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Brianna reaches out to her ex. Kayla's boyfriend plans to move out of state. Rachel decides she doesn't want a paternity test. Kiaya worries her girlfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-02 13:00:00" d="2020-06-02 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Models">Catfish: Models VII (707)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>When Traves asks for help with his online girlfriend Candy, it looks like classic catfishing. But when the guys dig deeper, they realise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-02 14:00:00" d="2020-06-02 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Models">Catfish: Models IV (406)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Single father Felipe is ready to settle down with Jasmine. However, the two have been talking online for eight months and have never met. Max returns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-02 15:00:00" d="2020-06-02 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Models">Catfish: Models VII (710)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dylan's fallen for a beautiful model with an elusive secret. With all the standard red flags, Nev and Max assume it's an open and shut case, but the truth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-02 16:00:00" d="2020-06-02 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Models">Catfish: Models I (102)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Trina is a dancer who always had trouble meeting trustworthy guys, until she met Scorpio, a fellow dancer, online. Will Trina finally get to rendezvous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-02 17:00:00" d="2020-06-02 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Models">Catfish: Models VII (702)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Alyssa's friend Mary urged her to sign up for a dating website and that's where Alyssa met Tyler. As Nev and Max help, they begin to wonder who's behind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-02 18:00:00" d="2020-06-02 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Models">Catfish: Models I (111)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Rico wants to move to England to care for his ailing mother, but his intense online relationship with Ja'mari, an international male model, is giving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-02 19:00:00" d="2020-06-02 20:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom UK">Teen Mom UK VII (702)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Chloe cries a river over Jordan while Megan gets super Intense with new boyfriend Tel. Amber struggles without Ste. New mum Emma gets her hopes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-02 20:00:00" d="2020-06-02 20:30:00"><n u="MTV Cribs: Footballers Stay Home">MTV Cribs: Footballers Stay Home I (101)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Manchester United star Jesse Lingard shows off his hard-earned England caps, and former FIFA Women's Player of the Year Lieke Martens reveals what she's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-02 20:30:00" d="2020-06-02 21:00:00"><n u="Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs">Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs I (104)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs features the funniest lockdown clips from across the world. This week it's the 'trick shot lockdown showdown'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-02 21:00:00" d="2020-06-02 22:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (819)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Amber starts a new romance. Maci is content co-parenting with Jen, Ryan's mom. Cheyenne ends her relationship with Matt, while Corey leaves to compete</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-02 22:00:00" d="2020-06-02 23:00:00"><n u="New: Rich Kids Go Skint">New: Rich Kids Go Skint II (201)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rich kids share homes with families living on the breadline</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-02 23:00:00" d="2020-06-03 00:00:00"><n u="Young, Dumb &amp; Banged Up In The Sun">Young, Dumb &amp; Banged Up In The Sun I (104)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Dale got caught up in Ibiza's party drug scene and was arrested as part of an island-wide sting. Charlie got stabbed in a Magaluf beach brawl and ended</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 00:00:00" d="2020-06-03 01:30:00"><n u="New: The Challenge: Total Madness">New: The Challenge: Total Madness XXXV (3506)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Jenna struggles to maintain her tumultuous relationship at home while competing for a life-changing amount of money. A prank gone wrong threatens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 01:30:00" d="2020-06-03 02:00:00"><n u="New: Ridiculousness">New: Ridiculousness XVI (1613)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Rob, Chanel and Steelo get the phone insurance for some 'Screen Crackers', and celebrate our differences with 'Two Types Of People'. (S16, ep13)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 02:00:00" d="2020-06-03 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! VI (607)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>James and Gary come to blows which sends shockwaves through the house and Charlotte's heart strings are pulled for Gary as she offers him support. (S6 ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 03:00:00" d="2020-06-03 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! VI (608)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>As their time in Sydney comes to an end, the singles make it their mission to have a storming night in the Whitsundays. The coupled housemates have raised suspicions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 03:50:00" d="2020-06-03 04:40:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! VII (701)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The Geordies are back where they belong, in Newcastle, for a jaw-dropping summer season of partying, pulling, bucking, necking on and getting mortal. (S7, ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-03 04:40:00" d="2020-06-03 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XV (1536)</n><t>M</t>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel and Steelo welcome legendary rapper Trina to discuss what it means to be 'Da Baddest', and why sometimes you just gotta 'Let 'Em Fight'. (S15, ep36)</k>  </p>
</a>
