<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2020-05-12 04:36:56"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-19 05:00:00" d="2020-05-19 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-19 07:00:00" d="2020-05-19 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria I (108)</n><t>M</t>    <k>80% Quinn gets Daria to babysit for her. Daria, who has no interest in being an authority figure since she doesn't respect authority, is stuck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-19 07:20:00" d="2020-05-19 08:10:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant V (508)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jazmin was a motivated teenager from a strict family. She fell in love with Dell and got pregnant at 17. Can she gain back her parents' trust and allow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-19 08:10:00" d="2020-05-19 09:00:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant V (509)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Girly girl Jordan from Baltimore is kicked out by her parents when she falls pregnant by Derek. Now homeless and struggling financially, how will the young couple cope? (S5, ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-19 09:00:00" d="2020-05-19 10:00:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant V (510)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Savon had big dreams before falling pregnant with the school's most notorious player Ely. After being dumped while pregnant she meets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-19 10:00:00" d="2020-05-19 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant UK">Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant UK I (107)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Alisha's family dinner turns into a family fallout. Charlie and Brett reach the end of the line. Laura tries to fix family problems and Charlotte becomes a super mum. (S1, ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-19 11:00:00" d="2020-05-19 12:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us V (507)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Best mates Jack and Grant teach each other lessons with bold tattoos. Bristol beauties Beth and Merissa get emotional. Tasmin gives boyfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-19 12:00:00" d="2020-05-19 12:30:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us V (508)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Mum and daughter besties Clare and Chloe put motherly love to the test. Girlfriends Shai and Abbie put their future on the line. And Geordie Shore's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-19 12:30:00" d="2020-05-19 13:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us V (510)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Love fills the air as Geordie Shore's Thalia and mum Vanessa get inked. All's not well for Liam and Amber. Will jokers Hollie and Chelsea see the funny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-19 13:00:00" d="2020-05-19 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Should've Swiped Left">Catfish: Should've Swiped Left III (307)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>John is ready to leave Detroit but one thing holds him back: Kelsey. The two have never spoken outside of online chats but John is sure she's the one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-19 14:00:00" d="2020-05-19 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Should've Swiped Left">Catfish: Should've Swiped Left VI (619)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Jasmine writes to Nev and Max asking for help for a &quot;friend&quot;. But they're perplexed when Jasmine drops a bombshell revelation: they've helped her friend before! (S6, ep19)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-19 15:00:00" d="2020-05-19 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Should've Swiped Left">Catfish: Should've Swiped Left IV (403)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Harold found his match with a beautiful fellow jock named Armani. Although they live in the same area, they've never met. Nev is joined by Angel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-19 16:00:00" d="2020-05-19 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Should've Swiped Left">Catfish: Should've Swiped Left VII (716)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Max attempt to help a young woman named Nae track down her elusive internet celebrity crush and soon find themselves embroiled in a Catfish conspiracy! (S7, ep16)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-19 17:00:00" d="2020-05-19 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Should've Swiped Left">Catfish: Should've Swiped Left V (507)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Ray is determined to meet his online love Lexi. After learning that her sister has meddled in their relationship in the past, Nev and Max find themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-19 18:00:00" d="2020-05-19 19:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant UK">Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant UK I (107)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Alisha's family dinner turns into a family fallout. Charlie and Brett reach the end of the line. Laura tries to fix family problems and Charlotte becomes a super mum. (S1, ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-19 19:00:00" d="2020-05-19 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Hooked On Love">Catfish: Hooked On Love VI (651)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Join Nev and Max on a trip down memory lane as they reminisce about the happiest highlights of the past seasons, and countdown the ten most amorous Catfish moments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-19 20:00:00" d="2020-05-19 21:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom UK">Teen Mom UK VII (707)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Megan is left speechless with a big surprise from new boyfriend Tel. Poor Amber ends up back in hospital. Chloe starts singing lessons and Emma's wish comes true. (S7, ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-19 21:00:00" d="2020-05-19 22:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (817)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Cheyenne questions the longevity of her &amp; Matt's relationship. To Maci's surprise, Ryan shows up to Bentley's birthday party. Amber accepts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-19 22:00:00" d="2020-05-19 23:00:00"><n u="New: Rich Kids Go Skint">New: Rich Kids Go Skint I (105)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jodie takes a break from posting shots of her shopping trips in Mayfair to move in with mum-of-two Becky in her small flat. (S1, ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-19 23:00:00" d="2020-05-20 00:00:00"><n u="Young, Dumb &amp; Banged Up In The Sun">Young, Dumb &amp; Banged Up In The Sun I (102)</n><t>M</t>    <k>A champagne brunch in Dubai ends badly for Rebecca when she is accused of having sex in a taxi. Daniel is chasing the high life in Miami</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 00:00:00" d="2020-05-20 01:30:00"><n u="New: The Challenge: Total Madness">New: The Challenge: Total Madness XXXV (3504)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Bear seeks to prove that no one can extinguish the fire that he has for Kailah. Ashley and Mattie get into a heated argument. The players compete</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 01:30:00" d="2020-05-20 02:00:00"><n u="New: Ridiculousness">New: Ridiculousness XVI (1603)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo get bent out of shape in 'Hinge Cringe', get trapped in a 'Giggle Prison' and take a visit to the angriest place on earth. (S16, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 02:00:00" d="2020-05-20 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! I (151)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The Geordie Shore cast head to Magaluf for the summer hols. The lads quickly make up for lost time with the ladies, and tensions explode</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 03:00:00" d="2020-05-20 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! I (152)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>There's more Magaluf madness as the gang struggle to get along. Under the watchful eye of Charlotte and Vicky, Gary continues to charm the ladies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 03:50:00" d="2020-05-20 04:40:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! II (201)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Yes, it's time to 'get on it like a car bonnet'! Series 2 kicks off with two feisty new housemates joining the house. but will it be a warm welcome</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-20 04:40:00" d="2020-05-20 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XV (1522)</n><t>M</t>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel and Steelo welcome rap legend Rick Ross to remain calm in the 'Eye Of The Storm', marvel at 'Big Tyme Beasts', and enjoy some hot sauce in 'Wingin' It'. (S15, ep22)</k>  </p>
</a>
