<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="28" t="2020-05-31 04:35:48"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 05:00:00" d="2020-06-07 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 07:00:00" d="2020-06-07 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria II (203)</n><t>M</t>    <k>80% A (very) brief burst of intellectual activity by Quinn gets her an instant reputation as a &quot;brain.&quot; (S2, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 07:20:00" d="2020-06-07 08:10:00"><n u="MTV Cribs Priciest Pads">MTV Cribs Priciest Pads I (101)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Take a peek into the most expensive homes of the rich and famous. In this episode: Paulina Rubio, Nelly, Russell &amp; Kimora in New York, Tommy Lee, Rasheed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 08:10:00" d="2020-06-07 09:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs Priciest Pads">MTV Cribs Priciest Pads I (102)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Take a peek into the most expensive homes of the rich and famous. In this episode: Pamela Anderson, Penny Hardaway, Joey Fatone, Gene Simmons, Usher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 09:00:00" d="2020-06-07 10:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs Priciest Pads">MTV Cribs Priciest Pads I (103)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Take a peek into the most expensive homes of the rich and famous. In this episode: Ice-T, Robbie Williams, The Osbournes, Mariah Carey, Master P and Babyface! (S1, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 10:00:00" d="2020-06-07 11:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs Priciest Pads">MTV Cribs Priciest Pads I (104)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Come see the most expensive homes of the rich and famous. In this episode: Russell and Kimora, Brody and Brandon Jenner, Kimberly Stewart, The Playboy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 11:00:00" d="2020-06-07 11:30:00"><n u="MTV Cribs: Footballers Stay Home">MTV Cribs: Footballers Stay Home I (101)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Manchester United star Jesse Lingard shows off his hard-earned England caps, and former FIFA Women's Player of the Year Lieke Martens reveals what she's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 11:30:00" d="2020-06-07 12:00:00"><n u="Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs">Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs I (101)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs features the funniest lockdown clips alongside specially designed celebrity challenges. This week famous faces compete</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 12:00:00" d="2020-06-07 12:30:00"><n u="Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs">Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs I (102)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs features the funniest lockdown clips from across the globe. This week, quarantine cuisine and the return</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 12:30:00" d="2020-06-07 13:00:00"><n u="Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs">Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs I (103)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs features the most bizarre lockdown clips from across the world. This week, hilarious home schooling, plus famous faces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 13:00:00" d="2020-06-07 13:30:00"><n u="Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs">Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs I (104)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs features the funniest lockdown clips from across the world. This week it's the 'trick shot lockdown showdown'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 13:30:00" d="2020-06-07 14:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs UK">MTV Cribs UK I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>This cult show is your access all areas pass to nosey around the pads of the famous. This week featuring the homes of reality king Joey Essex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 14:00:00" d="2020-06-07 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Out For Revenge">Catfish: Out For Revenge III (303)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Max are contacted by Carmen who is sounding the alarm on behalf of her cousin, Antwane. He's been in a three-year romance with a man named</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 15:00:00" d="2020-06-07 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Out For Revenge">Catfish: Out For Revenge VII (719)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and co-host Jane Carrey help aspiring sugarbaby Mike choose between his LA life of leisure and his affection for the mysterious Joey, a broke mechanic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 16:00:00" d="2020-06-07 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Out For Revenge">Catfish: Out For Revenge VII (713)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>A Tinder match ignited a fire for Jordan that caused Angel to end a real relationship to pursue him. Nev and his wife Laura uncover dark truths that could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 17:00:00" d="2020-06-07 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Out For Revenge">Catfish: Out For Revenge V (511)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Paris enlists Nev and Max to help her figure out who has been catfishing her for the past four years. But as the guys investigate, they make a shocking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 18:00:00" d="2020-06-07 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Out For Revenge">Catfish: Out For Revenge VII (739)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Justin Combs and Nev set out to help Cherie uncover Avion's identity, a mysterious stranger who contacted the 26-year-old sales rep after he bought</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 19:00:00" d="2020-06-07 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Out For Revenge">Catfish: Out For Revenge VI (602)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Alante has been planning a life with his online love. She’s perfect but her disappearances have Alante worried. Nev and Max help uncover a truth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 20:00:00" d="2020-06-07 21:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Out For Revenge">Catfish: Out For Revenge VII (728)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and NFL star Rashad Jennings help Deven find his mysterious online love James. James won't videochat yet he invites Deven to fly across the country to meet him! Deven needs answers. (S7, ep28)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 21:00:00" d="2020-06-07 22:00:00"><n u="Rich Kids Go Skint">Rich Kids Go Skint II (201)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rich kids share homes with families living on the breadline. (S2, ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 22:00:00" d="2020-06-07 23:00:00"><n u="True Love Or True Lies?">True Love Or True Lies? I (103)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Cameron and Shereece row, Chris puts the others through their paces, and two new couples shock the mansion. But can they finally add to their prize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 23:00:00" d="2020-06-08 00:00:00"><n u="One Night With My Ex">One Night With My Ex I (104)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Harry and Amber, Stefan and Emma and Louis and Molissa spend 24 hours together to explore where things went wrong. (S1, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 00:00:00" d="2020-06-08 01:00:00"><n u="Ex On The Beach: Most Explosive">Ex On The Beach: Most Explosive (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Ex On The Beach Most Explosive Moments takes a look at the madness and mayhem of the earlier series. Find out the truth behind mad moments, crazy fights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 01:00:00" d="2020-06-08 02:00:00"><n u="Families Of The Mafia">Families Of The Mafia I (103)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Karen and the crew celebrate the grand opening of her restaurant, which includes an unexpected guest. Billy continues to make amends with Taylor and Joe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 02:00:00" d="2020-06-08 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! VIII (807)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After checking out the local guys, girls and geysers in Iceland, the Geordies head back to the Toon, where it all kicks off as Aaron and Scott</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 03:00:00" d="2020-06-08 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! VIII (808)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Will Aaron and Marnie finally get together, and will Scott and Gary make up? Meanwhile, Charlotte and Holly announce Geordie Shore's first-ever wedding. (S8, ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 03:50:00" d="2020-06-08 04:40:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! IX (901)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Buzzin'! Our favourite party animals are back! Everyone is shocked when Vicky gets a promotion and becomes their boss. Holly tries to stay classy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-08 04:40:00" d="2020-06-08 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XVI (1602)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel and Steelo dodge &quot;face-seeking missiles&quot;, hang with some &quot;creepy adolescents&quot;, and feel the &quot;call of the void&quot;. (S16, ep2)</k>  </p>
</a>
