<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="31" t="2020-04-14 04:32:18"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 05:00:00" d="2020-04-21 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 07:00:00" d="2020-04-21 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria IV (406)</n><t>M</t>    <k>80% On an errand for her father, Daria runs into her school's annual parade where she encounters a lost child and strange feelings on a chance meeting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 07:20:00" d="2020-04-21 07:45:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (19)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Brichon shows us her crib, complete with two movie theatres, and Aishah takes us on a tour of her haunted hotel! Series 2, Episode 19</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 07:45:00" d="2020-04-21 08:10:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (20)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sisters Marie Claire and Monique show us around their sprawling crib, and Ashley gives us a tour of her working farm. Series 2, Episode 20</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 08:10:00" d="2020-04-21 08:35:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (21)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Meet Patrick and Alexis as they show off their modern Michigan mansion. Next, we head to New Jersey to check out Corrina's crib. Series 2, Episode 21</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 08:35:00" d="2020-04-21 09:00:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (22)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Meet cousins Jacob and Chase as they show off their palatial New Jersey home. Then we jet to Michigan, as Emily shows off a house with more color</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 09:00:00" d="2020-04-21 09:30:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (23)</n><t>M</t>    <k>See Dylan &amp; Lyris' New York City apartment in the sky with views of the Empire State Building and Central Park. Then see Kipling, Rio &amp; Selkirk's Idaho</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 09:30:00" d="2020-04-21 10:00:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (24)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Welcome to Michigan, where sisters Chloe, Cassidy and Chyna show off the house their dad built, and Darian gives us a tour of his eco-friendly home. Series 2, Episode 24</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 10:00:00" d="2020-04-21 10:30:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (103)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson plays cupid to help sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight feisty fly girl Felicia and her London</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 10:30:00" d="2020-04-21 11:00:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (104)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson ditches the dating apps and helps sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight Tanya calls in her Love Squad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 11:00:00" d="2020-04-21 12:00:00"><n u="Geordie OGs">Geordie OGs I (103)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Marnie gives Casey a sexy birthday present. Holly faces her fears at Sussex Uni. Aaron meets up with Nathan and Sam to talk about mental health</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 12:00:00" d="2020-04-21 13:00:00"><n u="Geordie OGs">Geordie OGs I (104)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Marnie shows off her baby bump in a magazine shoot. Gary plays golf with Chris Hughes. Aaron's shocked to find out who his opponent is in his MMA fight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 13:00:00" d="2020-04-21 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Showdowns">Catfish: Showdowns IV (417)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Hundra never planned on falling in love with a girl and is risking coming out on national TV to learn if her love is for real. Nev investigates to reveal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 14:00:00" d="2020-04-21 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Showdowns">Catfish: Showdowns VII (723)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Fashion designer Truth is hot for his online crush despite the fact he's in a relationship IRL. The drama deepens when Nev and co-host Zeke Thomas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 15:00:00" d="2020-04-21 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Showdowns">Catfish: Showdowns III (305)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Lucille led a simple life until she was asked to work for music producer Kidd Cole. Companies were never paid and one day Kidd couldn't be found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 16:00:00" d="2020-04-21 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Showdowns">Catfish: Showdowns VIII (802)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Alfred's thirsty to find Adonis, the man of his dreams. But as they dig for answers, word that Nev and Kamie are in town leads to the most explosive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 17:00:00" d="2020-04-21 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Showdowns">Catfish: Showdowns VII (739)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Justin Combs and Nev set out to help Cherie uncover Avion's identity, a mysterious stranger who contacted the 26-year-old sales rep after he bought</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 18:00:00" d="2020-04-21 18:30:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (103)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson plays cupid to help sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight feisty fly girl Felicia and her London</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 18:30:00" d="2020-04-21 19:00:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (104)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson ditches the dating apps and helps sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight Tanya calls in her Love Squad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 19:00:00" d="2020-04-21 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show VIII (802)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Alfred's thirsty to find Adonis, the man of his dreams. But as they dig for answers, word that Nev and Kamie are in town leads to the most explosive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 20:00:00" d="2020-04-21 21:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom UK">Teen Mom UK VII (703)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Heartbroken Chloe gets some advice she doesn't want to hear. Amber and Ste come to blows. The honeymoon period is over for Megan and new mum Emma tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 21:00:00" d="2020-04-21 22:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (813)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After her arrest, Amber is released from jail. Mackenzie finds out Josh cheated on her. Maci's son can't go to Jagger's first birthday party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 22:00:00" d="2020-04-21 23:00:00"><n u="New: Undercover Twins">New: Undercover Twins I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Eight guys arrive in a romantic luxury location, unaware that they will be meeting two girls rather than one. After a series of rapid-fire dates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 23:00:00" d="2020-04-22 00:00:00"><n u="New: Celebrity Ex On The Beach">New: Celebrity Ex On The Beach I (114)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Georgia and Miles get closer but will it all end in tears? Marissa is pushed to her 'mob wife' limits, and Joey and Lorena head down to the beach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 00:00:00" d="2020-04-22 01:00:00"><n u="Geordie OGs">Geordie OGs II (208)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Holly and Jacob begin to look at wedding venues. Marnie celebrates her birthday, whilst Sophie moves out of her Dad's forever. Aaron's MMA fight is finally</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 01:00:00" d="2020-04-22 01:30:00"><n u="New: Ridiculousness">New: Ridiculousness XV (1537)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rob, Steelo and Chanel welcome singer and rapper DaniLeigh as they question the thinking behind 'Bad Plans', and celebrate the kings of the jungle in 'Lion Vibes'. (S15, ep37)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 01:30:00" d="2020-04-22 02:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XV (1536)</n><t>M</t>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel and Steelo welcome legendary rapper Trina to discuss what it means to be 'Da Baddest', and why sometimes you just gotta 'Let 'Em Fight'. (S15, ep36)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 02:00:00" d="2020-04-22 03:00:00"><n u="RuPaul's Drag Race">RuPaul's Drag Race IV (406)</n><t>M</t>    <k>The dolls design ship-shaped parade floats for a pride-filled runway extravaganza. With extra special guest judges Kelly Osbourne and NCIS' Pauley Perrette. (S4, ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 03:00:00" d="2020-04-22 03:45:00"><n u="RuPaul's Drag Race">RuPaul's Drag Race IV (407)</n><t>M</t>    <k>The queens turn the publishing industry on its wig as they launch their own magazines. With Extra special guest judges actress Regina King and country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 03:45:00" d="2020-04-22 04:40:00"><n u="RuPaul's Drag Race">RuPaul's Drag Race IV (408)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Paired up with their best &quot;frenemies&quot;, the dolls struggle through their differences to pull off live runway duets. With guest judges Pamela Anderson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 04:40:00" d="2020-04-22 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XIV (1434)</n><t>M</t>    <k>62% Racing champ Josef Newgarden joins Rob, Steelo, and Chanel to find out what makes a car Indy-Structible, pay tribute to those who are Pong-Strong</k>  </p>
</a>
