<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2019-07-11 00:20:51"><p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 05:00:00" d="2019-07-17 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 07:00:00" d="2019-07-17 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria III (313)</n><t>M</t>    <k>81% Jane starts dating a guy, to the annoyance of her misanthropic friend Daria. (S3, ep13)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 07:20:00" d="2019-07-17 08:10:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant IV (401)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Mackenzie has always lived in the moment, until she has to suddenly get serious about her own life when her boyfriend is nearly paralyzed in a car accident</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 08:10:00" d="2019-07-17 09:00:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant IV (402)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Once her days were filled with college applications and racing quad bikes with friends, but after getting pregnant, Katie has to completely rearrange her priorities. (S4, ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 09:00:00" d="2019-07-17 10:00:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant IV (403)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Briana gets pregnant at the same time as her sister, but their relationship becomes tense when they make different decisions regarding teenage motherhood. (S4, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 10:00:00" d="2019-07-17 11:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (401)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Charlotte's boyfriend Josh joins her as co-host and her mum and dad put their marriage to the test. While business partners Scott and Stefan's friendship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 11:00:00" d="2019-07-17 11:30:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (402)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Friends Saffron and Sheniya send each other a message, mother and son Mary and Lewis test their family bond while lovebirds Emily and Chris</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 11:30:00" d="2019-07-17 12:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (403)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Geordie Shore star Chloe Ferry co-hosts the show, best mates Josh and Warren push banter to its limits, and Charlotte Crosby gets her revenge by inking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 12:00:00" d="2019-07-17 13:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (404)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The king of Essex, Joey Essex co-hosts with Charlotte. Geordie Shore lovebirds Chloe and Sam face a trust test, and Frenemies Becky and Zoe tell each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 13:00:00" d="2019-07-17 14:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (405)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Ex On The Beach star Natalie Harris is taught a lesson by her mum and Love Island hunks Tom and Rykard try to get one over on each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 14:00:00" d="2019-07-17 15:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (407)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Chloe Ferry is back as a guest host. Benny &amp; Scott test their bromance. Bobby Norris &amp; Charlie find out how well they know each other. Kobi &amp; Macauley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 15:00:00" d="2019-07-17 16:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (408)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Joey Essex co-hosts and couple Cameron and Shereece confess all. Christian and Megan teach each other a lesson, Jordan and Zoe test their relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 16:00:00" d="2019-07-17 17:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (409)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The Valleys star Lateysha co-hosts the show and Big Brother star Aisleyne and her BFF Amy cement their friendship. Father and son Darren and Dean don't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 17:00:00" d="2019-07-17 18:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (410)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Charlotte's boyfriend Josh co-hosts and her BFFs Lauren and Melissa put their friendship to the test. DJ Tom Zanetti and his brother get competitive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 18:00:00" d="2019-07-17 19:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (411)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Geordie Shore star Nathan drops in to co-host and cousins Becky and Kodi cause chaos. Panto pals Josh and Jimmy get personal and Jack Devlin and his friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 19:00:00" d="2019-07-17 20:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (412)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The series goes out with a bang as Geordie Shore star Aaron Chalmers is back co-hosting. AJ and Monique reveal their true feelings and mates Sam and Cheryl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 20:00:00" d="2019-07-17 21:00:00"><n u="New: Teen Mom UK: Catching Up...">New: Teen Mom UK: Catching Up... (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>. With The Mums. As we gear up for the new series of Teen Mom UK, Frankie Bridge sits down with the cast to have an honest discussion about the issues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 21:00:00" d="2019-07-17 22:00:00"><n u="New: Teen Mom OG">New: Teen Mom OG VIII (804)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Maci and Taylor have a photoshoot debuting their first toddler line, while Ryan's family prepares for his release from prison. Catelynn worries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 22:00:00" d="2019-07-17 23:00:00"><n u="New: Catfish: The TV Show">New: Catfish: The TV Show VII (731)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Slick Woods investigate the mystery of Oceanna and her enigmatic, online stalker, Nelly. (S7, ep31)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 23:00:00" d="2019-07-18 00:00:00"><n u="New: The Challenge: War Of The...">New: The Challenge: War Of The... XXXIII (3314)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>. Worlds. With the finals on the horizon, competitors must face the daunting &quot;Judgement Day&quot; challenge, where two players will be purged from the game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-18 00:00:00" d="2019-07-18 01:00:00"><n u="The Charlotte Show">The Charlotte Show III (305)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Charlotte and Josh discover they will be travelling abroad for work, but an argument over a smoothie threatens to ruin the trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-18 01:00:00" d="2019-07-18 02:00:00"><n u="Fear Factor">Fear Factor I (107)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Ludacris tests family bonds as parents and their kids compete for $50k. But with thousands of scorpions, leeches and the ultimate cord-cutting challenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-18 02:00:00" d="2019-07-18 03:00:00"><n u="Fear Factor">Fear Factor I (108)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Ludacris puts lifelong friendships to the test as they face acid-shooting beasts, face the fear of drowning and must save their phones hundreds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-18 03:00:00" d="2019-07-18 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore">Geordie Shore X (1005)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>When Anna says there's a job for the Geordies in another country, they're all buzzing! That is until they turn up to a Caravan site in Wales</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-18 03:50:00" d="2019-07-18 04:40:00"><n u="Geordie Shore">Geordie Shore X (1006)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Hamburg is about to feel the full force of Tash on Tours, but are they ready for Marnie kicking off at Aaron? Holly's getting paranoid about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-18 04:40:00" d="2019-07-18 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness IX (927)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel and Steelo swap places as Chanel teaches that &quot;cute&quot; kills, Steelo warns about &quot;death carts&quot; and Rob shows how people get down with PPP. (S9, ep27)</k>  </p>
</a>
