<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2019-07-11 00:20:51"><p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-15 05:00:00" d="2019-07-15 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-15 07:00:00" d="2019-07-15 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria III (311)</n><t>M</t>    <k>81% A series of strange events lead Daria to wonder if aliens have taken over the town. (S3, ep11)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-15 07:20:00" d="2019-07-15 08:10:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant III (303)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Raised by a single mum, Jamie is a straight A student with big plans for the future. But after getting pregnant she struggles to mould her immature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-15 08:10:00" d="2019-07-15 09:00:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant III (304)</n><t>M</t>    <k>After following in her mum's footsteps by becoming a teen mum, Danielle strives to prove she can do things differently. But she soon learns she needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-15 09:00:00" d="2019-07-15 10:00:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant III (305)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Regarded as the most likely to succeed in her family, Cleondra shocks everyone by getting pregnant so young. Now she faces the tough decision to leave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-15 10:00:00" d="2019-07-15 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom">Teen Mom 2 IX (910)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>46% Barbara flies to New York to meet with Jace's dad. Adam's parents break the rules of their custody agreement. Lux's dad surprises Kailyn at Lincoln's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-15 11:00:00" d="2019-07-15 12:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom">Teen Mom 2 IX (911)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>46% Lincoln gets a new brother while Kail offers Jenelle a peace offering; but her good deed backfires. Chelsea is forced to confront Adam's parents about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-15 12:00:00" d="2019-07-15 13:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom">Teen Mom 2 IX (912)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>46% Kail launches her haircare line with a big party in NYC, and a few surprise guests show up. Things don't go well for Luis when Briana lets him see Stella. (S9, ep12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-15 13:00:00" d="2019-07-15 14:00:00"><n u="The Hills: New Beginnings">The Hills: New Beginnings I (102)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>With new faces in the picture and returning favourites, The Hills is back for a new beginning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-15 14:00:00" d="2019-07-15 15:00:00"><n u="The Hills: New Beginnings">The Hills: New Beginnings I (103)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>With new faces in the picture and returning favourites, The Hills is back for a new beginning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-15 15:00:00" d="2019-07-15 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Top 5 Meltdowns">Catfish: Top 5 Meltdowns II (206)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After being bullied in her past, Jen relies on online communities to establish relationships. After meeting Skylar online, they immediately hit it off</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-15 16:00:00" d="2019-07-15 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Top 5 Meltdowns">Catfish: Top 5 Meltdowns IV (417)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Hundra never planned on falling in love with a girl and is risking coming out on national TV to learn if her love is for real. Nev investigates to reveal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-15 17:00:00" d="2019-07-15 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Top 5 Meltdowns">Catfish: Top 5 Meltdowns II (209)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Five months ago Artis met Jess online. Artis and Jess each were in relationships, but believed they'd found true love. But is Jess everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-15 18:00:00" d="2019-07-15 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Top 5 Meltdowns">Catfish: Top 5 Meltdowns III (304)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Lucille led a simple life until she was asked to work for music producer Kidd Cole. Companies were never paid and one day Kidd couldn't be found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-15 19:00:00" d="2019-07-15 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Top 5 Meltdowns">Catfish: Top 5 Meltdowns IV (411)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After a three-year online relationship, Tiana moved across the country to be with love-of-her-life James, and reveal her secret. Now in the same state</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-15 20:00:00" d="2019-07-15 21:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant">Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant I (116)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Ashley files a restraining order against Bar's mum. Kayla blocks Stephan after he misses an appointment for Izaiah. Jade struggles with being a single mum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-15 21:00:00" d="2019-07-15 21:30:00"><n u="The Charlotte Show">The Charlotte Show III (303)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Charlotte has an embarrassing accident which results in a trip to the mattress shop. Charlotte must tell her mam and Lauren some big news about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-15 21:30:00" d="2019-07-15 22:00:00"><n u="The Charlotte Show">The Charlotte Show III (304)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Charlotte and Josh invite their parents for a weekend away, but will their families still get on after a weekend together in the Lake District? (S3, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-15 22:00:00" d="2019-07-15 23:00:00"><n u="New: Double Shot At Love With DJ..">New: Double Shot At Love With DJ.. I (110)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>. Pauly D &amp; Vinny. The ladies jet set to Houston to get the DJ Pauly nightlife experience and then home with Vinny for a not-so-quiet slumber party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-15 23:00:00" d="2019-07-16 00:00:00"><n u="New: Are You The One?">New: Are You The One? VIII (801)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>In the most ambitious dating experiment ever attempted, a group of singles are put through an extensive matchmaking process to find their perfect match. (S8, ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 00:00:00" d="2019-07-16 00:30:00"><n u="New: Just Tattoo Of Us USA">New: Just Tattoo Of Us USA II (206)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Insecurities about one's body are put on blast leaving a bromance in the balance. Sisters reach a turning point in their relationship when a long-standing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 00:30:00" d="2019-07-16 01:00:00"><n u="New: Ridiculousness">New: Ridiculousness XII (1202)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>On an all-new episode of Ridiculousness, Rob, Chanel, and Steelo party with Moms Gone Wild, and witness a few Grand Exits. (S12, ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 01:00:00" d="2019-07-16 02:00:00"><n u="Fear Factor">Fear Factor I (103)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Ludacris sets up the ultimate fear party games for teams of couples. They must bob for snakes, play Fear Pong and drive blindfolded to win $50,000. (S1, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 02:00:00" d="2019-07-16 03:00:00"><n u="Fear Factor">Fear Factor I (104)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Ludacris has best friends face off against computer bugs and confront their fear of drowning. But to win $50,000 they must scale a moving car-carrying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 03:00:00" d="2019-07-16 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore">Geordie Shore X (1001)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>When Charlotte finds out about a pact between Gary and Aaron she hatches a plan - but will she end up with egg on her face? Meanwhile James is having</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 03:50:00" d="2019-07-16 04:40:00"><n u="Geordie Shore">Geordie Shore X (1002)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>James makes a shock announcement and two new housemates come through the door. But the newbies' first night out is ruined when a fight breaks out between</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 04:40:00" d="2019-07-16 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness IX (925)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel and Steelo celebrate summer vacation by getting 'Sand Blasted', take a trip to 'Painland' and party with 'The Bang Gang. (S9, ep25)</k>  </p>
</a>
