<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2019-08-10 01:41:36"><p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-16 05:00:00" d="2019-08-16 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-16 07:00:00" d="2019-08-16 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria I (104)</n><t>M</t>    <k>81% Daria reluctantly becomes involved in the opening of Lawndale's new student coffeehouse. She also becomes involved in its closing. (S1, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-16 07:20:00" d="2019-08-16 08:10:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant V (501)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Maddy, an all-American girl from Illinois, gets pregnant from a one night stand. Will Maddy choose to live with the father of her child and his family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-16 08:10:00" d="2019-08-16 09:00:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant V (502)</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this episode, ex-party girl Autumn tries to get her boyfriend to straighten up before their bundle of joy arrives. (S5, ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-16 09:00:00" d="2019-08-16 10:00:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant V (503)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Millina's mum is in jail, and partner Trevor's mum faces her own problems. Will this expectant couple be able to give their son the stability they never had growing up? (S5, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-16 10:00:00" d="2019-08-16 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VII (722)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Bristol lets Tripp go to Alaska with his dad. Catelynn and Tyler visit Butch in rehab. Gary and Kristina take Leah to visit Amber in LA</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-16 11:00:00" d="2019-08-16 12:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VII (723)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Catelynn finds out that Tyler's sister Amber trashed their old house. Amber's brother travels to LA to meet baby James. Cheyenne and Cory anxiously await</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-16 12:00:00" d="2019-08-16 13:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VII (724)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Catelynn and Tyler celebrate Carly's birthday. Bentley starts the 4th grade while Jen and Larry are relieved when Ryan returns to rehab. (S7, ep24)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-16 13:00:00" d="2019-08-16 14:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (807)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Catelynn celebrates Mother's Day at home while Tyler visits his sister in Texas. Maci goes to Washington D.C to advocate for PCOS, while Cheyenne</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-16 14:00:00" d="2019-08-16 15:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (808)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Amber and Gary discuss how to handle Leah's panic attacks. Cheyenne questions Cory's priorities. Maci throws Taylor a surprise 30th birthday party. (S8, ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-16 15:00:00" d="2019-08-16 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Shockers">Catfish: Shockers III (302)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Max are contacted by Carmen who is sounding the alarm on behalf of her cousin, Antwane. He's been in a three-year romance with a man named</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-16 16:00:00" d="2019-08-16 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Shockers">Catfish: Shockers V (513)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Former model Jayme has learned that her online boyfriend is not only fake, but appears to be catfishing other women too! Nev and Max help find the catfish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-16 17:00:00" d="2019-08-16 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Shockers">Catfish: Shockers II (211)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Aaliyah has been able to share her life struggles with Alicia. However, despite living only 70 blocks away, Alicia refuses to meet her as she hasn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-16 18:00:00" d="2019-08-16 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Shockers">Catfish: Shockers III (306)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>John is ready to leave Detroit but one thing holds him back: Kelsey. The two have never spoken outside of online chats but John is sure she's the one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-16 19:00:00" d="2019-08-16 19:55:00"><n u="Catfish: Shockers">Catfish: Shockers II (209)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Five months ago Artis met Jess online. Artis and Jess each were in relationships, but believed they'd found true love. But is Jess everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-16 19:55:00" d="2019-08-16 20:00:00"><n>The Official UK Number One</n><t>M</t>    <k>Check out this week's ultimate chart champion as we present The Official UK Number 1!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-16 20:00:00" d="2019-08-16 21:55:00"><n>Bring It On: All Or Nothing</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Hayden Panettiere stars as a cheerleader who transfers to a rough high school and joins the cheerleading squad, where she has to fight against her former</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-16 21:55:00" d="2019-08-16 23:00:00"><n u="The Hills: New Beginnings">The Hills: New Beginnings I (108)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>36% It's a new beginning for this iconic group, as they return to the Hills and reconnect for the first time in years. Old rivalries and romances collide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-16 23:00:00" d="2019-08-17 00:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show VII (735)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Kimiko Glenn joins Nev in helping Matthew find his elusive Instagram love, Chance. But as they search for answers, they run into unsurpassable roadblocks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 00:00:00" d="2019-08-17 01:00:00"><n u="Jersey Shore Family Vacation">Jersey Shore Family Vacation II (221)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>With Mike's sentencing behind him, the roomies head up north to a dude ranch for a weekend getaway. The Guidos try to fish, Snooki drinks like a fish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 01:00:00" d="2019-08-17 02:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Marnie's Best Bits">Geordie Shore: Marnie's Best Bits XIV (1408)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>It’s proper awks between the newbies, while Scotty T and Abbie begin to get closer. Zahida goes mental at Marty and Gaz gets his revenge on Sam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 02:00:00" d="2019-08-17 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Marnie's Best Bits">Geordie Shore: Marnie's Best Bits XVI (1603)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>It's Marnie's birthday, which means party time! But an appearance from her boyfriend sends tensions soaring, with Aaron and Nathan coming to blows! Anna sends the family to Tenerife. (S16, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 03:00:00" d="2019-08-17 03:55:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Marnie's Best Bits">Geordie Shore: Marnie's Best Bits XVI (1610)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>It's the last couple of days in the house and the Geordies are going out with a bang! Steph and Abbie make up, and suspicions arise over Marnie and Aaron</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 03:55:00" d="2019-08-17 04:20:00"><n u="Jackass">Jackass I (105)</n><t>M</t>    <k>69% Chris Pontius terrorizes the late night denizens of LA, Johnny Knoxville creates the world's first &quot;Beekini&quot; and Ryan Dunn attempts to immerse himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 04:20:00" d="2019-08-17 04:40:00"><n u="Jackass">Jackass I (107)</n><t>M</t>    <k>69% Chris Pontius puts on his best leopard print G-string to wrestle some alligators in Florida, and Johnny Knoxville lets the winds of peace rush through</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-17 04:40:00" d="2019-08-17 07:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness X (1027)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Celebrate the world of NASCAR with a salute to &quot;pass masters&quot;, an introduction to NASCAR exits, and a look at what happens when people get &quot;pavemental&quot;. (S10, ep27)</k>  </p>
</a>
