<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2019-07-11 00:20:51"><p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 05:00:00" d="2019-07-16 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 07:00:00" d="2019-07-16 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria III (312)</n><t>M</t>    <k>81% The whole school goes on a mandatory-voluntary harbour cruise to raise money via casino gambling. (S3, ep12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 07:20:00" d="2019-07-16 08:10:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant III (307)</n><t>M</t>    <k>After hiding her pregnancy for eight months, Izabella is forced to reconsider who her true friends are. She then risks her family ties when her boyfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 08:10:00" d="2019-07-16 09:00:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant III (308)</n><t>M</t>    <k>With an immature boyfriend and a distant mum, Kianna wants more stability for her baby and considers adoption. When no one supports her decision</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 09:00:00" d="2019-07-16 10:00:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant III (309)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Taylor's mum wants her to choose adoption, but Taylor and her boyfriend Nathan feel that they can overcome the challenges of being teen parents. (S3, ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 10:00:00" d="2019-07-16 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom">Teen Mom 2 IX (913)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>46% Kail gets a call from Jo's wife about their child support battle. Nathan and Jenelle go back to court, with a surprising turn. Chelsea throws Aubree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 11:00:00" d="2019-07-16 12:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom">Teen Mom 2 IX (914)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>46% Barb and Jenelle have a wild weekend in Atlanta, but things go too far when she brings up another cast member. Kail and Jo celebrate Isaac's birthday together. (S9, ep14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 12:00:00" d="2019-07-16 13:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom">Teen Mom 2 IX (915)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>46% Leah's girls reveal their true feelings about Jason. Chelsea takes a family vacation, but comes home to a shocking find. Jenelle tries to defend her family on social media. (S9, ep15)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 13:00:00" d="2019-07-16 14:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (802)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Maci struggles with how to tell Bentley that Ryan is in jail. Cory makes his relationship with Taylor official, but Ryder's disorder puts her in the hospital. (S8, ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 14:00:00" d="2019-07-16 15:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (803)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Catelynn gives birth to her third daughter. Cheyenne starts dating someone new and it doesn't take long for Cory to find out. (S8, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 15:00:00" d="2019-07-16 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Season 7 OMG Moments">Catfish: Season 7 OMG Moments VII (705)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>A former Catfish turns to Nev and Max for help when they fall hard in love online. Could this Catfish be playing Nev and Max? Or will the Catfish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 16:00:00" d="2019-07-16 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Season 7 OMG Moments">Catfish: Season 7 OMG Moments VII (711)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Kiaira and Cortney had a baby despite Kiaira never meeting Cortney or the baby! Nev and Max try to bring the family together, but is this the greatest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 17:00:00" d="2019-07-16 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Season 7 OMG Moments">Catfish: Season 7 OMG Moments VII (713)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>A Tinder match ignited a fire for Jordan that caused Angel to end a real relationship to pursue him. Nev and his wife Laura uncover dark truths that could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 18:00:00" d="2019-07-16 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Season 7 OMG Moments">Catfish: Season 7 OMG Moments VII (718)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Max try to help Nick determine if the person he kissed during a mysterious blindfolded rendezvous is actually his online love, Jasmine, or someone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 19:00:00" d="2019-07-16 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Season 7 OMG Moments">Catfish: Season 7 OMG Moments VII (719)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and co-host Jane Carrey help aspiring sugarbaby Mike choose between his LA life of leisure and his affection for the mysterious Joey, a broke mechanic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 20:00:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (803)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Catelynn gives birth to her third daughter. Cheyenne starts dating someone new and it doesn't take long for Cory to find out. (S8, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 22:00:00"><n u="New: The Hills: New Beginnings">New: The Hills: New Beginnings I (104)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>It's a new beginning for this group of friends. Not everything is what it seems under the sunny skies of the Hollywood Hills. (S1, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 22:00:00" d="2019-07-16 23:00:00"><n u="Are You The One?">Are You The One? VIII (801)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>In the most ambitious dating experiment ever attempted, a group of singles are put through an extensive matchmaking process to find their perfect match. (S8, ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-16 23:00:00" d="2019-07-17 00:00:00"><n u="New: The Charlotte Show">New: The Charlotte Show III (305)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Charlotte and Josh discover they will be travelling abroad for work, but an argument over a smoothie threatens to ruin the trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 00:00:00" d="2019-07-17 01:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us IV (404)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The king of Essex, Joey Essex co-hosts with Charlotte. Geordie Shore lovebirds Chloe and Sam face a trust test, and Frenemies Becky and Zoe tell each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 01:00:00" d="2019-07-17 02:00:00"><n u="Fear Factor">Fear Factor I (105)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Ludacris pits married, engaged, dating and blind date couples, against each other to play a guessing game in the dark, have an unforgettable</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 02:00:00" d="2019-07-17 03:00:00"><n u="Fear Factor">Fear Factor I (106)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Ludacris takes couples whose relationships have been on and off, and tests their bonds. Plus, David Hasselhoff's daughter seeks to redeem her family name. (S1, ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 03:00:00" d="2019-07-17 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore">Geordie Shore X (1003)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>It's the Newbies' first morning in the house but with Holly, Kyle and Charlotte gone how will the family get back together? A shock revelation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 03:50:00" d="2019-07-17 04:40:00"><n u="Geordie Shore">Geordie Shore X (1004)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>It's the day that Charlotte's been dreading, Gary introduces his new girlfriend to the family but will Psycho Charlotte put in an appearance? Meanwhile Marnie and Aaron get very flirty! (S10, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-07-17 04:40:00" d="2019-07-17 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness IX (926)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Radio and TV star Charlemagne Tha God joins Rob, Chanel and Steelo to &quot;put some respeck on my name&quot;, call out the &quot;donkeys of the day&quot; and realise</k>  </p>
</a>
