<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="30" t="2021-07-13 05:02:51"><p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 05:00:00" d="2021-07-20 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 07:00:00" d="2021-07-20 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria IV (410)</n><t>M</t>    <k>81% The Fashion Club tells (sub)urban legends to pass the time while they're stranded in a bad part of town; driving around Lawndale, Daria hears one of them. (S4, ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 07:20:00" d="2021-07-20 08:10:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show IV (110)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Catfish brings together couples who've interacted solely through screens. In this unseen episode, Stephanie searches for the man she's been talking to. (S1, ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 08:10:00" d="2021-07-20 09:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show I (111)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Rico wants to move to England to care for his ailing mother, but his intense online relationship with Ja'mari, an international male model, is giving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 09:00:00" d="2021-07-20 09:30:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (107)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson ditches the dating apps and helps sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight, Jade calls in her Love Squad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 09:30:00" d="2021-07-20 10:00:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (108)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson ditches the dating apps and helps sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight, Gina calls in her Love Squad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 10:00:00" d="2021-07-20 10:30:00"><n u="Awkward">Awkward II (211)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Jenna's imagination runs wild as she fictionalises her blog in an attempt to change her fate. In their re-imagination and examination of her past, Jenna</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 10:30:00" d="2021-07-20 11:00:00"><n u="Awkward">Awkward II (212)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Jenna's decision about the boys goes public. Combined with a trip to Europe, everything is seeming to go Jenna's way. (S2, ep12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 11:00:00" d="2021-07-20 12:00:00"><n u="16 &amp; Pregnant">16 &amp; Pregnant II (219)</n><t>M</t>    <k>While her dad's in Afghanistan, Megan gets pregnant. But with little money and a video game playing boyfriend not necessarily in for the long haul, she'll</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 12:00:00" d="2021-07-20 13:00:00"><n u="16 &amp; Pregnant">16 &amp; Pregnant III (301)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jordan and her sister were models and best friends until Jordan's pregnancy put all that on hold. Now her boyfriend and her sister are competing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 13:00:00" d="2021-07-20 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Disasters">Catfish: Disasters VIII (8036)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Bryn thought he'd met 'the one' when he was introduced to Stephanie, but as Nev and Kamie poke holes in Stephanie's story, Bryn begins to doubt his dreams. (S8, ep36)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 14:00:00" d="2021-07-20 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Disasters">Catfish: Disasters VI (603)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Danny is intent on building a life with his online love, despite her violent past. But when he enlists Nev and Max to help him meet her, they discover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 15:00:00" d="2021-07-20 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Disasters">Catfish: Disasters VII (725)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Model Dallas has had his sights set on sexy Safari ever since she slid into his DMs - but despite flirty promises, she won't meet. Nev and co-host Tallulah</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 16:00:00" d="2021-07-20 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Disasters">Catfish: Disasters VIII (8011)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>In the first ever virtual catfish episode, Nev and Kamie won't let quarantine stop them from helping love struck Jason find the dirt on his Insta-model Keith. (S8, ep11)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 17:00:00" d="2021-07-20 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Disasters">Catfish: Disasters V (505)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Jaylin is prepared to sacrifice a lifelong friendship and promising videogame career to be with a woman he's never even spoken to on the phone. (S5, ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 18:00:00" d="2021-07-20 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Disasters">Catfish: Disasters VII (707)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>When Traves asks for help with his online girlfriend Candy, it looks like classic catfishing. But when the guys dig deeper, they realise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 19:00:00" d="2021-07-20 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Disasters">Catfish: Disasters VIII (8027)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>For years, DeJuan has held an everlasting flame for Tynea, but as Nev and Kamie unearth a mystery involving twin sisters, it leaves them seeing double</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 20:00:00" d="2021-07-20 21:00:00"><n u="Rich Kids Go Skint">Rich Kids Go Skint II (204)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rich kids share homes with families living on the breadline. (S2, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 21:00:00" d="2021-07-20 22:00:00"><n u="16 &amp; Pregnant">16 &amp; Pregnant VI (606)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Kali and Auston were shocked to get pregnant so young. Auston moved in with Kali and while Kali's parents feel they've been forced to take him in, Auston's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 22:00:00" d="2021-07-20 22:30:00"><n u="MTV Cribs">MTV Cribs I (105)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Snoop around the homes of some of the biggest names in the business! This week featuring The Vamps singer Brad, supermodel Caprice and athletes Perri</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 22:30:00" d="2021-07-20 23:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs">MTV Cribs I (106)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Get ready to snoop around the homes of some of the biggest names in the business! This week featuring International Don Diablo and social media star Holly H. (S2, ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-20 23:00:00" d="2021-07-21 00:00:00"><n u="New: Geordie OGs">New: Geordie OGs IV (402)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Marnie plans some big life goals. Holly finds her dream home, but will she get a mortgage? Sophie realises her friends are moving on but she isn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-21 00:00:00" d="2021-07-21 01:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom 2 Uncut">Teen Mom 2 Uncut X (1030)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>In Teen Mom 2 Uncut, Jade recovers at Briana's house, but has to make a decision about her family. Kail juggles three different co-parenting relationships. (S10, ep30)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-21 01:00:00" d="2021-07-21 01:30:00"><n u="New: Ridiculousness">New: Ridiculousness XX (2023)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo check out the dating scene with &quot;back on the market&quot;, question whether some people are &quot;maybe a murderer&quot;, and appreciate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-21 01:30:00" d="2021-07-21 02:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XX (2022)</n><t>M</t>    <k>63% Rob, Chanel, and Steelo check out dangerous butts in &quot;rear-ended&quot;, enter a dimension of beer and bad jokes in &quot;the dad zone&quot;, and lost almost all their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-21 02:00:00" d="2021-07-21 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Series">Geordie Shore: Series 18 XVIII (1803)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Sophie decides the girls need a holiday to Blackpool while relationships between the boys hit a new low. Faith makes up with Chloe, although she might</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-21 03:00:00" d="2021-07-21 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Series">Geordie Shore: Series 18 XVIII (1804)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After their trip to Blackpool the gang couldn't be in a better place, but that soon changes. Faith falls out with Nathan, and tensions in Sam and Chloe's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-21 03:50:00" d="2021-07-21 04:15:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (20)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sisters Marie Claire and Monique show us around their sprawling crib, and Ashley gives us a tour of her working farm. (S2, ep20)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-21 04:15:00" d="2021-07-21 04:40:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (21)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Meet Patrick and Alexis as they show off their modern Michigan mansion. Next, we head to New Jersey to check out Corrina's crib. (S2, ep21)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-21 04:40:00" d="2021-07-21 05:00:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (22)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Meet cousins Jacob and Chase as they show off their palatial New Jersey home. Then we jet to Michigan, as Emily shows off a house with more colour</k>  </p>
</a>
