<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="28" t="2020-05-14 04:56:23"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 05:00:00" d="2020-05-21 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 07:00:00" d="2020-05-21 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria I (110)</n><t>M</t>    <k>80% The annual teachers-versus-deejays roller hockey game is coming, and there's a good chance the students will get to see Mr. DeMartino die of an aneurysm during the game. (S1, ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 07:20:00" d="2020-05-21 08:10:00"><n u="Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant">Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant I (102)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Ashley and Bar's baby shower goes from zero to one hundred, Brianna is caught in the middle of her mum and Danae, Kayla grows concerned that</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 08:10:00" d="2020-05-21 09:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant">Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant I (103)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Ashley and Bar deal with the baby shower aftermath, Kayla is conflicted about her feelings toward Stephan, tensions rise between Brianna and Danae</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 09:00:00" d="2020-05-21 10:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant">Teen Mom: Young &amp; Pregnant I (104)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Lexi's parents are growing concerned that she and Kyler don't have a plan for the baby's arrival. Brianna and Danae escape tensions at home with a visit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 10:00:00" d="2020-05-21 11:00:00"><n u="Catfish Keeps It">Catfish Keeps It 100 VII (755)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Max count down the Top Ten most heartless catfish from the past six seasons. From con artists to nude photo collectors, these devious catfish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 11:00:00" d="2020-05-21 11:30:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us I (101)</n><t>M</t>    <k>There are tears and fall outs as three couples come to the studio to get tattoos designed by their loved ones. Will the relationship of Geordie Shore's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 11:30:00" d="2020-05-21 12:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us I (106)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Union J’s Jaymi Hensley visits the studio with his brother, BFFs Alicia and Louise deliver some extreme tatts, and Geordie Shore’s Holly is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 12:00:00" d="2020-05-21 13:00:00"><n u="Just Tattoo Of Us">Just Tattoo Of Us I (107)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Newly engaged Jess Impiazzi and Denny Solomona put their relationship to the test, and drag queen pals The Vivienne and Trashley dish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 13:00:00" d="2020-05-21 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Repeat Offenders">Catfish: Repeat Offenders VIII (810)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After years of hot drama, Gemini is desperate to find Myranda. But the script flips with the first intervention ever for an infamous repeat catfish! (S8, ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 14:00:00" d="2020-05-21 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Repeat Offenders">Catfish: Repeat Offenders VII (737)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Justin Combs joins Nev to help CJ find Shana, a woman who CJ's been having a steamy relationship with for eight years but has never met! (S7, ep37)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 15:00:00" d="2020-05-21 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Repeat Offenders">Catfish: Repeat Offenders VII (708)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Mandy is in love with a guy that gives her everything but the truth! Mandy's son has had enough and calls in Nev and Max. But following the clues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 16:00:00" d="2020-05-21 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Repeat Offenders">Catfish: Repeat Offenders VI (610)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dylan receives an anonymous text warning him that his online love, Ally, is not who she says she is. After the mystery texter is revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 17:00:00" d="2020-05-21 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Repeat Offenders">Catfish: Repeat Offenders VII (740)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Laura joins Nev to help Angel find her online love, Antonio. He claims to live in Angel's small town, yet is never able to meet her! It's clear Antonio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 18:00:00" d="2020-05-21 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish Keeps It">Catfish Keeps It 100 VII (755)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Max count down the Top Ten most heartless catfish from the past six seasons. From con artists to nude photo collectors, these devious catfish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 19:00:00" d="2020-05-21 20:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (818)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Amber is shocked when security footage leaks from the night she was arrested. Andrew decides to share his side of the story. Catelynn confronts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 20:00:00" d="2020-05-21 21:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom UK">Teen Mom UK VII (708)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Chloe takes to the stage. Amber and Ste do some straight talking. Megan gets whisked away to Venice by new boyfriend Tel and Nasseh wants to prove</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 21:00:00" d="2020-05-21 21:30:00"><n u="Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs">Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs I (102)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs features the funniest lockdown clips from across the globe. This week, quarantine cuisine and the return</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 21:30:00" d="2020-05-21 22:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs UK">MTV Cribs UK I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>This cult show is your access all areas pass to nosey around the pads of the famous. This week featuring the homes of reality king Joey Essex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 22:00:00" d="2020-05-21 23:00:00"><n u="New: Jersey Shore Family Vacation">New: Jersey Shore Family Vacation III (324)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The guys' takeover of Angelina's bachelorette party starts with the strip club and ends with Pauly and Jenni in the same bed! (S3, ep24)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-21 23:00:00" d="2020-05-22 00:00:00"><n u="New: Families Of The Mafia">New: Families Of The Mafia I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Karen embarks on a journey with her daughter to visit her father, Sammy &quot;The Bull&quot; Gravano, after his release from prison. Jess attempts to let Billy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-22 00:00:00" d="2020-05-22 01:00:00"><n u="Ex On The Beach USA: Peak Of Love">Ex On The Beach USA: Peak Of Love IV (413)</n><t>M</t>    <k>A shocking lie detector test throws the entire house into a frenzy, causing a strong couple to lose trust in their relationship. Georgia finally learns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-22 01:00:00" d="2020-05-22 01:30:00"><n u="New: Ridiculousness">New: Ridiculousness XVI (1604)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo talk about the most devious furniture known to man, where all diseases get their start, and they discuss the subtle art of 'Funk Tests'. (S16, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-22 01:30:00" d="2020-05-22 02:00:00"><n u="New: Ridiculousness">New: Ridiculousness XVI (1605)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Rob, Chanel and Steelo get hurt close to home in 'Porch Pain', and check out food frenzies in 'Buffet Behaviour'. (S16, ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-22 02:00:00" d="2020-05-22 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! II (205)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The 'cheer us all up' party ends in carnage as Charlotte tries to move on and the boys exchange blows. Vicky and Ricci make their relationship official</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-22 03:00:00" d="2020-05-22 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! II (206)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Ricci and Gary rock the house, leaving Vicky and Charlotte stunned. Meanwhile, the girls set off on a road trip tackling a colonic, Geordie Style</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-22 03:50:00" d="2020-05-22 04:40:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! II (207)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The honeymoon period is over as Vicky and Ricci split. Rebecca reveals her secret party trick, much to Jay's delight, whilst Gary comes clean with Charlotte</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-22 04:40:00" d="2020-05-22 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XV (1524)</n><t>M</t>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel, and Steelo welcome Vine star Brittany Furlan to experience 'Six Seconds Of Heaven', prank some spouses in 'Marital Diss', and catch 'Wiener Fever'. (S15, ep24)</k>  </p>
</a>
