<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="26" t="2020-05-17 04:35:41"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 05:00:00" d="2020-05-24 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 07:00:00" d="2020-05-24 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria II (201)</n><t>M</t>    <k>80% Daria reluctantly gets involved in a poster contest in which she and Jane depict &quot;Student Life At The Dawn Of The Millennium&quot;. ather negatively. (S2, ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 07:20:00" d="2020-05-24 08:10:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (816)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Gary takes Amber to anger management class after audio is leaked from a dispute. Catelynn visits her psychiatrist after listening to Amber's audio leaks. (S8, ep16)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 08:10:00" d="2020-05-24 09:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (817)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Cheyenne questions the longevity of her &amp; Matt's relationship. To Maci's surprise, Ryan shows up to Bentley's birthday party. Amber accepts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 09:00:00" d="2020-05-24 10:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (818)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Amber is shocked when security footage leaks from the night she was arrested. Andrew decides to share his side of the story. Catelynn confronts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 10:00:00" d="2020-05-24 11:00:00"><n u="Rich Kids Go Skint">Rich Kids Go Skint I (101)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Fergus leads a life of privilege in Chelsea, but how will he cope living with Anna and her family in Croydon, who are struggling to make ends meet? (S1, ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 11:00:00" d="2020-05-24 12:00:00"><n u="Rich Kids Go Skint">Rich Kids Go Skint I (102)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sepii is 21, a medical student and a rich kid. But now she faces a reality check as she spends time living with a family on the breadline in Manchester. (S1, ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 12:00:00" d="2020-05-24 13:00:00"><n u="Rich Kids Go Skint">Rich Kids Go Skint I (103)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Successful entrepreneur Dhillan finds out what life is like for mum-of-three Elaine and her family, who get by on her disability benefits. (S1, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 13:00:00" d="2020-05-24 13:30:00"><n u="Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs">Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs I (102)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs features the funniest lockdown clips from across the globe. This week, quarantine cuisine and the return</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 13:30:00" d="2020-05-24 14:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs UK">MTV Cribs UK I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>This cult show is your access all areas pass to nosey around the pads of the famous. This week featuring the homes of reality king Joey Essex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 14:00:00" d="2020-05-24 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Kickoffs">Catfish: Kickoffs VII (734)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Taylor needs help after falling for a guy claiming to have gone to her school. Nev and co-host Tallulah dig into Taylor's tale only to uncover secrets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 15:00:00" d="2020-05-24 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Kickoffs">Catfish: Kickoffs IV (411)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After a three-year online relationship, Tiana moved across the country to be with love-of-her-life James, and reveal her secret. Now in the same state</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 16:00:00" d="2020-05-24 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Kickoffs">Catfish: Kickoffs VIII (802)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Alfred's thirsty to find Adonis, the man of his dreams. But as they dig for answers, word that Nev and Kamie are in town leads to the most explosive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 17:00:00" d="2020-05-24 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Kickoffs">Catfish: Kickoffs V (519)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Luis has fallen for a single mum, and now he's ready to take their online relationship to the next level. But first Nev and Max must</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 18:00:00" d="2020-05-24 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Kickoffs">Catfish: Kickoffs VII (713)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>A Tinder match ignited a fire for Jordan that caused Angel to end a real relationship to pursue him. Nev and his wife Laura uncover dark truths that could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 19:00:00" d="2020-05-24 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Kickoffs">Catfish: Kickoffs IV (417)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Hundra never planned on falling in love with a girl and is risking coming out on national TV to learn if her love is for real. Nev investigates to reveal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 20:00:00" d="2020-05-24 21:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Kickoffs">Catfish: Kickoffs VI (608)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Max receive emails from opposite sides of the same online romance, each concerned that the other may be a catfish! What happens next leaves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 21:00:00" d="2020-05-24 22:00:00"><n u="Rich Kids Go Skint">Rich Kids Go Skint I (105)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jodie takes a break from posting shots of her shopping trips in Mayfair to move in with mum-of-two Becky in her small flat. (S1, ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 22:00:00" d="2020-05-24 23:00:00"><n u="New: Undercover Twins">New: Undercover Twins I (105)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After the revelations, the boys get to know the twins as separate people. (S1, ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 23:00:00" d="2020-05-25 00:00:00"><n u="One Night With My Ex">One Night With My Ex I (102)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Can Laura ever trust Scott again after he cheated? Chloe and Christian had a messy breakup at university, and Luke left the country because Sophie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-25 00:00:00" d="2020-05-25 01:00:00"><n u="Ex On The Beach USA: Peak Of Love">Ex On The Beach USA: Peak Of Love IV (413)</n><t>M</t>    <k>A shocking lie detector test throws the entire house into a frenzy, causing a strong couple to lose trust in their relationship. Georgia finally learns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-25 01:00:00" d="2020-05-25 02:00:00"><n u="Families Of The Mafia">Families Of The Mafia I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Karen embarks on a journey with her daughter to visit her father, Sammy &quot;The Bull&quot; Gravano, after his release from prison. Jess attempts to let Billy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-25 02:00:00" d="2020-05-25 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! III (305)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Vicky and Ricci return to the house in time for Becca's birthday which goes off in usual Geordie style. Sophie sends Joel back to England</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-25 03:00:00" d="2020-05-25 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! III (306)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>An unexpected call means James has to choose between his best mates and Holly. Gary has another threesome and a night out trying to forget about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-25 03:50:00" d="2020-05-25 04:40:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! III (307)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The boy-girl divide returns! Charlotte and Gaz aren't speaking, Becca and Jay are continually arguing, while Holly and James' nurse-patient relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-25 04:40:00" d="2020-05-25 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XV (1527)</n><t>M</t>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel and Steelo welcome Siesta Key's Chloe Trautman as they check out some 'Ship Wrecks', and love to hate on their 'Frenemies'. (S15, ep27)</k>  </p>
</a>
