<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2019-08-13 02:21:24"><p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 05:00:00" d="2019-08-20 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 07:00:00" d="2019-08-20 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria I (108)</n><t>M</t>    <k>81% Quinn gets Daria to babysit for her. Daria, who has no interest in being an authority figure since she doesn't respect authority, is stuck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 07:20:00" d="2019-08-20 08:10:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant V (505)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Summer's mum has struggled with addiction. Summer wants her mum in her life, but can she believe her promises of being sober and there for her and the baby? (S5, ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 08:10:00" d="2019-08-20 09:00:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant V (506)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Karley wasn't able to resist the charms of bad boy Tony. Shortly into their relationship, she finds out she's pregnant with twins. Can Tony settle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 09:00:00" d="2019-08-20 10:00:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant V (507)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Aleah met her boyfriend Shawn in a juvenile detention centre. Now they live together and Aleah is pregnant with health worries. Will the couple be able to cope? (S5, ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 10:00:00" d="2019-08-20 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VII (728)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Mackenzie and Ryan welcome their first baby so Maci wants to make sure all the kids have a big, happy family. Bristol feels guilty about Tripp's dwindling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 11:00:00" d="2019-08-20 12:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VII (729)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Gary finally finds his father while Andrew tries to help Amber with her depression. Cory is jealous when Cheyenne gets attention from an ex-boyfriend. (S7, ep29)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 12:00:00" d="2019-08-20 13:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VII (730)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Tyler moves out to start the trial separation. Bristol seeks advice from a PTSD counsellor. Cheyenne and Cory hook up. Maci tries to come</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 13:00:00" d="2019-08-20 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show VII (734)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Taylor needs help after falling for a guy claiming to have gone to her school. Nev and co-host Tallulah dig into Taylor's tale only to uncover secrets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 14:00:00" d="2019-08-20 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show VII (735)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Kimiko Glenn joins Nev in helping Matthew find his elusive Instagram love, Chance. But as they search for answers, they run into unsurpassable roadblocks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 15:00:00" d="2019-08-20 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Top 5 Craziest Ever">Catfish: Top 5 Craziest Ever IV (417)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Hundra never planned on falling in love with a girl and is risking coming out on national TV to learn if her love is for real. Nev investigates to reveal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 16:00:00" d="2019-08-20 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Top 5 Craziest Ever">Catfish: Top 5 Craziest Ever VII (711)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Kiaira and Cortney had a baby despite Kiaira never meeting Cortney or the baby! Nev and Max try to bring the family together, but is this the greatest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 17:00:00" d="2019-08-20 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Top 5 Craziest Ever">Catfish: Top 5 Craziest Ever III (302)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Max are contacted by Carmen who is sounding the alarm on behalf of her cousin, Antwane. He's been in a three-year romance with a man named</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 18:00:00" d="2019-08-20 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Top 5 Craziest Ever">Catfish: Top 5 Craziest Ever II (209)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Five months ago Artis met Jess online. Artis and Jess each were in relationships, but believed they'd found true love. But is Jess everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 19:00:00" d="2019-08-20 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Top 5 Craziest Ever">Catfish: Top 5 Craziest Ever IV (409)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>When Blaire's Instagram lover Markie broke her heart, she moved on. But now Markie is back and wants to meet. Blaire needs Nev and Max's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 20:00:00" d="2019-08-20 21:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (808)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Amber and Gary discuss how to handle Leah's panic attacks. Cheyenne questions Cory's priorities. Maci throws Taylor a surprise 30th birthday party. (S8, ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 21:00:00" d="2019-08-20 22:00:00"><n u="New: The Hills: New Beginnings">New: The Hills: New Beginnings I (109)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>It's a new beginning for this iconic group, as they return to the Hills and reconnect for the first time in years. Old rivalries and romances collide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 22:00:00" d="2019-08-20 23:00:00"><n u="New: Ex On The Beach USA">New: Ex On The Beach USA III (303)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Things between Cameron and Geles heat up quickly, two new exes wash ashore, and Aubrey and Devin butt heads at the paint party Lexi and Allie planned for the house. (S3, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-20 23:00:00" d="2019-08-21 00:00:00"><n u="Are You The One?">Are You The One? VIII (807)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Jonathan tries to make amends with Basit. One couple grows closer while others struggle to overcome toxic dating behaviours. (S8, ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 00:00:00" d="2019-08-21 01:00:00"><n u="Geordie OGs">Geordie OGs I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Aaron misses his train to a press conference announcing his big fight, will he make it in time? Holly gets a tattoo removed and Marnie has her baby scan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 01:00:00" d="2019-08-21 02:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits">Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits X (1001)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>When Charlotte finds out about a pact between Gary and Aaron she hatches a plan - but will she end up with egg on her face? Meanwhile James is having</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 02:00:00" d="2019-08-21 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits">Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits X (1004)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>It's the day that Charlotte's been dreading, Gary introduces his new girlfriend to the family but will Psycho Charlotte put in an appearance? Meanwhile Marnie and Aaron get very flirty! (S10, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 03:00:00" d="2019-08-21 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits">Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits XI (1103)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Gaz's pulling competition causes a bust up for Aaron and Scott. Charlotte tells Holly some home truths about Kyle while the toga party sees Chloe and Scott</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 03:50:00" d="2019-08-21 04:40:00"><n u="MTV Cribs Priciest Pads">MTV Cribs Priciest Pads I (102)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Take a peek into the most expensive homes of the rich and famous. In this episode: Pamela Anderson, Penny Hardaway, Joey Fatone, Gene Simmons, Usher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 04:40:00" d="2019-08-21 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XI (1101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel and Steelo watch some videos that are &quot;straight fire&quot;, and get freaked out by pet lovers in &quot;man's best friends with benefits&quot;. (S11, ep1)</k>  </p>
</a>
