<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="31" t="2020-04-13 04:31:33"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 05:00:00" d="2020-04-20 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 07:00:00" d="2020-04-20 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria IV (405)</n><t>M</t>    <k>80% Mr O'Neill encourages his class to pick something to fail at for personal growth, but all they get is misery. Jane is becoming popular enough to replace</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 07:20:00" d="2020-04-20 07:45:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (16)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Climb up treehouses, hang out in blissed-out bedrooms and trek across acres of adventureland at Rita and Will's Cribs. Series 2, Episode 16</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 07:45:00" d="2020-04-20 08:10:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (17)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Hole up in Morgan's house that has it all, from a private petting zoo to indoor spas and an outdoor oasis. (S2, ep17)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 08:10:00" d="2020-04-20 08:35:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (18)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Meet Bradley, the son of an entrepreneur, who dreams of being in the NBA. Next we check out the crib of brothers, Josh and Tucker, who live in a custom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 08:35:00" d="2020-04-20 09:00:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (19)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Brichon shows us her crib, complete with two movie theatres, and Aishah takes us on a tour of her haunted hotel! Series 2, Episode 19</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 09:00:00" d="2020-04-20 09:30:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (20)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sisters Marie Claire and Monique show us around their sprawling crib, and Ashley gives us a tour of her working farm. Series 2, Episode 20</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 09:30:00" d="2020-04-20 10:00:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (21)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Meet Patrick and Alexis as they show off their modern Michigan mansion. Next, we head to New Jersey to check out Corrina's crib. Series 2, Episode 21</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 10:00:00" d="2020-04-20 10:30:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson plays cupid to help sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight heartbroken heartthrob Christian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 10:30:00" d="2020-04-20 11:00:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (102)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson plays cupid to help sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight single mum Charlotte and her Blackpool</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 11:00:00" d="2020-04-20 12:00:00"><n u="Geordie OGs">Geordie OGs I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Aaron misses his train to a press conference announcing his big fight, will he make it in time? Holly gets a tattoo removed and Marnie has her baby scan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 12:00:00" d="2020-04-20 13:00:00"><n u="Geordie OGs">Geordie OGs I (102)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Marnie and Casey do a photo shoot for OK! Magazine. Holly takes a class in public speaking and it's date night for Gary and Emma. The stress of Aaron's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 13:00:00" d="2020-04-20 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Meltdowns">Catfish: Meltdowns V (512)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Max travel across the country to discover the truth behind online romantic relationships</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 14:00:00" d="2020-04-20 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Meltdowns">Catfish: Meltdowns II (203)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Ramon met Paola on Facebook and established an exclusive online relationship. But after many failed attempts to video chat, is she really who he thinks she is? (S2, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 15:00:00" d="2020-04-20 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Meltdowns">Catfish: Meltdowns VII (734)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Taylor needs help after falling for a guy claiming to have gone to her school. Nev and co-host Tallulah dig into Taylor's tale only to uncover secrets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 16:00:00" d="2020-04-20 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Meltdowns">Catfish: Meltdowns VI (619)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Jasmine writes to Nev and Max asking for help for a &quot;friend&quot;. But they're perplexed when Jasmine drops a bombshell revelation: they've helped her friend before! (S6, ep19)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 17:00:00" d="2020-04-20 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Meltdowns">Catfish: Meltdowns V (508)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Joanna was about to meet her online love in the flesh, but a crazy night in Vegas caused the whole relationship to go sour. Now she's enlisted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 18:00:00" d="2020-04-20 18:30:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson plays cupid to help sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight heartbroken heartthrob Christian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 18:30:00" d="2020-04-20 19:00:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (102)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson plays cupid to help sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight single mum Charlotte and her Blackpool</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 19:00:00" d="2020-04-20 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show VIII (801)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>For the last six years, Red's been talking to Jalissa and her group of celebrity besties. Hot on the trail to meet Jalissa in LA, Nev and Kamie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 20:00:00" d="2020-04-20 21:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (813)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After her arrest, Amber is released from jail. Mackenzie finds out Josh cheated on her. Maci's son can't go to Jagger's first birthday party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 21:00:00" d="2020-04-20 22:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom UK">Teen Mom UK VII (703)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Heartbroken Chloe gets some advice she doesn't want to hear. Amber and Ste come to blows. The honeymoon period is over for Megan and new mum Emma tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 22:00:00" d="2020-04-20 23:00:00"><n u="Geordie OGs">Geordie OGs II (208)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Holly and Jacob begin to look at wedding venues. Marnie celebrates her birthday, whilst Sophie moves out of her Dad's forever. Aaron's MMA fight is finally</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-20 23:00:00" d="2020-04-21 00:00:00"><n u="New: Ex On The Beach USA: Peak...">New: Ex On The Beach USA: Peak... IV (409)</n><t>M</t>    <k>. Of Love. Georgia and Callum face their harshest critics. Marlon is caught between a rock and a hot place when an ex arrives. The Ice Ceremony takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 00:00:00" d="2020-04-21 01:00:00"><n u="Celebrity Ex On The Beach">Celebrity Ex On The Beach I (113)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>One of the boys get sent home leaving the girls in tears. It all gets too much for one of the original eight. Sophie may have finally met</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 01:00:00" d="2020-04-21 01:30:00"><n u="New: Ridiculousness">New: Ridiculousness XV (1536)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rob, Chanel and Steelo welcome legendary rapper Trina to discuss what it means to be 'Da Baddest', and why sometimes you just gotta 'Let 'Em Fight'. (S15, ep36)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 01:30:00" d="2020-04-21 02:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XV (1535)</n><t>M</t>    <k>62% Jasper and Errol join Rob, Steelo and Chanel to see who 'Can't Feel The Heat', and greet some 'Polite Fighters'. (S15, ep35)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 02:00:00" d="2020-04-21 03:00:00"><n u="RuPaul's Drag Race">RuPaul's Drag Race IV (403)</n><t>M</t>    <k>The queens team up to create commercials for RuPaul's albums 'Glamazon' and 'Champion', with special guest judges Amber Riley and Grammy Award-winner Natalie Cole. (S4, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 03:00:00" d="2020-04-21 03:45:00"><n u="RuPaul's Drag Race">RuPaul's Drag Race IV (404)</n><t>M</t>    <k>The dolls go to jail when they star in a sitcom acting challenge, &quot;Hot in Tuckaho&quot;, coached by 'Will &amp; Grace' co-creator Max Mutchnick. (S4, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 03:45:00" d="2020-04-21 04:40:00"><n u="RuPaul's Drag Race">RuPaul's Drag Race IV (405)</n><t>M</t>    <k>The queens compete in a star-studded TV game show featuring their most fabulous and funny celebrity impersonations. With extra special guest judges</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-21 04:40:00" d="2020-04-21 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XIV (1433)</n><t>M</t>    <k>62% Sean Kingston joins Rob, Chanel, and Steelo to check out some Jamaica-mania, get more than broken heart from Danger Beauties, and share gifts</k>  </p>
</a>
