<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2019-08-15 22:47:28"><p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 05:00:00" d="2019-08-21 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 07:00:00" d="2019-08-21 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria I (109)</n><t>M</t>    <k>81% Quinn decides she needs cosmetic surgery, and drags Daria to the doctor with her. The surgeon is very interested in Daria, whom she views as a long-term</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 07:20:00" d="2019-08-21 08:10:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant V (508)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jazmin was a motivated teenager from a strict family. She fell in love with Dell and got pregnant at 17. Can she gain back her parents' trust and allow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 08:10:00" d="2019-08-21 09:00:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant V (509)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Girly girl Jordan from Baltimore is kicked out by her parents when she falls pregnant by Derek. Now homeless and struggling financially, how will the young couple cope? (S5, ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 09:00:00" d="2019-08-21 10:00:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant V (510)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Savon had big dreams before falling pregnant with the school's most notorious player Ely. After being dumped while pregnant she meets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 10:00:00" d="2019-08-21 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (801)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Catelynn and Tyler move back in together after a trial separation. Ryan returns home after rehab and wants to meet up with Maci. Cheyenne and Cory argue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 11:00:00" d="2019-08-21 12:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (802)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Maci struggles with how to tell Bentley that Ryan is in jail. Cory makes his relationship with Taylor official, but Ryder's disorder puts her in the hospital. (S8, ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 12:00:00" d="2019-08-21 13:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (803)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Catelynn gives birth to her third daughter. Cheyenne starts dating someone new and it doesn't take long for Cory to find out. (S8, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 13:00:00" d="2019-08-21 13:30:00"><n u="MTV Cribs UK">MTV Cribs UK I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>This cult show is your access all areas pass to nosey around the pads of the famous. This week featuring the homes of reality king Joey Essex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 13:30:00" d="2019-08-21 14:00:00"><n u="The Charlotte Show">The Charlotte Show III (308)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Charlotte comes out of surgery after having her breast implants removed, but it looks like recovery will be slow and painful. It's Charlotte's birthday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 14:00:00" d="2019-08-21 15:00:00"><n u="The Hills: New Beginnings">The Hills: New Beginnings I (109)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>36% It's a new beginning for this iconic group, as they return to the Hills and reconnect for the first time in years. Old rivalries and romances collide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 15:00:00" d="2019-08-21 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Top 5 OMG Moments">Catfish: Top 5 OMG Moments III (302)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Max are contacted by Carmen who is sounding the alarm on behalf of her cousin, Antwane. He's been in a three-year romance with a man named</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 16:00:00" d="2019-08-21 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Top 5 OMG Moments">Catfish: Top 5 OMG Moments V (513)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Former model Jayme has learned that her online boyfriend is not only fake, but appears to be catfishing other women too! Nev and Max help find the catfish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 17:00:00" d="2019-08-21 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Top 5 OMG Moments">Catfish: Top 5 OMG Moments II (211)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Aaliyah has been able to share her life struggles with Alicia. However, despite living only 70 blocks away, Alicia refuses to meet her as she hasn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 18:00:00" d="2019-08-21 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Top 5 OMG Moments">Catfish: Top 5 OMG Moments III (306)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>John is ready to leave Detroit but one thing holds him back: Kelsey. The two have never spoken outside of online chats but John is sure she's the one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 19:00:00" d="2019-08-21 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Top 5 OMG Moments">Catfish: Top 5 OMG Moments II (209)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Five months ago Artis met Jess online. Artis and Jess each were in relationships, but believed they'd found true love. But is Jess everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 20:00:00" d="2019-08-21 21:00:00"><n u="New: Teen Mom OG">New: Teen Mom OG VIII (809)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Cheyenne meets Matt's family. Maci and Taylor discuss their birth control options. Catelynn and Tyler cause a stir on social media, and Amber gets answers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 21:00:00" d="2019-08-21 22:00:00"><n u="New: Teen Mom UK">New: Teen Mom UK VI (605)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Sassi launches 'Sassi's Salon'. Chloe decides she wants to be a midwife but Jordan has doubts. Megan finds out a secret about Dylan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 22:00:00" d="2019-08-21 23:00:00"><n u="New: Geordie OGs">New: Geordie OGs I (102)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Marnie and Casey do a photo shoot for OK! Magazine. Holly takes a class in public speaking and it's date night for Gary and Emma. The stress of Aaron's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-21 23:00:00" d="2019-08-22 00:00:00"><n u="New: Catfish: The TV Show">New: Catfish: The TV Show VII (736)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev helps a lovestruck Navajo girl on her vision quest to find the Zuni man she loves, a man who not only admitted to being a drug smuggler</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 00:00:00" d="2019-08-22 00:25:00"><n u="MTV Cribs UK">MTV Cribs UK I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>This cult show is your access all areas pass to nosey around the pads of the famous. This week featuring the homes of reality king Joey Essex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 00:25:00" d="2019-08-22 01:00:00"><n u="The Charlotte Show">The Charlotte Show III (308)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Charlotte comes out of surgery after having her breast implants removed, but it looks like recovery will be slow and painful. It's Charlotte's birthday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 01:00:00" d="2019-08-22 02:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits">Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits XII (1202)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Charlotte finally turns up with some bunnies and some bigger news for Gaz. Will Holly share her secret? Aaron and Scott's dates with Chantelle end badly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 02:00:00" d="2019-08-22 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits">Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits I (103)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Boss Anna is livid after viewing some embarrassing footage. The house has been trashed! Two more old housemates arrive. Marty kicks off over Chloe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 03:00:00" d="2019-08-22 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits">Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits XIII (1302)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>At a boat party in Ibiza, Aaron drops the G-bomb on Marnie, and single Gaz is back when he pulls Chantelle. But how will Holly react when she finds out? And Chloe's plans don't go smoothly. (S13, ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 03:50:00" d="2019-08-22 04:40:00"><n u="MTV Cribs Priciest Pads">MTV Cribs Priciest Pads I (103)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Take a peek into the most expensive homes of the rich and famous. In this episode: Ice-T, Robbie Williams, The Osbournes, Mariah Carey, Master P and Babyface! (S1, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 04:40:00" d="2019-08-22 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XI (1102)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel and Steelo watch some &quot;PG porno&quot;, fill their tanks up with &quot;nightmare fuel&quot;, and meet the superhero known as &quot;The Drunk Knight&quot;. (S11, ep2)</k>  </p>
</a>
