<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2019-08-15 22:47:35"><p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 05:00:00" d="2019-08-22 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 07:00:00" d="2019-08-22 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria I (110)</n><t>M</t>    <k>81% The annual teachers-versus-deejays roller hockey game is coming, and there's a good chance the students will get to see Mr. DeMartino die of an aneurysm during the game. (S1, ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 07:20:00" d="2019-08-22 08:10:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant V (511)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Pregnant Courtney has decided to reclaim her abstinence - which leaves her boyfriend Scott feeling frustrated and alone. Will their relationship survive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 08:10:00" d="2019-08-22 09:00:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant V (512)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Savannah had a difficult upbringing and relied on her boyfriend Stone for support. But after finding out she was pregnant, they soon split! Will they be able to co-parent as friends? (S5, ep12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 09:00:00" d="2019-08-22 10:00:00"><n u="16 and Pregnant">16 and Pregnant I (1)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Maci is the classic overachiever and cheerleader. Now that's all set to change as she's pregnant and planning to graduate early and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 10:00:00" d="2019-08-22 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (804)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Maci and Taylor have a photoshoot debuting their first toddler line, while Ryan's family prepares for his release from prison. Catelynn worries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 11:00:00" d="2019-08-22 12:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (805)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Ryan returns home and Maci is disappointed he doesn't make more of an effort with Bentley. Cheyenne and Matt's relationship is getting serious. (S8, ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 12:00:00" d="2019-08-22 13:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (806)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The ladies take their first girls trip in ten years to Florida. Catelynn breaks some news to Nova who doesn't take it well, while Maci plans a surprise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 13:00:00" d="2019-08-22 14:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom UK">Teen Mom UK VI (604)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Ste can't hold his tongue at Brooklyn's party. Chloe grills Jordan about his lads trip. Megan summons Dylan's girlfriend for a chat. Sassi has her braces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 14:00:00" d="2019-08-22 15:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom UK">Teen Mom UK VI (605)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Sassi launches 'Sassi's Salon'. Chloe decides she wants to be a midwife but Jordan has doubts. Megan finds out a secret about Dylan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 15:00:00" d="2019-08-22 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Should've Swiped Left">Catfish: Should've Swiped Left I (109)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Rod met Ebony on a dating web site four years ago, now it's time for the two to meet in person. Is Ebony who she says she is? What will happen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 16:00:00" d="2019-08-22 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Should've Swiped Left">Catfish: Should've Swiped Left VII (715)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Max agree to help Chelsea finally meet Charles in person. While Chelsea has only spoken to Charles once on the phone, the guys soon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 17:00:00" d="2019-08-22 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Should've Swiped Left">Catfish: Should've Swiped Left IV (401)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Smart, single mum Miracle fell for Javonni, a dreamy-eyed Instagrammer. With Max on hiatus, Nev teams up with TV personality Charlamagne to take Miracle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 18:00:00" d="2019-08-22 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Should've Swiped Left">Catfish: Should've Swiped Left V (515)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Catfish is going international with a trip to the UK! Nev and Max meet Spencer who's been holding on to a secret for six years: he's in a relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 19:00:00" d="2019-08-22 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Should've Swiped Left">Catfish: Should've Swiped Left VI (610)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dylan receives an anonymous text warning him that his online love, Ally, is not who she says she is. After the mystery texter is revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 20:00:00" d="2019-08-22 21:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom UK">Teen Mom UK VI (605)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Sassi launches 'Sassi's Salon'. Chloe decides she wants to be a midwife but Jordan has doubts. Megan finds out a secret about Dylan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 21:00:00" d="2019-08-22 22:00:00"><n u="The Hills: New Beginnings">The Hills: New Beginnings I (109)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>36% It's a new beginning for this iconic group, as they return to the Hills and reconnect for the first time in years. Old rivalries and romances collide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 22:00:00" d="2019-08-22 23:00:00"><n u="New: Jersey Shore Family Vacation">New: Jersey Shore Family Vacation II (222)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The girls extend an invite to the dude Ranch for Mike's surprise bachelor party. However, Pauly and Vinny extended some invites of their own to a bunch of strippers! (S2, ep22)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-22 23:00:00" d="2019-08-23 00:00:00"><n u="Geordie OGs">Geordie OGs I (102)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Marnie and Casey do a photo shoot for OK! Magazine. Holly takes a class in public speaking and it's date night for Gary and Emma. The stress of Aaron's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-23 00:00:00" d="2019-08-23 01:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show VII (736)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev helps a lovestruck Navajo girl on her vision quest to find the Zuni man she loves, a man who not only admitted to being a drug smuggler</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-23 01:00:00" d="2019-08-23 02:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits">Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits XIII (1308)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>It's Holly's birthday and she gets a massive surprise when Kyle shows up. Marty goes in on Chloe but takes it too far. Meanwhile, Aaron and Marnie's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-23 02:00:00" d="2019-08-23 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits">Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits XIV (1402)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Aaron and Marty decide to get close to newbies Sarah and Abbie. After her kick-off with Zahida, Chloe gets some big news. And the family is stunned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-23 03:00:00" d="2019-08-23 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits">Geordie Shore: Aaron's Best Bits XIV (1406)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The house is stunned to discover that Marnie left after Aaron and Chelsea got together. Elettra and Marty boot off over their hot tub frisk and Chloe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-23 03:50:00" d="2019-08-23 04:40:00"><n u="MTV Cribs Priciest Pads">MTV Cribs Priciest Pads I (104)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Come see the most expensive homes of the rich and famous. In this episode: Russell and Kimora, Brody and Brandon Jenner, Kimberly Stewart, The Playboy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2019-08-23 04:40:00" d="2019-08-23 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XI (1103)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel and Steelo test their criminal skills in &quot;the con-bine&quot;, get a little handsy with &quot;freak in the streets&quot;, and discover the weird underground</k>  </p>
</a>
