<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="31" t="2020-04-16 04:35:22"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 05:00:00" d="2020-04-23 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 07:00:00" d="2020-04-23 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria IV (408)</n><t>M</t>    <k>80% The Morgendorffers attend a weekend retreat at the Quiet Ivy mental-health spa to be evaluated, as Helen is being considered for promotion. (S4, ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 07:20:00" d="2020-04-23 07:45:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (28)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Meet Brittany as she takes us on a tour of her New Jersey home. Then travel across the country to check out Cody's California crib. Series 2, Episode 28</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 07:45:00" d="2020-04-23 08:10:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (29)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sybil takes us on a tour of her Sunshine State sanctuary, then it's a quick trip to Georgia, where Austin shows us his Marietta mansion. Series 2, Episode 29</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 08:10:00" d="2020-04-23 08:35:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (30)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Meet Mark as he shows off Toad Mountain Ranch. Next we're off to warmer climates to check out Anthony's Florida crib, aka Tony's Tavern. Series 2, Episode 30</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 08:35:00" d="2020-04-23 09:00:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (31)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Meet Jacki as she shows off her Maryland mansion. Then head out to the Hamptons, to check out Melissa and Brad's weekend crib. Series 2, Episode 31</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 09:00:00" d="2020-04-23 09:30:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (32)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Head out to the Wild Wild West to take a peak at Brooke's Montana log mansion. Then it's a quick trip across the border to visit Carter's Canadian crib</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 09:30:00" d="2020-04-23 10:00:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (33)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Welcome to Malibu, where Sara shows off her Persian palace. Then meet brothers Brandon and Tanner as they give us a tour of their Texas crib. Series 2, Episode 33</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 10:00:00" d="2020-04-23 10:30:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (107)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson ditches the dating apps and helps sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight, Jade calls in her Love Squad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 10:30:00" d="2020-04-23 11:00:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (108)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson ditches the dating apps and helps sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight, Gina calls in her Love Squad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 11:00:00" d="2020-04-23 12:00:00"><n u="Geordie OGs">Geordie OGs II (201)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Marnie could give birth at any moment. Sophie opens up to Holly about her heartbreak. Chester gives Gary the run around and Aaron faces up to the reality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 12:00:00" d="2020-04-23 13:00:00"><n u="Geordie OGs">Geordie OGs II (202)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Gary plans a life-changing surprise for Emma. Holly goes to see some unicorns. Sophie struggles to forget her ex and Marnie has a traumatic labour. (S2, ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 13:00:00" d="2020-04-23 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Celebrities">Catfish: Celebrities II (215)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Superfan Keyonnah can hardly believe her luck, she's almost certain that she's been having an online relationship with her childhood crush, the rapper Bow Wow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 14:00:00" d="2020-04-23 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Celebrities">Catfish: Celebrities V (515)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Catfish is going international with a trip to the UK! Nev and Max meet Spencer who's been holding on to a secret for six years: he's in a relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 15:00:00" d="2020-04-23 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Celebrities">Catfish: Celebrities V (517)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Fans of popular YouTube star Andrea Russett call on Nev and Max to help catch a potential stalker who is impersonating Andrea's family online</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 16:00:00" d="2020-04-23 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Celebrities">Catfish: Celebrities VII (721)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Nick Young, aka Swaggy P, help Sheila figure out if she's being romanced by Love &amp; Hip Hop's Rich Dollaz. Is it a fan girl crush or is Sheila</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 17:00:00" d="2020-04-23 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Celebrities">Catfish: Celebrities VII (724)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After chatting for years with Chris, Shakinah needs to move forward with her life. But when Nev and co-host Kamie Crawford find out that Chris</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 18:00:00" d="2020-04-23 18:30:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (107)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson ditches the dating apps and helps sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight, Jade calls in her Love Squad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 18:30:00" d="2020-04-23 19:00:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (108)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson ditches the dating apps and helps sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight, Gina calls in her Love Squad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 19:00:00" d="2020-04-23 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show VIII (804)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Kamie receive an anonymous email from a whistleblower reporting a catfishing! But when our hosts arrive to help the named victim, they uncover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 20:00:00" d="2020-04-23 21:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom UK">Teen Mom UK VII (704)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Amber and Ste welcome baby Hudson into the world. Chloe enjoys watching Jordan grovel while Emma makes new friends. Megan's desperate to make space</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 21:00:00" d="2020-04-23 22:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (814)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Catelynn, Maci and Cheyenne visit Amber to support her first court hearing. Maci lets Bentley go golfing with Ryan, while Cory tells Cheyenne</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 22:00:00" d="2020-04-23 23:00:00"><n u="New: Jersey Shore Family Vacation">New: Jersey Shore Family Vacation III (320)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>It's been five long years since we waved goodbye to our favourite MTV stars of Jersey Shore. Now the family reunites in Miami for the vacation of a lifetime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 23:00:00" d="2020-04-24 00:00:00"><n u="New: Floribama Shore">New: Floribama Shore III (316)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After an intense night out, the roommates try to pick up the pieces and work out their unresolved relationship issues before saying goodbye for the summer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-24 00:00:00" d="2020-04-24 01:00:00"><n u="Ex On The Beach USA: Peak Of Love">Ex On The Beach USA: Peak Of Love IV (409)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Georgia and Callum face their harshest critics. Marlon is caught between a rock and a hot place when an ex arrives. The Ice Ceremony takes an unexpected turn. (S4, ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-24 01:00:00" d="2020-04-24 01:30:00"><n u="New: Ridiculousness">New: Ridiculousness XV (1539)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Tommy Lee joins Rob, Steelo, and Chanel as they enter 'Total Mayhem', get blown away by 'Industrial Size Fans' and roll around 'In The Dirt'. (S15, ep39)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-24 01:30:00" d="2020-04-24 02:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XV (1538)</n><t>M</t>    <k>62% Puddle of Mudd frontman Wes Scantlin joins Rob, Chanel, and Steelo to get filthy with some 'Mudd Buddies', and hire some 'Scantlin Security'. (S15, ep38)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-24 02:00:00" d="2020-04-24 03:00:00"><n u="RuPaul's Drag Race">RuPaul's Drag Race IV (412)</n><t>M</t>    <k>A look back on the highlights, low-lights, and previously unseen footage from season four. (S4, ep12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-24 03:00:00" d="2020-04-24 03:45:00"><n u="RuPaul's Drag Race">RuPaul's Drag Race IV (413)</n><t>M</t>    <k>The competition reaches the finale as the top three queens compete in their final challenge, starring in the music video for RuPaul's hit 'Glamazon'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-24 03:45:00" d="2020-04-24 04:40:00"><n u="RuPaul's Drag Race">RuPaul's Drag Race IV (414)</n><t>M</t>    <k>RuPaul and the contestants of season four return for the annual reunion. For the first time, a live audience of fans are present. (S4, ep14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-24 04:40:00" d="2020-04-24 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XIV (1436)</n><t>M</t>    <k>62% NFL Superstar Jarvis Landry joins Rob, Steelo, and Chanel to honor some One Handed Wonders, and go to the kennel with The Dawg Pound. (S14, ep36)</k>  </p>
</a>
