<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="28" t="2021-07-09 07:09:42"><p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 05:00:00" d="2021-07-15 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 07:00:00" d="2021-07-15 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria IV (407)</n><t>M</t>    <k>81% Jake is excited to attend a franchising conference, hoping to meet a famous franchising genius, but when Helen is unable to attend, Daria decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 07:20:00" d="2021-07-15 08:10:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show I (104)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Jasmine has been texting with Mike for two years and thinks he could be the perfect step-father for her son. Although they live only 15 minutes apart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 08:10:00" d="2021-07-15 09:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show I (105)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Jarrod never thought he'd find love until he fell for Abby on Facebook. Jarrod thinks Abby could be &quot;the one&quot;, but she's refusing to see him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 09:00:00" d="2021-07-15 10:00:00"><n u="Rich Kids Go Skint">Rich Kids Go Skint II (201)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rich kids share homes with families living on the breadline. (S2, ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 10:00:00" d="2021-07-15 10:30:00"><n u="Awkward">Awkward II (205)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>As Jenna prepares to spend her first Valentine's day with a boyfriend, both she and Tamara become jealous as they confront the possibility that their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 10:30:00" d="2021-07-15 11:00:00"><n u="Awkward">Awkward II (206)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Still reeling from Jake's proclamation of love, Jenna tries to figure out if having sex with Jake will bring her some clarity about her own feelings. (S2, ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 11:00:00" d="2021-07-15 12:00:00"><n u="16 &amp; Pregnant">16 &amp; Pregnant II (212)</n><t>M</t>    <k>After a shotgun wedding, Brooke and Cody are forced to sacrifice car racing for parenthood. Now they're trying to balance high school life and moving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 12:00:00" d="2021-07-15 13:00:00"><n u="16 &amp; Pregnant">16 &amp; Pregnant II (214)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Emily, an all-American girl, has to leave her majorette baton and boyfriend behind, as she moves an hour away and faces the pressure of starting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 13:00:00" d="2021-07-15 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Troublemakers">Catfish: Troublemakers VIII (8011)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>In the first ever virtual catfish episode, Nev and Kamie won't let quarantine stop them from helping love struck Jason find the dirt on his Insta-model Keith. (S8, ep11)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 14:00:00" d="2021-07-15 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Troublemakers">Catfish: Troublemakers VI (617)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Robin is desperate to meet her hunky, long-distance love in person. Nev and Max agree to help her hunt him down, but what they uncover turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 15:00:00" d="2021-07-15 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Troublemakers">Catfish: Troublemakers VI (608)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Max receive emails from opposite sides of the same online romance, each concerned that the other may be a catfish! What happens next leaves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 16:00:00" d="2021-07-15 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Troublemakers">Catfish: Troublemakers IV (409)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>When Blaire's Instagram lover Markie broke her heart, she moved on. But now Markie is back and wants to meet. Blaire needs Nev and Max's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 17:00:00" d="2021-07-15 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Troublemakers">Catfish: Troublemakers VIII (8010)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After years of hot drama, Gemini is desperate to find Myranda. But the script flips with the first intervention ever for an infamous repeat catfish! (S8, ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 18:00:00" d="2021-07-15 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Troublemakers">Catfish: Troublemakers VII (729)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and co-host Kamie Crawford help Mathan find Leah, a girl he's been talking to for a decade yet can never meet! But Leah has shocking secrets beyond</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 19:00:00" d="2021-07-15 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Troublemakers">Catfish: Troublemakers III (306)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>John is ready to leave Detroit but one thing holds him back: Kelsey. The two have never spoken outside of online chats but John is sure she's the one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 20:00:00" d="2021-07-15 21:00:00"><n u="The Hills: New Beginnings">The Hills: New Beginnings II (208)</n><t>M</t>    <k>36% Brody and Audrina's flirtation heats up. The war between the Pratts and Wahlers finally reaches boiling point. Brandon is left out in the cold by Dani's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 21:00:00" d="2021-07-15 22:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom">Teen Mom 2 X (1030)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>45% Jade recovers at Briana's house, but has to make a decision about her family. Leah tries to balance Ali and Aleeah's unique needs. Kail juggles three</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 22:00:00" d="2021-07-15 23:00:00"><n u="Geordie OGs">Geordie OGs IV (401)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The OGs are back but will Aaron and Talia's relationship survive a new baby? Will Marnie and Casey stay strong after a recent split? Will Holly and Jacob</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-15 23:00:00" d="2021-07-16 00:00:00"><n u="New: Jersey Shore Family Vacation">New: Jersey Shore Family Vacation IV (419)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Jenni has a huge announcement. But before the celebration can begin, the roommates must deal with the elephant in the room currently casting a large shadow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 00:00:00" d="2021-07-16 01:00:00"><n u="Ex On The Beach US">Ex On The Beach US III (304)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Aubrey wigs out, Anthony regrets hooking up with Shannon, and Cameron's ex Alexis arrives. Billy and Lexi grow closer, while Devin and Marie take things slow. (S3, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 01:00:00" d="2021-07-16 01:30:00"><n u="New: Deliciousness">New: Deliciousness II (215)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Angela Kinsey, Kel Mitchell, Tim Chantarangsu, and Tiffani Thiessen talk about over the top waiters in &quot;tip seeking behaviour&quot;, and how burnt isn't enough</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 01:30:00" d="2021-07-16 02:00:00"><n u="Deliciousness">Deliciousness II (210)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Angela Kinsey, Kel Mitchell, and Tim Chantarangsu, join Tiffani Thiessen to answer the age-old question: &quot;will a dog eat it?&quot;, and to call out those</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 02:00:00" d="2021-07-16 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Series">Geordie Shore: Series 17 XVII (1709)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The gang wake up in the outback and immerse themselves in the local ways. A night at a strip joint brings tips for Abbie, and Sophie goes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 03:00:00" d="2021-07-16 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Series">Geordie Shore: Series 17 XVII (1710)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Things aren't alrite between Alex and Sophie, and Nathan sees red when he gets Alex back to the house. Chloe decides she needs to drink</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 03:50:00" d="2021-07-16 04:15:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (11)</n><t>M</t>    <k>First join brothers Chris and Kyle as they give us a tour of their Las Vegas lair, then head out to California to check out the quirky crib of David, Chris and Nick. (S2, ep11)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 04:15:00" d="2021-07-16 04:40:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (12)</n><t>M</t>    <k>See Devon's computerized crib full of gadgets. And at Sacha, Todd and Kendall's Utah ranch full of animals, you might want to think twice before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-16 04:40:00" d="2021-07-16 05:00:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (13)</n><t>M</t>    <k>We bet you've never seen anything like the homes on this episode of Teen Cribs. First it's Perry's Missouri cave crib, then off to Jill and Colt's</k>  </p>
</a>
