<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2020-05-16 04:54:43"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-23 05:00:00" d="2020-05-23 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-23 07:00:00" d="2020-05-23 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria I (113)</n><t>M</t>    <k>80% Watch Daria juggle the tribulations of being a teenage girl with career-fixated parents and a relentlessly popular younger sister, as well as attending</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-23 07:20:00" d="2020-05-23 08:10:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (813)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After her arrest, Amber is released from jail. Mackenzie finds out Josh cheated on her. Maci's son can't go to Jagger's first birthday party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-23 08:10:00" d="2020-05-23 09:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (814)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Catelynn, Maci and Cheyenne visit Amber to support her first court hearing. Maci lets Bentley go golfing with Ryan, while Cory tells Cheyenne</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-23 09:00:00" d="2020-05-23 10:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (815)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Cheyenne throws her first fundraising event. Amber's custody battle takes a turn when Andrew petitions to move James. Mackenzie tries to file for divorce</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-23 10:00:00" d="2020-05-23 11:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs Priciest Pads">MTV Cribs Priciest Pads I (101)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Take a peek into the most expensive homes of the rich and famous. In this episode: Paulina Rubio, Nelly, Russell &amp; Kimora in New York, Tommy Lee, Rasheed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-23 11:00:00" d="2020-05-23 12:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs Priciest Pads">MTV Cribs Priciest Pads I (102)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Take a peek into the most expensive homes of the rich and famous. In this episode: Pamela Anderson, Penny Hardaway, Joey Fatone, Gene Simmons, Usher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-23 12:00:00" d="2020-05-23 13:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs Priciest Pads">MTV Cribs Priciest Pads I (103)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Take a peek into the most expensive homes of the rich and famous. In this episode: Ice-T, Robbie Williams, The Osbournes, Mariah Carey, Master P and Babyface! (S1, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-23 13:00:00" d="2020-05-23 14:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs Priciest Pads">MTV Cribs Priciest Pads I (104)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Come see the most expensive homes of the rich and famous. In this episode: Russell and Kimora, Brody and Brandon Jenner, Kimberly Stewart, The Playboy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-23 14:00:00" d="2020-05-23 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Guest Presenters">Catfish: Guest Presenters IV (418)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>For shy Devan, meeting Rylan was love at first click. Devan wants to believe that Rylan is marriage material but her suspicious behaviour is leaving him with doubts. (S4, ep18)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-23 15:00:00" d="2020-05-23 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Guest Presenters">Catfish: Guest Presenters VII (728)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and NFL star Rashad Jennings help Deven find his mysterious online love James. James won't videochat yet he invites Deven to fly across the country to meet him! Deven needs answers. (S7, ep28)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-23 16:00:00" d="2020-05-23 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Guest Presenters">Catfish: Guest Presenters VII (735)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Kimiko Glenn joins Nev in helping Matthew find his elusive Instagram love, Chance. But as they search for answers, they run into unsurpassable roadblocks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-23 17:00:00" d="2020-05-23 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Guest Presenters">Catfish: Guest Presenters VII (726)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and co-host Slick Woods help 19-year-old Aubri find her Snapchat love, Brian. Brian says he lives at Aubri's college but has shady excuses not to meet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-23 18:00:00" d="2020-05-23 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Guest Presenters">Catfish: Guest Presenters IV (404)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Daisy met Marcus on Instagram and he instantly stole her heart. But Marcus won't speak to Daisy on the phone, let alone meet her in person</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-23 19:00:00" d="2020-05-23 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Guest Presenters">Catfish: Guest Presenters VII (725)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Model Dallas has had his sights set on sexy Safari ever since she slid into his DMs - but despite flirty promises, she won't meet. Nev and co-host Tallulah</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-23 20:00:00" d="2020-05-23 21:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Guest Presenters">Catfish: Guest Presenters VIII (801)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>For the last six years, Red's been talking to Jalissa and her group of celebrity besties. Hot on the trail to meet Jalissa in LA, Nev and Kamie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-23 21:00:00" d="2020-05-23 21:30:00"><n u="Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs">Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs I (102)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs features the funniest lockdown clips from across the globe. This week, quarantine cuisine and the return</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-23 21:30:00" d="2020-05-23 22:00:00"><n u="Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs">Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs I (101)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs features the funniest lockdown clips alongside specially designed celebrity challenges. This week famous faces compete</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-23 22:00:00" d="2020-05-23 22:30:00"><n u="New: Nick Cannon's Wild 'N' Out">New: Nick Cannon's Wild 'N' Out XIV (1412)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Nick Cannon and 2 Chainz battle it out in a VMA Themed episode with games: Pick Up And Kill It, Turn Me Up In The Headphones and Kick 'Em Out The Classroom. (S14, ep12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-23 22:30:00" d="2020-05-23 23:00:00"><n u="New: Nick Cannon's Wild 'N' Out">New: Nick Cannon's Wild 'N' Out XIV (1413)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Nick Cannon, Naomi, Jimmy, and Jey battle it out in games: Flow Job, Diss Side Dat Side, Bullspittin' and the Wildstyle battle. Rich The Kid performs, No Cap. (S14, ep13)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-23 23:00:00" d="2020-05-24 02:00:00"><n u="2019 MTV Video Music Awards">2019 MTV Video Music Awards (105)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Join host Sebastian Maniscalco for one of the biggest nights of year. Featuring performances from Taylor Swift, Shawn Mendes, Camila Cabello, Lil Nas X and more!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 02:00:00" d="2020-05-24 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! III (302)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>With the house reduced to carnage and Sophie losing even more faith in boyfriend Joel, there are still plenty of beaches to party on. Meanwhile Holly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 03:00:00" d="2020-05-24 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! III (303)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Sophie is elated as Joel surprises her with a visit. But will he be able to behave himself? And with everyone fearing that his worldie mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 03:50:00" d="2020-05-24 04:40:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! III (304)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The chaos in Cancun continues as Gaz celebrates his birthday in true Geordie style. Charlotte takes her holiday romance to the next level. Vicky erupts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-05-24 04:40:00" d="2020-05-24 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XV (1526)</n><t>M</t>    <k>62% Rob, Steelo and Chanel hang out with Hip-Hop superstar Wale, meet a few women with 'No Chill', see who's 'Numb To The Madness', and meet some 'Fans</k>  </p>
</a>
