<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2020-05-30 04:38:12"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 05:00:00" d="2020-06-06 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 07:00:00" d="2020-06-06 07:20:00"><n u="Say It In Song">Say It In Song I (106)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nana and his mum haven't seen his mother's sisters in years. With Foo's and the Song Squad's help Nana plans out a surprise reunion set to Sister Sledge's &quot;We Are Family&quot;. (S1, ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 07:20:00" d="2020-06-06 07:45:00"><n u="Say It In Song">Say It In Song I (107)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Mike's parents are frustrated that he works long hours and they don't get to see him often. With Vampire Weekend's &quot;Holiday&quot; playing, he surprises</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 07:45:00" d="2020-06-06 08:10:00"><n u="Say It In Song">Say It In Song I (108)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Leah's friends Kelsey &amp; Sarah are getting married. Unfortunately, she can't make it to the wedding. Instead, she wants to surprise them, so she turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 08:10:00" d="2020-06-06 08:35:00"><n u="Say It In Song">Say It In Song I (109)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Emmi's best friend, Sarah, is moving to New York City, but hasn't decided on a place yet. Emmi wants Sarah to move in with her, so she reaches</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 08:35:00" d="2020-06-06 09:00:00"><n u="Say It In Song">Say It In Song I (110)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Redfoo and the song squad cook up a special visit to the park involving dancing yogis choreographed to Zedd's &quot;I Want You To Know&quot; to help convince Tara's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 09:00:00" d="2020-06-06 11:00:00"><n u="Maroon 5: Official Top">Maroon 5: Official Top 20</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>We use official chart stats to count down the biggest hits from Maroon 5!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 11:00:00" d="2020-06-06 11:30:00"><n>MTV Asks Lewis Capaldi</n><t>M</t>    <k>MTV sits down with Lewis Capaldi to get the lowdown on his meteoric rise to the top! Expect some belly laughs, some sentimental stories, and some exclusive music performances</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 11:30:00" d="2020-06-06 12:00:00"><n>New: MTV Asks Liam Payne &amp;...</n><t>M</t>    <k>. &amp; Alesso @ Home. Becca Dudley chats to Liam Payne and Alesso about their new collab and 1D reunion rumours! All from the safety of their own homes of course!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 12:00:00" d="2020-06-06 12:30:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (1)</n><t>M</t>    <k>We meet ordinary teenagers who live in extraordinary homes and hear from the parents who give them what they want. Today, Lynsey and Ryan show off their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 12:30:00" d="2020-06-06 13:00:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (2)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Welcome to the great outdoors of Colorado, where we meet brothers Gannon and Wyatt. These twins have their own lake and beach - not something</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 13:00:00" d="2020-06-06 13:30:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (3)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Meet Alycia as she shows off her Cali crib. The first thing you see is a Fisker Tramonto, one of only 150 in the world, so you know Alycia is riding in style! Series 2, Episode 3</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 13:30:00" d="2020-06-06 14:00:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (4)</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this episode we're heading to Canada, to see the modern glass house that Mira calls home. Series 2, Episode 4</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 14:00:00" d="2020-06-06 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: OMG Moments">Catfish: OMG Moments VII (729)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and co-host Kamie Crawford help Mathan find Leah, a girl he's been talking to for a decade yet can never meet! But Leah has shocking secrets beyond</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 15:00:00" d="2020-06-06 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: OMG Moments">Catfish: OMG Moments VIII (803)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Kiana's convinced that her wife Sparkayla is being catfished by a girl claiming to be her sister! Nev and Kamie perform the first ever DNA test in Catfish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 16:00:00" d="2020-06-06 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: OMG Moments">Catfish: OMG Moments VIII (810)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After years of hot drama, Gemini is desperate to find Myranda. But the script flips with the first intervention ever for an infamous repeat catfish! (S8, ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 17:00:00" d="2020-06-06 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: OMG Moments">Catfish: OMG Moments VII (735)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Kimiko Glenn joins Nev in helping Matthew find his elusive Instagram love, Chance. But as they search for answers, they run into unsurpassable roadblocks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 18:00:00" d="2020-06-06 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: OMG Moments">Catfish: OMG Moments VII (711)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Kiaira and Cortney had a baby despite Kiaira never meeting Cortney or the baby! Nev and Max try to bring the family together, but is this the greatest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 19:00:00" d="2020-06-06 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: OMG Moments">Catfish: OMG Moments VII (724)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After chatting for years with Chris, Shakinah needs to move forward with her life. But when Nev and co-host Kamie Crawford find out that Chris</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 20:00:00" d="2020-06-06 21:00:00"><n u="Catfish: OMG Moments">Catfish: OMG Moments VIII (806)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Akirra contacts Catfish for help to stop her bae's online ex, Jamie, from harassing her and her boyfriend William. But the script is flipped</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 21:00:00" d="2020-06-06 21:30:00"><n u="Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs">Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs I (104)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Charlotte Crosby's Lockdown Laughs features the funniest lockdown clips from across the world. This week it's the 'trick shot lockdown showdown'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 21:30:00" d="2020-06-06 22:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs: Footballers Stay Home">MTV Cribs: Footballers Stay Home I (101)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Manchester United star Jesse Lingard shows off his hard-earned England caps, and former FIFA Women's Player of the Year Lieke Martens reveals what she's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 22:00:00" d="2020-06-06 22:30:00"><n u="Nick Cannon's Wild 'N' Out">Nick Cannon's Wild 'N' Out XIV (1402)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Nick Cannon and Davido battle it out in games: So Fly, Vowing Out, Twerk Werk and the Wildstyle battle. (S14, ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 22:30:00" d="2020-06-06 23:00:00"><n u="New: Nick Cannon's Wild 'N' Out">New: Nick Cannon's Wild 'N' Out XIV (1422)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Nick Cannon, Travis Mills and special guest PnB Rock battle it out in games: It's My Birthday, Flow Job, Star Sightings and the Wildstyle battle. (S14, ep22)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 23:00:00" d="2020-06-06 23:30:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XVI (1603)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel, and Steelo get bent out of shape in 'Hinge Cringe', get trapped in a 'Giggle Prison' and take a visit to the angriest place on earth. (S16, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-06 23:30:00" d="2020-06-07 00:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XVI (1604)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel, and Steelo talk about the most devious furniture known to man, where all diseases get their start, and they discuss the subtle art of 'Funk Tests'. (S16, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 00:00:00" d="2020-06-07 00:30:00"><n u="Jackass">Jackass I (102)</n><t>M</t>    <k>68% Johnny Knoxville sprains his ankle attempting to jump the LA River. Stunts include: Blind Driver, Naked Dave, Human Barbecue, Pontius Skating, Dave's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 00:30:00" d="2020-06-07 01:00:00"><n u="Jackass">Jackass I (104)</n><t>M</t>    <k>68% Johnny Knoxville dons a diaper and takes on a professional sumo wrestler, and Bam Margera wakes his parents up at 2 AM with a rousing death metal set. (S1, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 01:00:00" d="2020-06-07 01:30:00"><n u="Jackass">Jackass I (105)</n><t>M</t>    <k>68% Chris Pontius terrorizes the late night denizens of LA, Johnny Knoxville creates the world's first &quot;Beekini&quot; and Ryan Dunn attempts to immerse himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 01:30:00" d="2020-06-07 02:00:00"><n u="Jackass">Jackass I (107)</n><t>M</t>    <k>68% Chris Pontius puts on his best leopard print G-string to wrestle some alligators in Florida, and Johnny Knoxville lets the winds of peace rush through</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 02:00:00" d="2020-06-07 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! VIII (804)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>With Charlotte back in the house, all eyes are on Gary and Marnie and whether they'll decide to continue sleeping together. (S8, ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 03:00:00" d="2020-06-07 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! VIII (805)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Things kick off in the house as Aaron hears Vicky and the girls slagging him off on the eve of his third date with Vicky. (S8,ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 03:50:00" d="2020-06-07 04:40:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! VIII (806)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>New boy Kyle gets properly settled into the house by spending the night with Holly, and the Geordies take Tash on Tours international as</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-06-07 04:40:00" d="2020-06-07 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XVI (1601)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>62% Rob, Chanel and Steelo take matters into their own hands and become the &quot;pest control&quot; save dough in &quot;free massage&quot;, and steer clear of &quot;gassassins&quot;. (S16, ep1)</k>  </p>
</a>
