<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="31" t="2020-04-15 04:34:55"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 05:00:00" d="2020-04-22 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 07:00:00" d="2020-04-22 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria IV (407)</n><t>M</t>    <k>80% Jake is excited to attend a franchising conference, hoping to meet a famous franchising genius, but when Helen is unable to attend, Daria decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 07:20:00" d="2020-04-22 07:45:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (22)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Meet cousins Jacob and Chase as they show off their palatial New Jersey home. Then we jet to Michigan, as Emily shows off a house with more color</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 07:45:00" d="2020-04-22 08:10:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (23)</n><t>M</t>    <k>See Dylan &amp; Lyris' New York City apartment in the sky with views of the Empire State Building and Central Park. Then see Kipling, Rio &amp; Selkirk's Idaho</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 08:10:00" d="2020-04-22 08:35:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (24)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Welcome to Michigan, where sisters Chloe, Cassidy and Chyna show off the house their dad built, and Darian gives us a tour of his eco-friendly home. Series 2, Episode 24</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 08:35:00" d="2020-04-22 09:00:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (25)</n><t>M</t>    <k>See Juliette show off her Lake Placid winter wonderland, and then head into the complete opposite climate of Florida, where Beau takes us on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 09:00:00" d="2020-04-22 09:30:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (26)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Meet Ariana as she shows off her Michigan manor. Then meet sisters Brianna and Alyssa as they give us a tour of their Idaho castle. Series 2, Episode 26</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 09:30:00" d="2020-04-22 10:00:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (27)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Meet twins Allayla and Ciara as they take us on a tour of their Saratoga, New York, house of fun. Then jet over to the west coast farm that Connery calls home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 10:00:00" d="2020-04-22 10:30:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (105)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson ditches the dating apps and helps sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight Jake calls in his Love Squad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 10:30:00" d="2020-04-22 11:00:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (106)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson ditches the dating apps and helps sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight Fay calls in her Love Squad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 11:00:00" d="2020-04-22 12:00:00"><n u="Geordie OGs">Geordie OGs I (105)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Gary and Emma share some special news and Aaron gets stuck into training. Holly goes to the House of Lords and Marnie and Casey get a shock when a photo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 12:00:00" d="2020-04-22 13:00:00"><n u="Geordie OGs">Geordie OGs I (106)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Holly gives the low-down on Jacob's surprise proposal. Marnie and Casey reveal the gender of their baby. And, Aaron finally takes to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 13:00:00" d="2020-04-22 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Villains">Catfish: Villains IV (415)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>David is the only love Andria has ever known. Love letters and voice messages make Andria stay. But having never met after 10 years, she needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 14:00:00" d="2020-04-22 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Villains">Catfish: Villains VIII (801)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>For the last six years, Red's been talking to Jalissa and her group of celebrity besties. Hot on the trail to meet Jalissa in LA, Nev and Kamie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 15:00:00" d="2020-04-22 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Villains">Catfish: Villains VI (605)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After months of sexting with a hot model he met on a hookup app, Marvin is eager to meet him in person. Max and sidekick, singer Chantal Claret, agree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 16:00:00" d="2020-04-22 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Villains">Catfish: Villains II (209)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Five months ago Artis met Jess online. Artis and Jess each were in relationships, but believed they'd found true love. But is Jess everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 17:00:00" d="2020-04-22 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Villains">Catfish: Villains IV (412)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Falesha's name and pictures were stolen by a fake profile that nearly ruined her life. She thought her troubles were behind her, but four years later</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 18:00:00" d="2020-04-22 18:30:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (105)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson ditches the dating apps and helps sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight Jake calls in his Love Squad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 18:30:00" d="2020-04-22 19:00:00"><n u="Love Squad">Love Squad I (106)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Dating diva Charlotte Dawson ditches the dating apps and helps sassy singles find love on three real life dates. Tonight Fay calls in her Love Squad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 19:00:00" d="2020-04-22 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show VIII (803)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Kiana's convinced that her wife Sparkayla is being catfished by a girl claiming to be her sister! Nev and Kamie perform the first ever DNA test in Catfish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 20:00:00" d="2020-04-22 21:00:00"><n u="New: Teen Mom OG">New: Teen Mom OG VIII (814)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Catelynn, Maci and Cheyenne visit Amber to support her first court hearing. Maci lets Bentley go golfing with Ryan, while Cory tells Cheyenne</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 21:00:00" d="2020-04-22 22:00:00"><n u="New: Teen Mom UK">New: Teen Mom UK VII (704)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Amber and Ste welcome baby Hudson into the world. Chloe enjoys watching Jordan grovel while Emma makes new friends. Megan's desperate to make space</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 22:00:00" d="2020-04-22 23:00:00"><n u="New: Rich Kids Go Skint">New: Rich Kids Go Skint I (101)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Fergus leads a life of privilege in Chelsea, but how will he cope living with Anna and her family in Croydon, who are struggling to make ends meet? (S1, ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-22 23:00:00" d="2020-04-23 00:00:00"><n u="Celebrity Ex On The Beach">Celebrity Ex On The Beach I (114)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Georgia and Miles get closer but will it all end in tears? Marissa is pushed to her 'mob wife' limits, and Joey and Lorena head down to the beach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 00:00:00" d="2020-04-23 01:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show VII (729)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and co-host Kamie Crawford help Mathan find Leah, a girl he's been talking to for a decade yet can never meet! But Leah has shocking secrets beyond</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 01:00:00" d="2020-04-23 01:30:00"><n u="New: Ridiculousness">New: Ridiculousness XV (1538)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Puddle of Mudd frontman Wes Scantlin joins Rob, Chanel, and Steelo to get filthy with some 'Mudd Buddies', and hire some 'Scantlin Security'. (S15, ep38)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 01:30:00" d="2020-04-23 02:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XV (1537)</n><t>M</t>    <k>62% Rob, Steelo and Chanel welcome singer and rapper DaniLeigh as they question the thinking behind 'Bad Plans', and celebrate the kings of the jungle in 'Lion Vibes'. (S15, ep37)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 02:00:00" d="2020-04-23 03:00:00"><n u="RuPaul's Drag Race">RuPaul's Drag Race IV (409)</n><t>M</t>    <k>The queens campaign and debate as they vie to become the 2012 Wig Party candidate. (S4, ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 03:00:00" d="2020-04-23 03:45:00"><n u="RuPaul's Drag Race">RuPaul's Drag Race IV (410)</n><t>M</t>    <k>The queens are paired up with sexy dads for a drag runway makeover. With extra special guest judges Jesse Tyler Ferguson and Jennifer Love Hewitt. (S4, ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 03:45:00" d="2020-04-23 04:40:00"><n u="RuPaul's Drag Race">RuPaul's Drag Race IV (411)</n><t>M</t>    <k>The race goes to the dogs when the queens compete in a pageant of canine-inspired couture. With guest judges Wynonna Judd and Rose McGowan. (S4, ep11)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-23 04:40:00" d="2020-04-23 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XIV (1435)</n><t>M</t>    <k>62% Trey Songz joins Rob, Chanel, and Steelo to experience Pain Pleasure, watch out for Mr. Steal Your Girl, and learn to love electricity with some people</k>  </p>
</a>
