<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2020-04-09 04:35:04"><p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-16 05:00:00" d="2020-04-16 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-16 07:00:00" d="2020-04-16 07:20:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (8)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Get the tour of Harleigh's fun and colourful Florida home. Then join us as we head to Jesse's Virginia pad, and from there it's just a short</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-16 07:20:00" d="2020-04-16 07:45:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (9)</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this episode of Teen Cribs our first stop is Samantha's Pennsylvania princess palace, then we get to check out Dylan's Colorado mountain mansion. (S2, ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-16 07:45:00" d="2020-04-16 08:10:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (10)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Don't miss Nicole's tour of her amazing New Jersey home, complete with twenty-one cars! Then down in Virginia we check out Cody's crib, where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-16 08:10:00" d="2020-04-16 08:35:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (11)</n><t>M</t>    <k>First join brothers Chris and Kyle as they give us a tour of their Las Vegas lair, then head out to California to check out the quirky crib of David, Chris and Nick. (S2, ep11)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-16 08:35:00" d="2020-04-16 09:00:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (12)</n><t>M</t>    <k>See Devon's computerized crib full of gadgets. And at Sacha, Todd and Kendall's Utah ranch full of animals, you might want to think twice before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-16 09:00:00" d="2020-04-16 09:30:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (13)</n><t>M</t>    <k>We bet you've never seen anything like the homes on this episode of Teen Cribs. First it's Perry's Missouri cave crib, then off to Jill and Colt's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-16 09:30:00" d="2020-04-16 10:00:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (14)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Kayden's Utah crib is so massive, it fills up an entire episode! There's a room of Harry Potter memorabilia, an Indiana Jones themed theatre</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-16 10:00:00" d="2020-04-16 11:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Season 8 Boxset">Catfish: Season 8 Boxset VIII (801)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>For the last six years, Red's been talking to Jalissa and her group of celebrity besties. Hot on the trail to meet Jalissa in LA, Nev and Kamie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-16 11:00:00" d="2020-04-16 12:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Season 8 Boxset">Catfish: Season 8 Boxset VIII (802)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Alfred's thirsty to find Adonis, the man of his dreams. But as they dig for answers, word that Nev and Kamie are in town leads to the most explosive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-16 12:00:00" d="2020-04-16 13:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Season 8 Boxset">Catfish: Season 8 Boxset VIII (803)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Kiana's convinced that her wife Sparkayla is being catfished by a girl claiming to be her sister! Nev and Kamie perform the first ever DNA test in Catfish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-16 13:00:00" d="2020-04-16 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Season 8 Boxset">Catfish: Season 8 Boxset VIII (804)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev and Kamie receive an anonymous email from a whistleblower reporting a catfishing! But when our hosts arrive to help the named victim, they uncover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-16 14:00:00" d="2020-04-16 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Season 8 Boxset">Catfish: Season 8 Boxset VIII (805)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Joseph's been sending Sabrina money but his sister doesn't buy her lies and calls in Nev for some truth. What they discover is so shocking that they wonder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-16 15:00:00" d="2020-04-16 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Season 8 Boxset">Catfish: Season 8 Boxset VIII (806)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Akirra contacts Catfish for help to stop her bae's online ex, Jamie, from harassing her and her boyfriend William. But the script is flipped</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-16 16:00:00" d="2020-04-16 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Season 8 Boxset">Catfish: Season 8 Boxset VIII (807)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Nev gets a letter from a woman worried that her friend is being catfished by a guy named BJ. BJ comforted Danielle when she was shot, but now she needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-16 17:00:00" d="2020-04-16 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Season 8 Boxset">Catfish: Season 8 Boxset VIII (808)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>DeJohn is so in love with online beauty Cashay that he's ready to propose, but his younger brother Adonis is convinced Cashay is a lie. Can Nev and Kamie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-16 18:00:00" d="2020-04-16 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Season 8 Boxset">Catfish: Season 8 Boxset VIII (809)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Aaliyah is saving herself for model Jaquan, a guy she's dating exclusively but has never met. As Nev and Kamie dig into his story, they become alarmed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-16 19:00:00" d="2020-04-16 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Season 8 Boxset">Catfish: Season 8 Boxset VIII (810)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After years of hot drama, Gemini is desperate to find Myranda. But the script flips with the first intervention ever for an infamous repeat catfish! (S8, ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-16 20:00:00" d="2020-04-16 21:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom UK">Teen Mom UK VII (703)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Heartbroken Chloe gets some advice she doesn't want to hear. Amber and Ste come to blows. The honeymoon period is over for Megan and new mum Emma tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-16 21:00:00" d="2020-04-16 22:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom OG">Teen Mom OG VIII (813)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>After her arrest, Amber is released from jail. Mackenzie finds out Josh cheated on her. Maci's son can't go to Jagger's first birthday party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-16 22:00:00" d="2020-04-16 23:00:00"><n u="New: Jersey Shore Family Vacation">New: Jersey Shore Family Vacation III (319)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>It's been five long years since we waved goodbye to our favourite MTV stars of Jersey Shore. Now the family reunites in Miami for the vacation of a lifetime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-16 23:00:00" d="2020-04-17 00:00:00"><n u="New: Floribama Shore">New: Floribama Shore III (315)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>When Jeremiah's brother Josh arrives, it threatens to disrupt the rest of the summer. Codi buys some flowers for Candace, and the roommates confront</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-17 00:00:00" d="2020-04-17 01:00:00"><n u="Ex On The Beach USA: Peak Of Love">Ex On The Beach USA: Peak Of Love IV (408)</n><t>M</t>    <k>A perfect date turns into a perfect nightmare for one couple. Niall is met with serious competition for Allie's affection. Marlon and La Demi struggle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-17 01:00:00" d="2020-04-17 01:30:00"><n u="New: Ridiculousness">New: Ridiculousness XV (1534)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rob, Steelo and Chanel welcome rap superstar Tyga as they watch some people 'Get A Taste', and find out what kind of talents can make you 'Legendary'. (S15, ep34)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-17 01:30:00" d="2020-04-17 02:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XV (1532)</n><t>M</t>    <k>62% Iman Shumpert joins Rob, Chanel and Steelo as they 'Beat The Man', experience 'Public Passion', and try to survive some 'Bathroom Mania'. (S15, ep32)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-17 02:00:00" d="2020-04-17 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! XV (1505)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Anna announces that Scotty and Marty won't be coming back. But there's no time to feel down as the gang heads to Rome to show the Italians how to party Geordie style! (S15, ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-17 03:00:00" d="2020-04-17 03:45:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! XV (1506)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>The Radgies are in Rome and Boss Anna has work for them to do! Nathan is annoyed with Chloe, Gaz and Abbie get closer, and Aaron tells Gaz he wants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-17 03:45:00" d="2020-04-17 04:40:00"><n u="Geordie Shore Turns 21!">Geordie Shore Turns 21! XV (1507)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>While Nathan and Chloe make up, the rest of the gang head out to Lazer tag. Marnie and Aaron are not on the same page and a slip of the tongue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2020-04-17 04:40:00" d="2020-04-17 05:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XIV (1429)</n><t>M</t>    <k>62% Melvin Ingram joins Rob, Chanel, and Steelo to cheer on some Street Backs, load up some Cannon Arms, and enjoy some super hard hits in Bone Crushers. (S14, ep29)</k>  </p>
</a>
