<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2021-07-08 04:55:20"><p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-13 05:00:00" d="2021-07-13 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teleshopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-13 07:00:00" d="2021-07-13 07:20:00"><n u="Daria">Daria IV (405)</n><t>M</t>    <k>81% Mr O'Neill encourages his class to pick something to fail at for personal growth, but all they get is misery. Jane is becoming popular enough to replace</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-13 07:20:00" d="2021-07-13 08:10:00"><n u="Teen Mom">Teen Mom 3 I (113)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Katie wants to celebrate Molli's birthday with Joey. Briana reaches out to Devoin. Alex tries to co-parent with Matt, and Mackenzie and Josh disagree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-13 08:10:00" d="2021-07-13 09:00:00"><n u="Catfish: The TV Show">Catfish: The TV Show I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Sunny is in love with the man of her dreams. Jamison is a model, a TV writer, and also studying to be an anaesthesiologist. However, the pair have never met</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-13 09:00:00" d="2021-07-13 09:30:00"><n u="MTV Cribs UK">MTV Cribs UK I (103)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>This cult show is your access all areas pass to nosey around the pads of the famous. This week featuring Love Island love birds Alex &amp; Olivia Bowen &amp; Towie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-13 09:30:00" d="2021-07-13 10:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs UK">MTV Cribs UK I (104)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>This cult show is your access all areas pass to nosey around the pads of the famous. This week featuring the homes of TOWIE fav's Yaz &amp; Lockie, Jodie Harsh</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-13 10:00:00" d="2021-07-13 10:30:00"><n u="Awkward">Awkward II (201)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Jenna avoids dealing with the revelation that her mum wrote the carefrontation letter. Jake's gift forces her to decide whether she's ready to leave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-13 10:30:00" d="2021-07-13 11:00:00"><n u="Awkward">Awkward II (202)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Jenna revels in her new relationship status until she hears about the hidden camera filming at the Sanctuary for months. She then goes to great lengths</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-13 11:00:00" d="2021-07-13 12:25:00"><n u="16 &amp; Pregnant">16 &amp; Pregnant II (208)</n><t>M</t>    <k>West Virginia cheerleader Leah is having twins with a boy she was dating for one month. If that wasn't hard enough, she develops health issues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-13 12:25:00" d="2021-07-13 13:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs UK">MTV Cribs UK I (107)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>This cult show is your access all areas pass to nosey around the pads of the famous. This week featuring Diversity's Perri Kiely and rock 'n' roll family The Lowes. (S1, ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-13 13:00:00" d="2021-07-13 14:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Repeat Offenders">Catfish: Repeat Offenders VIII (8031)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Tam is in deep with her online girlfriend Jamena, and calls Nev and Kamie for help. Everything changes when Jamena refuses to be caught, proving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-13 14:00:00" d="2021-07-13 15:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Repeat Offenders">Catfish: Repeat Offenders VIII (8018)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Ryan thought he'd found his quarantine bae. But when Kamie and Nev start to dig, it's not long before they uncover that Micah may be more interested</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-13 15:00:00" d="2021-07-13 16:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Repeat Offenders">Catfish: Repeat Offenders VII (714)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Breana has waited to marry Josh for years, but her love fades when the boys uncover the man behind the profile. Now, Josh's past catches up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-13 16:00:00" d="2021-07-13 17:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Repeat Offenders">Catfish: Repeat Offenders IV (416)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Sydney and Ayissha were in an online romance for years before Sydney revealed she is not who she says. But Ayissha still loves her and seeks Nev and Max's help. (S4, ep16)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-13 17:00:00" d="2021-07-13 18:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Repeat Offenders">Catfish: Repeat Offenders VII (708)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Mandy is in love with a guy that gives her everything but the truth! Mandy's son has had enough and calls in Nev and Max. But following the clues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-13 18:00:00" d="2021-07-13 19:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Repeat Offenders">Catfish: Repeat Offenders VI (618)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>For years, Nicole has had her pictures stolen to make fake profiles, one of which has been catfishing Ryan for ten years. Is this a random troll</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-13 19:00:00" d="2021-07-13 20:00:00"><n u="Catfish: Repeat Offenders">Catfish: Repeat Offenders VIII (8021)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>When Jay met Vegas girl Anna, he thought he had hit the jackpot! Before he can cash in his chips, Nev and Kamie find that Anna may hold secrets that could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-13 20:00:00" d="2021-07-13 21:00:00"><n u="Rich Kids Go Skint">Rich Kids Go Skint II (202)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rich kids share homes with families living on the breadline. (S2, ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-13 21:00:00" d="2021-07-13 22:00:00"><n u="16 &amp; Pregnant">16 &amp; Pregnant VI (605)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Kash has been with boyfriend Nate for a year but struggles with his immaturity. Kash has to see if Nate can handle these new adult responsibilities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-13 22:00:00" d="2021-07-13 22:30:00"><n u="MTV Cribs">MTV Cribs I (103)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Get ready to snoop around the homes of some of the biggest names in the business! This week featuring triple threat Jojo Siwa and Brit comedy genius Tom Allen. (S2, ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-13 22:30:00" d="2021-07-13 23:00:00"><n u="MTV Cribs">MTV Cribs I (104)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Get ready to snoop around the homes of some of the biggest names in the business! This week featuring Drag queen superstar Alyssa Edwards</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-13 23:00:00" d="2021-07-14 00:00:00"><n u="True Life Crime UK">True Life Crime UK I (101)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Jayden Parkinson, seventeen, disappears in Oxford without a trace. MTV correspondent, Linda Adey, delves deep into the disturbing case of the missing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 00:00:00" d="2021-07-14 01:00:00"><n u="Teen Mom 2 Uncut">Teen Mom 2 Uncut X (1029)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>In Teen Mom 2 Uncut, Jade plans to fly home, but Briana tries to convince her to come back to Orlando instead. Kail reveals heartbreaking challenges around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 01:00:00" d="2021-07-14 01:30:00"><n u="New: Ridiculousness">New: Ridiculousness XX (2020)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rob, Chanel, and Steelo check out some mangled mouths in &quot;dentally ill&quot;, hit the skies in &quot;flying cars&quot;, and call out bald people attempting &quot;hair trickery&quot;. (S20, ep20)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 01:30:00" d="2021-07-14 02:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness XX (2019)</n><t>M</t>    <k>63% Rob, Chanel, and Steelo get buzzed in &quot;swarm chasers&quot;, strike a pose for &quot;swimsuit issues&quot;, and can't stop in &quot;always eating&quot;. (S20, ep19)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 02:00:00" d="2021-07-14 03:00:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Series">Geordie Shore: Series 17 XVII (1704)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Half the gang head off to Byron Bay leaving the rest wondering where they are! Chloe is going out of her mind without Sam whilst Abbie is trying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 03:00:00" d="2021-07-14 03:50:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Series">Geordie Shore: Series 17 XVII (1705)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Making up is a step too far for someone and they pack their bags. Chloe puts on a show for Sam. Grant gets cosy in the girl's room and Sophie's search</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 03:50:00" d="2021-07-14 04:40:00"><n u="Geordie Shore: Series">Geordie Shore: Series 17 XVII (1706)</n><t>M</t><e>F</e>    <k>Geordie House Parties are a thing of legend, but will it be the end of the party for Grant and Abbie? Sam sees red when Chloe gets up close with Alex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1126" o="2021-07-14 04:40:00" d="2021-07-14 05:00:00"><n u="Teen Cribs">Teen Cribs II (7)</n><t>M</t>    <k>First up on this West Coast edition of Teen Cribs is Tess' &quot;green&quot; home. Then we head across the border to Canada to see Austin's crib with a sweet</k>  </p>
</a>
