<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="45" t="2020-05-27 04:36:14"><p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 05:25:00" d="2020-06-03 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball tries to save Darwin from being kissed by a girl. / Principal Brown tries to “fix” Gumball’s dysfunctional family. / Gumball and Darwin babysit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 06:00:00" d="2020-06-03 07:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>When the Rust Bucket must tune-up in the same town as Zombozo's latest campaign trail stop Ben soon discovers the clown is using his speeches to hypnotise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 07:00:00" d="2020-06-03 07:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>The prize jewel on the Secret Joyful Burger menu is a mysterious burger, but to order it you need to know its name. And Larry refuses to tell the guys what it's called</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 07:15:00" d="2020-06-03 07:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple needs to be tall so that he can be in love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 07:30:00" d="2020-06-03 07:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 07:45:00" d="2020-06-03 08:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When the Sheriff's Dept fights a monster that copies their every move they'll have to find a way to fight without fighting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 08:00:00" d="2020-06-03 08:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O &quot;accidentally&quot; releases a whole space prison-full of space criminals and winds up on the wrong side of the law. On the right side</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 08:15:00" d="2020-06-03 08:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>You're watching the Unikingdom News Show Super Good Morning Time Program Action Information Show, a variety news program put on (badly) by Unikitty and the gang!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 08:30:00" d="2020-06-03 08:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 08:45:00" d="2020-06-03 09:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple and Onion spend a day in Falafel's shoes and use their positive attitude to prove he shouldn't be so grumpy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 09:00:00" d="2020-06-03 09:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 09:31:00" d="2020-06-03 10:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 10:00:00" d="2020-06-03 11:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>So she isn't left out of inside jokes, the Titans time travel to past adventures and insert Bumblebee into their memories. / Robin gets amnesia and starts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 11:00:00" d="2020-06-03 12:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>The kids find out Dad has been dressing as a woman. / Darwin is delighted when they discover their old childhood toys, but soon realises that some things</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 12:00:00" d="2020-06-03 13:00:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>After an excessive spending spree, the Golden Goose tells the gang it won't give them any more golden eggs until they learn the value of money</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 13:00:00" d="2020-06-03 14:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple needs to find a funny formula that will land him a comedic role in a movie. / Apple and Onion try to finish a story before the book disappears forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 14:00:00" d="2020-06-03 15:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>When Leslie's petals begin falling off he feels like his good looks are fading, Gumball and Darwin use everything they know about style and beauty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 15:00:00" d="2020-06-03 16:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Robin tries to teach the Titans valuable life lessons by reading them fairytales but the others co-opt his stories and spin them into their own twisted yarns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 16:00:00" d="2020-06-03 16:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>The prize jewel on the Secret Joyful Burger menu is a mysterious burger, but to order it you need to know its name. And Larry refuses to tell the guys what it's called</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 16:15:00" d="2020-06-03 16:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple is challenged to a fight by a grumpy Cheesesteak, so he and Onion go on a quest to find the source of Cheesesteak's grumpiness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 16:30:00" d="2020-06-03 16:45:00"><n>Ninjago</n>    <k>66% Back in Ninjago City, three criminals learn of the ninja's absence and stage a breakout of Kryptarium Prison, telling tall tales of how they were captured as they go</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 16:45:00" d="2020-06-03 17:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 17:00:00" d="2020-06-03 17:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Third Earth is being overrun by super tough, super buff Warrior Maidens and it looks like the ThunderCats are next on their hit list!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 17:15:00" d="2020-06-03 17:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>The gang is taking an airplane trip together, and Hawk is at the helm since today he's taking his captain's license test</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 17:30:00" d="2020-06-03 17:45:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>The gang decide to compete in the annual Thumb War competition, but a surprise forces Mao Mao to deal with the unthinkable. losing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 17:45:00" d="2020-06-03 18:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>After Charlie hurts his foot, the Bears have to sneak him into a hospital for medical assistance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 18:00:00" d="2020-06-03 18:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 18:31:00" d="2020-06-03 19:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple is challenged to a fight by a grumpy Cheesesteak, so he and Onion go on a quest to find the source of Cheesesteak's grumpiness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 19:00:00" d="2020-06-03 19:31:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life's like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 19:31:00" d="2020-06-03 19:45:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Tygra's feeling unappreciated by the other ThunderCats so he starts hanging out with Mumm-Ra and cleaning his Black Pyramid?! Whaaaaaaat?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 19:45:00" d="2020-06-03 20:00:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>You're watching the Unikingdom News Show Super Good Morning Time Program Action Information Show, a variety news program put on (badly) by Unikitty and the gang!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 20:00:00" d="2020-06-03 20:15:00"><n>New: Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>Vic gets sick and is stuck in his room</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 20:15:00" d="2020-06-03 20:30:00"><n>New: Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs</n>    <k>In a sardine-obsessed town, Flint Lockwood is a teenager trying to change the world. ne invention at a time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 20:30:00" d="2020-06-03 20:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 20:45:00" d="2020-06-03 21:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When Mao Mao discovers that he is not as popular as Badgerclops and Adorabat, they decide to reinvent him as a kinder, cuddlier hero</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 21:00:00" d="2020-06-03 21:15:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple and Onion need to join an exclusive club to see a rare whale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 21:15:00" d="2020-06-03 21:31:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Every time Mumm-Ra gets a hold of a magic artefact to restore his powers the ThunderCats just smash it and turn him into a dinky skeleton again. Until today that is!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 21:31:00" d="2020-06-03 22:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>When Darwin and Gumball reveal how they’d spend their perfect day, Gumball confesses that he would spend it with Penny. / Granny Jojo has brought</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 22:00:00" d="2020-06-03 23:00:00"><n>Regular Show</n>    <k>Mordecai and Rigby want to find a rare golden video game patch. / Mordecai wants to share a piece of cake with C.J. / The guys want to help Party Horse pass his U.S</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-03 23:00:00" d="2020-06-04 00:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball and Darwin are unwitting accomplices in a gas station robbery. / Gumball and Darwin accidentally destroy Mr Robinson’s new car… or do they? / Gumball experiences an impossibly unfortunate chain of events. / Gumball and Darwin accidentally create a loveable monster that eats their family. / Gumball is embarrassed when Mum comes to school to spend some “quality time”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 00:00:00" d="2020-06-04 01:00:00"><n>Adventure Time</n>    <k>A magic spell backfires and turns Ice King back into Simon. / Lumpy Space Princess reconnects with an old classmate. / Finn and Jake learn about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 01:00:00" d="2020-06-04 02:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 02:30:00" d="2020-06-04 03:05:00"><n>Steven Universe</n>    <k>Steven Universe is a half-human, half-Gem hero who's learning to save the world along with the Crystal Gems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 03:05:00" d="2020-06-04 03:40:00"><n>Uncle Grandpa</n>    <k>He’s everyone in the world’s magical Uncle and Grandpa! GOOD MORNING!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 03:40:00" d="2020-06-04 05:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>The Wattersons complain about their day and order a pizza from Larry. / Granny Jojo has brought a boyfriend to her birthday meal and Dad isn’t happy about it</k>  </p>
</a>
