<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="45" t="2020-05-31 04:36:11"><p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 05:25:00" d="2020-06-07 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball discovers that Bobert is planning to take over his identity and replace him! / Gumball and Darwin barely survive a school picnic in the Forest of Doom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 06:00:00" d="2020-06-07 07:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>When Ben and Max get into an argument, Ben goes Heatblast to blow off steam against Max's wishes; but Dr. Animo spots him and subsequently turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 07:00:00" d="2020-06-07 07:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Miss Simian discovers a failed test from Gumball's past that brings down his grade point average. This means he has to retake kindergarten all over again!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 07:15:00" d="2020-06-07 07:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple and Onion try to spread cheer during a city-wide heatwave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 07:30:00" d="2020-06-07 07:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 07:45:00" d="2020-06-07 08:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>After struggling to keep up, Adorabat gets a cybernetic &quot;Mega-Mech.&quot; But can fancy new powers make up for experience?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 08:00:00" d="2020-06-07 08:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O has gotten a hold of the last jar of Thundersnaps! But a difficult to open cookie jar is gonna send Lion-O and Cheetara chasing down a legend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 08:15:00" d="2020-06-07 08:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>It's opening night at the Unikingdom Film Festival!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 08:30:00" d="2020-06-07 08:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 08:45:00" d="2020-06-07 09:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple and Onion must remain legit enough to be in their favorite rapper's music video</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 09:00:00" d="2020-06-07 09:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 09:31:00" d="2020-06-07 10:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 10:00:00" d="2020-06-07 11:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! Starfire</n>    <k>The best of Starfire in crime-fighting, Teen Titan Go adventures! From saving the day to roommate battles, the fun never ends for these superheroes!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 11:00:00" d="2020-06-07 12:00:00"><n>The Best of Gumball: Richard</n>    <k>Richard discovers that going into a bank whilst wearing a motorcycle helmet can land you in a lot of trouble. / The kids find out Dad has been dressing as a woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 12:00:00" d="2020-06-07 13:00:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>There's a mishap in the lab causing tiny problems. / Richard puts on an amateur magic show. / Unikingdom's throwing a kingdom-wide dance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 13:00:00" d="2020-06-07 14:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple is put in charge of the Dollar Store for the very first time. / Apple tries to survive a weekend alone while taking care of Onion's plant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 14:00:00" d="2020-06-07 15:00:00"><n>The Best of Gumball &amp; Darwin</n>    <k>Everyone assumes Darwin &amp; Carrie's relationship is doomed. / The kids find out Dad has been dressing as a woman. / Gumball, Darwin and Banana</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 15:00:00" d="2020-06-07 16:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! Raven</n>    <k>The best of Raven in crime-fighting, Teen Titan Go adventures! From saving the day to epic roommate battles, the fun never ends for these superheroes!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 16:00:00" d="2020-06-07 16:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Miss Simian discovers a failed test from Gumball's past that brings down his grade point average. This means he has to retake kindergarten all over again!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 16:15:00" d="2020-06-07 16:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple and Onion invent a new game that attracts some unexpected attention</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 16:30:00" d="2020-06-07 16:45:00"><n>Ninjago</n>    <k>67% The Ice Emperor summons an enormous ice Behemoth to attack Lloyd and his faithful wolf companion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 16:45:00" d="2020-06-07 17:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 17:00:00" d="2020-06-07 17:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Cheetara is the fastest living person in the universe until Monkian beats her in a race?! Now Cheetara has to find something else to be the best at</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 17:15:00" d="2020-06-07 17:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>When the Score creeper traps Unikitty and the gang in his laser tag arena the gang must defeat the house team or be imprisoned forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 17:30:00" d="2020-06-07 17:45:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When bounty hunter Tanya Keys comes to town for Badgerclops, it's up to Mao Mao and Adorabat to save their friend -- even if he's been on the wrong side of the law</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 17:45:00" d="2020-06-07 18:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>Chloe’s professor is too mean to give her any face time to talk over her poor grade. The Bears take things into their own hands to help, causing big trouble for Chloe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 18:00:00" d="2020-06-07 18:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 18:31:00" d="2020-06-07 19:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple and Onion need to find a dream to follow, so that their lives don't head nowhere. / Apple and Onion must face their fears while trapped</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 19:00:00" d="2020-06-07 19:31:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life's like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 19:31:00" d="2020-06-07 19:45:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Vultureman has got a brand new invention but there's one big problem: he stole the idea from Panthro! Oh, also Vultureman is using his invention to take over Third Earth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 19:45:00" d="2020-06-07 20:00:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>It's opening night at the Unikingdom Film Festival!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 20:00:00" d="2020-06-07 20:15:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>The boys forget to get Chata a gift for Abuela Day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 20:15:00" d="2020-06-07 20:30:00"><n>Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs</n>    <k>Mr. Earl thinks of himself as the healthiest person in Swallow Falls, but he’s hiding a delicious, frosting-topped secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 20:30:00" d="2020-06-07 20:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 20:45:00" d="2020-06-07 21:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When they think each others' lives are easier, the heroes switch roles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 21:00:00" d="2020-06-07 21:15:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% With their 6 month friend anniversary approaching, Apple has to find a way not to lose his best friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 21:15:00" d="2020-06-07 21:31:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>A crying unicorn appears at the Cats' Lair and weepily tells the ThunderCats that all of her unicorn friends have been captured!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 21:31:00" d="2020-06-07 22:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball and Darwin hit snooze too many times on their alarm clock and miss the school-bus. / Things keep going missing in the house, so it’s up to Gumball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 22:00:00" d="2020-06-07 23:00:00"><n>Regular Show</n>    <k>Mordecai and Rigby get in a fight over Margaret and Mordecai sends them through time by destroying all the clocks. / By trying to change Benson’s opinion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 23:00:00" d="2020-06-08 00:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>For once in his life Gumball is the one who's owed an apology. / Gumball and Darwin befriend Clayton, who is a compulsive liar and begins contaminating them with lies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 00:00:00" d="2020-06-08 01:00:00"><n>Adventure Time</n>    <k>Jake is transported to a different world. / Finn reunites with an old friend. / Flame Princess asks Princess Bubblegum for help when her city is cooled down</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 01:00:00" d="2020-06-08 02:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 02:30:00" d="2020-06-08 03:05:00"><n>Steven Universe</n>    <k>Steven Universe is a half-human, half-Gem hero who's learning to save the world along with the Crystal Gems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 03:05:00" d="2020-06-08 03:40:00"><n>Uncle Grandpa</n>    <k>He’s everyone in the world’s magical Uncle and Grandpa! GOOD MORNING!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 03:40:00" d="2020-06-08 05:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball and Darwin cheat on their maths test, get detention and have to escape. / Gumball and Darwin get caught in the middle of a trash can war between Richard and Mr</k>  </p>
</a>
