<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="45" t="2020-04-16 04:37:38"><p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 05:25:00" d="2020-04-23 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Anais throws a party but no-one shows up as she has no friends or social skills. / Alan is so good-natured that Gumball feels compelled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 06:00:00" d="2020-04-23 07:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>When the Rust Bucket runs out of gas on a foggy East Coast road Ben Gwen and Max are forced to stay at hotel being menaced by Creepy Carl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 07:00:00" d="2020-04-23 07:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Anais is convinced that Gumball is being bullied by Tina Rex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 07:15:00" d="2020-04-23 07:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>61% Apple and Onion try to spread cheer during a city-wide heatwave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 07:30:00" d="2020-04-23 07:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 07:45:00" d="2020-04-23 08:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When Mao Mao underestimates enemy and friend alike, it almost costs him the entire kingdom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 08:00:00" d="2020-04-23 08:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O never pays attention during Tygra’s training sessions so when he’s asked to do a pop quiz on &quot;sword magic&quot; he accidentally opens a portal to the Astral Plane!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 08:15:00" d="2020-04-23 08:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>An asteroid is headed right for the kingdom, so Dr Fox leads the gang on a mission to save the kingdom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 08:30:00" d="2020-04-23 08:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 08:45:00" d="2020-04-23 09:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>61% Apple and Onion struggle to ride Gyranoid of the Future, the craziest roller coaster at the carnival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 09:00:00" d="2020-04-23 09:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 09:31:00" d="2020-04-23 10:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life's like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 10:00:00" d="2020-04-23 11:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Nicole encourages Gumball to do what comes naturally. reak stuff! / Gumball kind of teaches Darwin how to be a skater… / Darwin finds it harder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 11:00:00" d="2020-04-23 12:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Robin tries to destroy some pesky mocking birds but they come back bigger, stronger, and ready to mock. / Cyborg has a star-crossed crush on Jinx</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 12:00:00" d="2020-04-23 12:31:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple and Onion have to outwit a mean duck who's taken over their building's roof. / Apple helps Onion achieve his dream of competing on a baking show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 12:31:00" d="2020-04-23 13:00:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>Craig of the Creek follows a young boy and his two friends as they go on adventures in a world of untamed, kid-dominated wilderness in the creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 13:00:00" d="2020-04-23 13:31:00"><n>Summer Camp Island</n>    <k>Susie challenges the campers to a game of softball to get out of doing a chore. / Hedgehog finds a city underneath her bed as she looks for her missing diary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 13:31:00" d="2020-04-23 14:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>Chloe and Ice Bear drive up north to find the perfect Christmas tree. Meanwhile, Grizz and Panda are in charge of decorating Chloe's house. / Charlie meets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 14:00:00" d="2020-04-23 15:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>The Wattersons transform their house into The Big House. / The Wattersons discover a family of cartoon copycats who mimic their every move. / Grandpa Louie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 15:00:00" d="2020-04-23 16:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>After Robin swipes her cloak, Raven's figure is revealed and she transforms into Lady Legasus; meanwhile Cyborg gets stuck in the cloak, revealing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 16:00:00" d="2020-04-23 16:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball and Darwin unsuccessfully attempt to get a refund for their computer game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 16:15:00" d="2020-04-23 16:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>61% Apple and Onion’s favorite game attracts some unexpected attention</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 16:30:00" d="2020-04-23 16:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Adventures of Robin, Cyborg, Starfire, Raven and Beast Boy. They are superheroes who save the day, but what happens when they're not fighting crime?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 16:45:00" d="2020-04-23 17:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 17:00:00" d="2020-04-23 17:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O never pays attention during Tygra’s training sessions so when he’s asked to do a pop quiz on &quot;sword magic&quot; he accidentally opens a portal to the Astral Plane!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 17:15:00" d="2020-04-23 17:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Unikitty and the gang float helplessly through space</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 17:30:00" d="2020-04-23 17:45:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Badgerclops gets huge to destroy a towering monster but when he refuses to shrink down the kingdom faces a new terror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 17:45:00" d="2020-04-23 18:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>The Bears travel to the video game store</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 18:00:00" d="2020-04-23 18:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 18:31:00" d="2020-04-23 19:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple and Onion need to find a dream to follow so that their lives don't head nowhere. / Apple and Onion must face their fears while trapped</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 19:00:00" d="2020-04-23 19:31:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life's like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 19:31:00" d="2020-04-23 20:00:00"><n>New: Thundercats Roar: Exodus</n>    <k>Fleeing the destruction of their home planet Thundera Lion-O and the ThunderCats land on the mysterious dangerous all-around awesome world of Third Earth!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 20:00:00" d="2020-04-23 20:31:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple and Onion have to find a way to ride the Hot Air Balloon which is in their town for one day only. / Apple and Onion both leave their homes and follow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 20:31:00" d="2020-04-23 20:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 20:45:00" d="2020-04-23 21:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Mao Mao's desire to be a legend drives him to keep topping himself. But how much is enough?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 21:00:00" d="2020-04-23 21:15:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Unikitty and the gang float helplessly through space</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 21:15:00" d="2020-04-23 21:31:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Every time Mumm-Ra gets a hold of a magic artefact to restore his powers the ThunderCats just smash it and turn him into a dinky skeleton again. Until today that is!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 21:31:00" d="2020-04-23 22:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>When Alan ditches Gumball to do something more fun, Gumball is desperate to track him down and make him pay for his betrayal. / The Wattersons are forced</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 22:00:00" d="2020-04-23 23:00:00"><n>Regular Show</n>    <k>Mordecai and Rigby have to clean up their room. / Mordecai and Rigby want to make money for a video game by street performing. / Mordecai and Rigby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 23:00:00" d="2020-04-24 00:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Richard is left in charge for the day, but his lack of rules attracts unwanted guests to the Watterson house. / Gumball and Darwin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-24 00:00:00" d="2020-04-24 01:00:00"><n>Adventure Time</n>    <k>Finn longs to be an everyday guy. / Ice King, NEPTR, Tree Trunks, Shelby and Lemongrab are trapped inside a mysterious dungeon and must work together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-24 01:00:00" d="2020-04-24 02:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-24 02:30:00" d="2020-04-24 03:05:00"><n>Steven Universe</n>    <k>Steven Universe is a half-human, half-Gem hero who's learning to save the world along with the Crystal Gems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-24 03:05:00" d="2020-04-24 03:40:00"><n>Uncle Grandpa</n>    <k>He’s everyone in the world’s magical Uncle and Grandpa! GOOD MORNING!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-24 03:40:00" d="2020-04-24 05:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Granny JoJo's overprotective behavior puts the Wattersons in danger. / Gumball teaches Darwin a lesson after Darwin leaves him. / Gumball asks Idaho</k>  </p>
</a>
