<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="45" t="2020-04-13 04:32:56"><p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 05:25:00" d="2020-04-20 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Vice Principal Brown gives Gumball and Darwin the ancient school hamster, Chris Morris, to look after for the weekend. / When Darwin and Gumball reveal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 06:00:00" d="2020-04-20 07:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>When Ben goes Upgrade to transform the lawnmower into a superfast mowing machine he accidently draws the ire of Bob’s gnome-neighbours. / Ben stumbles into Dr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 07:00:00" d="2020-04-20 07:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball and Darwin accidentally create a loveable monster that eats their family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 07:15:00" d="2020-04-20 07:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>61% Apple needs to be tall so that he can be in love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 07:30:00" d="2020-04-20 07:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 07:45:00" d="2020-04-20 08:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When Rufus and Reg come to swindle the town, Sheriff Mao Mao teaches them a lesson in justice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 08:00:00" d="2020-04-20 08:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Cheetara is the fastest living person in the universe until Monkian beats her in a race?! Now Cheetara has to find something else to be the best at</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 08:15:00" d="2020-04-20 08:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>After an excessive spending spree, the Golden Goose tells the gang it won't give them any more golden eggs until they learn the value of money</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 08:30:00" d="2020-04-20 08:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 08:45:00" d="2020-04-20 09:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>61% Apple and Onion have to find a way to ride the Hot Air Balloon which is in their town for one day only</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 09:00:00" d="2020-04-20 09:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 09:31:00" d="2020-04-20 10:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life's like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 10:00:00" d="2020-04-20 11:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Elmore residents are going missing, and the cause of these disappearances may be closer to home than Gumball and Darwin think. / Gumball and Darwin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 11:00:00" d="2020-04-20 12:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Robin's perfect sandwich is missing and he will stop at nothing to find it. / Starfire creates a bond with Raven's father./Raven tries to put the spirit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 12:00:00" d="2020-04-20 12:31:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Onion worries his relationship with Apple is in jeopardy when a stray cat enters the picture. / When Falafel decides to pack up and leave the city Apple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 12:31:00" d="2020-04-20 13:00:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>Craig of the Creek follows a young boy and his two friends as they go on adventures in a world of untamed, kid-dominated wilderness in the creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 13:00:00" d="2020-04-20 13:31:00"><n>Summer Camp Island</n>    <k>Oscar must get Hedgehog a special sandwich in order to save their friendship. / At Alice's dress-up party the campers are magically turned into their costumes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 13:31:00" d="2020-04-20 14:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>Tabes helps the Bears rescue Charlie after he gets captured by a villainous game hunter. / Grizz helps Ranger Tabes and the Poppy Rangers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 14:00:00" d="2020-04-20 15:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball is late to meet Penny at the mall, but a series of misunderstandings on the way only delay him further. / When Mom sees Darwin gazing longingly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 15:00:00" d="2020-04-20 16:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Despite Raven's warnings Starfire showers love on the adorable twin destroyers of the universe. /Robin has been hiding something under his gloves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 16:00:00" d="2020-04-20 16:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball and Darwin’s martial arts costumes make them a laughing stock at school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 16:15:00" d="2020-04-20 16:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>61% Apple needs to find a funny formula that will land him a comedic in a movie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 16:30:00" d="2020-04-20 16:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Adventures of Robin, Cyborg, Starfire, Raven and Beast Boy. They are superheroes who save the day, but what happens when they're not fighting crime?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 16:45:00" d="2020-04-20 17:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 17:00:00" d="2020-04-20 17:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Cheetara is the fastest living person in the universe until Monkian beats her in a race?! Now Cheetara has to find something else to be the best at</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 17:15:00" d="2020-04-20 17:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>It's a sleepover at the castle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 17:30:00" d="2020-04-20 17:45:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When the Sheriff's Dept fights a monster that copies their every move they'll have to find a way to fight without fighting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 17:45:00" d="2020-04-20 18:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>Charlie meets a creature just like him named Ralph</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 18:00:00" d="2020-04-20 18:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 18:31:00" d="2020-04-20 19:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>When Falafel decides to pack up and leave the city Apple and Onion have to convince him to stay. / Onion worries his relationship with Apple is in jeopardy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 19:00:00" d="2020-04-20 19:31:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life's like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 19:31:00" d="2020-04-20 20:00:00"><n>New: Thundercats Roar</n>    <k>Lion-O is tasked with mapping the beaches of Third Earth which leads to him somehow draining the oceans of all water entirely. Woops! / Cheetara is the fastest living person in the universe until Monkian beats her in a race?! Now Cheetara has to find something else to be the best at</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 20:00:00" d="2020-04-20 20:31:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple and Onion have to prove that they're not selfish when they do their good deeds. / Apple needs to find a funny formula that will land him a comedic in a movie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 20:31:00" d="2020-04-20 20:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 20:45:00" d="2020-04-20 21:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When Mao Mao gets hungry for the perfect adventure Adorabat tells a white lie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 21:00:00" d="2020-04-20 21:15:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>It's a sleepover at the castle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 21:15:00" d="2020-04-20 21:31:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O &quot;accidentally&quot; releases a whole space prison-full of space criminals and winds up on the wrong side of the law. On the right side</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 21:31:00" d="2020-04-20 22:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>After being framed for feeding coffee to the squirrels in the park, Gumball proclaims that Mrs Robinson is pure evil. / Gumball and Darwin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 22:00:00" d="2020-04-20 23:00:00"><n>Regular Show</n>    <k>Mordecai, Rigby, Muscle Man and High Five Ghost make their own internet videos and compete to get the most views. / Mordecai and Rigby are picking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-20 23:00:00" d="2020-04-21 00:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball teaches Darwin a lesson after Darwin leaves him. / Granny JoJo's overprotective behavior puts the Wattersons in danger. / Gumball and Darwin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 00:00:00" d="2020-04-21 01:00:00"><n>Adventure Time</n>    <k>Finn and Jake challenge a giant monster to a fight but they end up fighting each other. / Princess Bubblegum and Lady Rainicorn go on a quest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 01:00:00" d="2020-04-21 02:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 02:30:00" d="2020-04-21 03:05:00"><n>Steven Universe</n>    <k>Steven Universe is a half-human, half-Gem hero who's learning to save the world along with the Crystal Gems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 03:05:00" d="2020-04-21 03:40:00"><n>Uncle Grandpa</n>    <k>He’s everyone in the world’s magical Uncle and Grandpa! GOOD MORNING!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 03:40:00" d="2020-04-21 05:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball and Darwin spice up their friendship by introducing a third best friend. / Gumball has to save Mr Robinson’s life during Elmore’s Senior Talent Show! / Gumball tries to save Darwin from being kissed by a girl. / Principal Brown tries to “fix” Gumball’s dysfunctional family. / Sarah, the new kid in school, is Gumball and Darwin's number one, slightly obsessive, fan. / Whilst Gumball and Darwin make fun of Mum and Dad for being old, their voices start to break. / The Wattersons are surprised to discover that their past actions have consequences. / The life of the background objects of Elmore are shown in a series of short skits. / The Watterson kids come up with a fool-proof plan</k>  </p>
</a>
