<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="9" t="2020-05-16 04:58:10"><p id_tv="1130" o="2020-05-23 05:25:00" d="2020-05-23 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>After Gumball and Darwin have too much sugary cereal they begin thinking about the mysteries of the universe. / Gumball, Darwin and Anais discover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-05-23 06:00:00" d="2020-05-23 22:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben stumbles upon a Xingo arcade game and goes OE-Shock Rock to power it up but when it receives too much juice Xingo leaps out into the real world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-05-23 22:00:00" d="2020-05-23 23:00:00"><n>Regular Show</n>    <k>The Government have announced a new fitness test that everyone has to pass or they will get fired. The test goes well for everyone except Rigby, who fails! / The friends put on a surprise leaving party for Margaret, but the abandoned ballroom they are in is haunted by past party guests… / Muscle Man is showing off and accidently sets off all the fireworks they had been saving for the Fourth of July! / Muscle Man is finding it very hard not to contact his girlfriend for a whole weekend!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-05-23 23:00:00" d="2020-05-24 00:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-05-24 00:00:00" d="2020-05-24 01:00:00"><n>Adventure Time</n>    <k>Finn and Jake have a silent contest. / Peppermint Butler thinks Princess Bubblegum is spending too much time inside and needs a suitor. / His kidnapping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-05-24 01:00:00" d="2020-05-24 02:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-05-24 02:30:00" d="2020-05-24 03:05:00"><n>Steven Universe</n>    <k>Steven Universe is a half-human, half-Gem hero who's learning to save the world along with the Crystal Gems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-05-24 03:05:00" d="2020-05-24 03:40:00"><n>Uncle Grandpa</n>    <k>He’s everyone in the world’s magical Uncle and Grandpa! GOOD MORNING!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-05-24 03:40:00" d="2020-05-24 05:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Darwin has promised to play video games with Gumball, but his promise with Banana Joe interferes. / The Wattersons must survive a bizarre</k>  </p>
</a>
