<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="44" t="2020-05-25 04:54:49"><p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 05:25:00" d="2020-06-01 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball is the star of his own comic, but struggles to match up to his heroic alter-ego. / After Gumball convinces himself that Penny doesn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 06:00:00" d="2020-06-01 07:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben is at the annual Big Bacon Pig Parade but childhood friend Penny Heaven has met the family to ruin Ben's fun with her safety-obsessed self</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 07:00:00" d="2020-06-01 07:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Richard discovers that going into a bank whilst wearing a motorcycle helmet can land you in a lot of trouble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 07:15:00" d="2020-06-01 07:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple and Onion have to prove that they're not selfish when they do their good deeds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 07:30:00" d="2020-06-01 07:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 07:45:00" d="2020-06-01 08:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>An explosive loner and his slacker best friend are waylaid from their journey into legend, only to find that their story is just beginning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 08:00:00" d="2020-06-01 08:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Tygra's feeling unappreciated by the other ThunderCats so he starts hanging out with Mumm-Ra and cleaning his Black Pyramid?! Whaaaaaaat?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 08:15:00" d="2020-06-01 08:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Unikitty finds an old, beatup recliner on the curb, but sees its inner beauty and brings it home to introduce to the gang!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 08:30:00" d="2020-06-01 08:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 08:45:00" d="2020-06-01 09:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple and Onion must conquer their obsessions of sausages and a video game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 09:00:00" d="2020-06-01 09:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 09:31:00" d="2020-06-01 10:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 10:00:00" d="2020-06-01 11:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>The Titans are outraged when their favourite cartoon is rebooted, so they come up with a plan to get this new show off the air. / Robin surprises</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 11:00:00" d="2020-06-01 12:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Hector is unhappy with his height. / Gumball and Darwin argue with the Internet. / Gumball and Darwin are at the convenience store considering playing truant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 12:00:00" d="2020-06-01 13:00:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Puppycorn is determined to become the Hot Dog King and joins an underground hot dog eating contest called Weiner Club. / During a fun fireworks show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 13:00:00" d="2020-06-01 14:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple is put in charge of the Dollar Store for the very first time. / Apple tries to survive a weekend alone while taking care of Onion's plant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 14:00:00" d="2020-06-01 15:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Leslie calls Gumball's bluff. / Gumball decides to put Mr. Small's eco-friendly principles to the test but it doesn't quite go as planned. / Sarah finds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 15:00:00" d="2020-06-01 16:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Robin decides to become a cat so that Starfire will finally love him. / After being defeated due to poor leg strength Raven and the Titans work out their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 16:00:00" d="2020-06-01 16:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Richard discovers that going into a bank whilst wearing a motorcycle helmet can land you in a lot of trouble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 16:15:00" d="2020-06-01 16:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% When Falafel decides to pack up and leave the city, Apple and Onion have to convince him to stay or they'll have to leave too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 16:30:00" d="2020-06-01 16:45:00"><n>Ninjago</n>    <k>66% The Ice Emperor learns of the ninja's arrival and sends his Blizzard Samurai warriors to destroy them and the villagers who sheltered them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 16:45:00" d="2020-06-01 17:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 17:00:00" d="2020-06-01 17:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>A crying unicorn appears at the Cats' Lair and weepily tells the ThunderCats that all of her unicorn friends have been captured!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 17:15:00" d="2020-06-01 17:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>It's time for the gang's yearly vacation, but Hawk refuses to go, claiming the gang's vacations are never fun for him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 17:30:00" d="2020-06-01 17:45:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When a Sweetypie isn't impressed with the sheriff dept's antics, our three heroes try everything to win him over</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 17:45:00" d="2020-06-01 18:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>Chloe and Ice Bear accidentally lose Chloe's prized hoodie to the ferocious dog next store. They go on a mission to get it back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 18:00:00" d="2020-06-01 18:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 18:31:00" d="2020-06-01 19:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple and Onion invent a new game that attracts some unexpected attention. / Apple and Onion both leave their homes and follow their dreams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 19:00:00" d="2020-06-01 19:31:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life's like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 19:31:00" d="2020-06-01 19:45:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O &quot;accidentally&quot; releases a whole space prison-full of space criminals and winds up on the wrong side of the law. On the right side</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 19:45:00" d="2020-06-01 20:00:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Unikitty finds an old, beatup recliner on the curb, but sees its inner beauty and brings it home to introduce to the gang!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 20:00:00" d="2020-06-01 20:15:00"><n>New: Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>When Vic &amp; Val accidently turn themselves and Don into babies, they must escape a daycare center in order to change back to their normal ages</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 20:15:00" d="2020-06-01 20:30:00"><n>New: Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs</n>    <k>In a sardine-obsessed town, Flint Lockwood is a teenager trying to change the world. ne invention at a time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 20:30:00" d="2020-06-01 20:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 20:45:00" d="2020-06-01 21:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When Mao Mao's old partner threatens the kingdom, his friends will need to learn about his past in order to protect the present</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 21:00:00" d="2020-06-01 21:15:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple and Onion try to spread cheer during a city-wide heatwave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 21:15:00" d="2020-06-01 21:31:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O is tasked with mapping the beaches of Third Earth which leads to him somehow draining the oceans of all water entirely. Woops!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 21:31:00" d="2020-06-01 22:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>It's Mother's Day, and Gumball and Darwin discover that Tobias and Banana Joe have both made a card for &quot;The Best Mum in the World&quot;. / Mum has forced</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 22:00:00" d="2020-06-01 23:00:00"><n>Regular Show</n>    <k>The guys want to help Muscle Man finish his bucket list. / The park guys want revenge on Muscle Man for all his terrible gifts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-01 23:00:00" d="2020-06-02 00:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball almost loses his mind trying to guess Darwin’s secret. / Gumball and Darwin are taught confusing lessons about honesty by the school councillor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-02 00:00:00" d="2020-06-02 01:00:00"><n>Adventure Time</n>    <k>Finn finds an old truck, and Jake calls Banana Man to help with the repairs. / Tree Trunks and Mr. Pig are getting married. / Abracadaniel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-02 01:00:00" d="2020-06-02 02:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-02 02:30:00" d="2020-06-02 03:40:00"><n>Make, Shake &amp; Jake</n>    <k>Mel, Shaun and Jake the dog explore the market, and create their own pretend fruit and veg stall! When Shaun munches into an apple, the rhythm</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-02 03:40:00" d="2020-06-02 05:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>When Gumball and Darwin decide it's time they join a crew, they agree that the coolest posse in Elmore is the Senior Citizens. / Gumball and Darwin</k>  </p>
</a>
