<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="45" t="2020-05-29 04:36:34"><p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 05:25:00" d="2020-06-05 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball sets out to solve the mystery of who stuffed Principal Brown into his locker. / Gumball and Darwin’s harmless pranks on Dad spiral hopelessly out of control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 06:00:00" d="2020-06-05 07:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben and Gwen spend the day volunteering at Repto Ranch and come face to face with King Koil but need to overcome their fear of snakes if they are to defeat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 07:00:00" d="2020-06-05 07:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball discovers that Rob, his old nemesis, is &quot;neme-seeing&quot; someone else. Devastated that Rob has fallen out of hate with him, Gumball refuses to accept</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 07:15:00" d="2020-06-05 07:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple tries to survive a weekend alone while taking care of Onion's plant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 07:30:00" d="2020-06-05 07:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 07:45:00" d="2020-06-05 08:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Mao Mao's desire to be a legend drives him to keep topping himself. But how much is enough?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 08:00:00" d="2020-06-05 08:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O never pays attention during Tygra’s training sessions so when he’s asked to do a pop quiz on &quot;sword magic&quot; he accidentally opens a portal to the Astral Plane!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 08:15:00" d="2020-06-05 08:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Dr. Fox's robot helpers go on strike, so Unikitty and Puppycorn volunteer to be her lab rats, er, research assistants in a bold new experiment rocketing them into space!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 08:30:00" d="2020-06-05 08:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 08:45:00" d="2020-06-05 09:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple is put in charge of the Dollar Store for the very first time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 09:00:00" d="2020-06-05 09:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 09:31:00" d="2020-06-05 10:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 10:00:00" d="2020-06-05 11:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Robin takes the Titans on an educational trip. / Aqualad uses shrimps and prime rib to win back Raven. / The Titans have Raven give them new super powers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 11:00:00" d="2020-06-05 12:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>The kids find out that Richard has been being picked on by the same person since high school. / Grandpa Louie has a new online friend - the only problem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 12:00:00" d="2020-06-05 13:00:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>When the Score creeper traps Unikitty and the gang in his laser tag arena the gang must defeat the house team or be imprisoned forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 13:00:00" d="2020-06-05 14:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple and Onion go on a guided bus tour as part of their plan to get Apple's shoe back. / Apple and Onion have to outwit a mean duck who's taken over their building's roof</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 14:00:00" d="2020-06-05 15:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Darwin finds it harder than expected to give up his favourite foodstuff. / Gumball kind of teaches Darwin how to be a skater… / Nicole encourages Gumball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 15:00:00" d="2020-06-05 16:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>The Titans go to an amusement park to see LeBron James but instead help solve a mystery. / It's Valentine's Day and Cyborg goes to great lengths</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 16:00:00" d="2020-06-05 16:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball discovers that Rob, his old nemesis, is &quot;neme-seeing&quot; someone else. Devastated that Rob has fallen out of hate with him, Gumball refuses to accept</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 16:15:00" d="2020-06-05 16:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple and Onion have to find a way to ride the Hot Air Balloon which is in their town for one day only</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 16:30:00" d="2020-06-05 16:45:00"><n>Ninjago</n>    <k>67% Guilt-ridden over having lost the Traveler's Tea, Cole embarks on a dangerous quest to the top of a nearby mountain in hopes of finding the legendary Traveler's Tree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 16:45:00" d="2020-06-05 17:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 17:00:00" d="2020-06-05 17:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Tygra takes Lion-O climbing up the peak of Hook Mountain to teach him a lesson about trust. But they get trapped by a snowstorm and take refuge in a creepy cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 17:15:00" d="2020-06-05 17:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Unikitty and the gang have crashed on a fabulous island</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 17:30:00" d="2020-06-05 17:45:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Worried that his sword is a glorified consolation prize, Mao Mao sets out to prove the worth of his weapon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 17:45:00" d="2020-06-05 18:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>Grizz gets cast in a movie about a Grizzly Bear! But Grizz soon realises the movie's depiction of grizzly Bears is not what he had in mind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 18:00:00" d="2020-06-05 18:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 18:31:00" d="2020-06-05 19:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple and Onion try to finish a story before the book disappears forever. / Apple needs to find a funny formula that will land him a comedic role in a movie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 19:00:00" d="2020-06-05 19:31:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life's like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 19:31:00" d="2020-06-05 19:45:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O is reminded that he needs to plug the Sword of Omens into the Cats' Lair each night or else the base will run out of power. That's fine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 19:45:00" d="2020-06-05 20:00:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Dr. Fox's robot helpers go on strike, so Unikitty and Puppycorn volunteer to be her lab rats, er, research assistants in a bold new experiment rocketing them into space!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 20:00:00" d="2020-06-05 20:15:00"><n>New: Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>Vic &amp; Val are in awe of the new magician in town, but things go awry when they agree to help him out with a new trick - despite Chata's wishes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 20:15:00" d="2020-06-05 20:30:00"><n>New: Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs</n>    <k>In a sardine-obsessed town, Flint Lockwood is a teenager trying to change the world. ne invention at a time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 20:30:00" d="2020-06-05 20:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 20:45:00" d="2020-06-05 21:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When the Sweetypies think the mythical Torbaclaun has come to Pure Heart Valley, Mao Mao tries to prove to them that it isn't real</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 21:00:00" d="2020-06-05 21:15:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple tries to survive a weekend alone while taking care of Onion's plant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 21:15:00" d="2020-06-05 21:31:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O wants to prove to the ThunderKittens that he’s not just some boring old adult like Tygra even if it means ignoring his instincts and messing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 21:31:00" d="2020-06-05 22:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball, Darwin and Anais discover that Banana Joe’s mom paints pictures which predict the future. / When Mr Small shows a health and safety video</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 22:00:00" d="2020-06-05 23:00:00"><n>Regular Show</n>    <k>Mordecai and Rigby make a deal with a Coffee Bean to help them stay awake to work major overtime to pay for concert tickets. / In order to impress Margret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 23:00:00" d="2020-06-06 00:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball and Darwin learn that it isn't wise to upset Hector, Elmore's resident Giant. / Nicole seeks to develop a sense of ambition in Gumball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 00:00:00" d="2020-06-06 01:00:00"><n>Adventure Time</n>    <k>Kim Kil Whan wants to teach his dad, Jake, responsibility. / Ice King goes on a spiritual journey. / A crusader against the dark arts seeks to banish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 01:00:00" d="2020-06-06 02:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 02:30:00" d="2020-06-06 03:05:00"><n>Steven Universe</n>    <k>Steven Universe is a half-human, half-Gem hero who's learning to save the world along with the Crystal Gems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 03:05:00" d="2020-06-06 03:40:00"><n>Uncle Grandpa</n>    <k>He’s everyone in the world’s magical Uncle and Grandpa! GOOD MORNING!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 03:40:00" d="2020-06-06 05:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>When Mum reveals that Gumball's real name is &quot;Zach&quot;, Gumball adopts a cheesy, annoying persona to match the name. / The kids finally get the puppy</k>  </p>
</a>
