<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="45" t="2021-07-08 05:07:04"><p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 05:20:00" d="2021-07-13 06:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV</n>    <k>The Nest / The Points / The Bus
Elmore residents are going missing, and the cause of these disappearances may be closer to home than Gumball and Darwin think</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 06:00:00" d="2021-07-13 06:35:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I</n>    <k>Winner Takes All / The Other Side / The Best Team
After months of training for Luchador Day Axel needs Masko to coach him against a pair of uninvited</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 06:35:00" d="2021-07-13 07:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 III</n>    <k>Speechless on the Seine / Poles Apart
While in Paris, France, Ben catches Zombozo robbing the Louvre, but when Zombozo hypnotizes Ben to remain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 07:00:00" d="2021-07-13 07:31:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I</n>    <k>The Mustache / Date The
Gumball and Darwin’s wish comes true when they suddenly turn into men. / Gumball discovers the difference between a “date”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 07:31:00" d="2021-07-13 08:00:00"><n u="Apple And Onion">Apple And Onion I</n>    <k>Hotdog's Movie Premiere / Tips
Apple and Onion square off against a no-nonsense security guard after they're banned from the premiere of their friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 08:00:00" d="2021-07-13 08:31:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV</n>    <k>Lication / Classic Titans
Robin introduces the other Titans to a money making application but they soon learn the dangers of a shareconomy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 08:31:00" d="2021-07-13 08:45:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (5)</n>    <k>54% Tower Renovation
The Titans go house hunting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 08:45:00" d="2021-07-13 09:00:00"><n u="The Fungies!">The Fungies! I (13)</n>    <k>Commander Beefy
Seth, eager to explore the stars and find a fellow explorer, sends a signal to space. But the explorer who receives the message Commander</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 09:00:00" d="2021-07-13 09:31:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V</n>    <k>The Petals / The Nuisance
When Leslie's petals begin falling off he feels like his good looks are fading Gumball and Darwin use everything they know about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 09:31:00" d="2021-07-13 10:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V</n>    <k>Don't Be An Icarus / Booty Eggs
Robin tries to tell some Greek myths, but the other Titans give their own fractured versions instead. / Not wanting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 10:00:00" d="2021-07-13 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III</n>    <k>The Teen Titans Go Easter Holiday Classic / Rad Dudes with Bad Tudes / History Lesson / The Art of Ninjutsu
The Easter Bunny is missing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 11:00:00" d="2021-07-13 12:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI</n>    <k>The Intelligence / The Potion / The Third / The Debt
Gumball and Darwin argue with the Internet. / The kids find out Dad has been dressing as a woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 12:00:00" d="2021-07-13 13:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III</n>    <k>Think About Your Future / Booty Scooty / Who's Laughing Now / Oregon Trail
The Titans are reckless with their money and health much to the detriment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 13:00:00" d="2021-07-13 13:31:00"><n u="Apple And Onion">Apple And Onion I</n>    <k>4 On 1 / Apple's In Trouble
Onion's fear of crowds threatens his basketball team's success. / Apple is challenged to a fight by a grumpy Cheesesteak</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 13:31:00" d="2021-07-13 14:00:00"><n u="We Bare Bears">We Bare Bears I</n>    <k>The Road / Shush Ninjas
The Bears flashback to when they were young cubs! On their way through the desert, they come upon a giant warehouse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 14:00:00" d="2021-07-13 15:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I</n>    <k>The Pressure / The Painting / The Responsible / The Dress
Gumball tries to save Darwin from being kissed by a girl. / Principal Brown tries to “fix”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 15:00:00" d="2021-07-13 16:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III</n>    <k>Snuggle Time / Oh Yeah! / Riding the Dragon / The Overbite
When yet another crime alert interrupts their relaxation, the Titans decide to become villains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 16:00:00" d="2021-07-13 16:15:00"><n u="Monster Beach">Monster Beach I (6)</n>    <k>It Cone from Outer Space
When Mutt won't stop scratching, the cone he has to wear around his head picks up radio signals and he realises</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 16:15:00" d="2021-07-13 16:30:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (32)</n>    <k>Jessica's Trail
Jessica wanders into an unfamiliar creek, leaving Craig to find her before his Mom notices!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 16:30:00" d="2021-07-13 16:45:00"><n u="Apple And Onion">Apple And Onion I (25)</n>    <k>Face Your Fears
Apple and Onion must face their fears while trapped in a pet shop so they can save French Fry from facing hers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 16:45:00" d="2021-07-13 17:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! I (17)</n>    <k>Sidekick
When he is tasked with looking after the Bat-cave Robin questions his relationship with Batman while struggling to keep the other Titans in line</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 17:00:00" d="2021-07-13 17:15:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (33)</n>    <k>Dinner At The Creek
Bernard is left in charge for the evening, so Craig sets out to find his own dinner at the creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 17:15:00" d="2021-07-13 17:30:00"><n u="New: Summer Camp Island">New: Summer Camp Island II</n>    <k>Glow Worm
Shark helps Oscar visit his past to learn something interesting about himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 17:30:00" d="2021-07-13 17:45:00"><n u="We Bare Bears">We Bare Bears I (10)</n>    <k>Primal
Have the Bears lost their survival instincts by living in the modern world? Grizz wants to know so he purposefully gets the Bears lost in the deep forest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 17:45:00" d="2021-07-13 18:00:00"><n u="The Fungies!">The Fungies! I (13)</n>    <k>Commander Beefy
Seth, eager to explore the stars and find a fellow explorer, sends a signal to space. But the explorer who receives the message Commander</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 18:00:00" d="2021-07-13 18:31:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V</n>    <k>The Matchmaker / The Box
Darwin likes a girl in his class so Gumball decides it’s time to play cupid. / A mysterious package shows up at the Watterson's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 18:31:00" d="2021-07-13 19:00:00"><n u="Apple And Onion">Apple And Onion I</n>    <k>Apple's In Trouble / Hotdog's Movie Premiere
Apple is challenged to a fight by a grumpy Cheesesteak so he and Onion go on a quest to find the source</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 19:00:00" d="2021-07-13 19:31:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! I</n>    <k>Caged Tiger / Nose Mouth
When Robin Cyborg and Beast Boy get trapped in an elevator the limits of their friendship are tested while Starfire and Raven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 19:31:00" d="2021-07-13 19:45:00"><n u="The Fungies!">The Fungies! I (14)</n>    <k>Snake It To The Limit
When Seth agrees to let an athletic snake replace his arm so he can finally be good at volleyball he learns he doesn't need a fancy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 19:45:00" d="2021-07-13 20:00:00"><n u="Unikitty!">Unikitty! II (20)</n>    <k>53% Trapped in Paradise
Unikitty and the gang have crashed on a fabulous island</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 20:00:00" d="2021-07-13 20:15:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (34)</n>    <k>72% Bug City
Craig discovers a bunch of bugs under a rock and decides to build them a city</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 20:15:00" d="2021-07-13 20:30:00"><n u="Summer Camp Island">Summer Camp Island II (17)</n>    <k>Glow Worm
Shark helps Oscar visit his past to learn something interesting about himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 20:30:00" d="2021-07-13 20:45:00"><n u="New: Monster Beach">New: Monster Beach I</n>    <k>Tiki'D Off
When Lost Patrol finds himself in a turf war with Dr. Knutt and the Tikis, it's every monster for himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 20:45:00" d="2021-07-13 21:00:00"><n u="New: ThunderCats Roar">New: ThunderCats Roar I</n>    <k>Killing Time
Mumm-Ra decides he'll nap for a thousand years till the ThunderCats are long gone. But when he wakes up, he discovers that Third Earth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 21:00:00" d="2021-07-13 21:15:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! VI (10)</n>    <k>We're Off to Get Awards
During an awards ceremony, Robin is swept up by a tornado and arrives in a magical land</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 21:15:00" d="2021-07-13 21:31:00"><n u="Apple And Onion">Apple And Onion I (11)</n>    <k>Apple's Focus
Apple helps Onion achieve his dream of competing on a baking show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 21:31:00" d="2021-07-13 22:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V</n>    <k>The List / The Deal
When the kids find out that Mom's life hasn't panned out exactly as she'd hoped they try to make her day a bit easier by taking on her chores</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 22:00:00" d="2021-07-13 22:30:00"><n u="I, Elvis Riboldi">I, Elvis Riboldi I</n>    <k>I, Elvis Riboldi, And The Miracle Drink / I, Elvis Riboldi, And The Pinkerton School
RE-TAW, a new mass-marketed energy drink, changes Elvis and friends' lives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 22:30:00" d="2021-07-13 23:00:00"><n u="I, Elvis Riboldi">I, Elvis Riboldi I</n>    <k>I, Elvis Riboldi, Get Homeschooled / I, Elvis Riboldi, Master Of The House
Elvis accidentally burns down Ms. Jennifer’s apartment and she moves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-13 23:00:00" d="2021-07-14 00:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball I</n>    <k>The Poltergeist / The Quest / The Spoon / The Car
Gumball and Darwin give Mr Robinson a home and end up saving his marriage. / Gumball and Darwin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-14 00:00:00" d="2021-07-14 01:00:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I</n>    <k>Saving Private Masko / Out of My Head / Gathering Dark / From Below
Masko takes Axel's call for more discipline too seriously and loses sight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-14 01:00:00" d="2021-07-14 02:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV</n>    <k>The Night / The Misunderstandings / The Roots / The Blame / The Slap / The Detective / The Fury / The Compilation
Ever wondered what the people of Elmore dream about? As night falls in Elmore the Moon takes us on a tour through the various dreams - and nightmares - of the inhabitants. / Gumball is late to meet Penny at the mall, but a series of misunderstandings on the way only delay him further. / When Mom sees Darwin gazing longingly at a fish-tank she thinks their mammalian lifestyle isn’t fulfilling her adopted son and deep down he longs to connect with his fishy roots. / The Parent Teacher Association of Elmore Junior High bans video games, so the kids try and prove that games aren't a bad influence. / Tobias follows every single high-five with a butt-slap so when Gumball doesn’t get one he feels insulted. He tries to get Tobias to slap his rear all day but it doesn’t work. / Anais arrives in the bedroom to find a messy crime-scene and her Daisy doll missing. She realises Gumball and Darwin are the chief suspects. / A mysterious figure from Nicole's past shows up and challenges her to a fight, but the kids are surprised when she refuses. / A compilation of some of the funniest, most bizarre clips uploaded onto the internet by the people of Elmore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-14 02:30:00" d="2021-07-14 03:05:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV</n>    <k>The Disaster / The Re-Run / The Stories
When Rob purchases a universal remote from the Awesome Store he discovers he can control the universe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-14 03:05:00" d="2021-07-14 03:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V</n>    <k>The Guy / The Boredom / The Vision
Anais has made a new friend, so Gumball and Darwin immediately assume there must be something wrong with him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2021-07-14 03:40:00" d="2021-07-14 05:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V</n>    <k>The Choices / The Code / The Test / The Slide / The Loophole / The Fuss / The News / The Vase / The Ollie
Nicole remembers the day she first met Richard</k>  </p>
</a>
