<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="45" t="2020-04-15 04:37:08"><p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 05:25:00" d="2020-04-22 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>After Gumball and Darwin have too much sugary cereal they begin thinking about the mysteries of the universe. / Gumball, Darwin and Anais discover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 06:00:00" d="2020-04-22 07:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>During Chefapalooza in the Rocky Montains three famous chefs and infamous bad-guys The Tri-Chefta hunt down Wildvine in hopes of creating their most exotic dish to date</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 07:00:00" d="2020-04-22 07:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball’s magic tinfoil helmet threatens to tear the Watterson family apart!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 07:15:00" d="2020-04-22 07:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>61% Apple and Onion want to become this week's &quot;Most Fun People&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 07:30:00" d="2020-04-22 07:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 07:45:00" d="2020-04-22 08:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When Mao Mao discovers that he is not as popular as Badgerclops and Adorabat, they decide to reinvent him as a kinder, cuddlier hero</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 08:00:00" d="2020-04-22 08:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O is tasked with mapping the beaches of Third Earth which leads to him somehow draining the oceans of all water entirely. Woops!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 08:15:00" d="2020-04-22 08:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>A super-grumpy volcano appears in the kingdom, so Unikitty takes the gang on an epic quest to cheer it up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 08:30:00" d="2020-04-22 08:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 08:45:00" d="2020-04-22 09:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>61% Apple and Onion must remain legit enough to be in their favorite rapper's music video</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 09:00:00" d="2020-04-22 09:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 09:31:00" d="2020-04-22 10:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life's like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 10:00:00" d="2020-04-22 11:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>When Gumball and Darwin accidentally find a sinister secret manifesto on Alan's memory stick, they decide they have to foil his plan for total world domination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 11:00:00" d="2020-04-22 12:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>A glimpse inside each Titan's dream world. / Robin tries to teach his superhero ways to Spanish speaking brothers Mas y Menos. / BB and Cyborg invite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 12:00:00" d="2020-04-22 12:31:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple and Onion both leave their homes and follow their dreams to the big city but things don’t go quite to plan. / Apple and Onion’s favorite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 12:31:00" d="2020-04-22 13:00:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>Craig of the Creek follows a young boy and his two friends as they go on adventures in a world of untamed, kid-dominated wilderness in the creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 13:00:00" d="2020-04-22 13:31:00"><n>Summer Camp Island</n>    <k>Alice lures Oscar and his monster friends for a tea party, but only to turn the monsters into cute babies. / Hedgehog gets bit by a cute puppy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 13:31:00" d="2020-04-22 14:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>To help raise money to save Darrell's store, the Bears use the stack as a taxi through a ride share app. / The Baby Bears sign up for a game of laser tag</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 14:00:00" d="2020-04-22 15:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Rocky is trying to find love with the help of the latest dating app… / Gumball and Darwin give Bobert specific instructions to ensure he acts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 15:00:00" d="2020-04-22 16:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Cyborg wants Pain Bot to be his “little buddy” but is the destructive robot too dangerous to be a sidekick? / Robin goes undercover to destroy the Hive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 16:00:00" d="2020-04-22 16:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball and Darwin are invited to a high school party, and have to bring a date!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 16:15:00" d="2020-04-22 16:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>61% Apple and Onion spend a day in Falafel's shoes and use their positive attitude to prove he shouldn't be so grumpy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 16:30:00" d="2020-04-22 16:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Adventures of Robin, Cyborg, Starfire, Raven and Beast Boy. They are superheroes who save the day, but what happens when they're not fighting crime?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 16:45:00" d="2020-04-22 17:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 17:00:00" d="2020-04-22 17:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O is tasked with mapping the beaches of Third Earth which leads to him somehow draining the oceans of all water entirely. Woops!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 17:15:00" d="2020-04-22 17:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Puppycorn witnesses Unikitty do a very embarrassing thing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 17:30:00" d="2020-04-22 17:45:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Mao Mao's desire to be a legend drives him to keep topping himself. But how much is enough?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 17:45:00" d="2020-04-22 18:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>Ice Bear has a Korean-style cooking show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 18:00:00" d="2020-04-22 18:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 18:31:00" d="2020-04-22 19:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple and Onion have to prove that they're not selfish when they do their good deeds. / Apple and Onion must conquer their obsessions of sausages and a video game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 19:00:00" d="2020-04-22 19:31:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life's like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 19:31:00" d="2020-04-22 20:00:00"><n>New: Thundercats Roar</n>    <k>Every time Mumm-Ra gets a hold of a magic artefact to restore his powers the ThunderCats just smash it and turn him into a dinky skeleton again. Until today that is! / Lion-O is tasked with mapping the beaches of Third Earth which leads to him somehow draining the oceans of all water entirely. Woops!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 20:00:00" d="2020-04-22 20:31:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple needs to be tall so that he can be in love. / Apple and Onion square off against a no-nonsense security guard after they’re banned from the premiere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 20:31:00" d="2020-04-22 20:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 20:45:00" d="2020-04-22 21:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Feeling left out Adorabat wishes Mao Mao and Badgerclops would spend less time with each other and more time with her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 21:00:00" d="2020-04-22 21:15:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Puppycorn witnesses Unikitty do a very embarrassing thing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 21:15:00" d="2020-04-22 21:31:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O never pays attention during Tygra’s training sessions so when he’s asked to do a pop quiz on &quot;sword magic&quot; he accidentally opens a portal to the Astral Plane!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 21:31:00" d="2020-04-22 22:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Nicole seeks to develop a sense of ambition in Gumball / Channel 6 Elmore News has all the top local stories. / Gumball and Darwin find themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 22:00:00" d="2020-04-22 23:00:00"><n>Regular Show</n>    <k>Mordecai and Rigby go on a road trip to return Margaret's sweater. / Mordecai and Rigby have to fix Benson’s car before he finds out they broke its window</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 23:00:00" d="2020-04-23 00:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Nicole gets upset with the family at the supermarket when her kids want chocolate, but she says no. / The Wattersons must survive a bizarre</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 00:00:00" d="2020-04-23 01:00:00"><n>Adventure Time</n>    <k>Five more stories set in the land of Ooo. / Finn and Jake are playing when Finn tosses their throwing disc into a tree. / Magic Man slips Finn a bag filled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 01:00:00" d="2020-04-23 02:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 02:30:00" d="2020-04-23 03:05:00"><n>Steven Universe</n>    <k>Steven Universe is a half-human, half-Gem hero who's learning to save the world along with the Crystal Gems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 03:05:00" d="2020-04-23 03:40:00"><n>Uncle Grandpa</n>    <k>He’s everyone in the world’s magical Uncle and Grandpa! GOOD MORNING!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-23 03:40:00" d="2020-04-23 05:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball and Darwin cheat on their maths test, get detention and have to escape. / Gumball and Darwin get caught in the middle of a trash can war between Richard and Mr</k>  </p>
</a>
