<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="45" t="2020-05-28 04:42:22"><p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 05:25:00" d="2020-06-04 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball goes to school in a dress and becomes the darling of Elmore High. / Gumball and Darwin challenge Dad to a “lazy-off”. / Gumball must learn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 06:00:00" d="2020-06-04 07:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>On their trip to Adrenaworld West, Ben takes a detour on a jungle cruise and finds himself hunted by the evil Tim Buktu. / While sightseeing at the Geyser</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 07:00:00" d="2020-06-04 07:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>When they see the school bullies making fun of Sussie, Gumball and Darwin decide to try and help her act less weird</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 07:15:00" d="2020-06-04 07:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% With their 6 month friend anniversary approaching, Apple has to find a way not to lose his best friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 07:30:00" d="2020-06-04 07:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 07:45:00" d="2020-06-04 08:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Feeling left out Adorabat wishes Mao Mao and Badgerclops would spend less time with each other and more time with her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 08:00:00" d="2020-06-04 08:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O is tasked with mapping the beaches of Third Earth which leads to him somehow draining the oceans of all water entirely. Woops!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 08:15:00" d="2020-06-04 08:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Richard's prepared one of the tastiest desserts ever, but he's locked it up tight until the friends have their boring dinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 08:30:00" d="2020-06-04 08:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 08:45:00" d="2020-06-04 09:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple needs to acquire a lifetime supply of toilet paper to finish his modern art sculpture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 09:00:00" d="2020-06-04 09:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 09:31:00" d="2020-06-04 10:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 10:00:00" d="2020-06-04 11:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>The Titans go house hunting. / Robin takes the other Titans on a trip. / Robin tries to teach the other Titans about real estate. / Robin hatches</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 11:00:00" d="2020-06-04 12:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Richard discovers that going into a bank whilst wearing a motorcycle helmet can land you in a lot of trouble. / When Gumball finds out that their 8-bit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 12:00:00" d="2020-06-04 13:00:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>When the kingdom runs out of inspiration, Unikitty takes it on herself to re-inspire the citizens. / The gang is taking an airplane trip together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 13:00:00" d="2020-06-04 14:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple is challenged to a fight by a grumpy Cheesesteak, so he and Onion go on a quest to find the source of Cheesesteak's grumpiness. / Apple and Onion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 14:00:00" d="2020-06-04 15:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball and Darwin discover the reason Dad's diet wasn't working was that he was actually on ten diets and eating a meal for each of them! / Miss Simian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 15:00:00" d="2020-06-04 16:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Starfire is visited by three ghosts and shown the true meaning of Black Friday. / The Titans learn about cartoon-style violence in order to get revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 16:00:00" d="2020-06-04 16:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>When they see the school bullies making fun of Sussie, Gumball and Darwin decide to try and help her act less weird</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 16:15:00" d="2020-06-04 16:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple and Onion square off against a no-nonsense security guard after they're banned from the premiere of their friend Hot Dog's new movie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 16:30:00" d="2020-06-04 16:45:00"><n>Ninjago</n>    <k>66% Lloyd and his wolf-companion find a cave with the mech inside and a message from Zane that provides a clue to his fate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 16:45:00" d="2020-06-04 17:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 17:00:00" d="2020-06-04 17:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O is reminded that he needs to plug the Sword of Omens into the Cats' Lair each night or else the base will run out of power. That's fine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 17:15:00" d="2020-06-04 17:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Concerned about Puppycorn's propensity to hurt himself constantly, the gang places him into Richard's old Safety Suit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 17:30:00" d="2020-06-04 17:45:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When Mao Mao underestimates enemy and friend alike, it almost costs him the entire kingdom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 17:45:00" d="2020-06-04 18:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>Chloe and the Bears take a road trip to see a meteor shower. Ice Bear, the only one licensed to drive, is put in charge, which becomes harder than he thought</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 18:00:00" d="2020-06-04 18:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 18:31:00" d="2020-06-04 19:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>When Falafel decides to pack up and leave the city, Apple and Onion have to convince him to stay or they'll have to leave too. / Onion worries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 19:00:00" d="2020-06-04 19:31:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life's like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 19:31:00" d="2020-06-04 19:45:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Tygra takes Lion-O climbing up the peak of Hook Mountain to teach him a lesson about trust. But they get trapped by a snowstorm and take refuge in a creepy cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 19:45:00" d="2020-06-04 20:00:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Richard's prepared one of the tastiest desserts ever, but he's locked it up tight until the friends have their boring dinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 20:00:00" d="2020-06-04 20:15:00"><n>New: Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>Vic and Val tag along with Xochi to a punk concert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 20:15:00" d="2020-06-04 20:30:00"><n>New: Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs</n>    <k>In a sardine-obsessed town, Flint Lockwood is a teenager trying to change the world. ne invention at a time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 20:30:00" d="2020-06-04 20:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 20:45:00" d="2020-06-04 21:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>The gang struggles to get rid of the King when he joins them as their new deputy-for-a-day!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 21:00:00" d="2020-06-04 21:15:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple is put in charge of the Dollar Store for the very first time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 21:15:00" d="2020-06-04 21:31:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O has gotten a hold of the last jar of Thundersnaps! But a difficult to open cookie jar is gonna send Lion-O and Cheetara chasing down a legend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 21:31:00" d="2020-06-04 22:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>The citizens of Elmore are feeling down because it’s January, so Gumball and Anais invent a new holiday called Sluzzle Tag. / In Biology class, Gumball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 22:00:00" d="2020-06-04 23:00:00"><n>Regular Show</n>    <k>The guys have to get Muscle Man married. / Mordecai and Rigby have to fix the garage door. / Mordecai and Rigby find a mysterious keyboard that allows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-04 23:00:00" d="2020-06-05 00:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball’s magic tinfoil helmet threatens to tear the Watterson family apart! / Anais is convinced that Gumball is being bullied by Tina Rex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 00:00:00" d="2020-06-05 01:00:00"><n>Adventure Time</n>    <k>Lumpy Space Princess and Marcy prank Breakfast Princess! / Lumpy Space Princess wants the Ice King to tell her version of Lumpy Space Prince's life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 01:00:00" d="2020-06-05 02:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 02:30:00" d="2020-06-05 03:05:00"><n>Steven Universe</n>    <k>Steven Universe is a half-human, half-Gem hero who's learning to save the world along with the Crystal Gems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 03:05:00" d="2020-06-05 03:40:00"><n>Uncle Grandpa</n>    <k>He’s everyone in the world’s magical Uncle and Grandpa! GOOD MORNING!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-05 03:40:00" d="2020-06-05 05:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Darwin starts sneezing repeatedly and it seems he can't stop. / Gumball jaywalks and is pulled over by Donut Cop. / Gumball confronts Clayton about</k>  </p>
</a>
