<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="45" t="2020-04-14 04:33:46"><p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 05:25:00" d="2020-04-21 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>The Wattersons complain about their day and order a pizza from Larry. / The citizens of Elmore are feeling down because it’s January, so Gumball and Anais</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 06:00:00" d="2020-04-21 07:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben Gwen and Max’s trip to Niagara Falls is cut short by the horrid Hydromanders – creatures menacing them and their fellow tourists. / While chilling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 07:00:00" d="2020-04-21 07:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball is embarrassed when Mum comes to school to spend some “quality time”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 07:15:00" d="2020-04-21 07:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>61% Apple helps Onion achieve his dream of competing on a baking show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 07:30:00" d="2020-04-21 07:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 07:45:00" d="2020-04-21 08:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>The gang decide to compete in the annual Thumb War competition, but a surprise forces Mao Mao to deal with the unthinkable. losing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 08:00:00" d="2020-04-21 08:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O &quot;accidentally&quot; releases a whole space prison-full of space criminals and winds up on the wrong side of the law. On the right side</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 08:15:00" d="2020-04-21 08:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Brock drags Master Frown along to join him in following his dream, to become the Flyer on a cheerleading team</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 08:30:00" d="2020-04-21 08:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 08:45:00" d="2020-04-21 09:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>61% Apple and Onion must find a way to use Burger's trampoline without making him feel used</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 09:00:00" d="2020-04-21 09:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 09:31:00" d="2020-04-21 10:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life's like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 10:00:00" d="2020-04-21 11:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Anais arrives in the bedroom to find a messy crime-scene and her Daisy doll missing. She realises that Gumball and Darwin are the chief suspects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 11:00:00" d="2020-04-21 12:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Brian: When The Brain captures the Titans. Nature:Beast Boy returns to nature and finds it much harsher than he expects. / Robin brings Starfire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 12:00:00" d="2020-04-21 12:31:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple is challenged to a fight by a grumpy Cheesesteak so he and Onion go on a quest to find the source of Cheesesteak's grumpiness. / Apple and Onion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 12:31:00" d="2020-04-21 13:00:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>Craig of the Creek follows a young boy and his two friends as they go on adventures in a world of untamed, kid-dominated wilderness in the creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 13:00:00" d="2020-04-21 13:31:00"><n>Summer Camp Island</n>    <k>Oscar learns that he can earn merit badges that unlock prizes. / Oscar's painting is unpopular so he goes on a journey of self-discovery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 13:31:00" d="2020-04-21 14:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>Charlie meets a creature just like him named Ralph. / The Bears have a relaxing day at the spa. Grizz tries to get everything the spa has to offer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 14:00:00" d="2020-04-21 15:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball saved himself from being trapped in The Void, just in time. The remote has now taken Gumball back to the beginning of that disastrous day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 15:00:00" d="2020-04-21 16:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>After Starfire is set up by Blackfire and sent to prison, the Titans work to make Blackfire a better sister while Starfire plots her revenge. / When Robin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 16:00:00" d="2020-04-21 16:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball is traumatised when accidentally kissed on the mouth by his Grandma JoJo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 16:15:00" d="2020-04-21 16:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>61% Onion's fear of crowds threatens his basketball team's success</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 16:30:00" d="2020-04-21 16:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Adventures of Robin, Cyborg, Starfire, Raven and Beast Boy. They are superheroes who save the day, but what happens when they're not fighting crime?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 16:45:00" d="2020-04-21 17:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 17:00:00" d="2020-04-21 17:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O &quot;accidentally&quot; releases a whole space prison-full of space criminals and winds up on the wrong side of the law. On the right side</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 17:15:00" d="2020-04-21 17:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Unikitty tries to prove to Master Frown she is no tyrant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 17:30:00" d="2020-04-21 17:45:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Feeling left out Adorabat wishes Mao Mao and Badgerclops would spend less time with each other and more time with her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 17:45:00" d="2020-04-21 18:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>Ice Bear has a Korean-style cooking show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 18:00:00" d="2020-04-21 18:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 18:31:00" d="2020-04-21 19:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple and Onion try to finish a story before the book disappears forever. / Apple needs to find a funny formula that will land him a comedic in a movie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 19:00:00" d="2020-04-21 19:31:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life's like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 19:31:00" d="2020-04-21 20:00:00"><n>New: Thundercats Roar</n>    <k>Lion-O never pays attention during Tygra’s training sessions so when he’s asked to do a pop quiz on &quot;sword magic&quot; he accidentally opens a portal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 20:00:00" d="2020-04-21 20:31:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple needs to acquire a lifetime supply of toilet paper to finish his modern art sculpture. / Apple tries to survive a weekend alone while taking care of Onion's plant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 20:31:00" d="2020-04-21 20:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 20:45:00" d="2020-04-21 21:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When the Sheriff's Dept fights a monster that copies their every move they'll have to find a way to fight without fighting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 21:00:00" d="2020-04-21 21:15:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Unikitty tries to prove to Master Frown she is no tyrant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 21:15:00" d="2020-04-21 21:31:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O is tasked with mapping the beaches of Third Earth which leads to him somehow draining the oceans of all water entirely. Woops!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 21:31:00" d="2020-04-21 22:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball and Darwin see an advert for the latest, cutting-edge Bobert operating system and excitedly talk Bobert into downloading it. / Hector is unhappy with his height</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 22:00:00" d="2020-04-21 23:00:00"><n>Regular Show</n>    <k>While playing a video game, Mordecai and Rigby make a bet in which the loser of the game has to wear a blonde hairstyle. Rigby cheats. / Mordecai wants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-21 23:00:00" d="2020-04-22 00:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball and Darwin try to get a game back from Tobias, but Darwin starts to feel like a sidekick to Gumball and refuses to follow his orders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 00:00:00" d="2020-04-22 01:00:00"><n>Adventure Time</n>    <k>Finn and Jake sneak into the Fire Kingdom, at the request of Flame Princess. / Finn has a dream about the Lich, Billy, and a snail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 01:00:00" d="2020-04-22 02:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 02:30:00" d="2020-04-22 03:05:00"><n>Steven Universe</n>    <k>Steven Universe is a half-human, half-Gem hero who's learning to save the world along with the Crystal Gems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 03:05:00" d="2020-04-22 03:40:00"><n>Uncle Grandpa</n>    <k>He’s everyone in the world’s magical Uncle and Grandpa! GOOD MORNING!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-22 03:40:00" d="2020-04-22 05:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball accidentally uploads a video of himself and wants it gone. / Gumball and Darwin's reputation is challenged and they really couldn't care less</k>  </p>
</a>
