<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="44" t="2020-04-10 04:37:54"><p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 05:25:00" d="2020-04-17 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball and Darwin help Rocky land an office job so that his dad, Mr Robinson, will be proud of him. / Gumball confronts Clayton about his fabled Seven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 06:00:00" d="2020-04-17 07:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben accidentally creates a giant sink hole and frees King Koil and his Kimodo Dragon from below. / After a series of reoccurring nightmares affect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 07:00:00" d="2020-04-17 07:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball experiences an impossibly unfortunate chain of events</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 07:15:00" d="2020-04-17 07:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>61% Apple and Onion must face their fears while trapped in a pet shop so they can save French Fry from facing hers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 07:30:00" d="2020-04-17 07:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 07:45:00" d="2020-04-17 08:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Badgerclops smells, but Mao Mao and Adorabat don't know how to tell him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 08:00:00" d="2020-04-17 08:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Tygra's feeling unappreciated by the other ThunderCats so he starts hanging out with Mumm-Ra and cleaning his Black Pyramid?! Whaaaaaaat?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 08:15:00" d="2020-04-17 08:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>The moon is bored of taking the nightshift, since everyone's always asleep. So Unikitty leads the gang in putting on an over-the-top late night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 08:30:00" d="2020-04-17 08:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 08:45:00" d="2020-04-17 09:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>61% Apple and Onion square off against a no-nonsense security guard after they’re banned from the premiere of their friend Hot Dog’s new movie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 09:00:00" d="2020-04-17 10:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 10:00:00" d="2020-04-17 10:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!: Night Begins To Shine</n>    <k>The Teen Titans and their musician friends square off against an evil Dragon for control of The Night Begins to Shine song in this epic final battle!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 10:45:00" d="2020-04-17 11:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 11:00:00" d="2020-04-17 12:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>When Rob purchases a universal remote from the Awesome Store, he discovers he can control the universe. He rewinds into the past and remembers Gumball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 12:00:00" d="2020-04-17 13:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple helps Onion achieve his dream of competing on a baking show. / Apple and Onion must find a way to use Burger's trampoline without making him feel used</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 13:00:00" d="2020-04-17 13:31:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Unikitty and the gang have crashed on a fabulous island. / The gang are at the local laundromat cleaning their clothes, when Unikitty finds Batman's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 13:31:00" d="2020-04-17 14:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life's like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 14:00:00" d="2020-04-17 15:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>When Gumball and Darwin accidentally find a sinister secret manifesto on Alan's memory stick, they decide they have to foil his plan for total world domination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 15:00:00" d="2020-04-17 16:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>While playing a fantasy adventure game the Titans are transported inside and must find the key to return home. / Raven teaches the other Titans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 16:00:00" d="2020-04-17 16:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball and Darwin’s harmless pranks on Dad spiral hopelessly out of control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 16:15:00" d="2020-04-17 16:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>61% Apple and Onion go on a guided bus tour as part of their plan to get Apple's shoe back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 16:30:00" d="2020-04-17 16:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Adventures of Robin, Cyborg, Starfire, Raven and Beast Boy. They are superheroes who save the day, but what happens when they're not fighting crime?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 16:45:00" d="2020-04-17 17:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 17:00:00" d="2020-04-17 17:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Tygra's feeling unappreciated by the other ThunderCats so he starts hanging out with Mumm-Ra and cleaning his Black Pyramid?! Whaaaaaaat?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 17:15:00" d="2020-04-17 17:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>The Land Lord has threatened Master Frown and Brock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 17:30:00" d="2020-04-17 17:45:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Mao Mao's legendary, gigantic and critical father visits his son at his new job as sheriff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 17:45:00" d="2020-04-17 18:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>The Bears travel to the video game store</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 18:00:00" d="2020-04-17 18:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 18:31:00" d="2020-04-17 19:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple and Onion’s favorite game attracts some unexpected attention. / Apple and Onion both leave their homes and follow their dreams to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 19:00:00" d="2020-04-17 19:31:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life's like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 19:31:00" d="2020-04-17 20:00:00"><n>New: Thundercats Roar</n>    <k>Lion-O &quot;accidentally&quot; releases a whole space prison-full of space criminals and winds up on the wrong side of the law. On the right side</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 20:00:00" d="2020-04-17 20:31:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple and Onion need to join an exclusive club to see a rare whale. / Apple is put in charge of the Dollar Store for the very first time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 20:31:00" d="2020-04-17 20:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 20:45:00" d="2020-04-17 21:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Badgerclops adopts an abandoned monster, but some things are better left in the wild</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 21:00:00" d="2020-04-17 21:15:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>The Land Lord has threatened Master Frown and Brock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 21:15:00" d="2020-04-17 21:31:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Cheetara is the fastest living person in the universe until Monkian beats her in a race?! Now Cheetara has to find something else to be the best at</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 21:31:00" d="2020-04-17 22:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Sarah finds a notebook from an awesome store! / Gumball is the star of his own comic, but struggles to match up to his heroic alter-ego</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 22:00:00" d="2020-04-17 23:00:00"><n>Regular Show</n>    <k>When Skip’s cousin arrives to watch him play a game in the park, he annoys everyone with his bad jokes! Until, Skip finds his cousin the perfect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-17 23:00:00" d="2020-04-18 00:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Nicole seeks to develop a sense of ambition in Gumball / When everyone in the Watterson household wants to watch their favourite show at the same time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-18 00:00:00" d="2020-04-18 01:00:00"><n>Adventure Time</n>    <k>The tears of a crying Cyclops might heal Finn and Jake’s broken toes. / Jake's Dad appears in a holographic message with a mysterious challenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-18 01:00:00" d="2020-04-18 02:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-18 02:30:00" d="2020-04-18 03:05:00"><n>Steven Universe</n>    <k>Steven Universe is a half-human, half-Gem hero who's learning to save the world along with the Crystal Gems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-18 03:05:00" d="2020-04-18 03:40:00"><n>Uncle Grandpa</n>    <k>He’s everyone in the world’s magical Uncle and Grandpa! GOOD MORNING!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-04-18 03:40:00" d="2020-04-18 05:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Things aren’t going Gumball’s way at school so he assumes there must be a Secret Society. / Alan is so good-natured that Gumball feels compelled</k>  </p>
</a>
