<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="45" t="2020-05-30 04:40:41"><p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 05:25:00" d="2020-06-06 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball is traumatised when accidentally kissed on the mouth by his Grandma JoJo. / Gumball and Darwin are invited to a high school party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 06:00:00" d="2020-06-06 07:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>While Gwen listens to a lecture on the Transcontinental Railroad, Ben sneaks away to the gift shop. But the Bounty Hunters appear and corner him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 07:00:00" d="2020-06-06 07:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball and Darwin discover the reason Dad's diet wasn't working was that he was actually on ten diets and eating a meal for each of them!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 07:15:00" d="2020-06-06 07:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple and Onion need to join an exclusive club to see a rare whale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 07:30:00" d="2020-06-06 07:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 07:45:00" d="2020-06-06 08:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Badgerclops gets huge to destroy a towering monster but when he refuses to shrink down the kingdom faces a new terror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 08:00:00" d="2020-06-06 08:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Every time Mumm-Ra gets a hold of a magic artefact to restore his powers the ThunderCats just smash it and turn him into a dinky skeleton again. Until today that is!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 08:15:00" d="2020-06-06 08:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>It's Lazy Sunday, and Unikitty and Puppycorn are having such an amazing time hanging out on the couch, they never want to move!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 08:30:00" d="2020-06-06 08:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 08:45:00" d="2020-06-06 09:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple and Onion struggle to ride Gyranoid of the Future, the craziest roller coaster at the carnival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 09:00:00" d="2020-06-06 09:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 09:31:00" d="2020-06-06 10:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 10:00:00" d="2020-06-06 11:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Top of the Titans</n>    <k>Birdarang is here to count down the raddest music. / The Titans follow their heart with songs. / Birdarang counts down the best musical moments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 11:00:00" d="2020-06-06 12:00:00"><n>The Best of Gumball &amp; Darwin</n>    <k>When Mom sees Darwin gazing longingly at a fish-tank she thinks their mammalian lifestyle isn’t fulfilling her adopted son and deep down he longs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 12:00:00" d="2020-06-06 13:00:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Dr. Fox is proud to unveil her new ultimate combat machine. / Unikitty finds an old, beatup recliner on the curb, but sees its inner beauty and brings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 13:00:00" d="2020-06-06 14:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple and Onion's party plans are interrupted by a grumpy guest. / Apple and Onion must remain legit enough to be in their favorite rapper's music video</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 14:00:00" d="2020-06-06 15:00:00"><n>Gumball: Darwin's Yearbook</n>    <k>With the help of his friends, Darwin completes his yearbook of Elmore Junior High adventures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 15:00:00" d="2020-06-06 16:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! Robin</n>    <k>The best of Robin in crime-fighting, Teen Titan Go adventures! From saving the day to epic roommate battles, the fun never ends for these superheroes!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 16:00:00" d="2020-06-06 16:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball and Darwin discover the reason Dad's diet wasn't working was that he was actually on ten diets and eating a meal for each of them!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 16:15:00" d="2020-06-06 16:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple and Onion both leave their homes and follow their dreams to the big city but things don't go quite to plan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 16:30:00" d="2020-06-06 16:45:00"><n>Ninjago</n>    <k>67% Cole awakens inside an icy cavern belonging to a legendary beast, and attempts to escape, only to discover a surprising truth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 16:45:00" d="2020-06-06 17:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 17:00:00" d="2020-06-06 17:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Tygra's feeling unappreciated by the other ThunderCats so he starts hanging out with Mumm-Ra and cleaning his Black Pyramid?! Whaaaaaaat?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 17:15:00" d="2020-06-06 17:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>The gang are at the local laundromat cleaning their clothes, when Unikitty finds Batman's uniform mixed in with her clothes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 17:30:00" d="2020-06-06 17:45:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Badgerclops adopts an abandoned monster, but some things are better left in the wild</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 17:45:00" d="2020-06-06 18:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>The Bears have lunch with Ranger Tabes. But when a mystery presents itself, Tabes goes into full on detective mode to find the culprit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 18:00:00" d="2020-06-06 18:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 18:31:00" d="2020-06-06 19:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple and Onion have to prove that they're not selfish when they do their good deeds. / Apple and Onion must conquer their obsessions of sausages and a video game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 19:00:00" d="2020-06-06 19:31:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life's like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 19:31:00" d="2020-06-06 19:45:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Third Earth is being overrun by super tough, super buff Warrior Maidens and it looks like the ThunderCats are next on their hit list!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 19:45:00" d="2020-06-06 20:00:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>It's Lazy Sunday, and Unikitty and Puppycorn are having such an amazing time hanging out on the couch, they never want to move!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 20:00:00" d="2020-06-06 20:15:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>When Vic &amp; Val accidently turn themselves and Don into babies, they must escape a daycare center in order to change back to their normal ages</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 20:15:00" d="2020-06-06 20:30:00"><n>Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs</n>    <k>Tim discovers a mermaid in the ocean but skeptical Flint doesn't believe they exist. When it proves to be real Sam finds she has a surprising connection</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 20:30:00" d="2020-06-06 20:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 20:45:00" d="2020-06-06 21:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Mao Mao's legendary, gigantic and critical father visits his son at his new job as sheriff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 21:00:00" d="2020-06-06 21:15:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple needs to acquire a lifetime supply of toilet paper to finish his modern art sculpture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 21:15:00" d="2020-06-06 21:31:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Panthro is getting a little fed up with having to fix things around the Cats' Lair constantly which is unfortunate because the ThunderCats are about to be attacked</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 21:31:00" d="2020-06-06 22:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Alan is so good-natured that Gumball feels compelled to make him lose his temper. / Things aren’t going Gumball’s way at school so he assumes there</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 22:00:00" d="2020-06-06 23:00:00"><n>Regular Show</n>    <k>After Rigby causes the guys to get locked in a meat locker, he must get help from some hot dogs in order to get them out. / Mordecai and Rigby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-06 23:00:00" d="2020-06-07 00:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Darwin develops a texting addiction when he and Gumball get their first cell phone. / Richard gets a job as a pizza delivery man, which worries Nicole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 00:00:00" d="2020-06-07 01:00:00"><n>Adventure Time</n>    <k>It is the first day of school for Sweet Pea. / Evergreen and his apprentice Gunter have to stop a meteor heading towards Earth. / Finn and Jake go camping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 01:00:00" d="2020-06-07 02:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 02:30:00" d="2020-06-07 03:05:00"><n>Steven Universe</n>    <k>Steven Universe is a half-human, half-Gem hero who's learning to save the world along with the Crystal Gems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 03:05:00" d="2020-06-07 03:40:00"><n>Uncle Grandpa</n>    <k>He’s everyone in the world’s magical Uncle and Grandpa! GOOD MORNING!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-07 03:40:00" d="2020-06-07 05:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball accidentally uploads a video of himself and wants it gone. / Gumball and Darwin's reputation is challenged and they really couldn't care less</k>  </p>
</a>
