<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="45" t="2020-06-01 04:36:01"><p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 05:25:00" d="2020-06-08 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball almost loses his mind trying to guess Darwin’s secret. / Gumball and Darwin are taught confusing lessons about honesty by the school councillor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 06:00:00" d="2020-06-08 07:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben accidentally creates a giant sink hole and frees King Koil and his Kimodo Dragon from below. / After a series of reoccurring nightmares affect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 07:00:00" d="2020-06-08 07:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Darwin likes a girl in his class so Gumball decides it’s time to play cupid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 07:15:00" d="2020-06-08 07:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple and Onion's party plans are interrupted by a grumpy guest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 07:30:00" d="2020-06-08 07:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 07:45:00" d="2020-06-08 08:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When a Sweetypie isn't impressed with the sheriff dept's antics, our three heroes try everything to win him over</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 08:00:00" d="2020-06-08 08:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O wants to prove to the ThunderKittens that he’s not just some boring old adult like Tygra even if it means ignoring his instincts and messing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 08:15:00" d="2020-06-08 08:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Unikitty comes to the conclusion that everyone would be a lot happier if they would just think the way she does, and with Dr. Fox's help, maybe they can!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 08:30:00" d="2020-06-08 08:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 08:45:00" d="2020-06-08 09:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple and Onion want to become this week's &quot;Most Fun People&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 09:00:00" d="2020-06-08 09:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 09:31:00" d="2020-06-08 10:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 10:00:00" d="2020-06-08 11:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Thinking it's a way to reconnect with her father Raven enters a beauty pageant. / The Titans must find a way to keep all the Jump City residents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 11:00:00" d="2020-06-08 12:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball and Darwin give Bobert specific instructions to ensure he acts in a safe and responsible manner. / Rocky is trying to find love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 12:00:00" d="2020-06-08 13:00:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Boredom levels in the castle hit dangerously high levels. / Hawkodile admits his love for Dr. Fox. / Hawkodile finds some defenseless chipmunks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 13:00:00" d="2020-06-08 14:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple needs to be tall so that he can be in love. / Apple and Onion must face their fears while trapped in a pet shop, so they can save French</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 14:00:00" d="2020-06-08 15:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>When Gumball and Darwin accidentally find a sinister secret manifesto on Alan's memory stick, they decide they have to foil his plan for total world domination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 15:00:00" d="2020-06-08 16:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>When her teammates turns evil it's up to Lady Legasus to stop the League of Legs. / The Titans start speaking Pig Latin to prevent Robin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 16:00:00" d="2020-06-08 16:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Darwin likes a girl in his class so Gumball decides it’s time to play cupid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 16:15:00" d="2020-06-08 16:30:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple and Onion go on a guided bus tour as part of their plan to get Apple's shoe back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 16:30:00" d="2020-06-08 16:45:00"><n>Ninjago</n>    <k>67% Akita tells the story of the &quot;Choosing&quot; and how she, and her twin brother, Kataru, went into the wilds to discover their animal forms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 16:45:00" d="2020-06-08 17:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 17:00:00" d="2020-06-08 17:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O &quot;accidentally&quot; releases a whole space prison-full of space criminals and winds up on the wrong side of the law. On the right side</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 17:15:00" d="2020-06-08 17:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Unikitty and gang have ordered some delicious Thai food for dinner. Unfortunately the wait for the delivery is proving too much, time itself seems to have slowed down</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 17:30:00" d="2020-06-08 17:45:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Mao Mao faces off with Badgerclops in a competition to determine whether cooking (and being a hero) is an art or a science</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 17:45:00" d="2020-06-08 18:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>To impress Lucy, Panda offers to babysit her brother, Clifford. But Clifford turns out to be too high maintenance for Panda to handle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 18:00:00" d="2020-06-08 18:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 18:31:00" d="2020-06-08 19:00:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>Apple needs to be tall so that he can be in love. / Apple and Onion spend a day in Falafel's shoes and use their positive attitude to prove he shouldn't be so grumpy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 19:00:00" d="2020-06-08 19:31:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life's like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 19:31:00" d="2020-06-08 19:45:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>A crying unicorn appears at the Cats' Lair and weepily tells the ThunderCats that all of her unicorn friends have been captured!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 19:45:00" d="2020-06-08 20:00:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Unikitty comes to the conclusion that everyone would be a lot happier if they would just think the way she does, and with Dr. Fox's help, maybe they can!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 20:00:00" d="2020-06-08 20:15:00"><n>New: Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>Vic and Val accidentally set off a time loop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 20:15:00" d="2020-06-08 20:30:00"><n>New: Cloudy with a Chance of Meatballs</n>    <k>In a sardine-obsessed town, Flint Lockwood is a teenager trying to change the world. ne invention at a time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 20:30:00" d="2020-06-08 20:45:00"><n>Teen Titans Go!</n>    <k>Teen Titans Go takes a comedic look at the superheroes' lives. Viewers will finally get the opportunity to watch what life is like for the super teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 20:45:00" d="2020-06-08 21:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Mao Mao tries to hide his love of cobbler</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 21:00:00" d="2020-06-08 21:15:00"><n>Apple &amp; Onion</n>    <k>62% Apple and Onion spend a day in Falafel's shoes and use their positive attitude to prove he shouldn't be so grumpy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 21:15:00" d="2020-06-08 21:31:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Vultureman has got a brand new invention but there's one big problem: he stole the idea from Panthro! Oh, also Vultureman is using his invention to take over Third Earth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 21:31:00" d="2020-06-08 22:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Nicole arranges a playdate for Anais with the son of a classy lady she met at the supermarket. / Darwin joins the school marching band, and his tin-whistle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 22:00:00" d="2020-06-08 23:00:00"><n>Regular Show</n>    <k>Mordecai and Rigby must compete against Garrett Bobby Ferguson - #1 in the universe / “The Hammer” gets unleashed into the real world and everybody needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-08 23:00:00" d="2020-06-09 00:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball teaches Darwin a lesson after Darwin leaves him. / Granny JoJo's overprotective behavior puts the Wattersons in danger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-09 00:00:00" d="2020-06-09 01:00:00"><n>Adventure Time</n>    <k>Finn has a toothache, so he has to go to the dentist. / It’s Super Porp Day. / Jake's son T.V. discovers a mysterious diary in the dried-up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-09 01:00:00" d="2020-06-09 02:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Meet the Wattersons: Mum, Dad, Anais, Darwin and of course Gumball… the 12-year-old cat with a flair for misadventure!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-09 02:30:00" d="2020-06-09 03:05:00"><n>Steven Universe</n>    <k>Steven Universe is a half-human, half-Gem hero who's learning to save the world along with the Crystal Gems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-09 03:05:00" d="2020-06-09 03:40:00"><n>Uncle Grandpa</n>    <k>He’s everyone in the world’s magical Uncle and Grandpa! GOOD MORNING!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1130" o="2020-06-09 03:40:00" d="2020-06-09 05:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball</n>    <k>Gumball teaches Darwin a lesson after Darwin leaves him. / Gumball asks Idaho to teach his family to live a simpler life. / Bobert loses a bet to Gumball</k>  </p>
</a>
