<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2021-07-09 07:26:29"><p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 05:37:00" d="2021-07-15 07:00:00"><n>Kessel, Byrd, Ellis - The North Sea Jazz</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 1982, legendary American guitarists Barney Kessel, Herb Ellis, and Charlie Byrd gave an unforgettable performance at the North Sea Jazz Festival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 07:00:00" d="2021-07-15 08:11:00"><n>Sarah Vaughan Live in '58 &amp; 64: The Divine One</n><t>M</t>    <k>This concert features the Divine One in her prime, wrapping her sultry voice around jazz standards such as Lover Man. Performances like these demonstrate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 08:11:00" d="2021-07-15 09:10:00"><n>Tel Aviv Sessions: Omri Mor</n><t>M</t>    <k>With his passion and his virtuosity, pianist Omri Mor amazes the audience of the music club Zappa in Tel Aviv. Pieces drawn from the heritage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 09:10:00" d="2021-07-15 10:00:00"><n>Dionne Warwick live at the 27 Club</n><t>M</t>    <k>Dionne Warwick's vocal artistry ranges from voluminous deep register to soft, fragile high notes. She masters the entire range with almost unnerving ease</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 10:00:00" d="2021-07-15 10:43:00"><n>John Coltrane: Live in Comblain-la-Tour</n><t>M</t>    <k>This broadcast of John Coltrane's 1965 performance at the short-lived Belgian jazz festival in Comblain-la-Tour features Trane's classic quartet with Elvin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 10:43:00" d="2021-07-15 12:24:00"><n>Aki Rissanen Trio at Jazzclub Unterfahrt, Munich</n><t>M</t>    <k>Live from 'Jazzclub Unterfahrt' in Munich, Germany, Finnish pianist Aki Rissanen performs his original compositions. Together with Antti Lotjonen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 12:24:00" d="2021-07-15 14:02:00"><n>Jacques Kuba Séguin: Litania Projekt</n><t>M</t>    <k>The experience of Jacques Kuba Séguin's 'Litania Projekt' seems to stop time for an instant. Together with his expressive Montreal musicians, Jacques</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 14:02:00" d="2021-07-15 14:54:00"><n u="Cannonball Adderley Brotherhood: Brussels">Cannonball Adderley Brotherhood: Brussels, 1980</n><t>M</t>    <k>Leading a group of alumni under the Cannonball Adderley Brotherhood name, the late saxophonist's younger brother, Nat Adderley, revives his classic 'Work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 14:54:00" d="2021-07-15 15:44:00"><n u="North Sea Jazz Cruise Episode">North Sea Jazz Cruise Episode 2</n><t>M</t>    <k>MS Rotterdam turns into the world's largest jazz club for a cruise that arrives in Rotterdam on the opening night of the prestigious North</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 15:44:00" d="2021-07-15 16:42:00"><n>Richard Bona - Jazz a Vienne</n><t>M</t>    <k>The wonderful Richard Bona conquered the world with his bass and his voice a long time ago. On 'Jazz a Vienne' stage Bona once again shows why audiences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 16:42:00" d="2021-07-15 18:22:00"><n>Jazzed Out London</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jazzed Out proves that a jazz session can take place anywhere. In this episode, London serves as a backdrop for sets by saxophonist Soweto Kinch, and pianist Neil Cowley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 18:22:00" d="2021-07-15 19:06:00"><n>Sarah McCoy - La Gaite Lyrique</n><t>M</t>    <k>Vocalist and pianist Sarah McCoy carries on a tradition perfected by Tom Waits, Amy Winehouse, Leon Russell, and Nina Simone, who turned the wreckage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 19:06:00" d="2021-07-15 19:43:00"><n>Jazz de Matosinhos and Sinfónica do Porto: Layas</n><t>M</t>    <k>30 minutes of. Orquestra Jazz de Matosinhos and Orquestra Sinfónica do Porto Casa da Música with Dirk Brossé (musical direction), Jason Moran (piano) and J.A</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 19:43:00" d="2021-07-15 20:05:00"><n>Sabrina Starke - InJazz 2019</n><t>M</t>    <k>Self-made award-winning singer-songwriter, producer and self-empowerment ambassador Sabrina Starke has won an impressive number of prestigious awards</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 20:05:00" d="2021-07-15 21:00:00"><n>Seine Sessions: Legendary Jazz</n><t>M</t>    <k>Entitled &quot;Legendary Jazz&quot;, this episode of the Seine Sessions hosted by Eddy King presents unique performances, and interviews with Steve McCraven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 21:00:00" d="2021-07-15 22:07:00"><n>Sven Hammond Soul: Tivoli de Helling</n><t>M</t>    <k>Although its music might sound like the soundtrack of any 1970s American car chase movie, the band Sven Hammond Soul is from the Netherlands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 22:07:00" d="2021-07-15 23:00:00"><n u="Ramón Valle &amp; Reinier Baas - Music Meeting">Ramón Valle &amp; Reinier Baas - Music Meeting 2020</n><t>M</t>    <k>Music Meeting 2020 presents this exclusive concert by pianist Ramón Valle and guitarist Reinier Baas, filmed at Concertgebouw De Vereeniging in Nijmegen, The Netherlands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 23:00:00" d="2021-07-16 00:00:00"><n>PC Qwintett: 75th birthday Pierre Courbois</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 00:00:00" d="2021-07-16 00:34:00"><n>Frank Paavo Quintet - JazzConnect, Westbroek</n><t>M</t>    <k>The saxophonist Frank Paavo has been active on the Amsterdam and Netherland's jazz scene since the early 1980s. His music is inspired by the hard-bop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 00:34:00" d="2021-07-16 01:47:00"><n>Jazz en Baie: Mayfair Electro Jazz Project</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Mayfair Electro Jazz Project at the Jazz en Baie Festival: an inspiring combination of well-known jazz instruments, electronic elements, vibrant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 01:47:00" d="2021-07-16 02:32:00"><n u="Jimmy Witherspoon Quartet &amp; Rozaa Wortham">Jimmy Witherspoon Quartet &amp; Rozaa Wortham 1985</n><t>M</t>    <k>Estival offers a thrilling and particularly surprising line-up that explores the rich world of contemporary music. Jimmy Witherspoon, known</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 02:32:00" d="2021-07-16 03:03:00"><n>TorTube: Dual City Concert Band ft. Hermine Deurlo</n><t>M</t>    <k>Foot Together is a TorTube episode featuring Dutch jazz icon Hermine Deurloo on the chromatic harmonica, in collaboration with the Dual City Concert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 03:03:00" d="2021-07-16 04:34:00"><n>Seun Kuti &amp; Egypt 80' - Cabaret Sauvage</n><t>M</t>    <k>Seun Anikulapo Kuti possesses the grace, energy and fury of his father, the legendary artist Fela Kuti. With the musicians of Fela Kuti's legendary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 04:34:00" d="2021-07-16 04:57:00"><n>Ramon Chicharron - Destination Nuits d'Afrique</n><t>M</t>    <k>Columbia-born multi-instrumentalist Ramon Chicharron left his country at age 19 to find his musical path. Today he expresses his roots via fusing sounds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 04:57:00" d="2021-07-16 05:28:00"><n>P. Damasiewicz &amp; Power of the Horns - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Power of Horns is a free jazz ensemble, created in 2007, and led by the multi-instrumentalist, composer Piotr Damasiewicz. Performing highly energetic</k>  </p>
</a>
