<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2020-06-01 04:36:03"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-08 07:00:00" d="2020-06-08 08:14:00"><n>Thomas Carbou: Spectacle Au Bleury</n><t>M</t>    <k>Thomas Carbou and Patrick Graham share an almost telepathic rapport, blending spontaneous improvisation, electronic looping, and Brazilian and Indian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-08 08:14:00" d="2020-06-08 09:23:00"><n>Chamber music: Sissoko &amp; Segal</n><t>M</t>    <k>The concert shows a brilliant interplay between the two musicians and combines the several worlds of jazz, Malian, and classical music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-08 09:23:00" d="2020-06-08 10:02:00"><n>The Hammond© Sessions: Sven Figee</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-08 10:02:00" d="2020-06-08 12:07:00"><n>Live at The Hordern Pavilion</n><t>M</t>    <k>Big hits, booty dancing, stage dives, fan freestyles, A$AP Rocky's debut Down Under tour had it all! At his sold-out Sydney show, hip hop's hottest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-08 12:07:00" d="2020-06-08 12:45:00"><n>Smooth Series at NSJ: George Benson &amp; Kenny G</n><t>M</t>    <k>This broadcast from the North Sea Jazz Archives presents a compilation with music of George Benson &amp; Kenny G</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-08 12:45:00" d="2020-06-08 14:02:00"><n>Africa Live! The Concerts: Tiken Jah Fakoly</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-08 14:02:00" d="2020-06-08 15:05:00"><n>The Flying Pickets - Don't Turn Around</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Flying Pickets are a British a cappella vocal group that was formed in 1982, transferring the art of a cappella to the pop music scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-08 15:05:00" d="2020-06-08 16:00:00"><n>Altin Gün - BIRD, Rotterdam</n><t>M</t>    <k>During their 2018 show at BIRD Rotterdam, Altin Gün released their new album &quot;On.&quot; Enjoy a new interpretation of Turkish traditional music, with a unique</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-08 16:00:00" d="2020-06-08 17:40:00"><n>Laurent Coulondre &quot;Gravity Zero&quot; - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>Laurent Coulondre is the rising star of the French jazz scene! His music explores jazz, funk, fusion, progressive rock and hardbop, resulting in groovy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-08 17:40:00" d="2020-06-08 18:08:00"><n>Paradox Live: Bertus Borgers &amp; The Young Retro's</n><t>M</t>    <k>PARADOX Tilburg is the most intimate jazz club in the Netherlands, with a devoted audience from all across Europe. This episode of PARADOX LIVE presents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-08 18:08:00" d="2020-06-08 19:07:00"><n>Lionel Hampton and his Orchestra at the Opera</n><t>M</t>    <k>Lionel Hampton was not the first jazz musician to take up the vibraphone, but he was the first to give the instrument an identity in jazz, applying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-08 19:07:00" d="2020-06-08 20:00:00"><n>Emilia Martensson - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>London based Emilia Martensson won the 'Vocalist of the Year-2016' award at The Parliamentary Jazz Awards. Heavily inspired by her native southern Swedish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-08 20:00:00" d="2020-06-08 21:00:00"><n>TorTube: Robin Nolan Trio - Swing de Paris</n><t>M</t>    <k>This recording features Dutch jazz icon Benjamin Herman in collaboration with English brothers and gypsy guitar masters Robin and Kevin Nolan along</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-08 21:00:00" d="2020-06-08 22:24:00"><n>Jazz en Baie: Mayfair Electro Jazz Project</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Mayfair Electro Jazz Project at the Jazz en Baie Festival: an inspiring combination of well-known jazz instruments, electronic elements, vibrant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-08 22:24:00" d="2020-06-09 00:00:00"><n>Piano and Sax: Charlie Mariano &amp; Wolfgang Dauner</n><t>M</t>    <k>Piano and saxophone - this is an individualistic jazz duo combination. But the melodiousness and maturity of Charlie Mariano's saxophone and the freshness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-09 00:00:00" d="2020-06-09 00:47:00"><n>The Morgenland Festival: A Trace of Grace</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode entitled &quot;A Trace Of Grace&quot; features the rich and complex music of Michel Godard and Kayhan Kalhor, two musicians interested in instruments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-09 00:47:00" d="2020-06-09 02:31:00"><n>James Taylor Quartet - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>Acid jazz pioneer James Taylor is a talented Hammond B3 organ player. Throughout the years, his James Taylor Quartet has developed a unique sound in which</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-09 02:31:00" d="2020-06-09 03:21:00"><n u="Michel Legrand Orchestra at Spa">Michel Legrand Orchestra at Spa, 1982</n><t>M</t>    <k>Michel Legrand and his orchestra perform a number of his beloved soundtrack compositions, &quot;The Summer Knows,&quot; &quot;What Are You Doing the Rest of Your Life?&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-09 03:21:00" d="2020-06-09 05:26:00"><n>Django Memories</n><t>M</t>    <k>To celebrate the release of Django, the Parisian New Morning Club pays tribute to the legendary guitarist Django Reinhardt and showcases the virtuosity</k>  </p>
</a>
