<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-04-14 04:34:00"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-21 06:07:00" d="2020-04-21 07:00:00"><n>The Definitive Collection: Louis Armstrong</n><t>M</t>    <k>Decades after his death, Louis Armstrong's historical recordings are still unique and widely appreciated. Born in August 1901, Louis Daniel Armstrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-21 07:00:00" d="2020-04-21 08:05:00"><n u="Charlie Byrd Trio">Charlie Byrd Trio 2</n><t>M</t>    <k>Charlie Byrd, the man who popularized Brazilian music all over the world with his Stan Getz collaboration Jazz Samba in 1962, plays an intimate New Orleans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-21 08:05:00" d="2020-04-21 09:23:00"><n>Terrasson &amp; Belmondo: A Nous Garo</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-21 09:23:00" d="2020-04-21 10:04:00"><n>Portrait of Maria Ana Bobone</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-21 10:04:00" d="2020-04-21 11:14:00"><n>Martin Goyette - Spectacle Astral 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>A veteran bluesman that can hold his head high next to our neighbors to the south, Martin Goyette made his bones with an undeniable and incredible voice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-21 11:14:00" d="2020-04-21 12:07:00"><n>Keita, Tinariwen Maal &amp; Sangare: Africa Live!</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-21 12:07:00" d="2020-04-21 14:02:00"><n>Jazzed Out Paris</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jazzed Out shows that each and every imaginable spot is a suitable location for a jazz session. In this episode, Paris serves as a backdrop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-21 14:02:00" d="2020-04-21 14:50:00"><n>Conservatory Concert Big Band</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-21 14:50:00" d="2020-04-21 15:29:00"><n>JV's Boogaloo Squad - Squad Goals</n><t>M</t>    <k>JV's Boogaloo Squad has truly crafted a unique and soulful sound that is both thrilling on impact and deeply evocative of timeless musical nostalgia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-21 15:29:00" d="2020-04-21 15:59:00"><n>Keita, Broennimann, Niggli - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Aly Keita, Jan Galega Broennimann and Lucas Niggli, all come from Africa. Their music reflects their passion for the homeland while incorporating various</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-21 15:59:00" d="2020-04-21 16:29:00"><n>Scott McLemore - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>With numerous years of experience in the jazz mecca, New York City, American drummer Scott McLemore is now based in Iceland, where he is part of a thriving local jazz scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-21 16:29:00" d="2020-04-21 17:40:00"><n>Belgium Sessions: Ben Sluijs</n><t>M</t>    <k>Saxophonist Ben Sluijs received a classical training. He has a strong melodic and harmonic approach to music. His music offers no room for showing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-21 17:40:00" d="2020-04-21 20:00:00"><n>Electro Deluxe au Trianon</n><t>M</t>    <k>Composed of 13 talented musicians, the Electro Deluxe ensemble offers a unique combination of jazz, funk, electronic music, and rap. Their Welcome</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-21 20:00:00" d="2020-04-21 21:00:00"><n>Morgenland Festival: One Way Ticket to Damascus</n><t>M</t>    <k>Bursting with sounds that could only be described as magical, &quot;MCO&quot; features the Syrian Expat Philharmonic Orchestra under conductor Naci Özgüç</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-21 21:00:00" d="2020-04-21 21:58:00"><n>A Barrel of Laughs</n><t>M</t>    <k>The documentary (2012) 'A Barrel of Laughs: 25 years of Tambours du Bronx' shows us the long road to success of the band 'Tambours du Bronx'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-21 21:58:00" d="2020-04-21 23:07:00"><n>Chamber music: Sissoko &amp; Segal</n><t>M</t>    <k>The concert shows a brilliant interplay between the two musicians and combines the several worlds of jazz, Malian, and classical music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-21 23:07:00" d="2020-04-22 00:00:00"><n>Comblain-la-Tour Jazz Festival: Jimmy McGriff Trio</n><t>M</t>    <k>Of the major soul-jazz pioneers, Hammond B3 organ player Jimmy McGriff (1936-2008) was the bluesiest and often insisted that he was more of a blues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 00:00:00" d="2020-04-22 00:46:00"><n>Moonlight Benjamin - WOMEX 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Moonlight Benjamin, performs a riff-heavy, groove-laden sonic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 00:46:00" d="2020-04-22 01:36:00"><n>Sazz Leonore sings Michael Bublé</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 01:36:00" d="2020-04-22 02:40:00"><n u="The Crusaders: Estival Lugano">The Crusaders: Estival Lugano 1987</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Crusaders, an American jazz fusion group that was popular in the '70s. Their performance at Estival is beyond soulful and an amazing show to watch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 02:40:00" d="2020-04-22 03:08:00"><n>Une Soirée de Poche: Nils Frahm</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this episode, the Berlin musician and composer Nils Frahm showcases his incredible piano dexterity. Frahm is known for his minimalist and experimental</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 03:08:00" d="2020-04-22 03:41:00"><n>Marion Williams Sings Spirituals</n><t>M</t>    <k>You can't help but be carried away by the powerful voice Marion Williams, who, with backing from her group and backup singers, sings gospel songs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 03:41:00" d="2020-04-22 05:21:00"><n>Aki Rissanen Trio at Jazzclub Unterfahrt, Munich</n><t>M</t>    <k>Live from 'Jazzclub Unterfahrt' in Munich, Germany, Finnish pianist Aki Rissanen performs his original compositions. Together with Antti Lotjonen</k>  </p>
</a>
