<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-05-14 05:00:09"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-21 07:00:00" d="2020-05-21 08:21:00"><n>Terrasson &amp; Belmondo: A Nous Garo</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-21 08:21:00" d="2020-05-21 09:20:00"><n u="Charlie Byrd Trio">Charlie Byrd Trio 2</n><t>M</t>    <k>Charlie Byrd, the man who popularized Brazilian music all over the world with his Stan Getz collaboration Jazz Samba in 1962, plays an intimate New Orleans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-21 09:20:00" d="2020-05-21 10:03:00"><n>Quincy Jones: 'Q' conducting his 'Dream Band'</n><t>M</t>    <k>'Jazz Icons: Quincy Jones' spotlights a young 'Q' conducting his 'dream band'—an 18-piece orchestra of world-renowned players such as Clark Terry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-21 10:03:00" d="2020-05-21 10:38:00"><n>McCoy Tyner Trio live at Estival Lugano</n><t>M</t>    <k>McCoy Tyner is considered one of the most influential jazz pianists of the 20th century, an honour he earned both with Coltrane and in his years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-21 10:38:00" d="2020-05-21 12:30:00"><n>Remember Häns'che Weiss - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>French guitar virtuoso Biréli Lagrene pays tribute to one of the most prominent exponents of gipsy jazz: German guitarist Häns'che Weiss (1951-2016)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-21 12:30:00" d="2020-05-21 14:01:00"><n>Tel Aviv Sessions: Yaron Herman and Avishai Cohen</n><t>M</t>    <k>For this session in Jerusalem's Yellow Submarine, pianist Yaron Herman invited trumpeter Avishai Cohen. Both musicians are considered among the very finest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-21 14:01:00" d="2020-05-21 14:48:00"><n>Belgium Sessions: Trio Florizoone - Massot</n><t>M</t>    <k>The trio Massot/Florizoone/Horbaczewski pushes the boundaries of jazz, folk and classical music. When improvising, the trio produces the weirdest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-21 14:48:00" d="2020-05-21 15:45:00"><n u="North Sea Jazz Cruise Episode">North Sea Jazz Cruise Episode 1</n><t>M</t>    <k>MS Rotterdam turns into the world's largest jazz club for a cruise that arrives in Rotterdam on the opening night of the prestigious North</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-21 15:45:00" d="2020-05-21 16:35:00"><n>House of the Gipsies - Sing Jazz 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>House of the Gipsies is bringing back the raw rhythms of nomadic tribes in Rajasthan to create a unique sound that can be described as Indo-Gypsy fusion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-21 16:35:00" d="2020-05-21 17:52:00"><n>Jazzed Out Berlin</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jazzed Out proves that a jazz session can take place anywhere. In this episode, Berlin serves as a backdrop for pianist Wolfert Brederode, and Hyperactive Kid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-21 17:52:00" d="2020-05-21 18:53:00"><n>Terry Callier: Live in Berlin</n><t>M</t>    <k>Terry Callier, the man who has written music history in the 1960s and 1970s, returns to the stage after a 15 year break</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-21 18:53:00" d="2020-05-21 20:01:00"><n>Paradox Live: Carte Blanche of Sanne Rambags</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of PARADOX LIVE presents the talented Dutch jazz singer Sanne Rambags accompanied by Jeroen van Vliet (piano) and Vincent Courtois (cello)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-21 20:01:00" d="2020-05-21 21:00:00"><n>Seine Sessions: Avant Garde</n><t>M</t>    <k>Entitled &quot;Avant-garde&quot;, this episode of the Seine Sessions hosted by Eddy King presents unique performances, and interviews with the Rodolphe Lauretta</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-21 21:00:00" d="2020-05-21 22:07:00"><n>Sven Hammond Soul: Tivoli de Helling</n><t>M</t>    <k>Although its music might sound like the soundtrack of any 1970s American car chase movie, the band Sven Hammond Soul is from the Netherlands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-21 22:07:00" d="2020-05-21 23:03:00"><n>Motor Music Jazz - Charles Gayle Trio</n><t>M</t>    <k>Born in the United States, Charles Gayle came to prominence in the 1990s. Gayle mostly plays free jazz on the saxophone, his main instrument, but he knows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-21 23:03:00" d="2020-05-22 00:00:00"><n>The Hammond© Sessions: Lachy Doley Group</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-22 00:00:00" d="2020-05-22 01:23:00"><n>Emile Parisien - Jazz a Vienne 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Saxophonist Emile Parisien and accordionist Vincent Peirani present their tribute to Austrian jazz keyboardist Joe Zawinul. Having played</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-22 01:23:00" d="2020-05-22 02:14:00"><n>The Mel Lewis Orchestra live at Estival Lugano</n><t>M</t>    <k>Estival offers a thrilling and particularly surprising line-up that explores the rich world of contemporary music. The Mel Lewis Orchestra was arguably</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-22 02:14:00" d="2020-05-22 02:52:00"><n>TorTube: Josee Koning - Who's The Bossa</n><t>M</t>    <k>Who's the Bossa? is a TorTube episode featuring Dutch jazz singer Josee Koning, the leading Brazilian musician in the Netherlands. Inspired by the music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-22 02:52:00" d="2020-05-22 04:43:00"><n>Bantu Jazz: Frédéric Gassita &amp; Friends</n><t>M</t>    <k>Pianist Frédéric Gassita studied classical music and jazz, the latter at the famed Berklee College of Music. Today he's a figurehead of jazz in Gabon, Africa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-22 04:43:00" d="2020-05-22 05:07:00"><n>Ramon Chicharron - Destination Nuits d'Afrique</n><t>M</t>    <k>Columbia-born multi-instrumentalist Ramon Chicharron left his country at age 19 to find his musical path. Today he expresses his roots via fusing sounds</k>  </p>
</a>
