<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2021-07-09 07:26:38"><p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 05:28:00" d="2021-07-16 06:08:00"><n>Freedoms Trio - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Freedoms Trio is an international project consisting of Norwegian Steinar Aadnekvam, Brazilian Rubem Farias, and Deodato Siquir from Mozambique</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 06:08:00" d="2021-07-16 07:00:00"><n>Paradox Live: Fay Claassen</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 07:00:00" d="2021-07-16 07:44:00"><n>Dion with Henri Segers and his orchestra</n><t>M</t>    <k>One of the most popular American rock &amp; roll performers of the days before the Beatles, Dion's music spans everything from doo-wop, rock and R&amp;B to straight blues. (1963)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 07:44:00" d="2021-07-16 09:02:00"><n>Terrasson &amp; Belmondo: A Nous Garo</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 09:02:00" d="2021-07-16 10:00:00"><n>The Sound of New York - Mark Turner</n><t>M</t>    <k>Mark Turner has developed a distinctive and highly personal style. His demanding compositional approach, his sharp improvisational skills and his great</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 10:00:00" d="2021-07-16 11:07:00"><n>Non Stop Travels: The Story of Michel Petrucciani</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 11:07:00" d="2021-07-16 11:39:00"><n>Summer Night Music - Love Conquers All</n><t>M</t>    <k>In Summer Night Music - Love Songs, artists from all over the world contribute their favourite love songs to an unusual and exciting event uniting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 11:39:00" d="2021-07-16 14:00:00"><n>Frédéric Gassita &amp; Les Solistes Francais</n><t>M</t>    <k>Frédéric Gassita's biggest influences are Ravel and Debussy, Chick Corea, and Herbie Hancock – whom he met as a student in Boston. His work combines</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 14:00:00" d="2021-07-16 15:04:00"><n>Michiel Borstlap: Blue, Reflective &amp; Frames</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 15:04:00" d="2021-07-16 16:12:00"><n>Long Tall Dex live at North Sea Jazz</n><t>M</t>    <k>This broadcast from the North Sea Jazz Archives presents the legendary saxophone player Dexter Gordon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 16:12:00" d="2021-07-16 17:21:00"><n>Episode 5: Chet Baker - Jazz Greats</n><t>M</t>    <k>American trumpet player Chet Baker was a popular champion of cool jazz. On May 2, 1964, he joined the Jacques Pelzer Quartet in Brussels. On September</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 17:21:00" d="2021-07-16 19:18:00"><n>Sven Hammond: 10th Year Anniversary Concert</n><t>M</t>    <k>The band Sven Hammond used to be known as Sven Hammond Soul. This time they celebrate their &quot;10-Year Party&quot;, and a funky show is guaranteed!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 19:18:00" d="2021-07-16 20:04:00"><n>BIRDtv: Bill Laurance Project</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of 'BIRD.tv' features the Snarky Puppys pianist: Bill Laurence! (2014)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 20:04:00" d="2021-07-16 21:00:00"><n>Paradox Live: James Brandon Lewis</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of PARADOX LIVE presents the American saxophone player James Brandon Lewis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 21:00:00" d="2021-07-16 22:35:00"><n>Incognito - Sing Jazz 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>Incognito is an acid jazz project formed by Jean-Paul &quot;Bluey&quot; Maunick and Paul &quot;Tubbs&quot; Williams, original members of the disco-funk Light of the World</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-16 22:35:00" d="2021-07-17 00:00:00"><n>Nubiyan Twist - Music Meeting</n><t>M</t>    <k>Nubiyan Twist, a London-based band that operates on the intersection of soul and jazz, performs at the International Music Meeting Festival 2019</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 00:00:00" d="2021-07-17 01:05:00"><n>Give Back: A Hip Hop Story</n><t>M</t>    <k>The documentary 'Give Back' is about the rise of artists who, alongside their stage life, wanted to develop an activity that would allow them to share</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 01:05:00" d="2021-07-17 01:51:00"><n>Linda May Han Oh - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Linda May Han Oh brings her quartet to jazzahead! 2019. This highly sought-after double bassist from Australia is also a productive composer, composing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 01:51:00" d="2021-07-17 02:24:00"><n>Gard Nilssen's Acoustic Unity - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Gard Nilssen's Acoustic Unity consists of drummer Gard Nilssen, saxophonist André Roligheten and bassist Ole Morten Vagan. The group's leader</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 02:24:00" d="2021-07-17 03:21:00"><n>The MotorMusic Jazz Sessions: Hoera</n><t>M</t>    <k>This MotorMusic Jazz Sessions episode features the Belgian musicians of Hoera who love to create, produce, and present original work and concepts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 03:21:00" d="2021-07-17 04:26:00"><n>Tribute to Elis Regina - Da Pá Virada Sessions</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Da Pá Virada Sessions series presents the best musicians of contemporary Brazilian music. Vocalist Vanessa Moreno, bassist Fi Marostica, keyboardist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 04:26:00" d="2021-07-17 05:28:00"><n>Hypnotic Brass Ensemble - Jazzwoche Burghausen</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Hypnotic Brass Ensembe consists of eight sons of jazz trumpeter and one-time Sun Ra Arkestra member Phil Cohran. The ensemble's music ranges</k>  </p>
</a>
