<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2021-07-10 05:04:32"><p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 05:28:00" d="2021-07-17 07:00:00"><n>Mister Joe Williams and the Basie Alumni Band</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Count Basie Alumni Band is joined by Joe Williams for a bluesy performance at the Brussels Jazz Club in 1980</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 07:00:00" d="2021-07-17 08:36:00"><n>Fred Hersch Trio - Jazz a Ramatuelle</n><t>M</t>    <k>At the age of 63, Fred Hersch is unquestionably one of today's key figures in jazz piano. Supported by John Hebert (double bass) and Eric McPherson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 08:36:00" d="2021-07-17 09:07:00"><n>Face au Public: Odetta</n><t>M</t>    <k>Legendary African-American folk singer Odetta (1930-2008) sang her spirituals with immeasurable sorrow and anguish. Her spiritual music expresses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 09:07:00" d="2021-07-17 10:00:00"><n u="Rahsaan Roland Kirk Live in">Rahsaan Roland Kirk Live in 1964</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rahsaan Roland Kirk: Live in '64 presents an astounding concert by this musical superhero playing his entire instrumental arsenal of saxophone, flute</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 10:00:00" d="2021-07-17 11:12:00"><n>Eartha Kitt: The Most Exciting Woman in the World</n><t>M</t>    <k>Fall in love with Eartha Kitt, powerhouse queen of blues and jazz with international flair. You'll be swooned by her devotion on stage, her throaty purr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 11:12:00" d="2021-07-17 11:57:00"><n>Aca Seca Trio - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Aca Seca Trio comes from Argentina. Yet, the trio has managed to distance themselves from Argentina's cultural treasure, tango. Performing different</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 11:57:00" d="2021-07-17 12:27:00"><n>Scott McLemore - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>With numerous years of experience in the jazz mecca, New York City, American drummer Scott McLemore is now based in Iceland, where he is part of a thriving local jazz scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 12:27:00" d="2021-07-17 14:01:00"><n>Majamisty TriO - Piano City Festival</n><t>M</t>    <k>Majamisty TriO, an ensemble from Novi Sad in Serbia, explores the space between jazz and classical music, occasionally expanding the possibilities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 14:01:00" d="2021-07-17 15:09:00"><n>Elliot Galvin Trio - November Music</n><t>M</t>    <k>The pianist Elliot Galvin is a member of the young UK jazz group Dinosaur. Performing with his own trio, the gifted musician has been compared to Django</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 15:09:00" d="2021-07-17 15:25:00"><n>BIRDtv: Shayna Steele</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 15:25:00" d="2021-07-17 15:56:00"><n>Seine Sessions: World Music</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of Seine Sessions 'World Music', presented by Eddy King, shows unique performances and interviews of among Teófilo Chantre, Tiwitine and Kinsy Ray</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 15:56:00" d="2021-07-17 16:54:00"><n>Salif Keita &amp; Les Ambassadeurs</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Golden Voice of Africa aka Salif Keita's music is a rich blend of traditional Malian music with European and American influences. Discover the various</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 16:54:00" d="2021-07-17 17:50:00"><n>Altin Gün - BIRD, Rotterdam</n><t>M</t>    <k>During their 2018 show at BIRD Rotterdam, Altin Gün released their new album &quot;On.&quot; Enjoy a new interpretation of Turkish traditional music, with a unique</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 17:50:00" d="2021-07-17 19:12:00"><n>Mizikopéyi Creole Big Band - Tropiques Atrium</n><t>M</t>    <k>Singer Tony Chasseur and pianist Thierry Vaton created the French big band MizikOpéyi in 2006. MizikOpéyi offers a mix of traditional and popular Caribbean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 19:12:00" d="2021-07-17 20:04:00"><n>The Brothers Four: Live in Comblain-la-Tour</n><t>M</t>    <k>Pioneering folk/pop quartet The Brothers Four was formed in 1957 by University of Washington fraternity brothers Bob Flick (upright bass, vocals)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 20:04:00" d="2021-07-17 21:00:00"><n u="Sarah Vaughan: Jazz from Newport, Brussels">Sarah Vaughan: Jazz from Newport, Brussels 1973</n><t>M</t>    <k>For the first of two appearances at the 1973 Jazz from Newport Festival in Brussels, Sarah Vaughan and her trio consisting of Carl Schroeder (piano)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 21:00:00" d="2021-07-17 21:20:00"><n u="Burton Greene - OTO Part">Burton Greene - OTO Part I</n><t>M</t>    <k>Legendary free jazz pianist Burton Greene rose to fame in New York City's free jazz scene of the 1960s. Exploring various spontaneous improvisational</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 21:20:00" d="2021-07-17 22:29:00"><n>Münchner Klaviersommer: Eliane Elias Trio</n><t>M</t>    <k>Eliane Elias's Brazilian samba roots and sensuous, alluring voice are a perfect match for her impressive instrumental bebop, jazz, and classical skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-17 22:29:00" d="2021-07-18 00:00:00"><n>The Morgenland Festival: Blossom</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Morgenland Chamber Orchestra has been an integral part of the Morgenland Festival since 2009. This ensemble of musicians from Germany and various guest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 00:00:00" d="2021-07-18 00:53:00"><n>Bakolo Music International - WOMEX 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Bakolo Music International, represents the pioneers of the golden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 00:53:00" d="2021-07-18 01:25:00"><n>Shinya Fukumori Trio - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Shinya Fukumori Trio performs music inspired by the Showa era of Japan fused with European aesthetics. Led by Munich-based Japanese drummer Shinya</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 01:25:00" d="2021-07-18 01:59:00"><n>Hedvig Mollestad Trio - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Hedvig Mollestad's Trio is an explosive and expansive trio that has gone from strength to strength, sharing big stages with the likes of John McLaughlin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 01:59:00" d="2021-07-18 03:31:00"><n>Jazzed Out New York City</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jazzed Out shows that each and every imaginable spot is a suitable location for a jazz session. In this episode, New York serves as a backdrop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 03:31:00" d="2021-07-18 04:18:00"><n>Winter 1980: Maynard Ferguson Big Band in Brussels</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Maynard Ferguson Big Band's Winter Tour of 1980 included a stop at the Brussels Jazz Club. Ferguson and his band turn in a performance that includes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 04:18:00" d="2021-07-18 05:09:00"><n>The Mel Lewis Orchestra live at Estival Lugano</n><t>M</t>    <k>Estival offers a thrilling and particularly surprising line-up that explores the rich world of contemporary music. The Mel Lewis Orchestra was arguably</k>  </p>
</a>
