<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-05-15 04:59:55"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-22 05:07:00" d="2020-05-22 05:34:00"><n>Daniel Erdmann's Velvet Revolution - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Velvet Revolution redefines what music can be in the 21st century: vivid, live, and unafraid to use force and power when the music asks for it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-22 05:34:00" d="2020-05-22 06:02:00"><n>Peter Gall Quintett - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Drummer and percussionist Peter Gall grew up in provincial Bavaria as the younger brother of pianist Chris Gall. Early on, Peter learned to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-22 06:02:00" d="2020-05-22 07:00:00"><n>Rita Reys &amp; The Pim Jacobs Trio at North Sea Jazz</n><t>M</t>    <k>This broadcast from the North Sea Jazz Archives presents &quot;Europe's First Lady of Song&quot;, popular Dutch jazz vocalist Rita Reys, accompanied by husband</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-22 07:00:00" d="2020-05-22 08:06:00"><n>Rhoda Scott &amp; La Velle: Hammond, Soul and Blues</n><t>M</t>    <k>Although American soul and jazz organist Rhoda Scott spent most of her career in France, this performance at the antique theatre of Vienne is special</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-22 08:06:00" d="2020-05-22 09:07:00"><n>Tribute to Ella Fitzgerald</n><t>M</t>    <k>The extraordinary Dee Dee Bridgewater pays tribute to Ella Fitzgerald by performing &quot;A-Tisket, A-Tasket&quot;, &quot;Mack the Knife&quot;, and other popular classics</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-22 09:07:00" d="2020-05-22 10:01:00"><n>The Sound of New York - Greg Osby</n><t>M</t>    <k>Alto saxophonist, producer, composer and educator Greg Osby has made an indelible mark on contemporary jazz both as a leader of his own ensembles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-22 10:01:00" d="2020-05-22 11:27:00"><n>Memoirs of a Hip 'Ole Black Man</n><t>M</t>    <k>His hands move with the speed of light, and his warm voice caresses his listeners' hearts and minds. Vinx De'Jon Parrette i's a true artist, passionate for his art. (2015)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-22 11:27:00" d="2020-05-22 12:33:00"><n>Tristan &amp; The Heavy Horns</n><t>M</t>    <k>Tristan is synonymous with funky guitars, Fender Rhodes pianos, synthesizers, and a well-travelled rhythm section. The instant they hit the stage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-22 12:33:00" d="2020-05-22 14:03:00"><n u="Jazz in Comblain-la-Tour">Jazz in Comblain-la-Tour, 1963</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 1963, the small Belgian town of Comblain-la-Tour hosted the talented groups of Charlie Galbraith, Knut Kiesewetter, Bud Shank and Pim Jacobs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-22 14:03:00" d="2020-05-22 16:06:00"><n>Solo Piano Summit</n><t>M</t>    <k>The &quot;Solo Piano Summit&quot; brings together a handful of top pianists with different musical backgrounds: Jacky Terrasson, Junior Mance, Geoff Keezer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-22 16:06:00" d="2020-05-22 16:49:00"><n>Guy Salomon Group - InJazz 2019</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Guy Salamon Group is an Amsterdam-based multi-international band led by Israeli drummer/composer Guy Salamon. The band plays a highly expressive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-22 16:49:00" d="2020-05-22 17:38:00"><n u="Michel Legrand Orchestra at Spa">Michel Legrand Orchestra at Spa, 1982</n><t>M</t>    <k>Michel Legrand and his orchestra perform a number of his beloved soundtrack compositions, &quot;The Summer Knows,&quot; &quot;What Are You Doing the Rest of Your Life?&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-22 17:38:00" d="2020-05-22 19:16:00"><n>A Tango Night - Live from Buenos Aires</n><t>M</t>    <k>On December 31, 2006, Daniel Barenboim came to celebrate the New Year in the Argentinean capital of Buenos Aires. For the pianist and conductor the tango</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-22 19:16:00" d="2020-05-22 20:03:00"><n>BIRDtv: Christian Scott</n><t>M</t>    <k>Since 2014, Rotterdam's ' BIRD' club and DJAZZ.tv have been collaborating for a series of music programmes: 'BIRD.tv'. This episode features a fantastic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-22 20:03:00" d="2020-05-22 21:00:00"><n>New York Jazz Quartet live in the French Quarter</n><t>M</t>    <k>Roland Hanna is joined by bassist George Mraz, drummer Marvin Smith, and saxophonists Frank Wess and Frank Foster. These veterans of the Count Basie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-22 21:00:00" d="2020-05-22 22:03:00"><n>Maceo Parker: Jazz a Juan</n><t>M</t>    <k>At 25, saxophonist Maceo Parker played in James Brown's band, but today he is also known for his collaborations with George Clinton's Parliament-Funkadelic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-22 22:03:00" d="2020-05-23 00:00:00"><n>Jazzed Out London</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jazzed Out proves that a jazz session can take place anywhere. In this episode, London serves as a backdrop for sets by saxophonist Soweto Kinch, and pianist Neil Cowley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 00:00:00" d="2020-05-23 01:12:00"><n>Brooklyn Vibes</n><t>M</t>    <k>Brooklyn Vibes documents artists like Charles Bradley, Justine D, and Nicky Fingaz who are part of the thriving Brooklyn creative scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 01:12:00" d="2020-05-23 01:46:00"><n>Max Andrzejewski's Hutte - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Max Andrzejewski's HUTTE is a Berlin-based band that has already released two very successful albums. Always highly energetic, adventurous, and expressive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 01:46:00" d="2020-05-23 02:21:00"><n>MDCIII - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>For his project 'MDCIII', Belgian reed player Mattias De Craene invites two compatriots Simon Segers and Lennert Jacobs, both experienced drummers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 02:21:00" d="2020-05-23 03:26:00"><n>The MotorMusic Jazz Sessions: Dominic J. Marshall</n><t>M</t>    <k>This MotorMusic Jazz Sessions episode features the British Dominic J. Marshall trio. With his incredible energy and authenticity, Marshall</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 03:26:00" d="2020-05-23 04:13:00"><n>Jose James - Jazz a Vienne</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jose James was discovered by the legendary DJ and radio broadcaster Gilles Peterson. Joined on stage by a group of talented musicians, the singer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 04:13:00" d="2020-05-23 05:45:00"><n>Al Di Meola: One of These Nights</n><t>M</t>  </p>
</a>
