<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a><n>The Sound of New York - Stefon Harris</n><s o="2020-06-05 09:06:00" d="2020-06-05 10:03:00" n="DJazz" id_tv="1166"></s><p><k>The passionate play, the energetic stage presence and the amazing virtuosity of vibraphonist Stefon Harris have propelled him to the forefront of the current jazz scene.</k><d>The series The Sound of New York. Music Today and Tomorrow is an exploration of the musical universe of a new generation of New York artists. Of diverse origins and all having a unique history and background, these musicians gave birth to a new sound that influences the music scene around the world. This new generation of artists combines sounds of yesterday and today, interacts with a range of other artistic forms, and plays with many influences, from Afro-American music to classical and contemporary music through hip-hop, R&amp;B, rock, and so much more. The passionate play, the energetic stage presence and the amazing virtuosity of vibraphonist Stefon Harris have propelled him to the forefront of the current jazz scene. Largely praised by his peers and critics alike, Harris's mission is to explore the rich potential of jazz composition and popularize the vibraphone. Harris has appeared alongside several jazz luminaries including Kenny Barron, Steve Turre, Kurt Elling and Charlie Hunter, and has released several albums that have been warmly received by critics. With a bachelor's and master's degree from New York's Manhattan School of Music, Harris credits his successful career with high school teachers, who quickly recognized his passion for music, and offered him lessons and the chance to bring the instruments home: &quot;My musical education and the opportunities I had to perform in ensembles such as the Empire State Youth Orchestra exposed me to other cultures and to a variety of musical styles&quot;. Harris is the creator of Harmony Cloud, an application to help beginners and professionals alike develop their ears, deepen their understanding of harmony, and explore the world of improvisation. In 2016, he was named director of the prestigious Jazz Arts Program at the Manhattan School of Music. Harris has performed around the world and his discography has six albums.</d></p><i><w>http://tv.sms.cz/televize/djazz/20200605/1410023424-The-sound-of-new-york-stefon-harris</w></i><x></x></a>
