<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-05-28 04:42:35"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-04 05:25:00" d="2020-06-04 07:00:00"><n>&quot;Long Tall Dexter&quot; Live in '64</n><t>M</t>    <k>Dexter Gordon: Live in '63 &amp; '64 features three concerts filmed in Holland, Switzerland, and Belgium that highlight the bebop legend's classic style and silky tone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-04 07:00:00" d="2020-06-04 08:48:00"><n>Stan Getz: The Last Recording</n><t>M</t>    <k>Regarded as the greatest instrumental soloist of all-time, Stanley Gayetzky, famously known as Stan Getz emerged as one of the most significant musical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-04 08:48:00" d="2020-06-04 09:21:00"><n>Chet Baker Quintet: Live in '64</n><t>M</t>    <k>Chet Baker was the interpreter of West Coast jazz in the early and mid-'50s. Baker had a generally restrained, intimate playing style and attracted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-04 09:21:00" d="2020-06-04 10:00:00"><n>Slim, Harrison &amp; Jones live in Brussels</n><t>M</t>    <k>What do Sunnyland Slim, Wilbert Harrison and Curtis Jones have in common? Right, the piano and the blues! Each has his individual style</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-04 10:00:00" d="2020-06-04 11:43:00"><n>J.E. &quot;Cannonball&quot; Adderley live in Switzerland</n><t>M</t>    <k>Cannonball Adderley: Live in '63 boasts two beautifully filmed concerts from one of the most celebrated sextets in jazz history, captured at the top of their game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-04 11:43:00" d="2020-06-04 12:38:00"><n>Irma Thomas: Soul Queen of New Orleans</n><t>M</t>    <k>Irma Thomas is the undisputed Soul Queen of New Orleans. In this rare 1992 live set from Mahogany Hall, her powerful voice gives songs like 'Bill Bailey'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-04 12:38:00" d="2020-06-04 14:01:00"><n u="Dusko Gojkovic - Brussels Jazz Club">Dusko Gojkovic - Brussels Jazz Club, 1980</n><t>M</t>    <k>Legendary Serbian jazz trumpeter, composer, and arranger Dusko Gojkovic takes the lead in this intimate concert at Brussels Jazz Club, in 1980</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-04 14:01:00" d="2020-06-04 15:25:00"><n>Benny Golson Quintet Feat Flavio Boltro</n><t>M</t>    <k>Creator of &quot;Whisper Not&quot;, one of the most famous standards, Benny Golson has composed more than 300 pieces for the biggest names in jazz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-04 15:25:00" d="2020-06-04 16:16:00"><n>George Shearing: The South Bank Show</n><t>M</t>    <k>George Shearing, blind since birth, is one of the world's greatest jazz pianists. Filmed on both sides of the Atlantic, this tribute to Shearing showcases</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-04 16:16:00" d="2020-06-04 17:00:00"><n>Michel Tasky live in Rio: Um Malandro em Paris</n><t>M</t>    <k>With his relaxed and clear voice, Belgian-born vocalist Michel Tasky took his French-Waalse roots to Brazil, where he established himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-04 17:00:00" d="2020-06-04 18:12:00"><n>Theophilus London - Nuits Sonores 2015</n><t>M</t>    <k>Theophilus London gained attention in 2011 with the release of his debut EP 'Lovers Holiday' and his debut album 'Timez Are Weird These Days'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-04 18:12:00" d="2020-06-04 19:14:00"><n>Tonya Baker: Live at Jazz a Vienne Festival</n><t>M</t>    <k>Psalmist, gifted songwriter, author, instructor, workshop instructor, and gospel singer Tonya Baker travels the world to share her gift of singing and her great wisdom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-04 19:14:00" d="2020-06-04 20:02:00"><n>Jacques Kuba Séguin: L'étude des Lueurs</n><t>M</t>    <k>Trumpeter Jacques Kuba Séguin's ensemble unites some of Montreal's most expressive musicians: double bassist Frédéric Alarie, pianist Jonathan Cayer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-04 20:02:00" d="2020-06-04 21:00:00"><n>Seine Sessions: Legendary Jazz</n><t>M</t>    <k>Entitled &quot;Legendary Jazz&quot;, this episode of the Seine Sessions hosted by Eddy King presents unique performances, and interviews with Steve McCraven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-04 21:00:00" d="2020-06-04 21:59:00"><n>Lisa Simone - Blues sur Seine</n><t>M</t>    <k>Lisa Simone, who's the legendary Nina Simone's only child, creates a magical atmosphere of warmth, passion and unity. She is joined on stage by guitarist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-04 21:59:00" d="2020-06-04 22:59:00"><n>Don Cherry's 'Multikulti'</n><t>M</t>    <k>Multikulti presents a never-before heard mixture of international sounds, from mainstream jazz to reggae, in his first collaboration with the amazing Peter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-04 22:59:00" d="2020-06-05 00:00:00"><n>Une Soirée de Poche: Son Lux</n><t>M</t>    <k>Son Lux is the dream of Los Angeles composer Ryan Lott, made possible with the help of two New Yorkers: guitarist Rafiq Bhatia and drummer Ian Chang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-05 00:00:00" d="2020-06-05 01:05:00"><n>PONYLAND - InJazz 2019</n><t>M</t>    <k>UK-based ensemble Ponyland brings together professional musicians from across Newcastle and Cumbria. Two drummers, vocals, lead and bass guitar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-05 01:05:00" d="2020-06-05 01:51:00"><n>Mister Joe Williams and the Basie Alumni Band</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Count Basie Alumni Band is joined by Joe Williams for a bluesy performance at the Brussels Jazz Club in 1980</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-05 01:51:00" d="2020-06-05 02:23:00"><n>TorTube: La Waltz 2, 3 and More</n><t>M</t>    <k>La Waltz 2, 3 and More is an episode of TorTube that pulls you into the world of De Tor. Veteran vocalist Humphrey Campbell shares the stage with chromatic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-05 02:23:00" d="2020-06-05 03:22:00"><n>Salif Keita &amp; Les Ambassadeurs</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Golden Voice of Africa aka Salif Keita's music is a rich blend of traditional Malian music with European and American influences. Discover the various</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-05 03:22:00" d="2020-06-05 04:39:00"><n>Bixiga 70 - BIRD 2019</n><t>M</t>    <k>Stemming from Brazil's Sao Paulo, Bixiga 70 is an exciting musical ensemble that combines jazz, funk, and Afro-Brazilian music, incorporating elements</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-05 04:39:00" d="2020-06-05 05:21:00"><n>Trio Abozekrys - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Trio Abozekrys comprises of oud player Mohamed Abozekry, his brother Abdallah Abozekry on saz, and Nicolas Thé on drums. Their jazz-inflected repertoire</k>  </p>
</a>
