<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-04-15 04:37:22"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 05:21:00" d="2020-04-22 06:01:00"><n>Seine Sessions: Funk &amp; Afro</n><t>M</t>    <k>Entitled &quot;Funk &amp; Afro&quot;, this episode of the Seine Sessions hosted by Eddy King presents unique performances, and interviews with Cool Jam, Bibi Tanga</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 06:01:00" d="2020-04-22 07:00:00"><n>The Morgenland Festival: A Trace of Grace</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode entitled &quot;A Trace Of Grace&quot; features the rich and complex music of Michel Godard and Kayhan Kalhor, two musicians interested in instruments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 07:00:00" d="2020-04-22 08:35:00"><n>Jazz Open Stuttgart: West Coast All Stars</n><t>M</t>    <k>This live recording is celebrating 50 years of West Coast Jazz. The West Coast Jazz movement had its origins about 50 years ago in Los Angeles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 08:35:00" d="2020-04-22 09:05:00"><n>Face au Public: Odetta</n><t>M</t>    <k>Legendary African-American folk singer Odetta (1930-2008) sang her spirituals with immeasurable sorrow and anguish. Her spiritual music expresses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 09:05:00" d="2020-04-22 10:02:00"><n>The Definitive Collection: Duke Ellington</n><t>M</t>    <k>Born Edward Kennedy Ellington on April 29, 1899, Duke Ellington is one of the world's greatest musicians and composers. Duke and his orchestra toured</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 10:02:00" d="2020-04-22 10:46:00"><n>Patáx: A Night to Remember 2/2</n><t>M</t>    <k>Patáx presents an accomplished mix of styles, including soul, jazz, funk and hip hop. Led by the passionate Spanish-American percussionist Jorge Perez</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 10:46:00" d="2020-04-22 11:44:00"><n>Rhoda Scott &amp; La Velle: Hammond, Soul and Blues</n><t>M</t>    <k>Although American soul and jazz organist Rhoda Scott spent most of her career in France, this performance at the antique theatre of Vienne is special</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 11:44:00" d="2020-04-22 13:09:00"><n>VEIN Plays Ravel</n><t>M</t>    <k>Innovation is at the heart of the approach of VEIN, a bold Swiss ensemble composed of brothers Michael and Florian Arbenz, and bassist Thomas Lähns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 13:09:00" d="2020-04-22 14:01:00"><n>Portrait of Marcus Miller</n><t>M</t>    <k>'The legend of the groove' is a series of documentaries about musicians who, between the late 1950s and now, have radically influenced the music of today's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 14:01:00" d="2020-04-22 15:36:00"><n>Jazz Dreams</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jazz Dreams follows the lives of three young jazz musicians from New Orleans as they begin their careers: Jason Marsalis, Irvin Mayfield and Courtney Bryan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 15:36:00" d="2020-04-22 17:26:00"><n>Theo Croker - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>In all likelihood, Theo Croker inherited his impalpable flair for trumpet playing and performing from his late grandfather, legendary trumpeter Doc Cheatham</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 17:26:00" d="2020-04-22 18:16:00"><n u="Jon Hendricks and Co: Estival">Jon Hendricks and Co: Estival 1986</n><t>M</t>    <k>John Carl Hendricks is one of the instigators of &quot;vocalese&quot;, an art form that aims to add lyrics to existing instrumental pieces and replace several</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 18:16:00" d="2020-04-22 18:45:00"><n>Mario Batkovic - WOMEX 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Mario Batkovic, aims to explore the sonic possibilities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 18:45:00" d="2020-04-22 19:38:00"><n u="Earl Hines Quartet in Spa">Earl Hines Quartet in Spa, 1977</n><t>M</t>    <k>Earl Hines and his group, consisting of Rudy Rutherford (reeds), Jimmy Leary (bass), and Eddie Graham (drums) perform in Spa in 1977. Singer Marva Josie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 19:38:00" d="2020-04-22 20:31:00"><n>The MotorMusic Jazz Sessions: Steiger</n><t>M</t>    <k>This MotorMusic Jazz Sessions episode features the Belgian musicians of Steiger, a young trio of pianists that mixes rock, classical music, and electronic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 20:31:00" d="2020-04-22 21:00:00"><n>Rebirth: Richard Lemz</n><t>M</t>    <k>The short documentary Rebirth in The Amsterdam Red Light District illustrates how brutal drummer Richard Lems' life was as an addict, portraying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 21:00:00" d="2020-04-22 21:30:00"><n>Ray Charles live at North Sea Jazz</n><t>M</t>    <k>This broadcast from the North Sea Jazz Archives presents a compilation with music of Ray Charles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-22 21:30:00" d="2020-04-23 00:00:00"><n>Florian Favre Trio - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>Pianist Florian Favre has already earned a firm place on the Swiss jazz scene. His trio, with Manu Hagmann on bass and Arthur Hnatek on drums, performs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-23 00:00:00" d="2020-04-23 01:05:00"><n>Ode to Miles: Bitches Brew Beyond</n><t>M</t>    <k>Trumpeter Wallace Roney revives Miles Davis' legendary album, Bitches Brew. In this project - a brainchild of Miles' family - Miles' nephew takes part</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-23 01:05:00" d="2020-04-23 02:35:00"><n>Casper the Funky Ghost: Bootsy Collins a Vienne</n><t>M</t>    <k>Bootsy Collins' syncopated, hard and relentlessly rhythmic music strongly influenced funk music's development. Now in his 60s, Bootsy maintains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-23 02:35:00" d="2020-04-23 03:38:00"><n>Terry Callier: Live in Berlin</n><t>M</t>    <k>Terry Callier, the man who has written music history in the 1960s and 1970s, returns to the stage after a 15 year break</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-23 03:38:00" d="2020-04-23 04:27:00"><n u="Carla Bley Sextet live at Estival Lugano">Carla Bley Sextet live at Estival Lugano 1986</n><t>M</t>    <k>Estival offers a thrilling and particularly surprising line-up that explores the rich world of contemporary music. Discover the special bond between</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-23 04:27:00" d="2020-04-23 05:35:00"><n>Kurt Rosenwinkel meets Peter Beets Trio</n><t>M</t>  </p>
</a>
