<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a><n>The Sound of New York - Damión Reid</n><s o="2021-07-14 20:28:00" d="2021-07-14 21:00:00" n="DJazz" id_tv="1166"></s><p><k>Damion Reid has toured with some of the biggest names in music including Greg Osby, Terence Blanchard, Robert Glasper, Cassandra Wilson, Bruce Hornsby, Lauryn Hill, Ravi Coltrane, Reggie Workman, and many others.</k><d>The series The Sound of New York. Music Today and Tomorrow is an exploration of the musical universe of a new generation of New York artists. Of diverse origins and all having a unique history and background, these musicians gave birth to a new sound that influences the music scene around the world. This new generation of artists combines sounds of yesterday and today, interacts with a range of other artistic forms, and plays with many influences, from Afro-American music to classical and contemporary music through hip-hop, R&amp;B, rock, and so much more. Native of West Covina, a city in eastern Los Angeles, Damion Reid is the son of a renowned bassist and a singer and opera teacher. At the age of three, young Reid was already performing at the local church, and at age 12 he found a mentor in world-renowned drummer Billy Higgins . During these highly formative years, Higgings passed on his passion for music and life to young Reid and, impressed by his student's ability to grasp music, both analytically and conceptually. Reid continued to cultivate his love of music during high school, and moved to Boston after receiving the prestigious Alan Dawson Scholarship from the Massachusetts New England Conservatory of Music. He then joined the ranks of the Thelonious Monk Institute of Jazz at the University of Southern California. To date, Damion Reid has toured with some of the biggest names in music including Greg Osby, Terence Blanchard, Robert Glasper, Cassandra Wilson, Bruce Hornsby, Lauryn Hill, Ravi Coltrane, Reggie Workman, and many others.</d></p><i><w>https://tv.sms.cz/televize/djazz/20210714/1540125566-The-sound-of-new-york-damion-reid</w></i><x></x></a>
