<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2020-05-13 04:36:27"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 05:14:00" d="2020-05-20 05:54:00"><n>Seine Sessions: Funk &amp; Afro</n><t>M</t>    <k>Entitled &quot;Funk &amp; Afro&quot;, this episode of the Seine Sessions (2016) hosted by Eddy King presents unique performances, and interviews</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 05:54:00" d="2020-05-20 07:00:00"><n>The Morgenland Festival: The Art of Duo</n><t>M</t>    <k>&quot;The Art of Duo&quot; presents an unprecedented duo featuring pianist Salman Gambarov and sheng player, a Chinese mouth-organ, Wu Wei</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 07:00:00" d="2020-05-20 08:01:00"><n>Les McCann: Live in New Orleans</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 08:01:00" d="2020-05-20 09:12:00"><n>Artvark Saxophone Quartet &amp; Ntjam Rosie: Homelands</n><t>M</t>    <k>Homelands is a collaboration between Artvark Saxophone Quartet and Cameroonian-Dutch singer Ntjam Rosie. The music is inspired by both traditional</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 09:12:00" d="2020-05-20 10:01:00"><n>Dionne Warwick live at the 27 Club</n><t>M</t>    <k>Dionne Warwick's vocal artistry ranges from voluminous deep register to soft, fragile high notes. She masters the entire range with almost unnerving ease</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 10:01:00" d="2020-05-20 11:03:00"><n>Chucho Valdes - Jazz a Vienne</n><t>M</t>    <k>Chucho Valdes and his Afro-Cuban Messengers are the prime example of Latin-inspired jazz music. During his performance the legendary pianist brings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 11:03:00" d="2020-05-20 11:55:00"><n u="Soul &amp; Jazz LIVE! Episode">Soul &amp; Jazz LIVE! Episode 2</n><t>M</t>    <k>Soul &amp; Jazz LIVE! episode 2 includes Camilla George, Terrace Martin, Resolution 88, Push, Rick Leon James, Lindsey Webster, Maurice Brown, Laila Biali</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 11:55:00" d="2020-05-20 13:06:00"><n>Jazz en Baie: Mayfair Electro Jazz Project</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Mayfair Electro Jazz Project at the Jazz en Baie Festival: an inspiring combination of well-known jazz instruments, electronic elements, vibrant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 13:06:00" d="2020-05-20 14:00:00"><n>Portrait of Maria Ana Bobone</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 14:00:00" d="2020-05-20 15:02:00"><n>A Different Way: Rodolfo Mederos</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rodolfo Mederos is a bandoneonist, a composer with an enormous oeuvre, one of the authorities on the tango – and an inspiration to new generations of musicians</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 15:02:00" d="2020-05-20 16:45:00"><n>James Taylor Quartet - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>Acid jazz pioneer James Taylor is a talented Hammond B3 organ player. Throughout the years, his James Taylor Quartet has developed a unique sound in which</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 16:45:00" d="2020-05-20 17:45:00"><n>Martin Goyette - Spectacle Astral 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>A veteran bluesman that can hold his head high next to our neighbors to the south, Martin Goyette made his bones with an undeniable and incredible voice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 17:45:00" d="2020-05-20 18:35:00"><n>Lucibela - WOMEX 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Lucibela, comes from the island of Sao Nicolau. Her assured</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 18:35:00" d="2020-05-20 19:29:00"><n>Masters of Jazz: Nina Simone live in Europe</n><t>M</t>    <k>Nina Simone: Live in '65 &amp; '68 features two incredible concerts from 1965 and 1968 showcasing the diva in all her glory. These recordings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 19:29:00" d="2020-05-20 20:17:00"><n>Belgium Sessions: Saxkartel</n><t>M</t>    <k>Saxkartel plays jazz and modern music with an uncommon approach: as a saxophone quartet, they perform chamber-like music without the accompaniment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 20:17:00" d="2020-05-20 21:00:00"><n>The Sound of New York - Matthew Stevens</n><t>M</t>    <k>Since graduating from Berklee College of Music in 2004, Matthew Stevens has earned an enviable reputation on the contemporary scene by appearing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 21:00:00" d="2020-05-20 22:07:00"><n>Lucky Peterson - Jazzwoche Burghausen</n><t>M</t>    <k>Legendary bluesman Lucky Peterson, master of the blues guitar and Hammond organ, celebrates 50 years on stage. He is accompanied by his band, augmented</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 22:07:00" d="2020-05-21 00:00:00"><n>BCUC - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>BCUC ('Bantu Continua Uhuru Consciousness') is a South African afro-psychedelic funk collective that combines traditional and modern sounds in a feast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-21 00:00:00" d="2020-05-21 00:42:00"><n>Matteo Myderwyk - InJazz 2019</n><t>M</t>    <k>Matteo Myderwyk is a 28-year-old Amsterdam-based pianist. He completed his master degree in piano classical and improvised music at Fontys Conservatorium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-21 00:42:00" d="2020-05-21 01:40:00"><n>Brooklyn Funk Essentials in Vienne</n><t>M</t>    <k>Brooklyn Funk Essentials mix jazz, funk, and hip-hop featuring musicians and poets from different cultures. This performance is in the beautiful antique</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-21 01:40:00" d="2020-05-21 03:04:00"><n>Wouter Hamel Live in Paradiso</n><t>M</t>    <k>What Jamie Cullum is to England, Wouter Hamel is to the Netherlands: a performer who knows the difference between jazz and pop!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-21 03:04:00" d="2020-05-21 03:55:00"><n u="Freddie Hubbard &amp; The Satchmo Legacy Live in">Freddie Hubbard &amp; The Satchmo Legacy Live in 1987</n><t>M</t>    <k>Estival offers a thrilling and particularly surprising line-up that explores the rich world of contemporary music. Freddie Hubbard is an American</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-21 03:55:00" d="2020-05-21 04:56:00"><n>Tel Aviv Sessions: Omri Mor</n><t>M</t>    <k>With his passion and his virtuosity, pianist Omri Mor amazes the audience of the music club Zappa in Tel Aviv. Pieces drawn from the heritage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-21 04:56:00" d="2020-05-21 07:00:00"><n>J.E. &quot;Cannonball&quot; Adderley live in Switzerland</n><t>M</t>    <k>Cannonball Adderley: Live in '63 boasts two beautifully filmed concerts from one of the most celebrated sextets in jazz history, captured at the top of their game</k>  </p>
</a>
