<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2020-05-16 04:58:19"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 05:45:00" d="2020-05-23 07:00:00"><n>Sammy Price and his All Star Orchestra</n><t>M</t>    <k>Texan pianist Sammy Price (1908-1992) played everything from blues and boogie-woogie to swing and jump-blues. Starting in Dallas as a singer and dancer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 07:00:00" d="2020-05-23 08:36:00"><n>Fred Hersch Trio - Jazz a Ramatuelle</n><t>M</t>    <k>At the age of 63, Fred Hersch is unquestionably one of today's key figures in jazz piano. Supported by John Hebert (double bass) and Eric McPherson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 08:36:00" d="2020-05-23 09:10:00"><n>Chet Baker Quintet: Live in '64</n><t>M</t>    <k>Chet Baker was the interpreter of West Coast jazz in the early and mid-'50s. Baker had a generally restrained, intimate playing style and attracted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 09:10:00" d="2020-05-23 10:04:00"><n>Dion with Henri Segers and his orchestra</n><t>M</t>    <k>One of the most popular American rock &amp; roll performers of the days before the Beatles, Dion's music spans everything from doo-wop, rock and R&amp;B to straight blues. (1963)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 10:04:00" d="2020-05-23 10:55:00"><n u="Sarah Vaughan: Jazz from Newport, Brussels">Sarah Vaughan: Jazz from Newport, Brussels 1973</n><t>M</t>    <k>For the second of two appearances at the 1973 Jazz from Newport Festival in Brussels, Sarah Vaughan and her trio consisting of Carl Schroeder (piano)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 10:55:00" d="2020-05-23 11:23:00"><n>Makiko Hirabayashi Trio - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Makiko Hirabayashi Trio represents the Danish jazz scene on jazzahead! 2019. Led by the Japanese pianist Makiko Hirabayashi, the trio blends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 11:23:00" d="2020-05-23 11:55:00"><n>Paul Heller / Jasper Van't Hof Group - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Paul Heller and Jasper Van't Hof Group is a classic jazz quartet: tenor saxophone, piano, double bass and drums. Combining energetic spontaneity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 11:55:00" d="2020-05-23 14:02:00"><n>Jazz Open Stuttgart: West Coast All Stars</n><t>M</t>    <k>This live recording is celebrating 50 years of West Coast Jazz. The West Coast Jazz movement had its origins about 50 years ago in Los Angeles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 14:02:00" d="2020-05-23 15:10:00"><n>Elliot Galvin Trio - November Music</n><t>M</t>    <k>The pianist Elliot Galvin is a member of the young UK jazz group Dinosaur. Performing with his own trio, the gifted musician has been compared to Django</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 15:10:00" d="2020-05-23 15:26:00"><n>BIRDtv: Myles Sanko</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of BIRD.tv (2015) presents the London-based French-Ghanian soul jazz singer Myles Sanko (.1980). His exceptional voice, his lyrics</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 15:26:00" d="2020-05-23 15:57:00"><n>Seine Sessions: World Music</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of Seine Sessions 'World Music', presented by Eddy King, shows unique performances and interviews of among Teófilo Chantre, Tiwitine and Kinsy Ray</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 15:57:00" d="2020-05-23 17:07:00"><n>Trio Chemirani: Dawâr</n><t>M</t>    <k>The veritable tombak virtuosos of Trio Chemirani, consisting of Chemirani Senior and Juniors, enrapture the Festival de Saintes. The Trio Chemirani's music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 17:07:00" d="2020-05-23 18:20:00"><n>Buzz Bros Band - Same New Story</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 18:20:00" d="2020-05-23 19:21:00"><n>Tel Aviv Sessions: Avi Lebovich Orchestra</n><t>M</t>    <k>The legendary Yellow Submarine Jazz Club in Jerusalem presents trombonist Avi Lebovich and his Orchestra. The Orchestra is a contemporary incarnation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 19:21:00" d="2020-05-23 20:03:00"><n>International Jazz Quintette de Jaspar et Thomas</n><t>M</t>    <k>The International Jazz Quintet led by guitarist René Thomas (1926-1975) and saxophonist Bobby Jaspar (1926-1963) is highly underrated. Enjoy this concert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 20:03:00" d="2020-05-23 21:00:00"><n>Teus Nobel live at the Bimhuis: Legacy</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teus Nobel is a Dutch trumpet and flugelhorn player. Teus dedicates his compositions to his all-time heroes Jarmo Hoogendijk, Woody Shaw, Christian Scott</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 21:00:00" d="2020-05-23 22:34:00"><n>Tigran Hamasyan &amp; Mathias Eick - November Music</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2019, Armenian pianist Tigran Hamasyan and Norwegian trumpeter Mathias Eick played a duo performance at November Music in 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-23 22:34:00" d="2020-05-24 00:00:00"><n>Keita, Tinariwen Maal &amp; Sangare: Africa Live!</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-24 00:00:00" d="2020-05-24 01:03:00"><n>The Garifuna Collektive - WOMEX 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, The Garifuna Collective, carries the legacy of Andy Palacio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-24 01:03:00" d="2020-05-24 01:36:00"><n>AJOYO - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Brooklyn-based band AJOYO is the brainchild of multi-reed player Yacine Boulares. Their music is a mystic brew of African tradition, jazz and soul</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-24 01:36:00" d="2020-05-24 02:11:00"><n>Lisbon Underground Music Ensemble - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Lisbon Underground Music Ensemble (L.U.M.E.) is a musical project by composer Marco Barroso. The 15-piece group is inspired by the big band tradition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-24 02:11:00" d="2020-05-24 03:14:00"><n>Christian Scott - Jazz a Vienne 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Christian Scott aTunde Adjuah blends jazz fusion, hip-hop and alternative rock, developing a unique and distinct sound. Scott's performance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-24 03:14:00" d="2020-05-24 04:06:00"><n u="Tania Maria: Live at Estival Lugano">Tania Maria: Live at Estival Lugano 1987</n><t>M</t>    <k>This performance of Brazilian Tania Maria promises to make you want to dance. The singer, composer and pianist sets fire to the Estival scene with her pop and jazzy song</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-24 04:06:00" d="2020-05-24 05:19:00"><n>Jeff Moran &amp; Thomas Carbou live a Quebec</n><t>M</t>    <k>Trumpeter Jacques Kuba Séguin's ensemble unites some of Montreal's most expressive musicians: double bassist Frédéric Alarie, pianist Jonathan Cayer</k>  </p>
</a>
