<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2021-07-08 05:07:17"><p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-13 05:28:00" d="2021-07-13 07:00:00"><n u="Soul &amp; Jazz LIVE! Episode">Soul &amp; Jazz LIVE! Episode 5</n><t>M</t>    <k>Soul &amp; Jazz LIVE! episode 5 includes Resolution 88, Push, Camilla George, Laila Biali, A/B Trio, Nubiyan Twist, Rick Leon James, Avery.Sunshine, Tropica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-13 07:00:00" d="2021-07-13 08:21:00"><n>Thomas Carbou: Spectacle Au Bleury</n><t>M</t>    <k>Thomas Carbou and Patrick Graham share an almost telepathic rapport, blending spontaneous improvisation, electronic looping, and Brazilian and Indian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-13 08:21:00" d="2021-07-13 09:18:00"><n>Saluzzi, Mariano &amp; Dauner live in Stuttgart</n><t>M</t>    <k>Dino Saluzzi, one of Argentina's tango music masters, has been building his legacy since the 80s. His accordion-like bandoneon defines Argentina's tango music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-13 09:18:00" d="2021-07-13 10:01:00"><n>Portrait of Sam Moore</n><t>M</t>    <k>'The legend of the groove' is a series of documentaries about musicians who, between the late 1950s and now, have radically influenced the music of today's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-13 10:01:00" d="2021-07-13 11:10:00"><n>Liz McComb in Paris: Back to Blues</n><t>M</t>    <k>Liz Mc Comb sings, among others, 'I'm Just a Poor Wayfaring Stranger' for all the immigrants in the world, followed by her famous 'Time Is Now'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-13 11:10:00" d="2021-07-13 12:06:00"><n>Istanbul Sessions: Burhan Ocal Paganini Trio</n><t>M</t>    <k>Live at the Istanbul IKSV, Öcal and his Paganini Trio play mythical interpretation of the compositions of Niccolo Paganini. (2011)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-13 12:06:00" d="2021-07-13 14:02:00"><n>Ryan Porter &amp; The West Coast Get Down - BIRD</n><t>M</t>    <k>Los Angeles-born saxophonist Kamasi Washington and trombonist Ryan Porter co-founded West Coast Get Down – a musical collective fusing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-13 14:02:00" d="2021-07-13 14:51:00"><n>Conservatory Concert Big Band</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-13 14:51:00" d="2021-07-13 16:14:00"><n>Tigran Hamasyan &amp; Mathias Eick - November Music</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2019, Armenian pianist Tigran Hamasyan and Norwegian trumpeter Mathias Eick played a duo performance at November Music in 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-13 16:14:00" d="2021-07-13 16:59:00"><n>Jazzmeia Horn - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jazzmeia Horn is a winner of the 2015 Thelonious Monk Institute International Jazz Competition. Blending spirituality, scat singing, smooth vocals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-13 16:59:00" d="2021-07-13 17:34:00"><n>Elliot Galvin - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Pianist Elliot Galvin, a rising star of UK jazz, is also a superbly gifted composer. His maverick imagination and magpie-like ability to blend disparate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-13 17:34:00" d="2021-07-13 18:39:00"><n>MotorMusic Jazz Sessions: Steven Delannoye</n><t>M</t>    <k>Tenor saxophone player Steven Delannoye and his New York Trio play with saxophonist Frank Vaganée. An intense and intriguing dialogue recalling the golden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-13 18:39:00" d="2021-07-13 20:02:00"><n>Maceo Parker: Jazz a Juan</n><t>M</t>    <k>At 25, saxophonist Maceo Parker played in James Brown's band, but today he is also known for his collaborations with George Clinton's Parliament-Funkadelic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-13 20:02:00" d="2021-07-13 21:00:00"><n>The Morgenland Festival: VIVA!</n><t>M</t>    <k>&quot;Viva&quot; is a perfect mixture of various instruments and musicians from all over the world. Vocalists Aynur and Dima Oshno perform with the All Star Band</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-13 21:00:00" d="2021-07-13 21:58:00"><n>Brooklyn Vibes</n><t>M</t>    <k>Brooklyn Vibes documents artists like Charles Bradley, Justine D, and Nicky Fingaz who are part of the thriving Brooklyn creative scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-13 21:58:00" d="2021-07-13 23:03:00"><n>Istanbul Sessions: Okay Timiz</n><t>M</t>    <k>Okay Temiz is perhaps the most famous percussionist in Turkey. The multi-instrumentalist demonstrates his incredible skills in this extraordinary concert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-13 23:03:00" d="2021-07-14 00:00:00"><n>Charles Mingus And Eric Dolphy live in Liege</n><t>M</t>    <k>Charles Mingus showcases an exceptional concert performed in April 1965 featuring the lineup: Jaki Byard (piano), Dannie Richmond (drums), Johnny Coles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 00:00:00" d="2021-07-14 00:55:00"><n>The Garifuna Collektive - WOMEX 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, The Garifuna Collective, carries the legacy of Andy Palacio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 00:55:00" d="2021-07-14 01:46:00"><n>Sazz Leonore sings Michael Bublé</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 01:46:00" d="2021-07-14 03:23:00"><n>Bill Evans' European Tour: Live in '64, '65 &amp; '70</n><t>M</t>    <k>Bill Evans: Live in '64, '65 &amp; '70 features five separate performances by one of the most revered pianists in music history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 03:23:00" d="2021-07-14 04:04:00"><n>North Sea Jazz Club: Marnix Busstra Band</n><t>M</t>    <k>Joined by piano talent Rembrandt Frerichs, the ever creative double bassist Arnold Dooyeweerd and the inspirational force of drummer Pieter Bast, Busstra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 04:04:00" d="2021-07-14 04:25:00"><n>Sammy Price and the Harlem Beggars</n><t>M</t>    <k>Pianist, singer and civil rights activist Sammy Price is joined by the gospel singers known as the Harlem Beggars for spirited renditions of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 04:25:00" d="2021-07-14 05:19:00"><n>Lynne Arriale - The MotorMusic Jazz Sessions</n><t>M</t>    <k>American pianist Lynne Arriale has been actively performing since the early 1990s. It has been a constant profession of her love for melody and musical discovery</k>  </p>
</a>
