<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="20" t="2021-07-12 05:00:57"><p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-19 05:34:00" d="2021-07-19 07:00:00"><n>Mestrinho - Da Pá Virada Sessions</n><t>M</t>    <k>Accordionist Mestrinho performs with Caina Cavalcante on guitar, Alex Buck on drums, and Carlinhos Noronha on bass. They combine the subtle rhythms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-19 07:00:00" d="2021-07-19 08:19:00"><n>November Music: R. Frerichs/H. Alizadeh/Cello8ctet</n><t>M</t>    <k>The November Music festival in 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands is the ultimate event for experiencing a broad range of music. It features a wonderful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-19 08:19:00" d="2021-07-19 09:18:00"><n>Sam Moore &amp; The London Community Gospel Choir</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sam Moore is best known for his work with the historic soul duo Sam &amp; Dave. The rapid-fire style, built on the call and response of gospel, was fashioned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-19 09:18:00" d="2021-07-19 10:04:00"><n>Paradox Live: Harmen Fraanje</n><t>M</t>    <k>In the TV show PARADOX LIVE you get a taste of the greatest concerts and interviews with artists from all around the world. This episode of PARADOX</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-19 10:04:00" d="2021-07-19 12:07:00"><n>Live at The Hordern Pavilion</n><t>M</t>    <k>Big hits, booty dancing, stage dives, fan freestyles, A$AP Rocky's debut Down Under tour had it all! At his sold-out Sydney show, hip hop's hottest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-19 12:07:00" d="2021-07-19 12:50:00"><n>Come Twogether ft. Benjamin Herman</n><t>M</t>    <k>Simon Oslender and Jérome Cardynaals have the jazz in their blood! Under the name 'Twogether' they celebrate a unique and soulful style of funky blues-jazz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-19 12:50:00" d="2021-07-19 14:02:00"><n>The Morgenland Festival: The Art of Duo</n><t>M</t>    <k>&quot;The Art of Duo&quot; presents an unprecedented duo featuring pianist Salman Gambarov and sheng player, a Chinese mouth-organ, Wu Wei</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-19 14:02:00" d="2021-07-19 15:08:00"><n>Mel Torme &amp; Avro's Big Band - The North Sea Jazz</n><t>M</t>    <k>American singer Mel Tormé gave an unforgettable performance at the North Sea Jazz Festival in The Hague in 1981. Tormé, who wrote &quot;The Christmas Song&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-19 15:08:00" d="2021-07-19 15:58:00"><n>William Sahel - GREVE Studio, Berlin</n><t>M</t>    <k>Willy Sahel was born in N'djamena, Chad. He mixes traditional rhythms with soul, jazz and gospel, singing in his mother tongue and eight other languages</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-19 15:58:00" d="2021-07-19 18:14:00"><n>Shalosh - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>Among Israel's many musical discoveries is Shalosh: three young musicians with an electrifying sound. Shalosh plays raw, edgy jazz with a rock attitude</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-19 18:14:00" d="2021-07-19 18:42:00"><n>Paradox Live: Jeroen van Vliet Moon Trio</n><t>M</t>    <k>In the TV show PARADOX LIVE (2016) you get a taste of the greatest concerts and interviews with artists from all around the world. This episode of PARADOX</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-19 18:42:00" d="2021-07-19 19:21:00"><n u="Freddie Hubbard Quintet in Brussels">Freddie Hubbard Quintet in Brussels, 1980</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Freddie Hubbard Quintet livens up the Brussels Jazz Club during this short but sweet session from the summer of 1980. The group consists of Hubbard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-19 19:21:00" d="2021-07-19 20:00:00"><n>Simin Tander &amp; Joerg Brinkmann - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Vocalist Simin Tander and cello player Jörg Brinkmann travel far and wide for their sound. Their music transgresses the borders of time in pursuit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-19 20:00:00" d="2021-07-19 21:00:00"><n>TorTube: La Waltz 2, 3 and More</n><t>M</t>    <k>La Waltz 2, 3 and More is an episode of TorTube that pulls you into the world of De Tor. Veteran vocalist Humphrey Campbell shares the stage with chromatic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-19 21:00:00" d="2021-07-19 21:51:00"><n u="29th Street Saxophone Quartet: Estival">29th Street Saxophone Quartet: Estival 1987</n><t>M</t>    <k>The 29th Street Saxophone Quartet is an American quartet founded in 1982 by alto saxophonists Bobby Watson and Ed Jackson, tenor saxophonist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-19 21:51:00" d="2021-07-20 00:00:00"><n>Peter Beets Trio &amp; Goudsmit: Tribute to Montgomery</n><t>M</t>    <k>Peter Beets teams up with Anton Goudsmit (guitar) in tribute to guitar icon and founding father of modern jazz Wes Montgomery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-20 00:00:00" d="2021-07-20 01:00:00"><n>Winston McAnuff - Electric Dread</n><t>M</t>    <k>Nicknamed &quot;Electric Dread&quot;, Winston McAnuff was born in the hills of Jamaica in 1957. On stage at the French world music festival Les Escales</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-20 01:00:00" d="2021-07-20 02:56:00"><n>Shabaka &amp; The Ancestors - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>No stranger to jazz club Moods, Shabaka Hutchings has appeared there with The Comet is Coming and Sons of Kemet. He returns with The Ancestors, a South</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-20 02:56:00" d="2021-07-20 03:26:00"><n>Milt Jacksons' Modern Jazz Quartet at the Bozar</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Modern Jazz Quartet (MJQ) was composed of Milt 'Bags' Jackson on vibraphone, John Lewis (piano), Percy Heath (bass), and Connie Kay (drums)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-20 03:26:00" d="2021-07-20 05:10:00"><n u="Yaron Herman &amp; Guests: Alter Ego">Yaron Herman &amp; Guests: Alter Ego(s)</n><t>M</t>    <k>With his jazz arrangements of Björk and Britney titles, pianist Yaron Herman proved to be the ideal headliner of the festival Île-de-France</k>  </p>
</a>
