<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a><n>The Sound of New York - Matthew Stevens</n><s o="2021-07-19 01:09:00" d="2021-07-19 01:41:00" n="DJazz" id_tv="1166"></s><p><k>Since graduating from Berklee College of Music in 2004, Matthew Stevens has earned an enviable reputation on the contemporary scene by appearing with several leading artists.</k><d>The series The Sound of New York. Music Today and Tomorrow is an exploration of the musical universe of a new generation of New York artists. Of diverse origins and all having a unique history and background, these musicians gave birth to a new sound that influences the music scene around the world. This new generation of artists combines sounds of yesterday and today, interacts with a range of other artistic forms, and plays with many influences, from Afro-American music to classical and contemporary music through hip-hop, R&amp;B, rock, and so much more. Since graduating from Berklee College of Music in 2004, Matthew Stevens has earned an enviable reputation on the contemporary scene by appearing with several leading artists, including Christian Scott, Terri Lyne Carrington, and Esperanza Spalding. Considered &quot;one of the most promising up-and-coming jazz guitarists of his generation,&quot; Stevens was named in the &quot;Emerging Guitarists&quot; category at DownBeat magazine's 63rd annual DownBeat Critics Poll. His performances have been acclaimed by several leading publications and media, including DownBeat, NPR, Jazz Times, Billboard, and The New York Times, and his first studio album, Woodwork, garnered rave reviews, including from LA Weekly which describes the album as an &quot;amalgam of modern jazz and neo-fusion elements that demonstrate an impressive sound versatility and ingenious production.&quot; On tour, Stevens traveled the United States, Canada, Europe, Asia, South Africa, and South America. He is also Adjunct Professor at New School and has conducted workshops at the Maryland Summer Jazz Workshop, USC and Berklee College of Music.</d></p><i><w>https://tv.sms.cz/televize/djazz/20210719/1540202296-The-sound-of-new-york-matthew-stevens</w></i><x></x></a>
