<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2021-07-11 05:01:34"><p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 05:09:00" d="2021-07-18 06:14:00"><n>Ibrahim Maalouf - On The Footsteps of Hildegard</n><t>M</t>    <k>With a children's choir and brass band, jazz trumpeter Ibrahim Maalouf performs music inspired by the 12th-century composer Hildegard of Bingen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 06:14:00" d="2021-07-18 07:00:00"><n>The Hammond© Sessions: Lachy Doley Group</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 07:00:00" d="2021-07-18 08:01:00"><n>Tel Aviv Sessions: Gilad Abro</n><t>M</t>    <k>The prestigious jazz club Levontin 7 presents bass player Gilad Abro and his Trio. Along with pianist Nitai Hershkovits and drummer Amir Bresler</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 08:01:00" d="2021-07-18 09:19:00"><n>Tinariwen: Concert Bouffes du Nord</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Malian-Berber band Tinariwen performed a one-off acoustic concert at the Théâtre des Bouffes du Nord in Paris during their European tour in the spring of 2011</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 09:19:00" d="2021-07-18 10:01:00"><n>Agnes Gosling Quartet - InJazz 2019</n><t>M</t>    <k>Agnes Gosling has matured as a writer and arranger. With her quartet, Gosling honors the tradition of great acoustic jazz while exploring new sounds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 10:01:00" d="2021-07-18 10:55:00"><n>Tivoli Utrecht: Sven Hammond Soul</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 10:55:00" d="2021-07-18 11:34:00"><n u="Miriam Makeba Live at Estival Lugano">Miriam Makeba Live at Estival Lugano 1985</n><t>M</t>    <k>Miriam Makeba, also named Mama Africa, was a South African singer, actress, United Nations goodwill ambassador, and civil-rights activist. She brought</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 11:34:00" d="2021-07-18 11:50:00"><n>BIRDtv: Myles Sanko</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of BIRD.tv (2015) presents the London-based French-Ghanian soul jazz singer Myles Sanko (.1980). His exceptional voice, his lyrics</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 11:50:00" d="2021-07-18 14:02:00"><n>Dee Dee Bridgewater: Red Earth</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this film, Grammy-winning American jazz singer Dee Dee Bridgewater explores her Malian roots. Aided by producer Cheick Tidiane Seck, she works</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 14:02:00" d="2021-07-18 14:49:00"><n>Paradox Live: Wolfert Brederode</n><t>M</t>    <k>In the TV show PARADOX LIVE you get a taste of the greatest concerts and interviews with artists from all around the world. This episode of PARADOX</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 14:49:00" d="2021-07-18 15:40:00"><n>George Shearing: The South Bank Show</n><t>M</t>    <k>George Shearing, blind since birth, is one of the world's greatest jazz pianists. Filmed on both sides of the Atlantic, this tribute to Shearing showcases</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 15:40:00" d="2021-07-18 16:36:00"><n>JazzArt Orchestra &amp; Jason Marsalis - Theater Odeon</n><t>M</t>    <k>Together with drummer and vibraphonist Jason Marsalis, the Dutch JazzArt Orchestra explores various intricacies of modern jazz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 16:36:00" d="2021-07-18 17:38:00"><n>Episode 3: Miles Davis - Jazz Greats</n><t>M</t>    <k>American trumpeter Miles Davis pioneered bebop, cool jazz, hardbop, modal jazz, and electronic music. On October 11, 1964, he performed in Milan with tenor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 17:38:00" d="2021-07-18 19:09:00"><n>Big Yuki - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>Big Yuki ventures a musical leap into the future. His unique compositions combine jazz, hiphop, soul, rock, and electronics. At Moods, Big Yuki blows up a storm on stage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 19:09:00" d="2021-07-18 21:00:00"><n>Benny Golson Quintet Feat Flavio Boltro</n><t>M</t>    <k>Creator of &quot;Whisper Not&quot;, one of the most famous standards, Benny Golson has composed more than 300 pieces for the biggest names in jazz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 21:00:00" d="2021-07-18 22:01:00"><n>Lionel Hampton - Münchner Klaviersommer</n><t>M</t>    <k>At Münchner Klaviersommer 1994, legendary American swing band leader Lionel Hampton performed jazz standards with Junior Mance on piano, Jimmy Woode</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 22:01:00" d="2021-07-18 23:30:00"><n>Royal Southern Brotherhood: Live at La Traverse</n><t>M</t>    <k>A spectacular gathering with the powerful rhythms of New Orleans and Southern rock. The band, led by Cyril Neville, Bart Walker and Tyrone Vaughan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-18 23:30:00" d="2021-07-19 00:00:00"><n>Marcus Miller: Thoughts on Miles</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this 2009 portrait of Marcus Miller, Miller looks back on his relationship with Miles Davis. He shares countless stories of the recording process</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-19 00:00:00" d="2021-07-19 01:09:00"><n>Runtown - La Machine de Moulin Rouge</n><t>M</t>    <k>Enjoy Runtown's first concert in Paris, where the Nigerian superstar brings many guests to his show. One of the most talented Nigerian afrobeat scenes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-19 01:09:00" d="2021-07-19 01:41:00"><n>The Sound of New York - Matthew Stevens</n><t>M</t>    <k>Since graduating from Berklee College of Music in 2004, Matthew Stevens has earned an enviable reputation on the contemporary scene by appearing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-19 01:41:00" d="2021-07-19 03:41:00"><n>Florian Favre Trio - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>Pianist Florian Favre has already earned a firm place on the Swiss jazz scene. His trio, with Manu Hagmann on bass and Arthur Hnatek on drums, performs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-19 03:41:00" d="2021-07-19 04:31:00"><n>MotorMusic: Hamster Axis of the one-click Panther</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode features energetic, unpolished jazz with a touch of humour: the young Antwerp band 'Hamster Axis of the one-click Panther'. The quintet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-19 04:31:00" d="2021-07-19 05:34:00"><n>Marius Neset - Jazz in Duketown</n><t>M</t>    <k>Copenhagen-based Norwegian saxophonist Marius Neset is known internationally for his collaborations with People Are Machines, Kaktusch, JazzKamikaze</k>  </p>
</a>
