<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-05-10 04:36:21"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-17 06:07:00" d="2020-05-17 07:00:00"><n>Agnes Gosling Quartet - InJazz 2019</n><t>M</t>    <k>Agnes Gosling has matured as a writer and arranger. With her quartet, Gosling honors the tradition of great acoustic jazz while exploring new sounds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-17 07:00:00" d="2020-05-17 08:19:00"><n>November Music: R. Frerichs/H. Alizadeh/Cello8ctet</n><t>M</t>    <k>The November Music festival in 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands is the ultimate event for experiencing a broad range of music. It features a wonderful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-17 08:19:00" d="2020-05-17 09:24:00"><n>Teus Nobel live at the Bimhuis Amsterdam</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teus Nobel is a Dutch trumpet and flugelhorn player. This broadcast was recorded at the Amsterdam BIMhuis. is based on his second album 'Legacy' This performance (2015)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-17 09:24:00" d="2020-05-17 10:02:00"><n>Une Soirée de Poche: Feist</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Pocket Party series (Les Soirées de Poche) consists of musical sessions and concerts recorded in intimate settings. This concert by Canadian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-17 10:02:00" d="2020-05-17 11:06:00"><n>Joon Moon: Live at Cabaret Frappé</n><t>M</t>    <k>Although Joon Moon's name and sound evoke the hushed world of old Hollywood, Joon Moon was born out of a resolutely modern encounter – the kind of meeting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-17 11:06:00" d="2020-05-17 11:45:00"><n u="Miriam Makeba Live at Estival Lugano">Miriam Makeba Live at Estival Lugano 1985</n><t>M</t>    <k>Miriam Makeba, also named Mama Africa, was a South African singer, actress, United Nations goodwill ambassador, and civil-rights activist. She brought</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-17 11:45:00" d="2020-05-17 12:01:00"><n>BIRDtv: Orlando Julius</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode (2015) features an old-timer from African music: the saxophonist and composer Orlando Julius (.1943). Doubtlessly, he is royalty among</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-17 12:01:00" d="2020-05-17 14:02:00"><n>Live at The Metro Theatre</n><t>M</t>    <k>The unconventional Sia Kate Isobelle Furler, simply known as Sia, has gained worldwide attention over the last few years. Her unique stage presence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-17 14:02:00" d="2020-05-17 14:51:00"><n>Paradox Live: Vein ft. Greg Osby</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of PARADOX LIVE presents the Swiss jazz band VEIN accompanied by saxophone player Greg Osby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-17 14:51:00" d="2020-05-17 15:40:00"><n u="North Sea Jazz Cruise Episode">North Sea Jazz Cruise Episode 2</n><t>M</t>    <k>MS Rotterdam turns into the world's largest jazz club for a cruise that arrives in Rotterdam on the opening night of the prestigious North</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-17 15:40:00" d="2020-05-17 16:12:00"><n>SWART. - InJazz 2019</n><t>M</t>    <k>SWART. is a modern jazz group founded by the Dutch saxophonist and composer Celia Swart. SWART.'s live performances balance intellectual creative</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-17 16:12:00" d="2020-05-17 17:24:00"><n>Django Reinhardt Tribute: Beets &amp; Rosenberg</n><t>M</t>    <k>The treasured compositions of guitarist Django Reinhardt, the founding father of hot club jazz, are engraved in everyone's memory. With infectious</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-17 17:24:00" d="2020-05-17 19:26:00"><n>Sylvie Courvoisier Trio - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sylvie Courvoisier Trio plays a contemporary take on the 1990s downtown Manhattan Knitting Factory scene. Virtuoso pianist Courvoisier likes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-17 19:26:00" d="2020-05-17 21:00:00"><n>Jazz Open Stuttgart: Blue Note All Stars</n><t>M</t>    <k>This concert features the &quot;Young Lions&quot; of the 90's, the cream of contemporary Jazz musicians. As a team of individualists, they mix new and traditional</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-17 21:00:00" d="2020-05-17 22:09:00"><n>Shai Maestro Trio - Jazz a La Villette</n><t>M</t>    <k>With his personal signature sound, Shai Maestro expresses an incredible musical fluidity that qualifies this trio as one of the most powerful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-17 22:09:00" d="2020-05-17 23:38:00"><n>Royal Southern Brotherhood: Live at La Traverse</n><t>M</t>    <k>A spectacular gathering with the powerful rhythms of New Orleans and Southern rock. The band, led by Cyril Neville, Bart Walker and Tyrone Vaughan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-17 23:38:00" d="2020-05-18 00:00:00"><n>Rebirth: Richard Lemz</n><t>M</t>    <k>The short documentary Rebirth in The Amsterdam Red Light District illustrates how brutal drummer Richard Lems' life was as an addict, portraying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-18 00:00:00" d="2020-05-18 01:21:00"><n>Jazzed Out Tokyo</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jazzed Out proves that a jazz session can take place anywhere. In this episode, Tokyo serves as a backdrop for Kyoto Jazz Massive, Sleep Walker, and Quasimode</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-18 01:21:00" d="2020-05-18 01:46:00"><n>Visions of Music: Rhythm &amp; Jews</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of the Visions of Music series is titled &quot;Rhythm and Jews&quot; but could also be called &quot;Klezmer&quot;. Klezmer is a Yiddish word that qualifies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-18 01:46:00" d="2020-05-18 03:46:00"><n>Florian Favre Trio - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>Pianist Florian Favre has already earned a firm place on the Swiss jazz scene. His trio, with Manu Hagmann on bass and Arthur Hnatek on drums, performs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-18 03:46:00" d="2020-05-18 04:34:00"><n>Belgium Sessions: Alano Gruarin Trio</n><t>M</t>    <k>Alano Gruarin's dynamic and enthusiastic personality in combination with his colourful virtuosity is reflected in his compositions: surprising modulations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-18 04:34:00" d="2020-05-18 05:18:00"><n>Misc: Jérôme Beaulieu live in Montreal</n><t>M</t>    <k>Modern jazz with a twist, based on a group effort rather than on personal virtuosity: 'Misc'! The 'Trio Jérôme Beaulieu' quickly made a name for itself</k>  </p>
</a>
