<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-05-31 04:36:13"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 06:01:00" d="2020-06-07 07:00:00"><n>Under the Surface - Live at Bimhuis 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Dutch band Under the Surface, formed by drummer Joost Lijbaart, vocalist Sanne Rambags and guitarist Bram Stadhouders, expresses its unique musical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 07:00:00" d="2020-06-07 08:00:00"><n u="Charlie Byrd Trio">Charlie Byrd Trio 1</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 08:00:00" d="2020-06-07 09:09:00"><n>Tel Aviv Sessions: Eli Degibri</n><t>M</t>    <k>This concert features Eli Degibri with Gadi Lehavi at the Enav Cultural Center. This duo is a great tribute to the music and produces an incredible emotion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 09:09:00" d="2020-06-07 10:02:00"><n>Seine Sessions: Funk &amp; Afro</n><t>M</t>    <k>Entitled &quot;Funk &amp; Afro&quot;, this episode of the Seine Sessions (2016) hosted by Eddy King presents unique performances, and interviews</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 10:02:00" d="2020-06-07 11:09:00"><n>Lianne La Havas - Casino de Paris</n><t>M</t>    <k>Lianne La Havas' performance at Casino de Paris shows the British singer-songwriter at her best. This concert is part of La Havas' 'Blood Tour', promoting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 11:09:00" d="2020-06-07 12:01:00"><n u="Tania Maria: Live at Estival Lugano">Tania Maria: Live at Estival Lugano 1987</n><t>M</t>    <k>This performance of Brazilian Tania Maria promises to make you want to dance. The singer, composer and pianist sets fire to the Estival scene with her pop and jazzy song</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 12:01:00" d="2020-06-07 12:17:00"><n>BIRDtv: Hypnotic Brass Ensemble</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rotterdam's BIRD is a club, café, and restaurant with a live music program that's deeply rooted in jazz. This episode is dedicated to seven brothers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 12:17:00" d="2020-06-07 14:02:00"><n>Ellen Pels - Love 1/2</n><t>M</t>    <k>Dutch jazz singer Ellen Pels presents her latest release, &quot;Love.&quot; Recorded live at Theater Odeon in Zwolle, the Netherlands, Ellen is joined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 14:02:00" d="2020-06-07 14:48:00"><n>Paradox Live: Jeroen van Vliet Moon Trio</n><t>M</t>    <k>In the TV show PARADOX LIVE (2016) you get a taste of the greatest concerts and interviews with artists from all around the world. This episode of PARADOX</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 14:48:00" d="2020-06-07 15:37:00"><n>Dee Dee Bridgewater: Motherland</n><t>M</t>    <k>With 'Red Earth', American singer Dee Dee Bridgewater goes on a Malian journey that merges and melds all borders. She brings her own experiences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 15:37:00" d="2020-06-07 16:33:00"><n>JazzArt Orchestra &amp; Jason Marsalis - Theater Odeon</n><t>M</t>    <k>Together with drummer and vibraphonist Jason Marsalis, the Dutch JazzArt Orchestra explores various intricacies of modern jazz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 16:33:00" d="2020-06-07 17:27:00"><n>Louis 'Satchmo' Armstrong and His All Stars</n><t>M</t>    <k>Louis Armstrong: Live in '59 is one of the only known complete Armstrong concerts from the 1950s to be captured on film. This 55-minute set, filmed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 17:27:00" d="2020-06-07 19:24:00"><n>Nik Bärtsch's Ronin Rhythm Clan - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>Ronin Rhythm Clan evolved from jazz club Moods back in 2002, where pianist Nik Bärtsch was artist-in-residence. Today, Bärtsch is known as founding father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 19:24:00" d="2020-06-07 21:00:00"><n>Jazz Open Stuttgart: Blue Note All Stars</n><t>M</t>    <k>This concert features the &quot;Young Lions&quot; of the 90's, the cream of contemporary Jazz musicians. As a team of individualists, they mix new and traditional</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 21:00:00" d="2020-06-07 22:01:00"><n>James &quot;Blood&quot; Ulmer - Phalanx Revisited</n><t>M</t>    <k>James 'Blood' Ulmer remains an initiator of 'free funk', which rebelled against the new order of neo-bop in the eighties. Now most of his original peers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 22:01:00" d="2020-06-07 23:19:00"><n>Thjorb?rn Risager &amp; The Black Tornado</n><t>M</t>    <k>Anyone who hears Thorbj?rn Risager singing rightly presumes that the artist comes from the American Midwest, as his powerful voice cuts through with the right twang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 23:19:00" d="2020-06-08 00:00:00"><n>Portrait of Sam Moore</n><t>M</t>    <k>'The legend of the groove' is a series of documentaries about musicians who, between the late 1950s and now, have radically influenced the music of today's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-08 00:00:00" d="2020-06-08 00:58:00"><n>Big Freedia - Eurockéennes 2015</n><t>M</t>    <k>New Orleans' Big Freedia has been popularizing bounce music, a subgenre of hip-hop, since the 1990s. Freedia is one of the most flamboyant artists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-08 00:58:00" d="2020-06-08 01:23:00"><n>Portrait of Ike Turner</n><t>M</t>    <k>'The legend of the groove' is a series of documentaries about musicians who, between the late 1950s and now, have radically influenced the music of today's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-08 01:23:00" d="2020-06-08 02:52:00"><n>Hadar Noiberg &amp; Chano Domínguez Duo - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>Israeli flautist Hadar Noiberg and Spanish pianist Chano Domínguez merge jazz and international music. They borrow from their respective countries' rhythms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-08 02:52:00" d="2020-06-08 03:52:00"><n>MotorMusic Jazz Session: From Rossini to Piazzolla</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode is all about the Habanera Duo, which sprung from a meeting of minds between flutist Marc Grauwels and accordion player Christophe Delporte</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-08 03:52:00" d="2020-06-08 04:37:00"><n>Daahoud Salim Quintet - InJazz 2019</n><t>M</t>    <k>Daahoud Salim and his group have already performed at major stages and festivals in Europe. They have won several impressive European jazz awards in 2016 and 2017</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-08 04:37:00" d="2020-06-08 07:00:00"><n>Omar Sosa - Quarteto Afrocubano</n><t>M</t>    <k>For his 2018 performance at Théâtre de Villefranche-sur-Saône, Omar Sosa brings to stage his Quarteto Afrocubano members Childo Tomas (electric</k>  </p>
</a>
