<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2021-07-09 07:26:21"><p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 05:19:00" d="2021-07-14 05:52:00"><n>Seine Sessions: Free &amp; Afro Jazz</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of Seine Sessions 'Free &amp; Afro Jazz', presented by Eddy King, shows unique blues performances and interviews of among Fantazio, Eddy Lopez and Banoit Savard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 05:52:00" d="2021-07-14 07:00:00"><n>The Morgenland Festival: I Will Not Be Sad</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jivan Gasparyan Jr has always been inspired by the folk melodies of his native Armenia. His grandfather, also a musician, taught him the art of duduk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 07:00:00" d="2021-07-14 08:01:00"><n>Rhoda Scott &amp; La Velle: Hammond, Soul and Blues</n><t>M</t>    <k>Although American soul and jazz organist Rhoda Scott spent most of her career in France, this performance at the antique theatre of Vienne is special</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 08:01:00" d="2021-07-14 09:04:00"><n>Tel Aviv Sessions: Avi Lebovich Orchestra</n><t>M</t>    <k>The legendary Yellow Submarine Jazz Club in Jerusalem presents trombonist Avi Lebovich and his Orchestra. The Orchestra is a contemporary incarnation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 09:04:00" d="2021-07-14 10:03:00"><n>Charles Lloyd Quartet live in Brussels</n><t>M</t>    <k>This 1966 recording features Charles Lloyd's quartet, accompanied by Keith Jarrett (piano), Cecil McBee (double bass) and Jack DeJohnette (drums), playing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 10:03:00" d="2021-07-14 10:47:00"><n>NSJ Archive: Astrud Gilberto &amp; Stan Getz</n><t>M</t>    <k>This concert from the North Sea Jazz Archives presents a compilation with music of Astrud Gilberto &amp; Stan Getz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 10:47:00" d="2021-07-14 12:04:00"><n>Lalah Hathaway - Sing Jazz 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>Winner of five Grammys in four consecutive years, including the Grammy for best R&amp;B album in 2017, Lalah Hathaway is a force impossible to ignore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 12:04:00" d="2021-07-14 13:16:00"><n>Christian Scott - The Centennial Trilogy</n><t>M</t>    <k>At his 2018 show at La Coopérative de Mai, Christian Scott celebrates 100 years of jazz with the program &quot;The Centennial Trilogy.&quot; Expect a unique</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 13:16:00" d="2021-07-14 14:00:00"><n>Portrait of Dee Dee Bridgewater</n><t>M</t>    <k>'The legend of the groove' is a series of documentaries about musicians who, between the late 1950s and now, have radically influenced the music of today's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 14:00:00" d="2021-07-14 15:06:00"><n>Celebrating Bird</n><t>M</t>    <k>Virtuoso saxophonist Charlie Parker was one of the great legends in American music. He created a new style of jazz and won equal fame as</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 15:06:00" d="2021-07-14 16:34:00"><n>Hadar Noiberg &amp; Chano Domínguez Duo - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>Israeli flautist Hadar Noiberg and Spanish pianist Chano Domínguez merge jazz and international music. They borrow from their respective countries' rhythms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 16:34:00" d="2021-07-14 17:52:00"><n>Thjorb?rn Risager &amp; The Black Tornado</n><t>M</t>    <k>Anyone who hears Thorbj?rn Risager singing rightly presumes that the artist comes from the American Midwest, as his powerful voice cuts through with the right twang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 17:52:00" d="2021-07-14 18:33:00"><n>Nelida Karr - WOMEX 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Nelida Karr, sings, plays various instruments. Her music reflects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 18:33:00" d="2021-07-14 19:20:00"><n>Jazz Legends: Show Time at the Blue Note</n><t>M</t>    <k>This show at the Blue Note takes us back to 1967 for an amazing night of jazz at the Blue Note Jazz Club in Brussels. Featuring Ted Curson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 19:20:00" d="2021-07-14 20:28:00"><n>MotorMusic Jazz Sessions: De Beren Gieren</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Dutch-Belgian acoustic-electronic piano threesome 'De Beren Gieren' ('The Bears Shriek', 'Les Ours Vautours') are known for their unique energetic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 20:28:00" d="2021-07-14 21:00:00"><n>The Sound of New York - Damión Reid</n><t>M</t>    <k>Damion Reid has toured with some of the biggest names in music including Greg Osby, Terence Blanchard, Robert Glasper, Cassandra Wilson, Bruce Hornsby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 21:00:00" d="2021-07-14 21:37:00"><n>Ruben Hein &amp; NJJO - Jazz in Duketown</n><t>M</t>    <k>Dutch singer, pianist, composer and bandleader Ruben Hein is artistic director and conductor of the National Youth Jazz Orchestra (NJJO). He performs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-14 21:37:00" d="2021-07-15 00:00:00"><n>Remember Häns'che Weiss - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>French guitar virtuoso Biréli Lagrene pays tribute to one of the most prominent exponents of gipsy jazz: German guitarist Häns'che Weiss (1951-2016)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 00:00:00" d="2021-07-15 00:36:00"><n u="Duets: Carla Bley and Steve Swallow in">Duets: Carla Bley and Steve Swallow in 1988</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 1988 Steve Swallow and Carla Bley began performing duet concerts in Europe, the United States, South America and Japan. Duets, an album of their songs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 00:36:00" d="2021-07-15 02:17:00"><n>Electro Deluxe au Trianon</n><t>M</t>    <k>Composed of 13 talented musicians, the Electro Deluxe ensemble offers a unique combination of jazz, funk, electronic music, and rap. Their Welcome</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 02:17:00" d="2021-07-15 03:17:00"><n>Ellen Pels - Love 2/2</n><t>M</t>    <k>Dutch jazz singer Ellen Pels presents her latest release, &quot;Love.&quot; Recorded live at Theater Odeon in Zwolle, the Netherlands, Ellen is joined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 03:17:00" d="2021-07-15 03:50:00"><n>Marion Williams Sings Spirituals</n><t>M</t>    <k>You can't help but be carried away by the powerful voice Marion Williams, who, with backing from her group and backup singers, sings gospel songs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-15 03:50:00" d="2021-07-15 05:37:00"><n>David Murray Quartet feat. Saul Williams - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>David Murray researched the relationship between avant-garde and tradition in a way that makes him stand out among his saxophonist peers. For his latest</k>  </p>
</a>
