<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2020-05-25 04:55:10"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-01 07:00:00" d="2020-06-01 07:59:00"><n>Louis Armstrong: Live in Australia</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 1964 Louis Armstrong recorded his biggest-selling record, Hello, Dolly! He made assorted television appearances, especially in the 1950s and 1960s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-01 07:59:00" d="2020-06-01 09:09:00"><n>Rhoda Scott &amp; La Velle: Hammond, Soul and Blues</n><t>M</t>    <k>Although American soul and jazz organist Rhoda Scott spent most of her career in France, this performance at the antique theatre of Vienne is special</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-01 09:09:00" d="2020-06-01 10:02:00"><n>Une Soirée de Poche: St. Paul &amp; The Broken Bones</n><t>M</t>    <k>Discover a thrilling performance by St. Paul and The Broken Bones, a soulful sextet from Birmingham, Alabama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-01 10:02:00" d="2020-06-01 12:04:00"><n>Live at The Metro Theatre</n><t>M</t>    <k>Angus &amp; Julia Stone are an Australian brother-sister folk-blues group which formed in 2006. Their parents played as a folk duo before Julia and Angus were born</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-01 12:04:00" d="2020-06-01 12:49:00"><n>Une Soirée de Poche: Timber Timbre</n><t>M</t>    <k>Canada's Timber Timbre is composed of musicians Taylor Kirk, Simon Trottier, Mathieu Charbonneau, and Mark Wheaton. With its timeless sound, the group</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-01 12:49:00" d="2020-06-01 14:04:00"><n>The Morgenland Festival: VIVA!</n><t>M</t>    <k>&quot;Viva&quot; is a perfect mixture of various instruments and musicians from all over the world. Vocalists Aynur and Dima Oshno perform with the All Star Band</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-01 14:04:00" d="2020-06-01 15:10:00"><n>Eartha Kitt: The Most Exciting Woman in the World</n><t>M</t>    <k>Fall in love with Eartha Kitt, powerhouse queen of blues and jazz with international flair. You'll be swooned by her devotion on stage, her throaty purr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-01 15:10:00" d="2020-06-01 15:40:00"><n>Mario Batkovic - WOMEX 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Mario Batkovic, aims to explore the sonic possibilities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-01 15:40:00" d="2020-06-01 17:42:00"><n>Yves Theiler Trio - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>Yves Theiler Trio plays contemporary jazz full of intricate rhythms. Never losing their wide appeal, the three musicians play contrasting polyrhythms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-01 17:42:00" d="2020-06-01 18:12:00"><n>Paradox Live: Vein ft. Greg Osby</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of PARADOX LIVE presents the Swiss jazz band VEIN accompanied by saxophone player Greg Osby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-01 18:12:00" d="2020-06-01 19:02:00"><n>Sonny Rollins Live in Denmark</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sonny Rollins: Live in '65 &amp; '68 features two intimate concerts filmed in the '60s for Danish television at the pinnacle of one of his most creative periods</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-01 19:02:00" d="2020-06-01 20:02:00"><n>Philip Clemo 'Dream Maps' - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Philip Clemo 'Dream Maps' is an interactive multimedia project consisting of six artists. Led by multidisciplinary artist Philip Clemo and exploring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-01 20:02:00" d="2020-06-01 21:00:00"><n>TorTube: Eric Vloeimans &amp; Florian Weber</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this broadcast of TorTube, the great trumpeter Eric Vloeimans and his associate, pianist Florian Weber, perform a set named &quot;A good conversation&quot; ('Een goed gesprek')</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-01 21:00:00" d="2020-06-01 22:40:00"><n>Fred Pallem &amp; Le Sacre du Tympan</n><t>M</t>    <k>Under the musical direction of Fred Pallem, the ensemble Le Sacre du Tympan delivers a tribute to the music of François de Roubaix, who can be described</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-01 22:40:00" d="2020-06-02 00:00:00"><n>John Lurie: A Lounge Lizard Alone</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 1978, John Lurie formed The Lounge Lizards jazz ensemble with his brother Evan; the pair played music together for 20 years. However, in this New Year's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-02 00:00:00" d="2020-06-02 01:25:00"><n>Tinariwen: Concert Bouffes du Nord</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Malian-Berber band Tinariwen performed a one-off acoustic concert at the Théâtre des Bouffes du Nord in Paris during their European tour in the spring of 2011</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-02 01:25:00" d="2020-06-02 02:23:00"><n u="Scatter The Atoms That Remain Part">Scatter The Atoms That Remain Part 2</n><t>M</t>    <k>Scatter The Atoms That Remain is a jazz quartet consisting of drummer Franklin Kiermyer, saxophonist Jovan Alexandre, pianist Davis Whitfield, and bassist Otto Gardner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-02 02:23:00" d="2020-06-02 03:44:00"><n>Cassandra Wilson: Soft Winds</n><t>M</t>    <k>Cassandra Wilson is an unequaled vocalist with a distinctive style; a jazz singer for a new generation. 'Soft Winds' sees her performing first-rate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-02 03:44:00" d="2020-06-02 05:39:00"><n>Sao Paulo Samba</n><t>M</t>    <k>Orquestra Sinfônica do Estado de Sao Paulo, John Neschling</k>  </p>
</a>
