<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-04-10 04:38:07"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 05:11:00" d="2020-04-17 05:57:00"><n>Jazzmeia Horn - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jazzmeia Horn is a winner of the 2015 Thelonious Monk Institute International Jazz Competition. Blending spirituality, scat singing, smooth vocals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 05:57:00" d="2020-04-17 07:00:00"><n>Agnes Gosling Quartet - InJazz 2019</n><t>M</t>    <k>Agnes Gosling has matured as a writer and arranger. With her quartet, Gosling honors the tradition of great acoustic jazz while exploring new sounds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 07:00:00" d="2020-04-17 08:22:00"><n>Thomas Carbou: Spectacle Au Bleury</n><t>M</t>    <k>Thomas Carbou and Patrick Graham share an almost telepathic rapport, blending spontaneous improvisation, electronic looping, and Brazilian and Indian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 08:22:00" d="2020-04-17 09:29:00"><n>Sarah Vaughan Live in '58 &amp; 64: The Divine One</n><t>M</t>    <k>This concert features the Divine One in her prime, wrapping her sultry voice around jazz standards such as Lover Man. Performances like these demonstrate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 09:29:00" d="2020-04-17 10:02:00"><n>Visions of Music: The Latin Tinge</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this episode of the Visions of Music series, Tito Puente explains the origins of Latin jazz, a trend founded in the '30s and' 40s by Dizzy Gillespie and Chano Pozo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 10:02:00" d="2020-04-17 11:07:00"><n>A Different Way: Rodolfo Mederos</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rodolfo Mederos is a bandoneonist, a composer with an enormous oeuvre, one of the authorities on the tango – and an inspiration to new generations of musicians</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 11:07:00" d="2020-04-17 12:20:00"><n>Buzz Bros Band - Same New Story</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 12:20:00" d="2020-04-17 14:02:00"><n>New Cool Collective Big Band at the Oosterpoort</n><t>M</t>    <k>New Cool Collective have been happily grooving on 24 years of fame thanks to their unique mix of jazz, dance, latin, salsa, afrobeat and boogaloo During this show (2010)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 14:02:00" d="2020-04-17 14:49:00"><n>Colin Stetson Solo at Pitchfork</n><t>M</t>    <k>This impressive solo concert by Colin Stetso, an American saxophonist known for his unique musical style influenced by a wide range of jazz genres</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 14:49:00" d="2020-04-17 16:32:00"><n u="Yaron Herman &amp; Guests: Alter Ego">Yaron Herman &amp; Guests: Alter Ego(s)</n><t>M</t>    <k>With his jazz arrangements of Björk and Britney titles, pianist Yaron Herman proved to be the ideal headliner of the festival Île-de-France</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 16:32:00" d="2020-04-17 17:35:00"><n u="Erroll Garner: Belgium">Erroll Garner: Belgium 1963</n><t>M</t>    <k>Erroll Garner was one of jazz's true original players and this showcases his improvisational brilliance on a parade of his most classic numbers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 17:35:00" d="2020-04-17 19:10:00"><n>Charles Bradley - Musiques en Stock 2016</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rooting his music in funk, soul and R&amp;B, Charles Bradley is hailed for shaping the contagious sound of Daptone Records. His 2016 performance at France's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 19:10:00" d="2020-04-17 20:03:00"><n>Live at the Office: BIGYUKI &amp; Now vs Now</n><t>M</t>    <k>Take a peek into Rotterdam's BIRD club, named after New Yorker saxophonist Charlie Parker. Discover a fantastic live concert deeply rooted in jazz, funk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 20:03:00" d="2020-04-17 21:00:00"><n>Paradox Live: James Brandon Lewis</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of PARADOX LIVE presents the American saxophone player James Brandon Lewis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 21:00:00" d="2020-04-17 21:55:00"><n>Gregory Porter - Jazz a Vienne</n><t>M</t>    <k>Gregory Porter's magnificent, burnished baritone can sink into a lyric with luxurious ease, the melody gently sculpted into new shapes at every turn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 21:55:00" d="2020-04-17 23:12:00"><n>Christian Scott - The Centennial Trilogy</n><t>M</t>    <k>At his 2018 show at La Coopérative de Mai, Christian Scott celebrates 100 years of jazz with the program &quot;The Centennial Trilogy.&quot; Expect a unique</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 23:12:00" d="2020-04-18 00:00:00"><n>Seine Sessions: Funk &amp; Afro</n><t>M</t>    <k>Entitled &quot;Funk &amp; Afro&quot;, this episode of the Seine Sessions (2016) hosted by Eddy King presents unique performances, and interviews</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 00:00:00" d="2020-04-18 01:33:00"><n>Agujetas, Cantaor</n><t>M</t>    <k>Manuel Agujetas is one of the greatest flamenco singers of all time, and one of the last representatives of the Jerez School and of the 'Cante Jondo'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 01:33:00" d="2020-04-18 02:19:00"><n>Petros Klampanis Group - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Petros Klampanis is a Greek bass player who now resides in the United States. Influenced early on by many music styles in Greece, Klampanis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 02:19:00" d="2020-04-18 02:56:00"><n>Adam Baldych Quartet - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Adam Baldych is an outstanding Polish violin player, known for his unparalleled classical technique. He is supported by the talented trio of Krzysztof</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 02:56:00" d="2020-04-18 03:56:00"><n>The MotorMusic Jazz Sessions: SCHNTZL</n><t>M</t>    <k>This MotorMusic Jazz Sessions episode features Belgian musicians from jazz duo SCHNTZL: Hendrik Lasure (piano) and Casper Van De Velde (drums)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 03:56:00" d="2020-04-18 04:54:00"><n>Motor Music Jazz - Mike Del Ferro &amp; David Linx</n><t>M</t>    <k>Belgium singer David Linx and Dutch pianist Mike del Ferro's distinctive voices are expressed through polyphonic contemporary musical pieces, inspired</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 04:54:00" d="2020-04-18 05:41:00"><n>OZMA - InJazz 2019</n><t>M</t>    <k>The French collective OZMA combines jazz's freedom with chamber music's finesse, rock's raw energy, and electronic soundscapes. Their performances dazzle</k>  </p>
</a>
