<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2020-04-12 04:34:37"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 05:27:00" d="2020-04-19 06:05:00"><n>Toko Telo - WOMEX 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Malagasy power trio Toko Telo, combines dazzling musicianship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 06:05:00" d="2020-04-19 07:00:00"><n>Jacques Kuba Séguin: L'étude des Lueurs</n><t>M</t>    <k>Trumpeter Jacques Kuba Séguin's ensemble unites some of Montreal's most expressive musicians: double bassist Frédéric Alarie, pianist Jonathan Cayer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 07:00:00" d="2020-04-19 08:04:00"><n>Buffalo Sax Hero: Don Menza in New Orleans</n><t>M</t>    <k>Legendary hardbop pianist Cedar Walton's super trio of bassist Tony Dumas and drummer Ralph Penland is joined by two stellar veterans of the great</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 08:04:00" d="2020-04-19 09:10:00"><n>Tel Aviv Sessions: Gilad Abro</n><t>M</t>    <k>The prestigious jazz club Levontin 7 presents bass player Gilad Abro and his Trio. Along with pianist Nitai Hershkovits and drummer Amir Bresler</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 09:10:00" d="2020-04-19 10:02:00"><n>Belgium Sessions: Trio Florizoone - Massot</n><t>M</t>    <k>The trio Massot/Florizoone/Horbaczewski pushes the boundaries of jazz, folk and classical music. When improvising, the trio produces the weirdest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 10:02:00" d="2020-04-19 11:36:00"><n>Live at The Sydney Entertainment Centre</n><t>M</t>    <k>Daryl Hall and John Oates wisely reunited a few years ago after a string of solo projects, and they put on the kind of show that makes it hard to believe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 11:36:00" d="2020-04-19 12:15:00"><n u="Miriam Makeba Live at Estival Lugano">Miriam Makeba Live at Estival Lugano 1985</n><t>M</t>    <k>Miriam Makeba, also named Mama Africa, was a South African singer, actress, United Nations goodwill ambassador, and civil-rights activist. She brought</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 12:15:00" d="2020-04-19 12:31:00"><n>BIRDtv: Boogieball</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode is a fantastic registration of the after party of the North Sea Jazz Festival: Boogieball. This mega jam session is a great coming together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 12:31:00" d="2020-04-19 14:01:00"><n>Anderson .Paak - Eurockéennes 2016</n><t>M</t>    <k>Anderson .Paak's performance at France's Eurockéennes Festival comes in the aftermath of his groundbreaking album 'Malibu'. In his show the artist presents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 14:01:00" d="2020-04-19 14:49:00"><n>Paradox Live: Bertus Borgers &amp; The Young Retro's</n><t>M</t>    <k>PARADOX Tilburg is the most intimate jazz club in the Netherlands, with a devoted audience from all across Europe. This episode of PARADOX LIVE presents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 14:49:00" d="2020-04-19 15:48:00"><n u="Blue Note: A Story of Modern Jazz - Part">Blue Note: A Story of Modern Jazz - Part I</n><t>M</t>    <k>&quot;Blue Note - A Story of Modern Jazz&quot; tells the story of Alfred Lion and Francis Wolff and their record label. It is the story of the rise of Modern Jazz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 15:48:00" d="2020-04-19 16:50:00"><n>Archie Shepp - Stars In Your Eyes</n><t>M</t>    <k>Directed during the Jazz festival in Porquerolles 2010, the documentary focuses on the links and meeting point between saxophonist Archie Shepp and guitarist Marc Ribot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 16:50:00" d="2020-04-19 17:10:00"><n>Sammy Price and the Harlem Beggars</n><t>M</t>    <k>Pianist, singer and civil rights activist Sammy Price is joined by the gospel singers known as the Harlem Beggars for spirited renditions of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 17:10:00" d="2020-04-19 19:14:00"><n>Yves Theiler Trio - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>Yves Theiler Trio plays contemporary jazz full of intricate rhythms. Never losing their wide appeal, the three musicians play contrasting polyrhythms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 19:14:00" d="2020-04-19 21:00:00"><n>Till Brönner - A Night in Berlin</n><t>M</t>    <k>Produced in the highest image and sound quality, this exclusive, 72-minute concert faithfully reflects the unique aesthetics and sophistication</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 21:00:00" d="2020-04-19 22:02:00"><n>McCoy Tyner Trio &amp; Ravi Coltrane - Jazz a Vienne</n><t>M</t>    <k>The legendary pianist McCoy Tyner has become one of the most influential pianists in jazz history. As a member of the John Coltrane Quartet in the 1960s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 22:02:00" d="2020-04-19 23:22:00"><n>Travellin' Blues: Big Daddy Wilson</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 23:22:00" d="2020-04-20 00:00:00"><n>Visions of Music: The Arabian Connection</n><t>M</t>    <k>The fascinating documentary Visions of Music - The Arabian Connection is mainly narrated by Rabih Abou-Khalil, who puts in context the history of music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-20 00:00:00" d="2020-04-20 01:04:00"><n u="Soul &amp; Jazz LIVE! Episode">Soul &amp; Jazz LIVE! Episode 4</n><t>M</t>    <k>Soul &amp; Jazz LIVE! episode 4 includes Michael J McEvoy, Maurice Brown, Resolution 88, Lindsey Webster, Bill Laurance, Pocket Dragon, YolanDa Brown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-20 01:04:00" d="2020-04-20 01:32:00"><n>Portrait of Plunky Branch</n><t>M</t>    <k>'The legend of the groove' is a series of documentaries about musicians who, between the late 1950s and now, have radically influenced the music of today's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-20 01:32:00" d="2020-04-20 02:49:00"><n>Klischee - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>Klischee is one of Switzerland's most in-demand live acts. Although it started out as a studio project, this band soon transformed into a stage favorite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-20 02:49:00" d="2020-04-20 03:54:00"><n>The MotorMusic Jazz Sessions: Dominic J. Marshall</n><t>M</t>    <k>This MotorMusic Jazz Sessions episode features the British Dominic J. Marshall trio. With his incredible energy and authenticity, Marshall</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-20 03:54:00" d="2020-04-20 04:54:00"><n>The Paris Reunion Band</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Paris Reunion Band was formed as homage to Kenny Clarke and the spirit of his fellow Paris jazzmen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-20 04:54:00" d="2020-04-20 07:00:00"><n>Gilberto Gil: Jazz a Vienne</n><t>M</t>    <k>Brazilian artist Gilberto Gil returns to Jazz a Vienne with music inspired by his latest album 'Fé na Festa': a mixture of celebration, tradition</k>  </p>
</a>
