<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2020-05-30 04:40:55"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 05:04:00" d="2020-06-06 05:33:00"><n>Julie Campiche - Schaffhauser Jazz Festival 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>On May 24, 2018, the Schaffhauser Jazz Festival hosted a performance by harpist Julie Campiche's quartet. Two of the group's own compositions develop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 05:33:00" d="2020-06-06 07:00:00"><n>Franco Ambrosetti Quintet live at Estival Lugano</n><t>M</t>    <k>The composer, trumpeter and bugle player Franco Ambrossetti performs with his quintet in his native Lugano as part of the Estival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 07:00:00" d="2020-06-06 08:21:00"><n>Terrasson &amp; Belmondo: A Nous Garo</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 08:21:00" d="2020-06-06 09:19:00"><n>Tel Aviv Sessions: Gilad Abro</n><t>M</t>    <k>The prestigious jazz club Levontin 7 presents bass player Gilad Abro and his Trio. Along with pianist Nitai Hershkovits and drummer Amir Bresler</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 09:19:00" d="2020-06-06 10:02:00"><n>Quincy Jones: 'Q' conducting his 'Dream Band'</n><t>M</t>    <k>'Jazz Icons: Quincy Jones' spotlights a young 'Q' conducting his 'dream band'—an 18-piece orchestra of world-renowned players such as Clark Terry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 10:02:00" d="2020-06-06 10:36:00"><n>Cecile McLorin Salvant Quartet - Jazz a Vienne</n><t>M</t>    <k>Singer Cecile McLorin Salvant performs vaudeville, country, blues, broadway songs, rarities, and her own compositions. An audience member once described</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 10:36:00" d="2020-06-06 11:05:00"><n>Kamil Piotrowicz Sextet - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Kamil Piotrowicz Sextet has already gained wide recognition in Poland. Featuring original music composed by pianist Kamil Piotrowicz, the group</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 11:05:00" d="2020-06-06 11:37:00"><n>Naissam Jalal Quest of the Invisible - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>In her trio, flutist Naissam Jalal brings together pianist Leonardo Montana and double bassist Claude Tchamitchian. The band's repertoire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 11:37:00" d="2020-06-06 14:00:00"><n u="Yaron Herman &amp; Guests: Alter Ego">Yaron Herman &amp; Guests: Alter Ego(s)</n><t>M</t>    <k>With his jazz arrangements of Björk and Britney titles, pianist Yaron Herman proved to be the ideal headliner of the festival Île-de-France</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 14:00:00" d="2020-06-06 15:44:00"><n>André Manoukian invite China Moses a Montlouis</n><t>M</t>    <k>French jazz musician André Manoukian, notably known for his role on the jury of the French version of Pop Idol, performs with bassist Christophe Wallemme</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 15:44:00" d="2020-06-06 15:55:00"><n>BIRDtv: Badbadnotgood</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode (2014) features the four-piece jazz/hip hop ensemble BADBADNOTGOOD, whose collaborators include the likes of rapper 'Tyler, The Creator'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 15:55:00" d="2020-06-06 16:23:00"><n>Seine Sessions: Hiphop Jazz</n><t>M</t>    <k>Entitled &quot;Hip-Hop Jazz&quot;, this episode of the Seine Sessions hosted by Eddy King presents unique performances, and interviews with DjeuhDjoah, Lieutenant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 16:23:00" d="2020-06-06 17:16:00"><n>Youssou N'Dour: Africa Live at Dakar</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 17:16:00" d="2020-06-06 18:14:00"><n>Seven Eleven: Back to the Source</n><t>M</t>    <k>Dutch band Seven Eleven is a mix of funk, jazz and hip hop. Founded in 1987, Seven Eleven is one of the first Dutch bands to perform with rappers, having</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 18:14:00" d="2020-06-06 19:09:00"><n>Brussels Jazz Orchestra &amp; Bert Joris - Big Valses</n><t>M</t>    <k>Founded in 1993 by Frank Vaganée, Serge Plume and Marc Godfroid, the Brussels Jazz Orchestra is recognised and has been subsidised by the Flemish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 19:09:00" d="2020-06-06 20:01:00"><n>Palais des Beaux-Arts: The Modern Jazz Quartet</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Modern Jazz Quartet (MJQ) was composed of Milt 'Bags' Jackson on vibraphone, John Lewis (piano), Percy Heath (bass), and Connie Kay (drums)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 20:01:00" d="2020-06-06 21:00:00"><n u="Sarah Vaughan &quot;The Divine One&quot; in">Sarah Vaughan &quot;The Divine One&quot; in 1958</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sarah Vaughan: Live in '58 &amp; 64 features the Divine One in her prime, wrapping her sultry voice around jazz standards such as &quot;Lover Man&quot;, &quot;Misty&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 21:00:00" d="2020-06-06 21:24:00"><n>Frank Paavo Quintet - JazzConnect, Westbroek</n><t>M</t>    <k>The saxophonist Frank Paavo has been active on the Amsterdam and Netherland's jazz scene since the early 1980s. His music is inspired by the hard-bop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 21:24:00" d="2020-06-06 22:23:00"><n>Chucho Valdes - Jazz a Vienne</n><t>M</t>    <k>Chucho Valdes and his Afro-Cuban Messengers are the prime example of Latin-inspired jazz music. During his performance the legendary pianist brings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 22:23:00" d="2020-06-07 00:00:00"><n>Jazz meets Klezmer: The Kol Simcha World Quintet</n><t>M</t>    <k>Kol Simcha is creating klezmer music for the new millenium. The quintet has adapted the music's traditional format by pairing a front line of clarinet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 00:00:00" d="2020-06-07 00:58:00"><n>Edina Mokus - WOMEX 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Edina Szirtes Mokus, expresses her talents with her own projects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 00:58:00" d="2020-06-07 01:28:00"><n>Atom String Quartet - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Atom String Quartet is known for its virtuosity as well as improvisation skills. Influenced by Polish folklore, classical, jazz, and contemporary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 01:28:00" d="2020-06-07 02:09:00"><n>Gabriel Grossi Quintet - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Gabriel Grossi is a Brazilian harmonica player, and today he is regarded as one of the leading musicians of the instrument. Paying his tributes to Mauricio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 02:09:00" d="2020-06-07 03:12:00"><n>Christian Scott - Jazz a Vienne 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Christian Scott aTunde Adjuah blends jazz fusion, hip-hop and alternative rock, developing a unique and distinct sound. Scott's performance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 03:12:00" d="2020-06-07 04:24:00"><n>Didier Lockwood - Theatre du Chatelet</n><t>M</t>    <k>On the Châtelet theatre's stage, French violinist Didier Lockwood celebrates the fortieth anniversary of a busy career together with some of his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 04:24:00" d="2020-06-07 04:56:00"><n>Moondog &amp; The London Saxophonique</n><t>M</t>    <k>Moondog, a gaunt, mysterious and extravagantly-garbed blind street musician was celebrated among New Yorkers for two decades before gaining acclaim</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-07 04:56:00" d="2020-06-07 06:01:00"><n>Ibrahim Maalouf - On The Footsteps of Hildegard</n><t>M</t>    <k>With a children's choir and brass band, jazz trumpeter Ibrahim Maalouf performs music inspired by the 12th-century composer Hildegard of Bingen</k>  </p>
</a>
