<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-05-29 04:36:36"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-05 05:21:00" d="2020-06-05 05:57:00"><n>Adam Baldych Quartet - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Adam Baldych is an outstanding Polish violin player, known for his unparalleled classical technique. He is supported by the talented trio of Krzysztof</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-05 05:57:00" d="2020-06-05 07:00:00"><n>PC Qwintett: 75th birthday Pierre Courbois</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-05 07:00:00" d="2020-06-05 08:04:00"><n>Saluzzi, Mariano &amp; Dauner live in Stuttgart</n><t>M</t>    <k>Dino Saluzzi, one of Argentina's tango music masters, has been building his legacy since the 80s. His accordion-like bandoneon defines Argentina's tango music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-05 08:04:00" d="2020-06-05 09:06:00"><n>Tel Aviv Sessions: Avi Lebovich Orchestra</n><t>M</t>    <k>The legendary Yellow Submarine Jazz Club in Jerusalem presents trombonist Avi Lebovich and his Orchestra. The Orchestra is a contemporary incarnation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-05 09:06:00" d="2020-06-05 10:03:00"><n>The Sound of New York - Stefon Harris</n><t>M</t>    <k>The passionate play, the energetic stage presence and the amazing virtuosity of vibraphonist Stefon Harris have propelled him to the forefront of the current jazz scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-05 10:03:00" d="2020-06-05 10:53:00"><n u="North Sea Jazz Cruise Episode">North Sea Jazz Cruise Episode 4</n><t>M</t>    <k>MS Rotterdam turns into the world's largest jazz club for a cruise that arrives in Rotterdam on the opening night of the prestigious North</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-05 10:53:00" d="2020-06-05 11:55:00"><n>Destination Nuits d'Afrique 2019</n><t>M</t>    <k>Degg J Force 3, Ramon Chicharron and Sékouba Bambino come from different musical cultures: hiphop, cumbia and jazz. In spite of this, these artists share</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-05 11:55:00" d="2020-06-05 14:03:00"><n>NSJ Big Band Show: Skymasters &amp; Dizzy Gillespie</n><t>M</t>    <k>This broadcast from the North Sea Jazz Archives presents the amazing Dizzy Gillespie, accompanied by The Skymasters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-05 14:03:00" d="2020-06-05 15:07:00"><n>Michiel Borstlap: Blue, Reflective &amp; Frames</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-05 15:07:00" d="2020-06-05 16:40:00"><n>Fred Hersch Trio - Jazz a Ramatuelle</n><t>M</t>    <k>At the age of 63, Fred Hersch is unquestionably one of today's key figures in jazz piano. Supported by John Hebert (double bass) and Eric McPherson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-05 16:40:00" d="2020-06-05 17:29:00"><n>Masters of Jazz: Oscar Peterson '63, '64 &amp; '65</n><t>M</t>    <k>Oscar Peterson: Live in '63, '64 &amp; '65 follows the incredible Oscar Peterson Trio through three years in three different countries, delighting audiences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-05 17:29:00" d="2020-06-05 19:01:00"><n>Scott DuBois Quartet Live In Munich</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rising star of the jazz guitar Scott DuBois leads his quartet, consisting of Gebhard Ullmann (reeds), Thomas Morgan (bass), and Kresten Osgood (drums)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-05 19:01:00" d="2020-06-05 20:04:00"><n>Live at the Office: BIGYUKI &amp; Now vs Now</n><t>M</t>    <k>Take a peek into Rotterdam's BIRD club, named after New Yorker saxophonist Charlie Parker. Discover a fantastic live concert deeply rooted in jazz, funk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-05 20:04:00" d="2020-06-05 21:00:00"><n>Une Soirée de Poche: Saul Williams</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2014, the musician Saul Williams had a very specific idea: to create a film under the city, in the &quot;real&quot; catacombs of Paris, those that are illegal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-05 21:00:00" d="2020-06-05 22:34:00"><n>Incognito - Sing Jazz 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>Incognito is an acid jazz project formed by Jean-Paul &quot;Bluey&quot; Maunick and Paul &quot;Tubbs&quot; Williams, original members of the disco-funk Light of the World</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-05 22:34:00" d="2020-06-06 00:00:00"><n>Pitchfork Music Festival: Run The Jewels</n><t>M</t>    <k>Run the Jewels, rap group founded by rapper/producer EL-P and rapper Killer Mike in 2013, delivered an electrifying performance at the 2015 Pitchfork Music Festival in Paris</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 00:00:00" d="2020-06-06 01:43:00"><n>Play Your Own Thing: A Story Of Jazz In Europe</n><t>M</t>    <k>„Play Your Own Thing&quot; portrays the development of jazz in Europe with its emancipation and expertise, its freedom and individualism, the development</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 01:43:00" d="2020-06-06 02:14:00"><n>Shake Stew - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Shake Stew is probably the most popular jazz act in their homeland, Austria. Combining afrobeat, jazz grooves, and hypnotic soundscapes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 02:14:00" d="2020-06-06 02:49:00"><n>Pauli Lyytinen Magnetia Orkesteri - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Pauli Lyytinen Magnetia Orkesteri is a classic jazz quartet that doesn't sound classic - the fresh sound is instilled in the quartet's DNA. Mixing steady</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 02:49:00" d="2020-06-06 03:50:00"><n>The MotorMusic Jazz Sessions: SCHNTZL</n><t>M</t>    <k>This MotorMusic Jazz Sessions episode features Belgian musicians from jazz duo SCHNTZL: Hendrik Lasure (piano) and Casper Van De Velde (drums)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-06 03:50:00" d="2020-06-06 05:04:00"><n>Kim Hoorweg at BIRD, Rotterdam</n><t>M</t>    <k>Kim Hoorweg landed her first record deal at the young age of 14. Since then, the Dutch singer has been involved in various music projects</k>  </p>
</a>
