<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a><n>The Sound of New York - Gerald Clayton</n><s o="2019-08-20 09:29:00" d="2019-08-20 10:15:00" n="DJazz" id_tv="1166"></s><p><k>The Sound of New York - Gerald Clayton
2018. Gerald Clayton. New York City, New York, United States</k><d>The series The Sound of New York. Music Today and Tomorrow is an exploration of the musical universe of a new generation of New York artists. Of diverse origins and all having a unique history and background, these musicians gave birth to a new sound that influences the music scene around the world. This new generation of artists combines sounds of yesterday and today, interacts with a range of other artistic forms, and plays with many influences, from Afro-American music to classical and contemporary music through hip-hop, R&amp;B, rock, and so much more. With three albums, several studio projects and countless international performances under the tie, Gerald Clayton has established himself over the last eight years as a leading figure in a new generation of jazz artists who master the vast array of styles that make up the vocabulary of today's jazz. Hailed by the New York Times for his &quot;impressive presence,&quot; Clayton is currently becoming an increasingly important place in the long and rich tradition of jazz. Born in 1984 in Utrecht, The Netherlands, Clayton moved to the United States at a young age. Having grown up in a musical family - his father is bassist and composer John Clayton, and his uncle saxophonist Jeff Clayton - he has always been exposed to a wide variety of musical styles. Clayton began his formal education at the prestigious Los Angeles County High School for the Arts, and continued his education at the USC Thorton School of Music. Named four times for a Grammy Award, the talented pianist and composer has performed on stage and in the studio with artists like Diana Krall, Roy Hargrove, Dianne Rives, Ambrose Akinmusire, Dayna Stephens, Kendrick Scott, John Scofield, Ben Williams, Charles Lloyd, and many others.</d></p><i><w>http://tv.sms.cz/televize/djazz/20190820/1310324427-The-sound-of-new-york-gerald-clayton</w></i><x></x></a>
