<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-05-27 04:36:16"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 05:29:00" d="2020-06-03 06:02:00"><n>Seine Sessions: World Music</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of Seine Sessions 'World Music', presented by Eddy King, shows unique performances and interviews of among Teófilo Chantre, Tiwitine and Kinsy Ray</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 06:02:00" d="2020-06-03 07:00:00"><n>The Morgenland Festival: Needless to Say</n><t>M</t>    <k>Featuring graduate of the Boston Conservatory and vocalist Dima Oshno, both songs &quot;Dream&quot; and &quot;Mugam&quot; are played by the All Star Band and express a range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 07:00:00" d="2020-06-03 08:03:00"><n>Bluesette: Toots Thielemans Songbook</n><t>M</t>    <k>Brussels-born harmonica player Jean &quot;Toots&quot; Thielemans started out as a jazz guitarist, but after his breakthrough as harmonica virtuoso, he has always</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 08:03:00" d="2020-06-03 09:04:00"><n>Terry Callier: Live in Berlin</n><t>M</t>    <k>Terry Callier, the man who has written music history in the 1960s and 1970s, returns to the stage after a 15 year break</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 09:04:00" d="2020-06-03 10:04:00"><n>Charles Mingus And Eric Dolphy live in Liege</n><t>M</t>    <k>Charles Mingus showcases an exceptional concert performed in April 1965 featuring the lineup: Jaki Byard (piano), Dannie Richmond (drums), Johnny Coles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 10:04:00" d="2020-06-03 10:47:00"><n>Patáx: A Night to Remember 2/2</n><t>M</t>    <k>Patáx presents an accomplished mix of styles, including soul, jazz, funk and hip hop. Led by the passionate Spanish-American percussionist Jorge Perez</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 10:47:00" d="2020-06-03 11:51:00"><n u="The Crusaders: Estival Lugano">The Crusaders: Estival Lugano 1987</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Crusaders, an American jazz fusion group that was popular in the '70s. Their performance at Estival is beyond soulful and an amazing show to watch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 11:51:00" d="2020-06-03 13:03:00"><n>Christian Scott - The Centennial Trilogy</n><t>M</t>    <k>At his 2018 show at La Coopérative de Mai, Christian Scott celebrates 100 years of jazz with the program &quot;The Centennial Trilogy.&quot; Expect a unique</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 13:03:00" d="2020-06-03 14:03:00"><n>The Sound of New York - Bilal</n><t>M</t>    <k>Bilal Sayeed Oliver, better known as Bilal, is an American singer-songwriter and producer currently residing in New York. Hailed by the public and critics</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 14:03:00" d="2020-06-03 15:03:00"><n u="On The Road With Duke Ellington:">On The Road With Duke Ellington: II</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 15:03:00" d="2020-06-03 16:37:00"><n>Hannah Williams &amp; The Affirmations - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>British singer Hannah Williams captures the sound of 1960s soul music, mixing it with funk and rock influences. This groovy blend caught music industry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 16:37:00" d="2020-06-03 17:57:00"><n>Travellin' Blues: Big Daddy Wilson</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 17:57:00" d="2020-06-03 18:44:00"><n>Bakolo Music International - WOMEX 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Bakolo Music International, represents the pioneers of the golden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 18:44:00" d="2020-06-03 19:29:00"><n>Earl 'Fatha' Hines Trio live in Comblain-la-Tour</n><t>M</t>    <k>With his powerful arms, Earl 'Fatha' Hines embraced nearly every era of jazz piano. Fellow pianists and critics regard Hines as a genius on his instrument</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 19:29:00" d="2020-06-03 20:24:00"><n>MotorMusic Jazz Sessions: Sluijs &amp; Vermeulen</n><t>M</t>    <k>Saxophonist Ben Sluijs and pianist Erik Vermeulen both had a classical training. Both musicians have a strong melodic and harmonic approach. Their music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 20:24:00" d="2020-06-03 21:00:00"><n>Blicher Hemmer Gadd - A Music documentary</n><t>M</t>    <k>Award-winning saxophonist Michael Blicher, Hammond wizard Dan Hemmer and legendary drummer Steve Gadd joined forces in 2014 to celebrate their shared</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 21:00:00" d="2020-06-03 22:03:00"><n>Etienne Mbappe - Jazzwoche Burghausen</n><t>M</t>    <k>The talented Cameroonian bassist and singer songwriter Etienne Mbappé surrounds himself with upcoming jazz talent from Paris in his band The Prophets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 22:03:00" d="2020-06-04 00:00:00"><n>Wouter Hamel Live in Paradiso</n><t>M</t>    <k>What Jamie Cullum is to England, Wouter Hamel is to the Netherlands: a performer who knows the difference between jazz and pop!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-04 00:00:00" d="2020-06-04 01:20:00"><n>November Music: R. Frerichs/H. Alizadeh/Cello8ctet</n><t>M</t>    <k>The November Music festival in 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands is the ultimate event for experiencing a broad range of music. It features a wonderful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-04 01:20:00" d="2020-06-04 03:01:00"><n>Electro Deluxe au Trianon</n><t>M</t>    <k>Composed of 13 talented musicians, the Electro Deluxe ensemble offers a unique combination of jazz, funk, electronic music, and rap. Their Welcome</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-04 03:01:00" d="2020-06-04 03:48:00"><n>Sarah McCoy - La Gaite Lyrique</n><t>M</t>    <k>Vocalist and pianist Sarah McCoy carries on a tradition perfected by Tom Waits, Amy Winehouse, Leon Russell, and Nina Simone, who turned the wreckage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-04 03:48:00" d="2020-06-04 04:32:00"><n u="29th Street Saxophone Quartet: Estival">29th Street Saxophone Quartet: Estival 1987</n><t>M</t>    <k>The 29th Street Saxophone Quartet is an American quartet founded in 1982 by alto saxophonists Bobby Watson and Ed Jackson, tenor saxophonist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-04 04:32:00" d="2020-06-04 05:25:00"><n>Istanbul Sessions: Telvin Trio</n><t>M</t>    <k>During the opening night of the Alt Jazz Club, two exceptional guitarists gigged with their respective formations: the veteran guitarist Erkan</k>  </p>
</a>
