<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="20" t="2020-04-13 04:33:10"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-20 07:00:00" d="2020-04-20 08:36:00"><n>Fred Hersch Trio - Jazz a Ramatuelle</n><t>M</t>    <k>At the age of 63, Fred Hersch is unquestionably one of today's key figures in jazz piano. Supported by John Hebert (double bass) and Eric McPherson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-20 08:36:00" d="2020-04-20 09:32:00"><n>Lex Jasper Trio: Happy Days Are Here Again</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-20 09:32:00" d="2020-04-20 10:05:00"><n>North Sea Jazz Archive: Dexter Gordon</n><t>M</t>    <k>'North Sea Jazz Archive' shows an amazing collection of clips recorded at the famous North Sea Jazz Festival in the Netherlands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-20 10:05:00" d="2020-04-20 12:07:00"><n>Live at The Hordern Pavilion</n><t>M</t>    <k>Big hits, booty dancing, stage dives, fan freestyles, A$AP Rocky's debut Down Under tour had it all! At his sold-out Sydney show, hip hop's hottest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-20 12:07:00" d="2020-04-20 12:50:00"><n>Tim Kliphuis and the NCO: The Changing Seasons</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Netherlands Chamber Orchestra commissioned violinist Tim Kliphuis, internationally known for his genre-crossing approach to music, to write</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-20 12:50:00" d="2020-04-20 14:05:00"><n>The Morgenland Festival: The Art of Duo</n><t>M</t>    <k>&quot;The Art of Duo&quot; presents an unprecedented duo featuring pianist Salman Gambarov and sheng player, a Chinese mouth-organ, Wu Wei</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-20 14:05:00" d="2020-04-20 14:59:00"><n u="Sarah Vaughan: Jazz from Newport, Brussels">Sarah Vaughan: Jazz from Newport, Brussels 1973</n><t>M</t>    <k>For the first of two appearances at the 1973 Jazz from Newport Festival in Brussels, Sarah Vaughan and her trio consisting of Carl Schroeder (piano)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-20 14:59:00" d="2020-04-20 16:04:00"><n>Tamara Murphy - Spirograph Studies</n><t>M</t>    <k>Spirograph Studies have leapt onto the Australian music scene with their detailed, textural approach to playing improvised music. Post-rock, post-jazz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-20 16:04:00" d="2020-04-20 17:57:00"><n>Remember Häns'che Weiss - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>French guitar virtuoso Biréli Lagrene pays tribute to one of the most prominent exponents of gipsy jazz: German guitarist Häns'che Weiss (1951-2016)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-20 17:57:00" d="2020-04-20 18:26:00"><n>The Hammond© Sessions: Sven Figee</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-20 18:26:00" d="2020-04-20 19:10:00"><n u="Jimmy Witherspoon Quartet &amp; Rozaa Wortham">Jimmy Witherspoon Quartet &amp; Rozaa Wortham 1985</n><t>M</t>    <k>Estival offers a thrilling and particularly surprising line-up that explores the rich world of contemporary music. Jimmy Witherspoon, known</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-20 19:10:00" d="2020-04-20 20:00:00"><n>Janning Trumann 6 - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Trombonist Janning Trumann's sextet with pianist Lucas Leidinger, trumpeter Verneri Pohjola, vibraphonist Dierk Peters, drummer Thomas Sauerborn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-20 20:00:00" d="2020-04-20 21:00:00"><n>Emie R. Roussel Trio - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Emie R. Roussel Trio delivers creative and bewitching jazz with undeniable ardor and chemistry. Roussel has been experiencing a meteoric rise since</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-20 21:00:00" d="2020-04-20 22:19:00"><n>November Music 2017: Daniel Herskedal</n><t>M</t>    <k>Norwegian tuba player and composer Daniel Herskedal trained at the Trondheim and Copenhagen Music Conservatories. He is at the head of a formidable</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-20 22:19:00" d="2020-04-21 00:00:00"><n>Michel Petrucciani Trio</n><t>M</t>    <k>Recorded in Stuttgart in 1998, this performance features pianist Michel Petrucciani, drummer Steve Gadd and bassist Anthony Jackson. The musicians achieve</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-21 00:00:00" d="2020-04-21 00:58:00"><n>Youssou N'Dour: Africa Live at Dakar</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-21 00:58:00" d="2020-04-21 01:49:00"><n>Istanbul Sessions: Telvin Trio</n><t>M</t>    <k>During the opening night of the Alt Jazz Club, two exceptional guitarists gigged with their respective formations: the veteran guitarist Erkan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-21 01:49:00" d="2020-04-21 02:31:00"><n>Teus Nobel live at the Bimhuis: Legacy</n><t>M</t>    <k>Teus Nobel is a Dutch trumpet and flugelhorn player. Teus dedicates his compositions to his all-time heroes Jarmo Hoogendijk, Woody Shaw, Christian Scott</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-21 02:31:00" d="2020-04-21 04:12:00"><n>André Manoukian invite China Moses a Montlouis</n><t>M</t>    <k>French jazz musician André Manoukian, notably known for his role on the jury of the French version of Pop Idol, performs with bassist Christophe Wallemme</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-21 04:12:00" d="2020-04-21 06:07:00"><n>Gregory Porter at the Blue Note Festival</n><t>M</t>    <k>Gregory Porter's magnificent, burnished baritone can sink into a lyric with luxurious ease, the melody gently sculpted into new shapes at every turn</k>  </p>
</a>
