<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-05-11 04:35:09"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-18 05:18:00" d="2020-05-18 07:00:00"><n>Richard Bona - Jazz a Vienne</n><t>M</t>    <k>The wonderful Richard Bona conquered the world with his bass and his voice a long time ago. On 'Jazz a Vienne' stage Bona once again shows why audiences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-18 07:00:00" d="2020-05-18 07:55:00"><n>Count Basie and his Orchestra live in Charleroi</n><t>M</t>    <k>Count Basie is one of the most important bandleaders of the swing era. With the exception of a brief period in the early '50s, he led</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-18 07:55:00" d="2020-05-18 09:06:00"><n>Tel Aviv Sessions: Eli Degibri</n><t>M</t>    <k>This concert features Eli Degibri with Gadi Lehavi at the Enav Cultural Center. This duo is a great tribute to the music and produces an incredible emotion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-18 09:06:00" d="2020-05-18 10:00:00"><n>Une Soirée de Poche: Son Lux</n><t>M</t>    <k>Son Lux is the dream of Los Angeles composer Ryan Lott, made possible with the help of two New Yorkers: guitarist Rafiq Bhatia and drummer Ian Chang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-18 10:00:00" d="2020-05-18 12:18:00"><n>Django Memories</n><t>M</t>    <k>To celebrate the release of Django, the Parisian New Morning Club pays tribute to the legendary guitarist Django Reinhardt and showcases the virtuosity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-18 12:18:00" d="2020-05-18 12:50:00"><n>North Sea Jazz Archive: Wayne Shorter Quartet</n><t>M</t>    <k>This broadcast from the North Sea Jazz Archives presents the great Wayne Shorter Quartet. Shorter's maxim is to reinvent his music during each concert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-18 12:50:00" d="2020-05-18 14:00:00"><n>Morgenland Festival: One Way Ticket to Damascus</n><t>M</t>    <k>Bursting with sounds that could only be described as magical, &quot;MCO&quot; features the Syrian Expat Philharmonic Orchestra under conductor Naci Özgüç</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-18 14:00:00" d="2020-05-18 15:53:00"><n>Gregory Porter at the Blue Note Festival</n><t>M</t>    <k>Gregory Porter's magnificent, burnished baritone can sink into a lyric with luxurious ease, the melody gently sculpted into new shapes at every turn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-18 15:53:00" d="2020-05-18 16:48:00"><n>Oum - Music Meeting Festival 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>Singer/songwiter Oum gives a unique glance at ethnic Morrocan musical aesthetics. Deeply influenced by gospel, jazz, soul and R&amp;B genres, today</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-18 16:48:00" d="2020-05-18 17:46:00"><n u="Scatter The Atoms That Remain Part">Scatter The Atoms That Remain Part 2</n><t>M</t>    <k>Scatter The Atoms That Remain is a jazz quartet consisting of drummer Franklin Kiermyer, saxophonist Jovan Alexandre, pianist Davis Whitfield, and bassist Otto Gardner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-18 17:46:00" d="2020-05-18 18:17:00"><n>Une Soirée de Poche: Tinariwen</n><t>M</t>    <k>Their music is hardly ordinary: the traditional North-African music style 'tichumaren' is mixed with elements of western pop and rock music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-18 18:17:00" d="2020-05-18 19:06:00"><n u="Jon Hendricks and Co: Estival">Jon Hendricks and Co: Estival 1986</n><t>M</t>    <k>John Carl Hendricks is one of the instigators of &quot;vocalese&quot;, an art form that aims to add lyrics to existing instrumental pieces and replace several</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-18 19:06:00" d="2020-05-18 20:02:00"><n>Simin Tander &amp; Joerg Brinkmann - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Vocalist Simin Tander and cello player Jörg Brinkmann travel far and wide for their sound. Their music transgresses the borders of time in pursuit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-18 20:02:00" d="2020-05-18 21:00:00"><n>Trio Abozekrys - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Trio Abozekrys comprises of oud player Mohamed Abozekry, his brother Abdallah Abozekry on saz, and Nicolas Thé on drums. Their jazz-inflected repertoire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-18 21:00:00" d="2020-05-18 22:12:00"><n>Jazz en Baie: Djangolized with Rhoda Scott</n><t>M</t>    <k>Aurore Voilqué has surrounded herself with an array of talented musicians including Jean-Baptiste Gaudray, Julie Saury, and Rhoda Scott to pay tribute</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-18 22:12:00" d="2020-05-19 00:00:00"><n>La Gaité Lyrique: Robert Glasper &amp; Jason Moran</n><t>M</t>    <k>As part of the Blue Note Jazz Festival and Blue Note Records' 75th anniversary, pianists Robert Glasper and Jason Moran delivered a stunning jazz piano</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-19 00:00:00" d="2020-05-19 01:03:00"><n>Salif Keita &amp; Les Ambassadeurs</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Golden Voice of Africa aka Salif Keita's music is a rich blend of traditional Malian music with European and American influences. Discover the various</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-19 01:03:00" d="2020-05-19 02:44:00"><n>Laurent Coulondre &quot;Gravity Zero&quot; - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>Laurent Coulondre is the rising star of the French jazz scene! His music explores jazz, funk, fusion, progressive rock and hardbop, resulting in groovy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-19 02:44:00" d="2020-05-19 03:16:00"><n>Jacques Kuba Séguin: L'étude des Lueurs</n><t>M</t>    <k>Trumpeter Jacques Kuba Séguin's ensemble unites some of Montreal's most expressive musicians: double bassist Frédéric Alarie, pianist Jonathan Cayer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-19 03:16:00" d="2020-05-19 04:57:00"><n>Mont Saint-Michel: Steve Grossman &amp; Peter King</n><t>M</t>    <k>Every year, the Jazz en Baie festival takes place in the beautiful bay of Mont Saint-Michel. Today's broadcast shows a special gathering between saxophone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-19 04:57:00" d="2020-05-19 05:57:00"><n>Lisa Simone - Blues sur Seine</n><t>M</t>    <k>Lisa Simone, who's the legendary Nina Simone's only child, creates a magical atmosphere of warmth, passion and unity. She is joined on stage by guitarist</k>  </p>
</a>
