<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2020-05-26 04:40:41"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-02 05:39:00" d="2020-06-02 06:41:00"><n>Aretha Franklin: A trip in Paris</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-02 06:41:00" d="2020-06-02 07:00:00"><n>Thelonious Monk live in Palais des Beaux-Arts</n><t>M</t>    <k>Thelonious Monk: Live in '65 features an intimate concert filmed three days apart in Belgium in the Winter of 1965 with a legendary quartet that includes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-02 07:00:00" d="2020-06-02 08:24:00"><n>Jane Monheit: Some Other Time</n><t>M</t>    <k>Discover a phenomenal performance by the young jazz sensation Jane Monheit, recorded at the Jazz Open Stuttgart, in 2003</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-02 08:24:00" d="2020-06-02 09:24:00"><n>Tel Aviv Sessions: Omri Mor</n><t>M</t>    <k>With his passion and his virtuosity, pianist Omri Mor amazes the audience of the music club Zappa in Tel Aviv. Pieces drawn from the heritage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-02 09:24:00" d="2020-06-02 10:04:00"><n>Marcus Miller: Thoughts on Miles</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this 2009 portrait of Marcus Miller, Miller looks back on his relationship with Miles Davis. He shares countless stories of the recording process</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-02 10:04:00" d="2020-06-02 11:09:00"><n>B.B. King: The King of the Blues in Stuttgart</n><t>M</t>    <k>This uptempo, funky performance proves that B.B. King, one of the Masters of the Blues Guitar has still got it. The band features some of today's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-02 11:09:00" d="2020-06-02 12:19:00"><n>Trio Chemirani: Dawâr</n><t>M</t>    <k>The veritable tombak virtuosos of Trio Chemirani, consisting of Chemirani Senior and Juniors, enrapture the Festival de Saintes. The Trio Chemirani's music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-02 12:19:00" d="2020-06-02 14:02:00"><n>Jazzed Out Berlin</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jazzed Out proves that a jazz session can take place anywhere. In this episode, Berlin serves as a backdrop for pianist Wolfert Brederode, and Hyperactive Kid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-02 14:02:00" d="2020-06-02 15:48:00"><n>Brussels Jazz Orchestra: Changing Faces</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Brussels Jazz Orchestra (BJO) is not the kind of jazz orchestra that sticks to standards. During this project the BJO performs with David Linx</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-02 15:48:00" d="2020-06-02 16:19:00"><n u="Duets: Carla Bley and Steve Swallow in">Duets: Carla Bley and Steve Swallow in 1988</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 1988 Steve Swallow and Carla Bley began performing duet concerts in Europe, the United States, South America and Japan. Duets, an album of their songs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-02 16:19:00" d="2020-06-02 16:50:00"><n>High Definition Quartet - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>The High Definition Trio has already gained numerous awards due to its original musical vision. Combining improvisation with contemporary electronic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-02 16:50:00" d="2020-06-02 17:16:00"><n>World Orchestra - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>World Orchestra consists of musicians from all over the world. Taking inspiration from different musical cultures and led by Polish saxophonist Grzech</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-02 17:16:00" d="2020-06-02 18:22:00"><n>MotorMusic Jazz Sessions: Linus</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of the DJAZZ series &quot;Belgium Sessions,&quot; presents 'Linus', a duo of two composers and improvisers: baritone guitar player Ruben Machtelinckx</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-02 18:22:00" d="2020-06-02 20:00:00"><n>Maceo Parker: Jazz a Juan</n><t>M</t>    <k>At 25, saxophonist Maceo Parker played in James Brown's band, but today he is also known for his collaborations with George Clinton's Parliament-Funkadelic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-02 20:00:00" d="2020-06-02 21:00:00"><n>The Morgenland Festival: I Will Not Be Sad</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jivan Gasparyan Jr has always been inspired by the folk melodies of his native Armenia. His grandfather, also a musician, taught him the art of duduk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-02 21:00:00" d="2020-06-02 21:59:00"><n>Wynton in the South Bank Show</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-02 21:59:00" d="2020-06-02 23:00:00"><n>Istanbul Sessions: BaBa ZuLa in Club Nublu</n><t>M</t>    <k>Since its formation in 1996, the band 'Baba Zula' has been mixing traditional music with electro sounds, thus taking the lead in the revival of Turkish jazzfunk scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-02 23:00:00" d="2020-06-03 00:00:00"><n>Comblain-la-Tour Jazz Festival: Jimmy McGriff Trio</n><t>M</t>    <k>Of the major soul-jazz pioneers, Hammond B3 organ player Jimmy McGriff (1936-2008) was the bluesiest and often insisted that he was more of a blues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 00:00:00" d="2020-06-03 00:51:00"><n>Lucibela - WOMEX 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Lucibela, comes from the island of Sao Nicolau. Her assured</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 00:51:00" d="2020-06-03 01:47:00"><n>Oum - Music Meeting Festival 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>Singer/songwiter Oum gives a unique glance at ethnic Morrocan musical aesthetics. Deeply influenced by gospel, jazz, soul and R&amp;B genres, today</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 01:47:00" d="2020-06-03 02:41:00"><n u="Anita Oday Live in Sweden">Anita Oday Live in Sweden 1963</n><t>M</t>    <k>Anita O'Day boasts two wonderful concerts from 1963 and 1970 that present the &quot;jazz singer supreme&quot; in impeccable form. This show is a testimony</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 02:41:00" d="2020-06-03 03:12:00"><n>Une Soirée de Poche: Tinariwen</n><t>M</t>    <k>Their music is hardly ordinary: the traditional North-African music style 'tichumaren' is mixed with elements of western pop and rock music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 03:12:00" d="2020-06-03 03:51:00"><n u="Freddie Hubbard Quintet in Brussels">Freddie Hubbard Quintet in Brussels, 1980</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Freddie Hubbard Quintet livens up the Brussels Jazz Club during this short but sweet session from the summer of 1980. The group consists of Hubbard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-06-03 03:51:00" d="2020-06-03 05:29:00"><n>Mont Saint-Michel: Steve Grossman &amp; Peter King</n><t>M</t>    <k>Every year, the Jazz en Baie festival takes place in the beautiful bay of Mont Saint-Michel. Today's broadcast shows a special gathering between saxophone</k>  </p>
</a>
