<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a><n>The Sound of New York - Luis Perdomo &amp; Mimi Jones</n><s o="2021-07-20 09:03:00" d="2021-07-20 10:00:00" n="DJazz" id_tv="1166"></s><p><k>Born in 1971 in Caracas, Luis Perdomo began appearing on television and radio in Venezuela at the age of 12. Bassist and singer Mimi Jones, born Miriam Sullivan, grew up in the Bronx.</k><d>The series The Sound of New York. Music Today and Tomorrow is an exploration of the musical universe of a new generation of New York artists. Of diverse origins and all having a unique history and background, these musicians gave birth to a new sound that influences the music scene around the world. This new generation of artists combines sounds of yesterday and today, interacts with a range of other artistic forms, and plays with many influences, from Afro-American music to classical and contemporary music, through hip-hop, R&amp;B, rock, and so much more. Born in 1971 in Caracas, Luis Perdomo began appearing on television and radio in Venezuela at the age of 12. Despite his success in his homeland, young Perdomo quickly realized he would have to travel to New York to fulfill his musical dreams. In 1993, Perdomo moved to New York after receiving a scholarship from the Manhattan School of Music. He graduated with a bachelor's degree in 1997 and a master's degree in 2000. Perdomo has collaborated on more than 200 recordings, has performed alongside artists of the caliber of Dave Douglas, David Sanchez and Tom Harrell, was a member of the quartet of Ravi Coltrane for 10 years, and has three albums named at the Grammy Awards in his name. Bassist and singer Mimi Jones, born Miriam Sullivan, grew up in the Bronx. Discovered accidentally by a teacher at the LaGuardia High School of Music and Art, Jones was recruited from the school's jazz ensemble. Jones has been a member of the Tia Fuller Quartet, has been recognized as a US Jazz Ambassador, and toured around the world with artists including Rachel Z, Kenny Barron, Lionel Hampton, Ravi Coltrane, Roy Hargrove, and Luis Perdomo.</d></p><i><w>https://tv.sms.cz/televize/djazz/20210720/1540216477-The-sound-of-new-york-luis-perdomo-mimi-jones</w></i><x></x></a>
