<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-05-12 04:39:20"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-19 05:57:00" d="2020-05-19 07:00:00"><n>Ella Fitzgerald in Brussels: The American Songbook</n><t>M</t>    <k>'Ella Fitzgerald: Live in '57' features 'The First Lady Of Song' in a distinct performance. Shot in Belgium, this 1957 concert sees her performing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-19 07:00:00" d="2020-05-19 08:28:00"><n>Cassandra Wilson: Soft Winds</n><t>M</t>    <k>Cassandra Wilson is an unequaled vocalist with a distinctive style; a jazz singer for a new generation. 'Soft Winds' sees her performing first-rate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-19 08:28:00" d="2020-05-19 09:26:00"><n>Tel Aviv Sessions: Gilad Abro</n><t>M</t>    <k>The prestigious jazz club Levontin 7 presents bass player Gilad Abro and his Trio. Along with pianist Nitai Hershkovits and drummer Amir Bresler</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-19 09:26:00" d="2020-05-19 10:01:00"><n>Visions of Music: Going Back To New Orleans</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of the Visions of Music series is about trumpet player Nicholas Payton, a dynamic performer who plays acoustic jazz and post-bop and enjoys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-19 10:01:00" d="2020-05-19 10:59:00"><n>Peter Beets: Chopin meets the Blues</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this broadcast, Peter Beets teams up with double bassist Marius Beets (Peter's brother) and drummer Gijs Dijkhuizen. The trio presents Chopin's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-19 10:59:00" d="2020-05-19 11:37:00"><n>The Morgenland Festival: Needless to Say</n><t>M</t>    <k>Featuring graduate of the Boston Conservatory and vocalist Dima Oshno, both songs &quot;Dream&quot; and &quot;Mugam&quot; are played by the All Star Band and express a range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-19 11:37:00" d="2020-05-19 14:04:00"><n>Live at The Metro Theatre</n><t>M</t>    <k>Public Enemy, also known as PE, is an influential hip hop group from Long Island, New York, known for its politically charged lyrics, criticism</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-19 14:04:00" d="2020-05-19 15:05:00"><n u="Duke Ellington: Jazz from Newport, Brussels">Duke Ellington: Jazz from Newport, Brussels, 1973</n><t>M</t>    <k>The foremost jazz composer and bandleader of the twentieth century, Duke Ellington, returns with his orchestra to the festival where he revived his career</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-19 15:05:00" d="2020-05-19 16:21:00"><n u="Kurt Rosenwinkel - Bandit">Kurt Rosenwinkel - Bandit 65</n><t>M</t>    <k>Bandit 65 is the breathtakingly virtuoso trio of guitarists Kurt Rosenwinkel and Tim Motzer with percussionist Gintas Janusonis. With great power</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-19 16:21:00" d="2020-05-19 16:53:00"><n>Olga Amelchenko Quartet - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Saxophonist Olga Amelchenko and her new quartet toy with musical boundaries and labels, incorporating modern jazz with folk and rock music, proposing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-19 16:53:00" d="2020-05-19 17:25:00"><n>Janning Trumann 6 - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Trombonist Janning Trumann's sextet with pianist Lucas Leidinger, trumpeter Verneri Pohjola, vibraphonist Dierk Peters, drummer Thomas Sauerborn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-19 17:25:00" d="2020-05-19 18:22:00"><n>MotorMusic Jazz Sessions: Sluijs &amp; Vermeulen</n><t>M</t>    <k>Saxophonist Ben Sluijs and pianist Erik Vermeulen both had a classical training. Both musicians have a strong melodic and harmonic approach. Their music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-19 18:22:00" d="2020-05-19 20:02:00"><n>Mondriaan Jazz 2017: FORQ</n><t>M</t>    <k>Forq is an instrumental quartet with an aggressive sound and a penchant for sonic exploration. The band pushes further down the sonic rabbit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-19 20:02:00" d="2020-05-19 21:00:00"><n>The Morgenland Festival: A Trace of Grace</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode entitled &quot;A Trace Of Grace&quot; features the rich and complex music of Michel Godard and Kayhan Kalhor, two musicians interested in instruments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-19 21:00:00" d="2020-05-19 21:44:00"><n>Oh Purity in Watching Landscapes</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-19 21:44:00" d="2020-05-19 23:06:00"><n>Tinariwen: Concert Bouffes du Nord</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Malian-Berber band Tinariwen performed a one-off acoustic concert at the Théâtre des Bouffes du Nord in Paris during their European tour in the spring of 2011</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-19 23:06:00" d="2020-05-20 00:00:00"><n>Palais des Beaux-Arts: The Modern Jazz Quartet</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Modern Jazz Quartet (MJQ) was composed of Milt 'Bags' Jackson on vibraphone, John Lewis (piano), Percy Heath (bass), and Connie Kay (drums)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 00:00:00" d="2020-05-20 00:45:00"><n>Vishten - WOMEX 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Vishten, has been active for 15 years with traditional French songs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 00:45:00" d="2020-05-20 01:51:00"><n>Tamara Murphy - Spirograph Studies</n><t>M</t>    <k>Spirograph Studies have leapt onto the Australian music scene with their detailed, textural approach to playing improvised music. Post-rock, post-jazz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 01:51:00" d="2020-05-20 02:59:00"><n>Sarah Vaughan Live in '58 &amp; 64: The Divine One</n><t>M</t>    <k>This concert features the Divine One in her prime, wrapping her sultry voice around jazz standards such as Lover Man. Performances like these demonstrate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 02:59:00" d="2020-05-20 03:35:00"><n>Tim Kliphuis and the NCO: The Changing Seasons</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Netherlands Chamber Orchestra commissioned violinist Tim Kliphuis, internationally known for his genre-crossing approach to music, to write</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 03:35:00" d="2020-05-20 04:16:00"><n>Earl 'Fatha' Hines Trio live in Comblain-la-Tour</n><t>M</t>    <k>With his powerful arms, Earl 'Fatha' Hines embraced nearly every era of jazz piano. Fellow pianists and critics regard Hines as a genius on his instrument</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-05-20 04:16:00" d="2020-05-20 05:14:00"><n>Classic Meets Jazz</n><t>M</t>    <k>Tzimon Barto, the young American classical pianist and Wolfgang Dauner, the internationally renowned German jazz pianist join their talents</k>  </p>
</a>
