<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a><n>The Sound of New York - Vicente Archer</n><s o="2019-07-15 01:29:00" d="2019-07-15 02:08:00" n="DJazz" id_tv="1166"></s><p><k>The Sound of New York - Vicente Archer
2018. Vicente Archer. New York City, New York, United States</k><d>The series The Sound of New York. Music Today and Tomorrow is an exploration of the musical universe of a new generation of New York artists. Of diverse origins and all having a unique history and background, these musicians gave birth to a new sound that influences the music scene around the world. This new generation of artists combines sounds of yesterday and today, interacts with a range of other artistic forms, and plays with many influences, from Afro-American music to classical and contemporary music through hip-hop, R&amp;B, rock, and so much more. Guitarist Vicente Archer was born in Woodstock, New York. It was in this historic, culturally rich city that he became interested in great local jazz artists such as Dave Holland, Jimmy Cobb and Jack DeJohnette. Self-taught, Archer began his musical career at the age of 16 by learning guitar to the sound of Wes Montgomery's and George Benson's albums of his parents. He gradually began to make a name for himself by performing with various ensembles in the Hudson Valley area, from Albany to New York. After graduating from high school, Archer was accepted at the New England Conservatory in Boston, where he began studying jazz. After his first year at the NEC, he was transferred to Northeastern University in Boston, where he moved from guitar to acoustic bass. Impressed by Archer's talent, saxophonist Donald Harrison invited him to perform on his Impulse album Free To Be. After graduating, Archer moved to New York, where he quickly began performing on stage and touring with Kenny Garret, Freddie Hubbard, Roy Haynes, Stefon Harris, the Lincoln Center Jazz Orchestra, and Wynton Marsalis. Vicente Archer has established himself today as one of the main new bass players.</d></p><i><w>http://tv.sms.cz/televize/djazz/20190715/1300237136-The-sound-of-new-york-vicente-archer</w></i><x></x></a>
