<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-04-09 04:36:15"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-16 05:11:00" d="2020-04-16 07:00:00"><n>Live in France: Jimmy Smith</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jimmy Smith: Live in '69 boasts an incredible 90-minute concert from 1969 filmed in Paris</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-16 07:00:00" d="2020-04-16 08:00:00"><n>Saluzzi, Mariano &amp; Dauner live in Stuttgart</n><t>M</t>    <k>Dino Saluzzi, one of Argentina's tango music masters, has been building his legacy since the 80s. His accordion-like bandoneon defines Argentina's tango music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-16 08:00:00" d="2020-04-16 09:16:00"><n>November Music: R. Frerichs/H. Alizadeh/Cello8ctet</n><t>M</t>    <k>The November Music festival in 's-Hertogenbosch, the Netherlands is the ultimate event for experiencing a broad range of music. It features a wonderful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-16 09:16:00" d="2020-04-16 10:05:00"><n>Comblain-la-Tour Jazz Festival: Jimmy McGriff Trio</n><t>M</t>    <k>Of the major soul-jazz pioneers, Hammond B3 organ player Jimmy McGriff (1936-2008) was the bluesiest and often insisted that he was more of a blues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-16 10:05:00" d="2020-04-16 10:52:00"><n u="Jazz in Comblain-la-Tour">Jazz in Comblain-la-Tour, 1963</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 1963, the small Belgian town of Comblain-la-Tour hosted the talented groups of Charlie Galbraith, Knut Kiesewetter, Bud Shank and Pim Jacobs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-16 10:52:00" d="2020-04-16 12:51:00"><n>Antonio Farao feat. Gregoire Maret - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>Antonio Farao and Gregoire Maret perform in a dynamic, multi-faceted collaboration of piano and mouth harp. Their program consists of original compositions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-16 12:51:00" d="2020-04-16 14:03:00"><n u="Dusko Gojkovic - Brussels Jazz Club">Dusko Gojkovic - Brussels Jazz Club, 1980</n><t>M</t>    <k>Legendary Serbian jazz trumpeter, composer, and arranger Dusko Gojkovic takes the lead in this intimate concert at Brussels Jazz Club, in 1980</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-16 14:03:00" d="2020-04-16 14:41:00"><n>Belgium Sessions: Hijaz</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this DJAZZ Belgium Sessions performance, which was recorded at AED Studios in Lint, Belgium, we witness Europe's finest jazz musicians at work This performance (2006)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-16 14:41:00" d="2020-04-16 15:32:00"><n>George Shearing: The South Bank Show</n><t>M</t>    <k>George Shearing, blind since birth, is one of the world's greatest jazz pianists. Filmed on both sides of the Atlantic, this tribute to Shearing showcases</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-16 15:32:00" d="2020-04-16 16:43:00"><n>Salomao Soares Trio - Da Pá Virada Sessions</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Salomao Soares Trio consists of Salomao Soares on piano, Paulo Almeida on drums, and Thiago Alves on bass. Band leader Soares was a finalist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-16 16:43:00" d="2020-04-16 17:56:00"><n>Christian Scott - Jazz a Vienne 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Christian Scott aTunde Adjuah blends jazz fusion, hip-hop and alternative rock, developing a unique and distinct sound. Scott's performance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-16 17:56:00" d="2020-04-16 18:51:00"><n>Africa Live! The Concerts: Corneille</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-16 18:51:00" d="2020-04-16 20:04:00"><n>Une Soirée de Poche: Saul Williams</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2014, the musician Saul Williams had a very specific idea: to create a film under the city, in the &quot;real&quot; catacombs of Paris, those that are illegal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-16 20:04:00" d="2020-04-16 21:00:00"><n>Seine Sessions: Hiphop Jazz</n><t>M</t>    <k>Entitled &quot;Hip-Hop Jazz&quot;, this episode of the Seine Sessions hosted by Eddy King presents unique performances, and interviews with DjeuhDjoah, Lieutenant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-16 21:00:00" d="2020-04-16 22:05:00"><n>Joon Moon: Live at Cabaret Frappé</n><t>M</t>    <k>Although Joon Moon's name and sound evoke the hushed world of old Hollywood, Joon Moon was born out of a resolutely modern encounter – the kind of meeting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-16 22:05:00" d="2020-04-16 23:02:00"><n>Istanbul Sessions: Büyükberber</n><t>M</t>    <k>During this concert at the legendary Nardis Jazz Club, clarinetist Oguz Büyükberber is assisted by Erdal Akyol on bass and Cem Aksel on drums</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-16 23:02:00" d="2020-04-17 00:00:00"><n u="Jazz a Antibes Juan-les-pins: John McLaughlin">Jazz a Antibes Juan-les-pins: John McLaughlin 2</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 00:00:00" d="2020-04-17 00:55:00"><n>Matteo Myderwyk - InJazz 2019</n><t>M</t>    <k>Matteo Myderwyk is a 28-year-old Amsterdam-based pianist. He completed his master degree in piano classical and improvised music at Fontys Conservatorium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 00:55:00" d="2020-04-17 02:08:00"><n>Django Reinhardt Tribute: Beets &amp; Rosenberg</n><t>M</t>    <k>The treasured compositions of guitarist Django Reinhardt, the founding father of hot club jazz, are engraved in everyone's memory. With infectious</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 02:08:00" d="2020-04-17 02:37:00"><n>TorTube: Benjamin Herman - Mokum Swing</n><t>M</t>    <k>This recording features Dutch jazz icon Benjamin Herman in collaboration with English brothers and gypsy guitar masters Robin and Kevin Nolan along</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 02:37:00" d="2020-04-17 03:33:00"><n>Istanbul Sessions: Mercan Dede</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this broadcast, Arkin Allen, also known as Mercan Dede, performs at the Borusan Müzik Evi. This Turkish musician and DJ combines the Sufi tradition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 03:33:00" d="2020-04-17 04:43:00"><n>Ricardo Herz Trio - Da Pá Virada Sessions</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Ricardo Herz Trio consists of Ricardo Herz on violin, Michi Ruzitschka on nylon string guitar, and Pedro Ito on percussion. Band leader Ricardo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-17 04:43:00" d="2020-04-17 05:11:00"><n>Kirke Karja Quartet - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Kirke Karja is a new face on the Estonian jazz scene. Yet, the pianist has become one of the brightest young musicians within the homeland's jazz circles</k>  </p>
</a>
