<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-04-16 04:37:51"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-23 05:35:00" d="2020-04-23 07:00:00"><n>The Art Farmer Quartet live In England</n><t>M</t>    <k>Art Farmer: Live in '64 highlights an amazing one-hour concert featuring the great flugelhornist in his prime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-23 07:00:00" d="2020-04-23 08:02:00"><n>Tel Aviv Sessions: Omri Mor</n><t>M</t>    <k>With his passion and his virtuosity, pianist Omri Mor amazes the audience of the music club Zappa in Tel Aviv. Pieces drawn from the heritage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-23 08:02:00" d="2020-04-23 09:23:00"><n>Cassandra Wilson: Soft Winds</n><t>M</t>    <k>Cassandra Wilson is an unequaled vocalist with a distinctive style; a jazz singer for a new generation. 'Soft Winds' sees her performing first-rate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-23 09:23:00" d="2020-04-23 10:04:00"><n>The Definitive Collection: Louis Armstrong</n><t>M</t>    <k>Decades after his death, Louis Armstrong's historical recordings are still unique and widely appreciated. Born in August 1901, Louis Daniel Armstrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-23 10:04:00" d="2020-04-23 10:59:00"><n u="Tania Maria: Live at Estival Lugano">Tania Maria: Live at Estival Lugano 1987</n><t>M</t>    <k>This performance of Brazilian Tania Maria promises to make you want to dance. The singer, composer and pianist sets fire to the Estival scene with her pop and jazzy song</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-23 10:59:00" d="2020-04-23 12:51:00"><n>Spanish Harlem Orchestra - Moods</n><t>M</t>    <k>Spanish Harlem Orchestra rejuvenates New York-style 'salsa dura', performing razor-sharp arrangements to a tee in their high-voltage show at Moods</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-23 12:51:00" d="2020-04-23 14:01:00"><n>Guy Salomon Group - InJazz 2019</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Guy Salamon Group is an Amsterdam-based multi-international band led by Israeli drummer/composer Guy Salamon. The band plays a highly expressive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-23 14:01:00" d="2020-04-23 14:37:00"><n>PC Qwintett: 75th birthday Pierre Courbois</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-23 14:37:00" d="2020-04-23 15:36:00"><n>Crossroads: From Blues to Bossa</n><t>M</t>    <k>From Blues to Bossa On the search for the roots and origins of Jazz, we journey into the European and African music traditions and discover the cultural</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-23 15:36:00" d="2020-04-23 16:25:00"><n>House of the Gipsies - Sing Jazz 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>House of the Gipsies is bringing back the raw rhythms of nomadic tribes in Rajasthan to create a unique sound that can be described as Indo-Gypsy fusion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-23 16:25:00" d="2020-04-23 18:02:00"><n>Jazzed Out London</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jazzed Out proves that a jazz session can take place anywhere. In this episode, London serves as a backdrop for sets by saxophonist Soweto Kinch, and pianist Neil Cowley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-23 18:02:00" d="2020-04-23 18:56:00"><n>Charles Bradley at La Cigale</n><t>M</t>    <k>On April 26, 2012, the world-famous vocalist Charles Bradley and his Extraordinaires grace the stage of the Cigale in Paris</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-23 18:56:00" d="2020-04-23 20:02:00"><n>New York Jazz Quartet: Jazz at Duke's Place</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-23 20:02:00" d="2020-04-23 21:00:00"><n>Seine Sessions: Free &amp; Afro Jazz</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of Seine Sessions 'Free &amp; Afro Jazz', presented by Eddy King, shows unique blues performances and interviews of among Fantazio, Eddy Lopez and Banoit Savard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-23 21:00:00" d="2020-04-23 21:55:00"><n>Tivoli Utrecht: Sven Hammond Soul</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-23 21:55:00" d="2020-04-23 23:06:00"><n>Jeff Moran &amp; Thomas Carbou live a Quebec</n><t>M</t>    <k>Trumpeter Jacques Kuba Séguin's ensemble unites some of Montreal's most expressive musicians: double bassist Frédéric Alarie, pianist Jonathan Cayer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-23 23:06:00" d="2020-04-24 00:00:00"><n>Paradox Live: Harmen Fraanje</n><t>M</t>    <k>In the TV show PARADOX LIVE you get a taste of the greatest concerts and interviews with artists from all around the world. This episode of PARADOX</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-24 00:00:00" d="2020-04-24 01:24:00"><n>Emile Parisien - Jazz a Vienne 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Saxophonist Emile Parisien and accordionist Vincent Peirani present their tribute to Austrian jazz keyboardist Joe Zawinul. Having played</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-24 01:24:00" d="2020-04-24 02:10:00"><n>Mister Joe Williams and the Basie Alumni Band</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Count Basie Alumni Band is joined by Joe Williams for a bluesy performance at the Brussels Jazz Club in 1980</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-24 02:10:00" d="2020-04-24 02:48:00"><n>TorTube: Josee Koning - Who's The Bossa</n><t>M</t>    <k>Who's the Bossa? is a TorTube episode featuring Dutch jazz singer Josee Koning, the leading Brazilian musician in the Netherlands. Inspired by the music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-24 02:48:00" d="2020-04-24 03:58:00"><n>Trio Chemirani: Dawâr</n><t>M</t>    <k>The veritable tombak virtuosos of Trio Chemirani, consisting of Chemirani Senior and Juniors, enrapture the Festival de Saintes. The Trio Chemirani's music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-24 03:58:00" d="2020-04-24 05:00:00"><n>Chucho Valdés Septet: Cuba Cuba</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Chucho Valdés Septet was formed by Chucho Valdés as part of the Jazz Open Stuttgart, in 1999</k>  </p>
</a>
