<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2020-04-11 04:36:07"><p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 05:41:00" d="2020-04-18 07:00:00"><n u="Astrud Gilberto Band Live at Estival Lugano">Astrud Gilberto Band Live at Estival Lugano 1985</n><t>M</t>    <k>Estival offers a thrilling and particularly surprising line-up that explores the rich world of contemporary music. &quot;The Girl From Ipanema&quot;, Astrud</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 07:00:00" d="2020-04-18 07:59:00"><n>Louis Armstrong: Live in Australia</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 1964 Louis Armstrong recorded his biggest-selling record, Hello, Dolly! He made assorted television appearances, especially in the 1950s and 1960s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 07:59:00" d="2020-04-18 09:16:00"><n>Tinariwen: Concert Bouffes du Nord</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Malian-Berber band Tinariwen performed a one-off acoustic concert at the Théâtre des Bouffes du Nord in Paris during their European tour in the spring of 2011</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 09:16:00" d="2020-04-18 10:07:00"><n>The Definitive Collection: Duke Ellington</n><t>M</t>    <k>Born Edward Kennedy Ellington on April 29, 1899, Duke Ellington is one of the world's greatest musicians and composers. Duke and his orchestra toured</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 10:07:00" d="2020-04-18 11:32:00"><n>Live at The Metro Theatre</n><t>M</t>    <k>The unconventional Sia Kate Isobelle Furler, simply known as Sia, has gained worldwide attention over the last few years. Her unique stage presence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 11:32:00" d="2020-04-18 12:04:00"><n>Shinya Fukumori Trio - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Shinya Fukumori Trio performs music inspired by the Showa era of Japan fused with European aesthetics. Led by Munich-based Japanese drummer Shinya</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 12:04:00" d="2020-04-18 12:40:00"><n>OZMA - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>The music of the French five-piece ensemble OZMA approaches electronic music soundscapes with the freedom of jazz, the refinement of chamber music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 12:40:00" d="2020-04-18 14:01:00"><n>Paolo Fresu 'Dentro il Vulcano' Live in Stromboli</n><t>M</t>    <k>Paolo Fresu began studying the trumpet at age 11 in his native Sardinia. After several incursions into the world of pop, Fresu fell in</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 14:01:00" d="2020-04-18 15:33:00"><n>Peter Beets Trio &amp; Goudsmit: Tribute to Montgomery</n><t>M</t>    <k>Peter Beets teams up with Anton Goudsmit (guitar) in tribute to guitar icon and founding father of modern jazz Wes Montgomery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 15:33:00" d="2020-04-18 16:04:00"><n>BIRDtv: Boogieball with The NPG and Questlove</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 16:04:00" d="2020-04-18 16:35:00"><n>Seine Sessions: World Music</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of Seine Sessions 'World Music', presented by Eddy King, shows unique performances and interviews of among Teófilo Chantre, Tiwitine and Kinsy Ray</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 16:35:00" d="2020-04-18 17:27:00"><n>Tinariwen - Les Déferlantes Sud de France 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Grammy Award-winning group Tinariwen comes from the Sahara Desert region of northern Mali. AllMusic calls Tinariwen 'the voice of rebellion'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 17:27:00" d="2020-04-18 18:09:00"><n>Nelida Karr - WOMEX 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Nelida Karr, sings, plays various instruments. Her music reflects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 18:09:00" d="2020-04-18 19:23:00"><n>Buddy Rich and his Big Band at North Sea Jazz</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 19:23:00" d="2020-04-18 20:00:00"><n>Face au Public: Odetta</n><t>M</t>    <k>Legendary African-American folk singer Odetta (1930-2008) sang her spirituals with immeasurable sorrow and anguish. Her spiritual music expresses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 20:00:00" d="2020-04-18 21:00:00"><n>Jazz de Matosinhos and Sinfónica do Porto: Layas</n><t>M</t>    <k>30 minutes of. Orquestra Jazz de Matosinhos and Orquestra Sinfónica do Porto Casa da Música with Dirk Brossé (musical direction), Jason Moran (piano) and J.A</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 21:00:00" d="2020-04-18 22:26:00"><n>Münchner Klaviersommer: Eliane Elias Trio</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-18 22:26:00" d="2020-04-19 00:00:00"><n>Jazz meets Klezmer: The Kol Simcha World Quintet</n><t>M</t>    <k>Kol Simcha is creating klezmer music for the new millenium. The quintet has adapted the music's traditional format by pairing a front line of clarinet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 00:00:00" d="2020-04-19 00:51:00"><n>Invisible World - WOMEX 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Invisible World, is based at the jazz crossroads where East European</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 00:51:00" d="2020-04-19 01:19:00"><n>Kamil Piotrowicz Sextet - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Kamil Piotrowicz Sextet has already gained wide recognition in Poland. Featuring original music composed by pianist Kamil Piotrowicz, the group</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 01:19:00" d="2020-04-19 01:50:00"><n>Benjamin Schaefer Quiet Fire - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Benjamin Schaefer Quiet Fire consists of five young European jazz musicians. Exploring different emotional states of human beings through the music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 01:50:00" d="2020-04-19 03:33:00"><n>Live at The Metro Theatre</n><t>M</t>    <k>Public Enemy, also known as PE, is an influential hip hop group from Long Island, New York, known for its politically charged lyrics, criticism</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 03:33:00" d="2020-04-19 04:23:00"><n>Masters of Jazz: Oscar Peterson '63, '64 &amp; '65</n><t>M</t>    <k>Oscar Peterson: Live in '63, '64 &amp; '65 follows the incredible Oscar Peterson Trio through three years in three different countries, delighting audiences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2020-04-19 04:23:00" d="2020-04-19 05:27:00"><n>Elliot Galvin Trio - November Music</n><t>M</t>    <k>The pianist Elliot Galvin is a member of the young UK jazz group Dinosaur. Performing with his own trio, the gifted musician has been compared to Django</k>  </p>
</a>
