<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2021-07-13 05:05:21"><p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-20 05:10:00" d="2021-07-20 07:00:00"><n>Ray Charles - The North Sea Jazz</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 1980, legendary American singer-pianist Ray Charles gave an unforgettable performance at the North Sea Jazz Festival in The Hague. This mercurial artist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-20 07:00:00" d="2021-07-20 08:00:00"><n>Count Basie and his Orchestra live in Charleroi</n><t>M</t>    <k>Count Basie is one of the most important bandleaders of the swing era. With the exception of a brief period in the early '50s, he led</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-20 08:00:00" d="2021-07-20 09:03:00"><n>Chamber music: Sissoko &amp; Segal</n><t>M</t>    <k>The concert shows a brilliant interplay between the two musicians and combines the several worlds of jazz, Malian, and classical music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-20 09:03:00" d="2021-07-20 10:00:00"><n>The Sound of New York - Luis Perdomo &amp; Mimi Jones</n><t>M</t>    <k>Born in 1971 in Caracas, Luis Perdomo began appearing on television and radio in Venezuela at the age of 12. Bassist and singer Mimi Jones, born Miriam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-20 10:00:00" d="2021-07-20 11:30:00"><n>Travellin' Blues: Big Daddy Wilson</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-20 11:30:00" d="2021-07-20 12:39:00"><n>Trio Chemirani: Dawâr</n><t>M</t>    <k>The veritable tombak virtuosos of Trio Chemirani, consisting of Chemirani Senior and Juniors, enrapture the Festival de Saintes. The Trio Chemirani's music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-20 12:39:00" d="2021-07-20 14:00:00"><n u="Soul &amp; Jazz LIVE! Episode">Soul &amp; Jazz LIVE! Episode 1</n><t>M</t>    <k>Soul &amp; Jazz LIVE! episode 1 includes Bill Laurance, Lindsey Webster, Terrace Martin, Avery.Sunshine, A/B Trio, Pocket Dragon, Resolution 88, Kathy Kosins, and YolanDa Brown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-20 14:00:00" d="2021-07-20 15:38:00"><n>Jong Metropole live at Radio Kootwijk</n><t>M</t>    <k>Metropole blends the best of different music genres, borrowing from the performance strength of classical strings to the swing, improvisation, and jazz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-20 15:38:00" d="2021-07-20 16:16:00"><n>Matteo Myderwyk - InJazz 2019</n><t>M</t>    <k>Matteo Myderwyk is a 28-year-old Amsterdam-based pianist. He completed his master degree in piano classical and improvised music at Fontys Conservatorium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-20 16:16:00" d="2021-07-20 16:45:00"><n>Makiko Hirabayashi Trio - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Makiko Hirabayashi Trio represents the Danish jazz scene on jazzahead! 2019. Led by the Japanese pianist Makiko Hirabayashi, the trio blends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-20 16:45:00" d="2021-07-20 17:31:00"><n>Mn'JAM Experiment - jazzahead!</n><t>M</t>    <k>Mn'JAM experiment is a multimedia performance that combines music with visual arts. Bringing together live looping, wordless singing, vocal improvisation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-20 17:31:00" d="2021-07-20 18:26:00"><n>The MotorMusic Jazz Sessions: Steiger</n><t>M</t>    <k>This MotorMusic Jazz Sessions episode features the Belgian musicians of Steiger, a young trio of pianists that mixes rock, classical music, and electronic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-20 18:26:00" d="2021-07-20 20:02:00"><n>Soul Makossa: Manu Dibango in Stuttgart</n><t>M</t>    <k>Manu Dibango, the greatest of African saxophonists, is one of the founding fathers of a modern African musical style that is open to jazz, R&amp;B, salsa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-20 20:02:00" d="2021-07-20 21:00:00"><n>Morgenland Festival: One Way Ticket to Damascus</n><t>M</t>    <k>Bursting with sounds that could only be described as magical, &quot;MCO&quot; features the Syrian Expat Philharmonic Orchestra under conductor Naci Özgüç</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-20 21:00:00" d="2021-07-20 21:52:00"><n>Dee Dee Bridgewater: Motherland</n><t>M</t>    <k>With 'Red Earth', American singer Dee Dee Bridgewater goes on a Malian journey that merges and melds all borders. She brings her own experiences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-20 21:52:00" d="2021-07-20 23:04:00"><n u="North Sea Jazz Archive: Buddy Rich in">North Sea Jazz Archive: Buddy Rich in 1978</n><t>M</t>    <k>This broadcast from the North Sea Jazz Archives presents the legendary drummer Buddy Rich</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-20 23:04:00" d="2021-07-21 00:00:00"><n>Ella Fitzgerald in Brussels: The American Songbook</n><t>M</t>    <k>'Ella Fitzgerald: Live in '57' features 'The First Lady Of Song' in a distinct performance. Shot in Belgium, this 1957 concert sees her performing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-21 00:00:00" d="2021-07-21 00:46:00"><n>Moonlight Benjamin - WOMEX 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2018, WOMEX was held in Las Palmas, Gran Canaria. One of its showcase participants, Moonlight Benjamin, performs a riff-heavy, groove-laden sonic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-21 00:46:00" d="2021-07-21 01:40:00"><n>Final Step Live @ Il Magazzino: Three Sails</n><t>M</t>    <k>From the polyglot border region of Ticino in Switzerland – well-known for its beautiful Lake Maggiore and the International Film Festival in Locarno</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-21 01:40:00" d="2021-07-21 02:28:00"><n u="Earl Hines Quartet in Spa">Earl Hines Quartet in Spa, 1977</n><t>M</t>    <k>Earl Hines and his group, consisting of Rudy Rutherford (reeds), Jimmy Leary (bass), and Eddie Graham (drums) perform in Spa in 1977. Singer Marva Josie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-21 02:28:00" d="2021-07-21 02:59:00"><n>Paradox Live: Philippe Lemm Trio</n><t>M</t>    <k>Cet épisode de PARADOX LIVE présente l'incroyable batteur de jazz néerlandais Philippe Lemm avec son trio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-21 02:59:00" d="2021-07-21 03:54:00"><n u="Anita Oday Live in Sweden">Anita Oday Live in Sweden 1963</n><t>M</t>    <k>Anita O'Day boasts two wonderful concerts from 1963 and 1970 that present the &quot;jazz singer supreme&quot; in impeccable form. This show is a testimony</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1166" o="2021-07-21 03:54:00" d="2021-07-21 05:25:00"><n>Jazz Open Stuttgart: West Coast All Stars</n><t>M</t>    <k>This live recording is celebrating 50 years of West Coast Jazz. The West Coast Jazz movement had its origins about 50 years ago in Los Angeles</k>  </p>
</a>
