<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="36" t="2021-07-09 07:27:58"><p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 05:00:00" d="2021-07-15 06:00:00"><n>Best Premier League Goals 03/04</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Premier League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 06:00:00" d="2021-07-15 06:30:00"><n>Best PL Goals: Newcastle</n><t>O</t>    <k>Enjoy all of the best goals scored over the years by Newcastle United in the Premier League, including classic strikes by Alan Shearer, Laurent Robert and others</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 06:30:00" d="2021-07-15 07:00:00"><n>PL 100 Club: Dwight Yorke</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest goalscorers in Premier League history. This episode features the best of Dwight Yorke's goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 07:00:00" d="2021-07-15 07:15:00"><n>PL Greatest:Birmingham/A Villa '02</n><t>O</t>    <k>Birmingham: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for each of the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. Here, for Birmingham City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 07:15:00" d="2021-07-15 07:30:00"><n>PL Greatest: Bradford/L'Pool 2000</n><t>O</t>    <k>Bradford: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for each of the league's 49 clubs, as voted for by fans. Here, for Bradford City, their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 07:30:00" d="2021-07-15 07:45:00"><n>PL Greatest: Bolton/Chelsea 2005</n><t>O</t>    <k>Chelsea: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for the league's 49 clubs, as voted for by fans. For Chelsea, the win over Bolton in</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 07:45:00" d="2021-07-15 08:00:00"><n>PL Greatest: Man Utd/Liverpool '09</n><t>O</t>    <k>Liverpool: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for each of the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. For Liverpool, the 4-1 win at Old Trafford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 08:00:00" d="2021-07-15 08:30:00"><n>PL Legends: Paul Ince</n><t>O</t>    <k>Series profiling some of the greatest players to grace the Barclays Premier League. Here the focus is on former Manchester United and Liverpool midfielder Paul Ince</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 08:30:00" d="2021-07-15 09:00:00"><n>PL Legends: Sheringham</n><t>O</t>    <k>A profile of former Tottenham and Manchester United striker Teddy Sheringham. The former England international was part of the Red Devils' treble-winning season in 1999</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 09:00:00" d="2021-07-15 09:30:00"><n>Best PL Goals: Newcastle/Liverpool</n><t>O</t>    <k>Enjoy some of the best Premier League goals from past meetings between Newcastle United and Liverpool</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 09:30:00" d="2021-07-15 10:00:00"><n>Best PL Goals: Liverpool/Man Utd</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at some of the best Premier League goals scored in matches between rivals Liverpool and Manchester United</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 10:00:00" d="2021-07-15 10:30:00"><n>PL 100 Club: Romelu Lukaku</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest goalscorers in Premier League history. This episode features the best of Everton and Man Utd striker Romelu Lukaku's goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 10:30:00" d="2021-07-15 11:00:00"><n>PL 100 Club: Les Ferdinand</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest goalscorers in Premier League history. As part of Black History Month, here the focus is on former Newcastle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 11:00:00" d="2021-07-15 13:00:00"><n>PL Retro: Chelsea v Man Utd 2006</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at an important match from the Premier League's history. Here, Jose Mourinho's Chelsea look to make it back-to-back titles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 13:00:00" d="2021-07-15 13:30:00"><n>Gary Neville's Soccerbox: Henry</n><t>O</t>    <k>Gary Neville sits down with Arsenal icon Thierry Henry as they relive some of the most compelling matches that the two shared during their careers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 13:30:00" d="2021-07-15 14:00:00"><n>Gary Neville's Soccerbox: Keane</n><t>O</t>    <k>Gary Neville sits down with former Tottenham Hotspur striker Robbie Keane as they relive some of the most compelling matches that the two shared during their careers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 14:00:00" d="2021-07-15 16:00:00"><n>Premier League Years 2002/03</n><t>O</t>    <k>Enjoy all of the most memorable moments from the 2002-03 Premier League season, accompanied by hit music from the time, major news stories and more</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 16:00:00" d="2021-07-15 16:15:00"><n>PL Greatest: Man Utd/Liverpool '09</n><t>O</t>    <k>Liverpool: Enjoy the greatest Premier League game for each of the league's 47 clubs, as voted for by fans. For Liverpool, the 4-1 win at Old Trafford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 16:15:00" d="2021-07-15 16:30:00"><n>PL Greatest Games:Man U/L'Pool '95</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic matches in the Premier League. Here, Man United host Liverpool in October 1995, as Eric Cantona returned from his lengthy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 16:30:00" d="2021-07-15 16:45:00"><n>PL Greatest Games:L'Pool/Man U '97</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic matches in the Premier League. Here, Liverpool meet Manchester United at Anfield in 1997, in a match that had a happy outcome for the Red Devils</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 16:45:00" d="2021-07-15 17:00:00"><n>PL Greatest Games:L'Pool/Man U '01</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic matches in the Premier League. Here, Liverpool meet Manchester United in 2001, as a Michael Owen brace guided the home side to victory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 17:00:00" d="2021-07-15 18:00:00"><n>Best Premier League Goals 09/10</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back over the best goals in recent seasons in the Premier League. Here, the 2009-10 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 18:00:00" d="2021-07-15 19:45:00"><n>Premier League 2020/21</n><t>O</t>    <k>Aston Villa meet Newcastle United at Villa Park in Saturday evening action from the Premier League season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 19:45:00" d="2021-07-15 20:00:00"><n>Matchday +: Liverpool v Man City</n><t>O</t>    <k>Take an alternative look at the clash between Liverpool and Manchester City, as Sky Sports takes you behind the scenes to experience the full flavour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 20:00:00" d="2021-07-15 21:45:00"><n>Premier League 2020/21</n><t>O</t>    <k>Brighton and Hove Albion meet Aston Villa at the Amex Stadium in Saturday evening action. Brighton are unbeaten in their last five league games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 21:45:00" d="2021-07-15 22:00:00"><n>Matchday Plus: Man City v Spurs</n><t>O</t>    <k>Take an alternative look at the clash between Manchester City and Spurs, as Sky Sports takes you behind the scenes to experience the full flavour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 22:00:00" d="2021-07-15 22:30:00"><n>PL 100: Thierry Henry</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of the players to have bagged 100 goals or more in the Premier League. Here, take a look at Thierry Henry, considered one of the greatest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 22:30:00" d="2021-07-15 23:00:00"><n>Gary Neville's Soccerbox: Zola</n><t>O</t>    <k>Gary Neville sits down with Chelsea great Gianfranco Zola to discuss their time in the game and some of the most notable matches in which they played</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 23:00:00" d="2021-07-15 23:30:00"><n>PL Icons: Paolo Di Canio</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at one of the most iconic players to have graced the Premier League. Here, the focus is on the eccentric former West Ham United forward Paolo Di Canio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-15 23:30:00" d="2021-07-16 01:30:00"><n>PL Retro: Bournemouth v Liverpool</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember one of the Premier League's great games as Bournemouth host Liverpool at Vitality Stadium in December 2016. Down 3-1, the hosts would make a stunning comeback</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-16 01:30:00" d="2021-07-16 02:00:00"><n>PL Icons: Cristiano Ronaldo</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at one of the most iconic players to have graced the Premier League. Here, the focus is on global superstar Cristiano Ronaldo, who was prolific</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-16 02:00:00" d="2021-07-16 04:00:00"><n>PL Years 03/04: Invincibles</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic season in the Premier League, as Arsene Wenger's Arsenal steamrollered all opposition on their way to the title</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-16 04:00:00" d="2021-07-16 04:15:00"><n>PL Greatest Games:Man U/L'Pool '10</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic matches in the Premier League. Here, Manchester United meet Liverpool in 2010, with a Dimitar Berbatov hat-trick proving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-16 04:15:00" d="2021-07-16 04:30:00"><n>PL Greatest Games:Man U/L'Pool '14</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic matches in the Premier League. Here, Man United host Liverpool in March 2014 in a remarkable contest that saw the visitors</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-16 04:30:00" d="2021-07-16 04:45:00"><n>PL Greatest : Chelsea/Man Utd 2012</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic Premier League match. Here, rewind to 2012 for a memorable, ill-tempered clash between high-flying Chelsea and Man Utd at Stamford Bridge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1178" o="2021-07-16 04:45:00" d="2021-07-16 05:00:00"><n>PL Greatest : Man Utd/Chelsea 2014</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic Premier League match. Here, rewind to 2014 for a pulsating encounter between Manchester United and Chelsea at Old Trafford</k>  </p>
</a>
