<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="47" t="2021-07-09 07:28:38"><p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 06:00:00" d="2021-07-15 06:30:00"><n>Best Championship Goals 2017/18</n><t>O</t>    <k>Enjoy some of the finest goals from the Sky Bet Championship during the 2017-2018 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 06:30:00" d="2021-07-15 07:00:00"><n>Best Goals: Carabao Cup 2018/19</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at all the very best goals scored from across another memorable season in the 2018-19 Carabao Cup</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 07:00:00" d="2021-07-15 07:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Reading/Cardiff '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Reading host Cardiff City at the Madejski Stadium in 2017 in a game with a thrilling conclusion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 07:15:00" d="2021-07-15 07:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest:Bristol C/Man Utd '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL Cup. Here, Bristol City host Premier League Man Utd at Ashton Gate in the 2017-18 competition's quarter-finals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 07:30:00" d="2021-07-15 07:45:00"><n u="EFL Greatest:Leeds/Bristol City">EFL Greatest:Leeds/Bristol City 18</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Leeds United host Bristol City at Elland Road in the Sky Bet Championship in a match that saw a dramatic comeback</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 07:45:00" d="2021-07-15 08:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest: Hibs v Rang '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive a classic match from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Hibs host Rangers at Easter Road in a thrilling December 2017 encounter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 08:00:00" d="2021-07-15 08:30:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Del Piero</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling the greatest footballers of all time. Here, a look at Italian forward Alessandro Del Piero, who holds the record for both goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 08:30:00" d="2021-07-15 09:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns - Captains</n><t>O</t>    <k>Some of the most inspirational players in football, these are the greatest captains of all time. With exclusive interviews with the likes of Carles Puyol</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 09:00:00" d="2021-07-15 09:30:00"><n>Football Years: 93/94</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at past football seasons. Here, relive the 1993-1994 campaign, as Manchester United signed Roy Keane, Roberto Baggio dominated for Juventus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 09:30:00" d="2021-07-15 09:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Arsenal/Man City '18</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL Cup. Here, Arsenal and Man City go head-to-head in the final of the 2017-18 competition at Wembley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 09:45:00" d="2021-07-15 10:00:00"><n>EFL Greatest: A.Villa/Wolves 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Aston Villa host Wolves at Villa Park in a memorable Midlands derby in the 2017-18 campaign</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 10:00:00" d="2021-07-15 10:15:00"><n>SPFL Greatest: Hibs v Hearts '18</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the Scottish Professional Football League. Here, Edinburgh rivals Hibs and Hearts go head-to-head at Easter Road in March 2018</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 10:15:00" d="2021-07-15 10:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Celtic V Rangers '96</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Celtic meet Rangers in November 1996 at Celtic Park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 10:30:00" d="2021-07-15 11:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest: George Weah</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling the greatest footballers of all time. Here, Liberian striker George Weah, who was 1995 FIFA World Player of the Year, and a champion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 11:00:00" d="2021-07-15 11:30:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Finals</n><t>O</t>    <k>Football has been blessed with epic matches where triumph and heartbreak are entwined. From 'golden goal' winners to penalty shoot-out thrillers, enjoy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 11:30:00" d="2021-07-15 12:00:00"><n>Football Years: 94/95</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some memorable seasons in the world of football. Here, the focus is on the 1994-1995 campaign, which saw surprise league winners in England and France</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 12:00:00" d="2021-07-15 13:00:00"><n>Championship Season Review 17/18</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive all the key moments from the 2017-2018 Sky Bet Championship season, as Wolves charged towards the title and a tight relegation battle ensured at the bottom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 13:00:00" d="2021-07-15 13:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Fulham/QPR 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, promotion-chasing Fulham host QPR at Craven Cottage in a west London derby that saw a memorable comeback</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 13:15:00" d="2021-07-15 13:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest: M'boro/Wolves 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Middlesbrough host Wolves at the Riverside in 2018 in a game that saw the visitors reduced to nine men</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 13:30:00" d="2021-07-15 13:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Cardiff/Wolves 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Cardiff City host Wolves at the Cardiff City Stadium in 2018 in a match that had a dramatic ending</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 13:45:00" d="2021-07-15 14:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Rangers V Celtic '97</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Rangers meet Celtic in the top flight back in a vital clash in the 1996-97 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 14:00:00" d="2021-07-15 14:30:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Gheorghe Hagi</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling the greatest footballers of all time. This episode looks at Gheorghe Hagi, widely considered Romania's finest ever player</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 14:30:00" d="2021-07-15 15:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Comebacks</n><t>O</t>    <k>Sometimes all appears lost. Hope has disappeared and a team is simply down and out. But fortunes can be reversed. Here, take a look at some of football's greatest comebacks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 15:00:00" d="2021-07-15 15:30:00"><n>Football Years 95/96</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive the 1995-96 season as the Bosman ruling changed football. Plus, England hosted the Euros, Auxerre and Atletico Madrid were surprise league winners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 15:30:00" d="2021-07-15 16:30:00"><n>Championship Season Review 18/19</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at a memorable 2018-19 season in the Sky Bet Championship, including a dramatic race for promotion and the captivating end-of-season play-offs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 16:30:00" d="2021-07-15 16:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Derby/Cardiff 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Derby County take on Cardiff City at Pride Park in the 2017-18 campaign in a match with implications</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 16:45:00" d="2021-07-15 17:00:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Derby/Leeds 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Derby County take on Marcelo Bielsa's Leeds United at Pride Park in a Championship match that saw five goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 17:00:00" d="2021-07-15 17:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: West Brom/Leeds 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, West Brom take on Leeds United at The Hawthorns in a high-scoring Championship match that saw one side dominate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 17:15:00" d="2021-07-15 17:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Celtic v Rangers '98</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Celtic face Rangers in the top flight back in 1998</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 17:30:00" d="2021-07-15 18:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Kaka</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling the greatest footballers of all time. Here, a look at Kaka, the AC Milan midfielder who won titles in Serie A and the Champions League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 18:00:00" d="2021-07-15 18:30:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Controversies</n><t>O</t>    <k>Football is the beautiful game - but it has an ugly side. When law and order breaks down, it can be unrecognisable from the sport loved by millions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 18:30:00" d="2021-07-15 19:00:00"><n>Football Years 96/97</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the 1996-1997 football season, as an African nation won a major tournament for the first time, one of the decade's finest goals was scored</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 19:00:00" d="2021-07-15 19:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest Games: Old Firm</n><t>O</t>    <k>Scottish football's biggest game is back at Ibrox as Rangers host Celtic in the SPFL Ladbrokes Premiership. Celtic won the first meeting between the sides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 19:30:00" d="2021-07-15 20:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest Games: Old Firm</n><t>O</t>    <k>Celtic host Rangers at Celtic Park in the SPFL Ladbrokes Premiership. Celtic are looking to remain on track to stay unbeaten through a full league season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 20:00:00" d="2021-07-15 21:00:00"><n>EFL Play-Off Final: League 1 20/21</n><t>O</t>    <k>Blackpool meet Lincoln City to determine the third and final team to gain promotion from EFL League One to the EFL Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 21:00:00" d="2021-07-15 22:00:00"><n>EFL Play-Off Final: League 2 20/21</n><t>O</t>    <k>Morecambe meet Newport County to determine the third and final team to gain promotion from EFL League Two to EFL League One</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 22:00:00" d="2021-07-15 23:00:00"><n>EFL Play-Off Final: C'Ship 20/21</n><t>O</t>    <k>With a place in the Premier League on the line, Brentford meet Swansea City in the Sky Bet Championship play-off final at Wembley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 23:00:00" d="2021-07-15 23:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest Games: Old Firm</n><t>O</t>    <k>Rangers play Celtic at Ibrox in the SPFL Ladbrokes Premiership. Celtic will be looking to avoid defeat as they aim to remain on track to complete</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 23:30:00" d="2021-07-15 23:45:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Rangers v Celtic '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Rangers host Celtic at Ibrox in September 2017 in the Ladbrokes Premiership. Celtic came into the clash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 23:45:00" d="2021-07-16 00:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Celtic v Rangers '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Celtic meet Rangers in a tense encounter in the final Old Firm derby of 2017</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-16 00:00:00" d="2021-07-16 00:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: A. Villa/B'ham 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Aston Villa host Birmingham City at Villa Park in a high-scoring Second City derby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-16 00:15:00" d="2021-07-16 00:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest: A. Villa/Forest 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Aston Villa host Nottingham Forest at Villa Park in an enthralling, end-to-end encounter that saw 10 goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-16 00:30:00" d="2021-07-16 00:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Charlton/S'land '98</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive a classic clash from the English Football League - here, rewind to May 1998 for the First Division play-off final at Wembley, as Charlton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-16 00:45:00" d="2021-07-16 01:00:00"><n>EFL Greatest:Gillingham/M.City '99</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive a classic match from the English Football League. Here, remember the thrilling 1998-99 Second Division play-off final between Gillingham</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-16 01:00:00" d="2021-07-16 03:00:00"><n>Retro C'Ship 00: B'burn v Man City</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic clash from the second tier from over the years. Here, back in 2000, Blackburn Rovers and Manchester City go head-to-head</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-16 03:00:00" d="2021-07-16 04:00:00"><n>Championship Season Review 13/14</n><t>O</t>    <k>A season review of the 2013-2014 season in the Sky Bet Championship, with a look at all of the biggest stories and key matches from across the season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-16 04:00:00" d="2021-07-16 06:00:00"><n>Retro C'Ship 19: A. Villa v Derby</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from years gone by in the Championship play-offs. Here, the 2019 play-off final between Aston Villa and Derby County</k>  </p>
</a>
