<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="50" t="2019-08-15 22:56:04"><p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 05:00:00" d="2019-08-21 05:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Leeds v A.Villa '16</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic matches in English football. Here, Leeds United face Aston Villa in the Sky Bet Championship, with the sides meeting in the league</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 05:15:00" d="2019-08-21 05:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest: H'field v Leeds 2017</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic matches in English football. Here, a West Yorkshire derby as Huddersfield Town play Leeds United in 2017 in the Sky Bet Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 05:30:00" d="2019-08-21 06:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Comebacks</n><t>O</t>    <k>Sometimes all appears lost. Hope has disappeared and a team is simply down and out. But fortunes can be reversed. Here, take a look at some of football's greatest comebacks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 06:00:00" d="2019-08-21 06:30:00"><n>Football's Greatest: David Villa</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series looking at some of football's greats. Here, a look at Spanish striker David Villa, a record goalscorer for his country, and a UEFA European</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 06:30:00" d="2019-08-21 07:00:00"><n>Football Years: 91/92</n><t>O</t>    <k>The 1991-92 season was a memorable year for football. Kenny Dalglish returned at Blackburn Rovers, Wrexham knocked Arsenal out of the FA Cup, Denmark</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 07:00:00" d="2019-08-21 07:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: A.Villa/N.Forest '16</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic matches from the English Football League. Here, Aston Villa play Nottingham Forest in a thrilling draw in September</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 07:15:00" d="2019-08-21 07:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest:Cardiff/Bristol C '16</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic matches in English football. Here, Cardiff City face Bristol City in a Severnside derby in the Sky Bet Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 07:30:00" d="2019-08-21 07:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Burton v B'ham '16</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic matches in English football. Here, Burton Albion face Birmingham City in 2016 in the Sky Bet Championship, in what was the sides' first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 07:45:00" d="2019-08-21 08:00:00"><n>EFL Greatest: B'ham/A.Villa '16</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic action from the English Football League. Here, local rivals Birmingham City and Aston Villa clash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 08:00:00" d="2019-08-21 08:30:00"><n>EFL Goals: Championship Midweek</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the goals from the midweek fixtures in the Sky Bet Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 08:30:00" d="2019-08-21 09:00:00"><n>Game Changers: Transfer Special</n><t>O</t>    <k>Game Changers join Sky Sports News for a behind-the-scenes peek of the all the drama and tension of transfer deadline day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 09:00:00" d="2019-08-21 09:30:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Goals</n><t>O</t>    <k>From spectacular volleys, to the perfect team move, enjoy the greatest goals in football history. With exclusive interviews with the likes of Marco</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 09:30:00" d="2019-08-21 10:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Transfers</n><t>O</t>    <k>A football transfer can cost millions or nothing at all. Some can transform a club. Some can rock it to its core. This show counts downs the most important</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 10:00:00" d="2019-08-21 10:30:00"><n>Football Years 95/96</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive the 1995-96 season as the Bosman ruling changed football. Plus, England hosted the Euros, Auxerre and Atletico Madrid were surprise league winners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 10:30:00" d="2019-08-21 11:00:00"><n>Football Years 96/97</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the 1996-1997 football season, as an African nation won a major tournament for the first time, one of the decade's finest goals was scored</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 11:00:00" d="2019-08-21 12:00:00"><n>FL Play Offs: Derby v QPR</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic Football League play-off finals from years gone by. Here, Derby County take on Queens Park Rangers at Wembley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 12:00:00" d="2019-08-21 12:15:00"><n>One2Eleven - Robert Pires</n><t>O</t>    <k>Former France midfielder Robert Pires - who played 79 times for his country - gives his #one2eleven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 12:15:00" d="2019-08-21 12:30:00"><n>One2Eleven - Emmanuel Petit</n><t>O</t>    <k>Former France and Arsenal midfielder Emmanuel Petit reveals his #one2eleven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 12:30:00" d="2019-08-21 13:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest:Roberto Carlos</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling of some of football's greatest players. Here, the focus is on former Real Madrid and Brazil full-back Roberto Carlos - a UEFA Champions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 13:00:00" d="2019-08-21 13:30:00"><n>EFL Goals: Championship Midweek</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the goals from the midweek fixtures in the Sky Bet Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 13:30:00" d="2019-08-21 13:45:00"><n>SPFL Greatest: Hibs v Celtic '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, rewind to December 2017 and a memorable four-goal encounter between Hibs and Celtic at Easter Road</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 13:45:00" d="2019-08-21 14:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Celtic V Rangers '96</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Celtic meet Rangers in November 1996 at Celtic Park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 14:00:00" d="2019-08-21 14:30:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Entertainers</n><t>O</t>    <k>Celebrate some of the game's greatest entertainers - the players who make football fun. Featuring exclusive interviews with Zlatan Ibrahimovic, Ronaldinho and Gheorghe Hagi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 14:30:00" d="2019-08-21 15:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns - Captains</n><t>O</t>    <k>Some of the most inspirational players in football, these are the greatest captains of all time. With exclusive interviews with the likes of Carles Puyol</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 15:00:00" d="2019-08-21 15:30:00"><n>Football Years: 97/98</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the 1997-1998 football season, as Ronaldo and Rivaldo made major moves in European football, Arsenal won the double, and France claimed the World Cup on home soil</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 15:30:00" d="2019-08-21 16:00:00"><n>Game Changers: Transfer Special</n><t>O</t>    <k>Game Changers join Sky Sports News for a behind-the-scenes peek of the all the drama and tension of transfer deadline day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 16:00:00" d="2019-08-21 17:00:00"><n>FL Play Offs:L. Orient v Rotherham</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic Football League play-off finals from years gone by. Here, Leyton Orient face Rotherham United at Wembley in the League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 17:00:00" d="2019-08-21 17:15:00"><n>One2Eleven - Hector Bellerin</n><t>O</t>    <k>Pacy Spanish full-back Hector Bellerin gives his #one2eleven of the best footballers he's played alongside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 17:15:00" d="2019-08-21 17:30:00"><n>One2Eleven - Ruben Baraja</n><t>O</t>    <k>Former Spain midfielder Ruben Baraja - who won 43 caps for his nation - gives his #one2eleven of the best footballers he played with across his career</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 17:30:00" d="2019-08-21 18:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest:Roberto Baggio</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling of some of football's greatest players. Here, the focus is on former Juventus, Milan and Italy forward Roberto Baggio, one of the game's great mavericks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 18:00:00" d="2019-08-21 18:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest:Sheff U/Sheff Wed '09</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic clash from the English Football League. Here, Sheffield United and Sheffield Wednesday meet in a thrilling Steel City derby in September 2009</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 18:15:00" d="2019-08-21 18:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest: P'boro/So'ton 2011</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic clash from the English Football League. Here, Peterborough and Southampton meet in an eight-goal thriller in League 1 in February 2011</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 18:30:00" d="2019-08-21 18:45:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Rangers v Celtic '09</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Rangers meet Celtic in the top flight back in October 2009</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 18:45:00" d="2019-08-21 19:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Rangers v Celtic '10</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Rangers take on Celtic at Ibrox in the top flight in the 2009-2010 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 19:00:00" d="2019-08-21 19:30:00"><n>EFL Goals: Championship Midweek</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the goals from the midweek fixtures in the Sky Bet Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 19:30:00" d="2019-08-21 20:00:00"><n>Soccer AM - The Best Bits</n><t>O</t>    <k>John Fendley and Jimmy Bullard are joined by guests from the world of sport and entertainment for the Saturday morning football show, with regular</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 20:00:00" d="2019-08-21 23:15:00"><n>Live EFL: Preston v Stoke City</n><t>O</t>    <k>Preston North End take on Stoke City at Deepdale in the Sky Bet Championship. A four-goal thriller ended level in a 2-2 draw last season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 23:15:00" d="2019-08-21 23:45:00"><n>EFL Goals: Championship Midweek</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the goals from the midweek fixtures in the Sky Bet Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-21 23:45:00" d="2019-08-22 00:00:00"><n u="EFL Greatest:Sheff Wed/N'castle">EFL Greatest:Sheff Wed/N'castle 17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic matches in English football. Here, Sheffield Wednesday take on Newcastle United in 2017 in the Sky Bet Championship, with both sides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-22 00:00:00" d="2019-08-22 00:30:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Cafu</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling of some of football's greatest players. Here, remember Brazilian legend Cafu, a two-time World Cup winner, and his country's most capped</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-22 00:30:00" d="2019-08-22 01:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Ian Rush</n><t>O</t>    <k>A profile of former Liverpool and Wales great Ian Rush. A prolific striker, Rush won five league titles, three FA Cups and the European Cup across a glittering career</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-22 01:00:00" d="2019-08-22 01:30:00"><n>EFL Goals: Championship Midweek</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the goals from the midweek fixtures in the Sky Bet Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-22 01:30:00" d="2019-08-22 02:00:00"><n>Football Years 92/93</n><t>O</t>    <k>The 1992-93 season was a glorious year for football. It saw a whole new ball game in the English Premier League, and a new era in European football</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-22 02:00:00" d="2019-08-22 02:30:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Controversies</n><t>O</t>    <k>Football is the beautiful game - but it has an ugly side. When law and order breaks down, it can be unrecognisable from the sport loved by millions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-22 02:30:00" d="2019-08-22 03:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Coaches</n><t>O</t>    <k>Through strategy and motivation, coaches can shape the game to their will. Here, the greatest football coaches of all time, with exclusive interviews</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-22 03:00:00" d="2019-08-22 03:15:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Celtic v Rangers '00</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Celtic meet Rangers at Celtic Park in an eight-goal encounter back in the 2000-2001 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-22 03:15:00" d="2019-08-22 03:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Rangers v Celtic '00</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Rangers host Celtic at Ibrox in the 2000-2001 season in a match that produced six goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-22 03:30:00" d="2019-08-22 03:45:00"><n>One2Eleven - Danny Gabbidon</n><t>O</t>    <k>Former Wales centre-back Danny Gabbidon - who won 49 caps for his country - picks his #one2eleven of the best footballers he played alongside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-22 03:45:00" d="2019-08-22 04:00:00"><n>One2Eleven - Andy Townsend</n><t>O</t>    <k>Former Republic of Ireland midfielder Andy Townsend - who won 70 caps for his country - gives his #one2eleven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-08-22 04:00:00" d="2019-08-22 07:00:00"><n>FL Play Offs: Burton v Fleetwood</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic Football League play-off finals from years gone by. Here, Burton Albion and Fleetwood Town meet at Wembley in the League</k>  </p>
</a>
