<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="46" t="2021-07-08 05:07:35"><p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 06:00:00" d="2021-07-13 07:00:00"><n>Championship Season Review 18/19</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at a memorable 2018-19 season in the Sky Bet Championship, including a dramatic race for promotion and the captivating end-of-season play-offs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 07:00:00" d="2021-07-13 07:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Brentford/Fulham '14</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic action from the English Football League. Here, a west London derby in the Sky Bet Championship between Brentford and Fulham at Griffin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 07:15:00" d="2021-07-13 07:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Derby/N.Forest '15</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic English Football League action. Here, a Midlands derby in the Sky Bet Championship between Derby County and Nottingham Forest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 07:30:00" d="2021-07-13 07:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest:Norwich/Ipswich '15</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic action from the EFL. Here, Norwich City and Ipswich Town clash in an East Anglian derby at Carrow Road back in March 2015</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 07:45:00" d="2021-07-13 08:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest: Rangers v Celtic'11</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Rangers meet Celtic at Ibrox in a six-goal thriller from the 2011-2012 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 08:00:00" d="2021-07-13 08:30:00"><n>Football's Greatest:Roberto Baggio</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling of some of football's greatest players. Here, the focus is on former Juventus, Milan and Italy forward Roberto Baggio, one of the game's great mavericks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 08:30:00" d="2021-07-13 09:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Comebacks</n><t>O</t>    <k>Sometimes all appears lost. Hope has disappeared and a team is simply down and out. But fortunes can be reversed. Here, take a look at some of football's greatest comebacks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 09:00:00" d="2021-07-13 09:30:00"><n>Football Years 95/96</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive the 1995-96 season as the Bosman ruling changed football. Plus, England hosted the Euros, Auxerre and Atletico Madrid were surprise league winners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 09:30:00" d="2021-07-13 09:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Wolves/Leeds '15</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic action from the EFL. Here, Wolverhampton Wanderers host Leeds United at Molineux in April 2015 in a thrilling game that saw seven goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 09:45:00" d="2021-07-13 10:00:00"><n>EFL Greatest:Swindon/Sheff Utd '15</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive a classic match from the English Football League. Here, Swindon Town host Sheffield United at the County Ground in a 10-goal thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 10:00:00" d="2021-07-13 10:15:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Rangers v Celtic '12</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Celtic travel to Ibrox knowing a win over Rangers would clinch the Scottish title</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 10:15:00" d="2021-07-13 10:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest: Hearts v Hibs '98</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Hearts and Hibernian meet in an Edinburgh derby from the top flight on New Year's Day, 1998</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 10:30:00" d="2021-07-13 11:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Vieira</n><t>O</t>    <k>A profile of former France and Arsenal midfielder Patrick Vieira. One of the game's all-time greats, Vieira's power and precision saw him win the Premier</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 11:00:00" d="2021-07-13 11:30:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Controversies</n><t>O</t>    <k>Football is the beautiful game - but it has an ugly side. When law and order breaks down, it can be unrecognisable from the sport loved by millions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 11:30:00" d="2021-07-13 12:00:00"><n>Football Years 96/97</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the 1996-1997 football season, as an African nation won a major tournament for the first time, one of the decade's finest goals was scored</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 12:00:00" d="2021-07-13 13:00:00"><n>Championship Season Review 13/14</n><t>O</t>    <k>A season review of the 2013-2014 season in the Sky Bet Championship, with a look at all of the biggest stories and key matches from across the season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 13:00:00" d="2021-07-13 13:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Norwich/Ipswich '15</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic action from the English Football League. Here, East Anglian rivals Norwich City and Ipswich Town meet at Carrow Road</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 13:15:00" d="2021-07-13 13:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Derby v Leeds 2015</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic action from the EFL. Here, Derby County take on Leeds United at Pride Park in August 2015 in a game that saw a thrilling late winner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 13:30:00" d="2021-07-13 13:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Hull v Reading 2015</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic action from the EFL. Here, Hull City take on Reading at the KC Stadium in December 2015 in a thrilling clash that saw a late winner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 13:45:00" d="2021-07-13 14:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest: Hibs v Hearts '00</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Hibernian and Hearts contest a thrilling eight-goal Edinburgh derby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 14:00:00" d="2021-07-13 14:30:00"><n>Football's Greatest: M Desailly</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling of some of football's greatest players. Here, a look at French great Marcel Desailly, a UEFA Champions League, UEFA European</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 14:30:00" d="2021-07-13 15:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Coaches</n><t>O</t>    <k>Through strategy and motivation, coaches can shape the game to their will. Here, the greatest football coaches of all time, with exclusive interviews</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 15:00:00" d="2021-07-13 15:30:00"><n>Football Years: 97/98</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the 1997-1998 football season, as Ronaldo and Rivaldo made major moves in European football, Arsenal won the double, and France claimed the World Cup on home soil</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 15:30:00" d="2021-07-13 16:30:00"><n>Championship Season Review 14/15</n><t>O</t>    <k>A season review of the 2014-2015 Sky Bet Championship season, with a look at all of the biggest stories and key matches from another eventful year</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 16:30:00" d="2021-07-13 16:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: QPR v M'boro 2016</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic action from the English Football League. Here, QPR host Middlesbrough in a five-goal thriller at Loftus Road in the 2015-16 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 16:45:00" d="2021-07-13 17:00:00"><n>EFL Greatest: B'ham v M'boro 2016</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic action from the English Football League. Here, Birmingham City take on Middlesbrough at St Andrew's in a four-goal thriller in the 2015-16 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 17:00:00" d="2021-07-13 17:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: M'boro/Brighton '16</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic matches from the English Football League. Here, Middlesbrough take on Brighton and Hove Albion in a tense Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 17:15:00" d="2021-07-13 17:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest: Hibs v Hearts '02</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Hibernian met Hearts at Easter Road in the Edinburgh derby in March 2002</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 17:30:00" d="2021-07-13 18:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Matthaus</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling of some of football's greatest players. Here, a look at German great Lothar Matthaus, capped 150 times, and a UEFA European Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 18:00:00" d="2021-07-13 18:30:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Upsets</n><t>O</t>    <k>Conventional wisdom says that the mighty will prevail and the plucky underdog will stumble. But sometimes, miracles do happen. Here, count</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 18:30:00" d="2021-07-13 19:00:00"><n>Football Years: 98/99</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the 1998-1999 campaign, in which Denilson broke the transfer record, Steven Gerrard and John Terry made their debuts and Manchester United</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 19:00:00" d="2021-07-13 19:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest Games: Old Firm</n><t>O</t>    <k>Rangers host rivals Celtic at Ibrox in the final Old Firm derby meeting of the 2018-19 season. Rangers won 1-0 the last time the sides met on this ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 19:30:00" d="2021-07-13 19:45:00"><n>One2Eleven - Ian Harte</n><t>O</t>    <k>Former Republic of Ireland full-back Ian Harte - who won 63 caps for the country - gives his #one2eleven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 19:45:00" d="2021-07-13 20:00:00"><n>One2Eleven - Steve Lomas</n><t>O</t>    <k>Former Northern Ireland midfielder Steve Lomas gives his #one2eleven of the best footballers he played with</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 20:00:00" d="2021-07-13 21:00:00"><n>EFL Play-Off Final: League 1 18/19</n><t>O</t>    <k>Charlton Athletic take on Sunderland at Wembley in the Sky Bet League One play-off final. These sides famously met in the Division One play-off final</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 21:00:00" d="2021-07-13 22:00:00"><n>EFL Play-Off Final: League 2 18/19</n><t>O</t>    <k>Newport County and Tranmere Rovers face off at Wembley in the Sky Bet League Two play-off final, with the final place in next season's League One on the line</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 22:00:00" d="2021-07-13 23:00:00"><n>EFL Play-Off Final: C'Ship 18/19</n><t>O</t>    <k>Dean Smith's Aston Villa and Frank Lampard's Derby County meet at Wembley in the Sky Bet Championship play-off final, as the final side in next year's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 23:00:00" d="2021-07-13 23:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest Games: Old Firm</n><t>O</t>    <k>Celtic and Rangers see out 2019 against one another at Celtic Park as they meet in the SPFL Premiership. Celtic were victorious in the first league meeting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-13 23:30:00" d="2021-07-14 00:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest Games: Old Firm</n><t>O</t>    <k>Glasgow rivals Celtic and Rangers collide at Celtic Park in a big clash from the Scottish Premiership. The sides come into this separated by a single point at the top</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 00:00:00" d="2021-07-14 00:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: A.Villa/N.Forest '16</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic matches from the English Football League. Here, Aston Villa play Nottingham Forest in a thrilling draw in September</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 00:15:00" d="2021-07-14 00:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest:Cardiff/Bristol C '16</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic matches in English football. Here, Cardiff City face Bristol City in a Severnside derby in the Sky Bet Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 00:30:00" d="2021-07-14 00:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Burton v B'ham '16</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic matches in English football. Here, Burton Albion face Birmingham City in 2016 in the Sky Bet Championship, in what was the sides' first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 00:45:00" d="2021-07-14 01:00:00"><n>EFL Greatest: B'ham/A.Villa '16</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic action from the English Football League. Here, local rivals Birmingham City and Aston Villa clash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 01:00:00" d="2021-07-14 03:45:00"><n>Retro C'Ship 98: Charlton v S'land</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive a classic encounter from the play-offs over the years - here, Charlton Athletic and Sunderland meet in the 1997-98 Championship play-off final</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 03:45:00" d="2021-07-14 04:00:00"><n>One2Eleven - Michael O'Neill</n><t>O</t>    <k>Former Northern Ireland midfielder and current Northern Ireland boss Michael O'Neill gives his #one2eleven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 04:00:00" d="2021-07-14 06:00:00"><n>Retro L1 19: Charlton v S'land</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to look back at a classic League One play-off final, as Charlton and Sunderland go head-to-head in the 2019 final at Wembley. It was to go right to the wire</k>  </p>
</a>
