<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="55" t="2019-07-11 00:21:15"><p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 05:00:00" d="2019-07-15 05:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest:Cardiff/Bristol C '16</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic matches in English football. Here, Cardiff City face Bristol City in a Severnside derby in the Sky Bet Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 05:15:00" d="2019-07-15 05:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Burton v B'ham '16</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic matches in English football. Here, Burton Albion face Birmingham City in 2016 in the Sky Bet Championship, in what was the sides' first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 05:30:00" d="2019-07-15 06:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Entertainers</n><t>O</t>    <k>Celebrate some of the game's greatest entertainers - the players who make football fun. Featuring exclusive interviews with Zlatan Ibrahimovic, Ronaldinho and Gheorghe Hagi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 06:00:00" d="2019-07-15 06:30:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Andrea Pirlo</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling the greatest footballers of all time. Here, a look at Andrea Pirlo, the AC Milan star whose passing and vision made him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 06:30:00" d="2019-07-15 07:00:00"><n>Football Years: 99/00</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive the 1999-2000 season, as Thierry Henry went to Arsenal, Galatasaray won the first piece of European silverware by a Turkish club, and France</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 07:00:00" d="2019-07-15 07:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Derby/Cardiff 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Derby County take on Cardiff City at Pride Park in the 2017-18 campaign in a match with implications</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 07:15:00" d="2019-07-15 07:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Derby/Leeds 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Derby County take on Marcelo Bielsa's Leeds United at Pride Park in a Championship match that saw five goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 07:30:00" d="2019-07-15 07:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: West Brom/Leeds 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, West Brom take on Leeds United at The Hawthorns in a high-scoring Championship match that saw one side dominate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 07:45:00" d="2019-07-15 08:00:00"><n>EFL Greatest: A. Villa/B'ham 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Aston Villa host Birmingham City at Villa Park in a high-scoring Second City derby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 08:00:00" d="2019-07-15 08:30:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Stoitchkov</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling the greatest footballers of all time. Here, Hirsto Stoitchkov, the Bulgarian striker who dominated for CSKA Sofia and Barcelona, winning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 08:30:00" d="2019-07-15 09:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest:Iker Casillas</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling the greatest footballers of all time. This episode features goalkeeper Iker Casillas, Spain's most capped player and the captain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 09:00:00" d="2019-07-15 09:30:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Entertainers</n><t>O</t>    <k>Celebrate some of the game's greatest entertainers - the players who make football fun. Featuring exclusive interviews with Zlatan Ibrahimovic, Ronaldinho and Gheorghe Hagi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 09:30:00" d="2019-07-15 10:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns - Captains</n><t>O</t>    <k>Some of the most inspirational players in football, these are the greatest captains of all time. With exclusive interviews with the likes of Carles Puyol</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 10:00:00" d="2019-07-15 10:30:00"><n>Football Years: 93/94</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at past football seasons. Here, relive the 1993-1994 campaign, as Manchester United signed Roy Keane, Roberto Baggio dominated for Juventus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 10:30:00" d="2019-07-15 11:00:00"><n>Football Years: 94/95</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some memorable seasons in the world of football. Here, the focus is on the 1994-1995 campaign, which saw surprise league winners in England and France</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 11:00:00" d="2019-07-15 12:00:00"><n>FL Play Offs: Derby v West Brom</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic Football League play-off finals from years gone by. Here, Derby County take on West Bromwich Albion at Wembley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 12:00:00" d="2019-07-15 12:15:00"><n>One2Eleven - Bojan</n><t>O</t>    <k>Spain and Stoke City forward Bojan gives his #one2eleven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 12:15:00" d="2019-07-15 12:30:00"><n>One2Eleven - Johan Djourou</n><t>O</t>    <k>Switzerland defender Johan Djourou names his #one2eleven of the best XI he's played alongside in his career</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 12:30:00" d="2019-07-15 13:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Xavi</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling the greatest footballers of all time. This episode features Spanish maestro Xavi, who played an integral role in both Barcelona</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 13:00:00" d="2019-07-15 13:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Bradford/Arsenal '12</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at some of the greatest matches from English football. Here, League 2 side Bradford City take on Premier League giants Arsenal in the Football</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 13:15:00" d="2019-07-15 13:30:00"><n u="EFL Greatest:AFC W'don/Plymouth">EFL Greatest:AFC W'don/Plymouth 16</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic matches in English football. Here, AFC Wimbledon meet Plymouth Argyle at Wembley Stadium in the final of the Sky Bet League 2 play-offs in May 2016</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 13:30:00" d="2019-07-15 13:45:00"><n>SPFL Greatest: Aber v Rang '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Aberdeen play host to Rangers in December 2017, with the sides meeting for the second time in a week</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 13:45:00" d="2019-07-15 14:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest: Hibs v Rang '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive a classic match from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Hibs host Rangers at Easter Road in a thrilling December 2017 encounter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 14:00:00" d="2019-07-15 14:30:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Finals</n><t>O</t>    <k>Football has been blessed with epic matches where triumph and heartbreak are entwined. From 'golden goal' winners to penalty shoot-out thrillers, enjoy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 14:30:00" d="2019-07-15 15:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Comebacks</n><t>O</t>    <k>Sometimes all appears lost. Hope has disappeared and a team is simply down and out. But fortunes can be reversed. Here, take a look at some of football's greatest comebacks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 15:00:00" d="2019-07-15 15:30:00"><n>Football Years 95/96</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive the 1995-96 season as the Bosman ruling changed football. Plus, England hosted the Euros, Auxerre and Atletico Madrid were surprise league winners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 15:30:00" d="2019-07-15 16:00:00"><n>Football Years 96/97</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the 1996-1997 football season, as an African nation won a major tournament for the first time, one of the decade's finest goals was scored</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 16:00:00" d="2019-07-15 17:00:00"><n>FL Play Offs: Leeds Utd v Watford</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic Football League play-off finals from years gone by. Here, Leeds United take on Watford at the Millennium Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 17:00:00" d="2019-07-15 17:15:00"><n>One2Eleven - Valon Behrami</n><t>O</t>    <k>Switzerland midfielder Valon Behrami picks his #one2eleven of the best XI he has played alongside across his career</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 17:15:00" d="2019-07-15 17:30:00"><n>One2Eleven: Van Der Vaart</n><t>O</t>    <k>Former Spurs winger and Netherlands star Rafael van der Vaart gives his one2eleven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 17:30:00" d="2019-07-15 18:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Rivaldo</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling the greatest footballers of all time. Here, a look at Rivaldo, the Brazilian star who won World Player of the Year in 1999 and the World Cup in 2002</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 18:00:00" d="2019-07-15 18:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Derby v QPR 2014</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at a classic match from the English Football League. Here, Derby County meet QPR in the Sky Bet Championship play-off final at Wembley in the 2013/2014 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 18:15:00" d="2019-07-15 18:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest: H'field/Reading '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic matches in English football. Here, Huddersfield Town play Reading in the final of the Sky Bet Championship play-offs at Wembley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 18:30:00" d="2019-07-15 18:45:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Celtic v Rangers '99</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Celtic face Glasgow rivals Rangers at Celtic Park in 1999</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 18:45:00" d="2019-07-15 19:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Rangers v Celtic '99</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Rangers face Celtic at Ibrox in a six-goal thriller from the top flight back in the 1999-2000 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 19:00:00" d="2019-07-15 20:00:00"><n>EFL Championship Goals</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of the goals and major talking points from Wednesday's fixtures in the Sky Bet Championship. Matches include Norwich v Hull and Nott'm Forest v Aston Villa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 20:00:00" d="2019-07-15 20:30:00"><n u="EFL Goals: League 1 &amp;">EFL Goals: League 1 &amp; 2</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the key moments and goals from the latest round of fixtures in Sky Bet Leagues 1 and 2. Here, the Easter Monday matches</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 20:30:00" d="2019-07-15 20:45:00"><n>SPFL Round-Up</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the latest goals and major moments from the latest round of fixtures in the SPFL Ladbrokes Premiership</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 20:45:00" d="2019-07-15 21:00:00"><n>SPFL Round-Up</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the latest goals and major moments from the latest round of fixtures in the SPFL Ladbrokes Premiership</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 21:00:00" d="2019-07-15 22:00:00"><n>EFL Championship Goals</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the goals and key moments from the latest round of fixtures in the 2018-19 Sky Bet Championship season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 22:00:00" d="2019-07-15 22:30:00"><n u="EFL Goals: League 1 &amp;">EFL Goals: League 1 &amp; 2</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the key moments and goals from the opening weekend of matches in Sky Bet Leagues 1 and 2</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 22:30:00" d="2019-07-15 22:45:00"><n>SPFL Round-Up</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the latest goals and major moments from the latest round of fixtures in the SPFL Ladbrokes Premiership</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 22:45:00" d="2019-07-15 23:00:00"><n>SPFL Round-Up</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the latest goals and major moments from the latest round of fixtures in the SPFL Ladbrokes Premiership</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-15 23:00:00" d="2019-07-16 00:00:00"><n>FL Play Offs: M'boro v Norwich</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic Football League play-off finals from years gone by. Here, Middlesbrough take on Norwich City at Wembley in the Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 00:00:00" d="2019-07-16 00:30:00"><n>MLS Round Up Show</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the latest goals and major talking points from the latest round of matches in the 2019 Major League Soccer season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 00:30:00" d="2019-07-16 01:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Matthaus</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling of some of football's greatest players. Here, a look at German great Lothar Matthaus, capped 150 times, and a UEFA European Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 01:00:00" d="2019-07-16 01:30:00"><n>Football Years 90/91</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some memorable seasons in the world of football. Here, the focus is on the 1990-1991 campaign, beginning with the World Cup and featuring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 01:30:00" d="2019-07-16 02:00:00"><n>Football Years: 91/92</n><t>O</t>    <k>The 1991-92 season was a memorable year for football. Kenny Dalglish returned at Blackburn Rovers, Wrexham knocked Arsenal out of the FA Cup, Denmark</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 02:00:00" d="2019-07-16 02:30:00"><n>Football Countdowns - Captains</n><t>O</t>    <k>Some of the most inspirational players in football, these are the greatest captains of all time. With exclusive interviews with the likes of Carles Puyol</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 02:30:00" d="2019-07-16 03:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Finals</n><t>O</t>    <k>Football has been blessed with epic matches where triumph and heartbreak are entwined. From 'golden goal' winners to penalty shoot-out thrillers, enjoy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 03:00:00" d="2019-07-16 03:15:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Rangers v Celtic '99</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Rangers take on Celtic in the top flight back in 1999</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 03:15:00" d="2019-07-16 03:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Celtic v Rangers '99</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Celtic face Glasgow rivals Rangers at Celtic Park in 1999</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 03:30:00" d="2019-07-16 03:45:00"><n>One2Eleven - Joe Cole</n><t>O</t>    <k>Former England midfielder Joe Cole - who earned 56 caps for the country - gives his #one2eleven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 03:45:00" d="2019-07-16 04:00:00"><n>One2Eleven - Stuart Pearce</n><t>O</t>    <k>Former England defender Stuart Pearce - who won 78 caps for his country - gives his #one2eleven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 04:00:00" d="2019-07-16 05:00:00"><n>FL Play Offs: Preston NE v Swindon</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic Football League play-off finals from years gone by. Here, Preston North End face Swindon Town at Wembley in the League</k>  </p>
</a>
