<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="45" t="2021-07-09 07:28:22"><p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 06:00:00" d="2021-07-14 07:00:00"><n>Championship Season Review 19/20</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive the dramatic 2019-20 season in the Sky Bet Championship. There was to be a thrilling tussle at the top that would go down to the very final minutes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 07:00:00" d="2021-07-14 07:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Wolves v Derby '16</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic action from the English Football League. Here, Wolves host Derby County at Molineux in a five-goal thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 07:15:00" d="2021-07-14 07:30:00"><n>Football League Archive 2017</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic action from the English Football League. Here, Nottingham Forest take on Newcastle United at the City Ground in a game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 07:30:00" d="2021-07-14 07:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Leeds v A.Villa '16</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic matches in English football. Here, Leeds United face Aston Villa in the Sky Bet Championship, with the sides meeting in the league</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 07:45:00" d="2021-07-14 08:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Rangers v Celtic '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Rangers host Celtic at Ibrox in September 2017 in the Ladbrokes Premiership. Celtic came into the clash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 08:00:00" d="2021-07-14 08:30:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Ian Rush</n><t>O</t>    <k>A profile of former Liverpool and Wales great Ian Rush. A prolific striker, Rush won five league titles, three FA Cups and the European Cup across a glittering career</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 08:30:00" d="2021-07-14 09:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Debuts</n><t>O</t>    <k>A professional debut is a memorable experience for every footballer, and sometimes they can be something quite extraordinary. Here, a look</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 09:00:00" d="2021-07-14 09:30:00"><n>Football Years: 99/00</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive the 1999-2000 season, as Thierry Henry went to Arsenal, Galatasaray won the first piece of European silverware by a Turkish club, and France</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 09:30:00" d="2021-07-14 09:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: H'field v Leeds 2017</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic matches in English football. Here, a West Yorkshire derby as Huddersfield Town play Leeds United in 2017 in the Sky Bet Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 09:45:00" d="2021-07-14 10:00:00"><n u="EFL Greatest:Sheff Wed/N'castle">EFL Greatest:Sheff Wed/N'castle 17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic matches in English football. Here, Sheffield Wednesday take on Newcastle United in 2017 in the Sky Bet Championship, with both sides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 10:00:00" d="2021-07-14 10:15:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Celtic v Rangers '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Celtic meet Rangers in a tense encounter in the final Old Firm derby of 2017</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 10:15:00" d="2021-07-14 10:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Hearts v Rangers '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Hearts host Rangers in October 2017 in a four-goal thriller that saw the Ibrox club come from behind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 10:30:00" d="2021-07-14 11:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest: David Villa</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series looking at some of football's greats. Here, a look at Spanish striker David Villa, a record goalscorer for his country, and a UEFA European</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 11:00:00" d="2021-07-14 11:30:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Goals</n><t>O</t>    <k>From spectacular volleys, to the perfect team move, enjoy the greatest goals in football history. With exclusive interviews with the likes of Marco</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 11:30:00" d="2021-07-14 12:00:00"><n>Football Years 90/91</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some memorable seasons in the world of football. Here, the focus is on the 1990-1991 campaign, beginning with the World Cup and featuring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 12:00:00" d="2021-07-14 13:00:00"><n>Championship Season Review 15/16</n><t>O</t>    <k>A review of the 2015-2016 Sky Bet Championship season, with a look at all of the biggest stories and key matches from another eventful year</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 13:00:00" d="2021-07-14 13:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Fulham v A.Villa '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember some classic matches from English football. In this episode, Fulham looked to maintain their playoff hopes against Aston Villa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 13:15:00" d="2021-07-14 13:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest: N.Forest/Ipswich '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic matches in English football. Here, Nottingham Forest look to avoid relegation from the Sky Bet Championship as they face Ipswich Town in May 2017</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 13:30:00" d="2021-07-14 13:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: B'ford v Swindon '13</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember some classic matches from English football. Here, Bradford City face Swindon Town in December 2013 in Sky Bet League 1</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 13:45:00" d="2021-07-14 14:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest: Rang v Aber '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Rangers host rivals Aberdeen at Ibrox in November 2017 in a game that saw the Glasgow club dominate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 14:00:00" d="2021-07-14 14:30:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Cafu</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling of some of football's greatest players. Here, remember Brazilian legend Cafu, a two-time World Cup winner, and his country's most capped</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 14:30:00" d="2021-07-14 15:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Transfers</n><t>O</t>    <k>A football transfer can cost millions or nothing at all. Some can transform a club. Some can rock it to its core. This show counts down the most important</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 15:00:00" d="2021-07-14 15:30:00"><n>Football Years: 91/92</n><t>O</t>    <k>The 1991-92 season was a memorable year for football. Kenny Dalglish returned at Blackburn Rovers, Wrexham knocked Arsenal out of the FA Cup, Denmark</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 15:30:00" d="2021-07-14 16:30:00"><n>Championship Season Review 16/17</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at the 2016-2017 season in the Sky Bet Championship, remembering all of the biggest stories as they happened across another eventful season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 16:30:00" d="2021-07-14 16:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Bradford/Arsenal '12</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at some of the greatest matches from English football. Here, League 2 side Bradford City take on Premier League giants Arsenal in the Football</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 16:45:00" d="2021-07-14 17:00:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Derby v Hull 2017</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Derby County and Hull City go head-to-head in a thrilling encounter back in 2017</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 17:00:00" d="2021-07-14 17:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Sheff W/Sheff U 2017</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, relive a thrilling Steel City derby between rivals Sheffield Wednesday and Sheffield United at Hillsborough Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 17:15:00" d="2021-07-14 17:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest: Aber v Rang '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Aberdeen play host to Rangers in December 2017, with the sides meeting for the second time in a week</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 17:30:00" d="2021-07-14 18:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Baresi</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling the greatest footballers of all time. Here, Italian legend Franco Baresi, who spent his entire club career at Milan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 18:00:00" d="2021-07-14 18:30:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Entertainers</n><t>O</t>    <k>Celebrate some of the game's greatest entertainers - the players who make football fun. Featuring exclusive interviews with Zlatan Ibrahimovic, Ronaldinho and Gheorghe Hagi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 18:30:00" d="2021-07-14 19:00:00"><n>Football Years 92/93</n><t>O</t>    <k>The 1992-93 season was a glorious year for football. It saw a whole new ball game in the English Premier League, and a new era in European football</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 19:00:00" d="2021-07-14 19:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest Games: Old Firm</n><t>O</t>    <k>One of football's most famous rivalries returns as Rangers meet Celtic at Ibrox in New Year's weekend from the Old Firm derby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 19:30:00" d="2021-07-14 20:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest Games: Old Firm</n><t>O</t>    <k>Celtic meet Rangers at Celtic Park in a huge derby from the Scottish Premiership. Rangers won their last league meeting 1-0 back in January</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 20:00:00" d="2021-07-14 21:00:00"><n>EFL Play-Off Final: League 1 19/20</n><t>O</t>    <k>With a place in the Sky Bet Championship on the line, the two League One play-off finalists go head-to-head at Wembley Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 21:00:00" d="2021-07-14 22:00:00"><n>EFL Play-Off Final: League 2 19/20</n><t>O</t>    <k>The Sky Bet League Two Play-Off final from Wembley Stadium, as two teams battle it out to reach League One</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 22:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:00:00"><n>EFL Play-Off Final: C'Ship 19/20</n><t>O</t>    <k>West London sides collide in the Sky Bet Championship play-off final at Wembley as Brentford and Fulham go head-to-head for the final place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 23:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest Games: Old Firm</n><t>O</t>    <k>The Old Firm Derby returns as Rangers host Celtic at Ibrox in the Scottish Premiership</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-14 23:30:00" d="2021-07-15 00:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest Games: Old Firm</n><t>O</t>    <k>The Old Firm derby returns as Celtic host Rangers at Celtic Park in the SPFL Ladbrokes Premiership. This is the first meeting since Rangers were promoted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 00:00:00" d="2021-07-15 00:15:00"><n>Efl Greatest: Leeds/Sheff Utd 2017</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at a classic match from the EFL. Here, Leeds and Sheffield United go head-to-head at Elland Road in a thrilling contest back in 2017</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 00:15:00" d="2021-07-15 00:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Ipswich/Sheff W '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at a classic match from the EFL. Here, Ipswich Town and Sheffield Wednesday meet at Portman Road in a four-goal thriller back in 2017</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 00:30:00" d="2021-07-15 00:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: QPR/Brentford 2017</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, QPR and Brentford go head-to-head at Loftus Road in a west London derby in 2017 that had a dramatic finish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 00:45:00" d="2021-07-15 01:00:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Sheff U/Bristol '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Sheffield United host Bristol City at Bramall Lane in 2017 in a game with a late dramatic twist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 01:00:00" d="2021-07-15 03:45:00"><n>Retro L1 99: Gillingham v Man City</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive a classic encounter from the play-offs over the years - here, Gillingham and Manchester City meet in the Second Divison play-off final in the 1998-99 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 03:45:00" d="2021-07-15 04:00:00"><n>One2Eleven - Steve Lomas</n><t>O</t>    <k>Former Northern Ireland midfielder Steve Lomas gives his #one2eleven of the best footballers he played with</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2021-07-15 04:00:00" d="2021-07-15 06:00:00"><n>Retro C'Ship SF 19: Leeds v Derby</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic clash from the Championship play-offs. Here, a dramatic semi-final second leg from the 2018-19 season as Leeds and Derby</k>  </p>
</a>
