<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="55" t="2019-07-11 00:21:15"><p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 05:00:00" d="2019-07-16 05:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: B'ham/A.Villa '16</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic action from the English Football League. Here, local rivals Birmingham City and Aston Villa clash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 05:15:00" d="2019-07-16 05:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Wolves v Derby '16</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic action from the English Football League. Here, Wolves host Derby County at Molineux in a five-goal thriller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 05:30:00" d="2019-07-16 06:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Comebacks</n><t>O</t>    <k>Sometimes all appears lost. Hope has disappeared and a team is simply down and out. But fortunes can be reversed. Here, take a look at some of football's greatest comebacks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 06:00:00" d="2019-07-16 06:30:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Xavi</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling the greatest footballers of all time. This episode features Spanish maestro Xavi, who played an integral role in both Barcelona</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 06:30:00" d="2019-07-16 07:00:00"><n>Football Years 92/93</n><t>O</t>    <k>The 1992-93 season was a glorious year for football. It saw a whole new ball game in the English Premier League, and a new era in European football</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 07:00:00" d="2019-07-16 07:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: A. Villa/Forest 2018</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Aston Villa host Nottingham Forest at Villa Park in an enthralling, end-to-end encounter that saw 10 goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 07:15:00" d="2019-07-16 07:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Bolton/Preston '01</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic clash from the Football League. Here, Bolton Wanderers and Preston North End meet in the First Division play-off final</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 07:30:00" d="2019-07-16 07:45:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Sheff Utd/Wolves '03</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic English Football League clash. Here, Sheffield United and Wolves meet in the First Division play-off final at the Millennium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 07:45:00" d="2019-07-16 08:00:00"><n>EFL Greatest: N.Forest/Yeovil '07</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive a classic clash from the English Football League. Here, Nottingham Forest face Yeovil in their Sky Bet League One play-off semi-final second</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 08:00:00" d="2019-07-16 08:30:00"><n>Football's Greatest:Roberto Carlos</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling of some of football's greatest players. Here, the focus is on former Real Madrid and Brazil full-back Roberto Carlos - a UEFA Champions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 08:30:00" d="2019-07-16 09:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest:Roberto Baggio</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling of some of football's greatest players. Here, the focus is on former Juventus, Milan and Italy forward Roberto Baggio, one of the game's great mavericks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 09:00:00" d="2019-07-16 09:30:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Controversies</n><t>O</t>    <k>Football is the beautiful game - but it has an ugly side. When law and order breaks down, it can be unrecognisable from the sport loved by millions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 09:30:00" d="2019-07-16 10:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Coaches</n><t>O</t>    <k>Through strategy and motivation, coaches can shape the game to their will. Here, the greatest football coaches of all time, with exclusive interviews</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 10:00:00" d="2019-07-16 10:30:00"><n>Football Years: 97/98</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the 1997-1998 football season, as Ronaldo and Rivaldo made major moves in European football, Arsenal won the double, and France claimed the World Cup on home soil</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 10:30:00" d="2019-07-16 11:00:00"><n>Football Years: 98/99</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the 1998-1999 campaign, in which Denilson broke the transfer record, Steven Gerrard and John Terry made their debuts and Manchester United</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 11:00:00" d="2019-07-16 12:00:00"><n>FL Play Offs: Wycombe v Southend</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic Football League play-off finals from years gone by. Here, Wycombe Wanderers and Southend United meet at Wembley in the League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 12:00:00" d="2019-07-16 12:15:00"><n>One2Eleven: Van Bronckhorst</n><t>O</t>    <k>Former Arsenal, Barcelona and Netherlands star Giovanni Van Bronckhorst picks the best 11 players he played alongside during an illustrious career</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 12:15:00" d="2019-07-16 12:30:00"><n>One2Eleven: Rui Costa</n><t>O</t>    <k>Former AC Milan and Portugal star Rui Costa gives his #one2eleven on Fantasy Football Club</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 12:30:00" d="2019-07-16 13:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Vieira</n><t>O</t>    <k>A profile of former France and Arsenal midfielder Patrick Vieira. One of the game's all-time greats, Vieira's power and precision saw him win the Premier</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 13:00:00" d="2019-07-16 13:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Man Utd v So'ton '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember some classic matches from English football. Here, Manchester United take on Southampton in the final of the EFL Cup at Wembley Stadium in March 2017</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 13:15:00" d="2019-07-16 13:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Luton/Blackpool '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at a classic match from the English Football League. Here, Luton Town host Blackpool in the play-offs in Sky Bet League 2 at Kenilworth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 13:30:00" d="2019-07-16 13:45:00"><n>SPFL Greatest: Hibs v Hearts '18</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the Scottish Professional Football League. Here, Edinburgh rivals Hibs and Hearts go head-to-head at Easter Road in March 2018</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 13:45:00" d="2019-07-16 14:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Celtic V Rangers '96</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Celtic meet Rangers in November 1996 at Celtic Park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 14:00:00" d="2019-07-16 14:30:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Upsets</n><t>O</t>    <k>Conventional wisdom says that the mighty will prevail and the plucky underdog will stumble. But sometimes, miracles do happen. Here, count</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 14:30:00" d="2019-07-16 15:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Debuts</n><t>O</t>    <k>A professional debut is a memorable experience for every footballer, and sometimes they can be something quite extraordinary. Here, a look</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 15:00:00" d="2019-07-16 15:30:00"><n>Football Years: 99/00</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive the 1999-2000 season, as Thierry Henry went to Arsenal, Galatasaray won the first piece of European silverware by a Turkish club, and France</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 15:30:00" d="2019-07-16 16:00:00"><n>Football Years 90/91</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some memorable seasons in the world of football. Here, the focus is on the 1990-1991 campaign, beginning with the World Cup and featuring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 16:00:00" d="2019-07-16 17:00:00"><n>FL Play Offs: Derby v QPR</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic Football League play-off finals from years gone by. Here, Derby County take on Queens Park Rangers at Wembley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 17:00:00" d="2019-07-16 17:15:00"><n>One2Eleven: Alberto Aquilani</n><t>O</t>    <k>Former Liverpool midfielder Alberto Aquilani gives his one2eleven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 17:15:00" d="2019-07-16 17:30:00"><n>One2Eleven: Djibril Cisse</n><t>O</t>    <k>Former Liverpool and QPR striker Djibril Cisse gives his one2eleven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 17:30:00" d="2019-07-16 18:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest: M Desailly</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling of some of football's greatest players. Here, a look at French great Marcel Desailly, a UEFA Champions League, UEFA European</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 18:00:00" d="2019-07-16 18:15:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Exeter/Carlisle '17</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive some classic matches in English football. Here, Exeter City face Carlisle United in the second leg of their Sky Bet League 2 play-off semi-final</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 18:15:00" d="2019-07-16 18:30:00"><n>EFL Greatest: Derby v Hull 2017</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic match from the EFL. Here, Derby County and Hull City go head-to-head in a thrilling encounter back in 2017</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 18:30:00" d="2019-07-16 18:45:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Celtic v Rangers '00</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Celtic meet Rangers at Celtic Park in an eight-goal encounter back in the 2000-2001 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 18:45:00" d="2019-07-16 19:00:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Rangers v Celtic '00</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Rangers host Celtic at Ibrox in the 2000-2001 season in a match that produced six goals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 19:00:00" d="2019-07-16 20:00:00"><n>EFL Championship Goals</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the goals and key moments from the latest round of fixtures in the 2018-19 Sky Bet Championship season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 20:00:00" d="2019-07-16 20:30:00"><n u="EFL Goals: League 1 &amp;">EFL Goals: League 1 &amp; 2</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the key moments and goals from the latest round of fixtures in Sky Bet Leagues 1 and 2</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 20:30:00" d="2019-07-16 20:45:00"><n>SPFL Round-Up</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the latest goals and major moments from the latest round of fixtures in the SPFL Ladbrokes Premiership</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 20:45:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00"><n>SPFL Round-Up</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the latest goals and major moments from the latest round of fixtures in the SPFL Ladbrokes Premiership</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 22:00:00"><n>EFL Championship Goals</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the goals and key moments from the latest round of fixtures in the 2018-19 Sky Bet Championship season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 22:00:00" d="2019-07-16 22:30:00"><n u="EFL Goals: League 1 &amp;">EFL Goals: League 1 &amp; 2</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the key moments and goals from the latest round of fixtures in Sky Bet Leagues 1 and 2</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 22:30:00" d="2019-07-16 22:45:00"><n>SPFL Round-Up</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the latest goals and major moments from the latest round of fixtures in the SPFL Ladbrokes Premiership</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 22:45:00" d="2019-07-16 23:00:00"><n>SPFL Round-Up</n><t>O</t>    <k>A round-up of all the latest goals and major moments from the latest round of fixtures in the SPFL Ladbrokes Premiership</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-16 23:00:00" d="2019-07-17 00:00:00"><n>FL Play Offs:L. Orient v Rotherham</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic Football League play-off finals from years gone by. Here, Leyton Orient face Rotherham United at Wembley in the League</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-17 00:00:00" d="2019-07-17 00:30:00"><n>Football's Greatest: Ian Rush</n><t>O</t>    <k>A profile of former Liverpool and Wales great Ian Rush. A prolific striker, Rush won five league titles, three FA Cups and the European Cup across a glittering career</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-17 00:30:00" d="2019-07-17 01:00:00"><n>Football's Greatest: David Villa</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series looking at some of football's greats. Here, a look at Spanish striker David Villa, a record goalscorer for his country, and a UEFA European</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-17 01:00:00" d="2019-07-17 01:30:00"><n>Football Years: 93/94</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at past football seasons. Here, relive the 1993-1994 campaign, as Manchester United signed Roy Keane, Roberto Baggio dominated for Juventus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-17 01:30:00" d="2019-07-17 02:00:00"><n>Football Years: 94/95</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some memorable seasons in the world of football. Here, the focus is on the 1994-1995 campaign, which saw surprise league winners in England and France</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-17 02:00:00" d="2019-07-17 02:30:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Controversies</n><t>O</t>    <k>Football is the beautiful game - but it has an ugly side. When law and order breaks down, it can be unrecognisable from the sport loved by millions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-17 02:30:00" d="2019-07-17 03:00:00"><n>Football Countdowns: Coaches</n><t>O</t>    <k>Through strategy and motivation, coaches can shape the game to their will. Here, the greatest football coaches of all time, with exclusive interviews</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-17 03:00:00" d="2019-07-17 03:15:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Rangers v Celtic '99</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Rangers face Celtic at Ibrox in a six-goal thriller from the top flight back in the 1999-2000 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-17 03:15:00" d="2019-07-17 03:30:00"><n>SPFL Greatest:Celtic v Rangers '00</n><t>O</t>    <k>Classic action from the Scottish Premiership. Here, Celtic meet Rangers at Celtic Park in an eight-goal encounter back in the 2000-2001 season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-17 03:30:00" d="2019-07-17 03:45:00"><n>One2Eleven - Sol Campbell</n><t>O</t>    <k>Former England defender Sol Campbell - who won 73 caps for his country - gives his #one2eleven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-17 03:45:00" d="2019-07-17 04:00:00"><n>One2Eleven - Gordon Banks</n><t>O</t>    <k>England's legendary 1966 World Cup-winning goalkeeper Gordon Banks gives his one2eleven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1179" o="2019-07-17 04:00:00" d="2019-07-17 07:00:00"><n>FL Play Offs: Burton v Fleetwood</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic Football League play-off finals from years gone by. Here, Burton Albion and Fleetwood Town meet at Wembley in the League</k>  </p>
</a>
