<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="51" t="2020-05-16 04:27:46"><p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 05:00:00" d="2020-05-23 05:30:00"><n u="Quest">Quest (6)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Lucknow, India
Food in Lucknow is a mixture of central Asian and local cuisines. Join Alex as she goes to explore this city, meet the Nawabs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 05:30:00" d="2020-05-23 06:00:00"><n u="XP Guide">XP Guide (34)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Bangkok
Derived from two Thai words, &quot;Bang&quot; meaning Village and &quot;Kok&quot; meaning Olive is &quot;Village of Olives&quot;. The city transformed from a fishing village</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 06:00:00" d="2020-05-23 06:30:00"><n u="Xplore Egypt">Xplore Egypt (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Aswan
We continue to explore Aswan with the eyes of the local inhabitants of the country, soaking in the Nile seascape and enjoying a horse carriage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 06:30:00" d="2020-05-23 07:00:00"><n u="Off The Grid">Off The Grid (23)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Monts De Cristal , Gabon
Get ready to take on exciting wildlife adventures of Monte De Crystal with Emeline. The national park enveloped by misty clouds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 07:00:00" d="2020-05-23 07:30:00"><n u="Xplore Philippines">Xplore Philippines (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cebu
Cebu is the second largest metropolis in the country and offers a perspective of Philippines busy life. Boracay is an exquisite beach destination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 07:30:00" d="2020-05-23 08:00:00"><n u="Xplore Thailand">Xplore Thailand (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Koh Samui
Shimmering sands, cool azure waters and a little heaven tucked under the wings of an endless sky. This is the island of Ko Samui in Thailand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 08:00:00" d="2020-05-23 08:30:00"><n u="XP Guide">XP Guide (26)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Copenhagen
A homely place where the aroma of freshly baked bread greets you as people smoothly glide along on their bicycles. Welcome to Copenhagen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 08:30:00" d="2020-05-23 09:00:00"><n u="Quest">Quest (7)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Lucknow, India
The spices used in Lucknowi recipes were a matter of both social fashion and social prestige. The cooks were quite adventurous with their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 09:00:00" d="2020-05-23 09:30:00"><n u="Xplore Egypt">Xplore Egypt (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Luxor
An absolute architectural delight, in this episode, we take you for a sight-seeing through Luxor as we delve deeper into myths, mysteries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 09:30:00" d="2020-05-23 10:00:00"><n u="Off The Grid">Off The Grid (24)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Lope National Park, Gabon
Emeline puts on her adventurous garb as she strolls around the gorgeous rainforest and savanna of Lope National Park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 10:00:00" d="2020-05-23 10:30:00"><n u="Kissed By The Sea">Kissed By The Sea (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Gozo Island, Malta
At Gozo island, Tara tries scuba-diving, visits Calypso Caves, explores the rugged landscape of Gozo and finally visits the Ta'Pinnu shrine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 10:30:00" d="2020-05-23 11:00:00"><n u="Xplore Thailand">Xplore Thailand (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Phuket
A traveller lives in the wind that carries him from one end of the world to another. Would you recognize its edge? Welcoming you to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 11:00:00" d="2020-05-23 11:15:00"><n u="Best From The Rest">Best From The Rest (30)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Must Visit, Budapest
Budapest is the &quot;Pearl of Danube&quot;. With so many places to visit and things to see, here are the best things to do while you are in Budapest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 11:15:00" d="2020-05-23 11:30:00"><n u="Landmarks">Landmarks (12)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Pampalmousse Garden
Mighty mountains, cascading waterfalls, exotic forests, impressive cliffs - the dramatic landscape of Mauritius is explained</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 11:30:00" d="2020-05-23 12:00:00"><n u="Quest">Quest (8)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Lucknow - Rewa, India
Take a stroll down the lanes of Lucknow and indulge in some comfort food and also discover some old favourite receipes to share</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 12:00:00" d="2020-05-23 12:30:00"><n u="Xplore Egypt">Xplore Egypt (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Alexandria
Our anchor is now in the last phase of her journey. Tune in as she lazes about on the beaches of Hurghada and feasts upon authentic Middle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 12:30:00" d="2020-05-23 13:00:00"><n u="Off The Grid">Off The Grid (25)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Libreville ,Gabon
The capital of Gabon, Libreville offers an off the grid route to the host Emeline. From the scenic trails of Pongara National</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 13:00:00" d="2020-05-23 13:30:00"><n u="Kissed By The Sea">Kissed By The Sea (5)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mauritius
Explore the magical island of Mauritius with Sakshi as she visits an abandoned lighthouse, and experiences water activities like snorkeling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 13:30:00" d="2020-05-23 14:00:00"><n u="Great World Hotels">Great World Hotels (10)</n><t>D</t>    <k>One And Only Mauritius
Incomparable and distinguished, OneandOnly Le Saint Géran in Mauritius is nestled peacefully in the silver white sands, Balmy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 14:00:00" d="2020-05-23 14:30:00"><n u="City Breaks">City Breaks (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Valencia
Travel to an ancient Spanish city, Valencia with our host as she explores “City of Arts and Science” then visits Valencia Cathedral, El Cabanyal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 14:30:00" d="2020-05-23 15:00:00"><n u="Food Fact Fun">Food Fact Fun (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Toronto, Canada
Be it a Vietnamese sandwich shop or kimchi fries, Alex begins his adventures in Toronto by sampling the wares of Asian food shops at Market 707</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 15:00:00" d="2020-05-23 15:30:00"><n u="Unwind">Unwind (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Nikara Yala, Sri Lanka
Indeya, in this episode unwinds in Sri Lanka at a nature resort. Here she visits a 2200-year-old Buddhist temple, later tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 15:30:00" d="2020-05-23 16:00:00"><n u="World Spas">World Spas (8)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Sarovar Premier, Kerala
Kerala's Sarovar Premier spa retreat is known for its Ayurvedic spa therapies, offering treatments based on the natural principles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 16:00:00" d="2020-05-23 16:30:00"><n u="Kissed By The Sea">Kissed By The Sea (6)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mauritius
Join Sakshi as she ziplines, enjoying the stunning landscapes and followed by a submarine ride. Further explores the capital, Port Louis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 16:30:00" d="2020-05-23 17:00:00"><n u="XP Guide">XP Guide (53)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tel Aviv
Tel Aviv, by far the most international city in Israel emerges as the perfect mix of the contemporary and the classic. Explore the city centre</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 17:00:00" d="2020-05-23 17:30:00"><n u="City Breaks">City Breaks (8)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Belfast
Join our host in Belfast, as she explores a city dotted with Victorian buildings to vibrant streets. Starting from City hall to visiting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 17:30:00" d="2020-05-23 18:00:00"><n u="Food Fact Fun">Food Fact Fun (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Niagara, Canada
Besides witnessing dance performances near the Niagara Falls, Alex tucks into a lavish 5-course meal and learns about regional wines in Toronto</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 18:00:00" d="2020-05-23 18:30:00"><n u="World Heritage">World Heritage (10)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Ancient Temple of Egypt
Explore the ancient heritage sites of Abu Simbel, the Philae complex of Nubia and the Hatshepsut Temple to unravel the mystical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 18:30:00" d="2020-05-23 19:00:00"><n u="Great World Hotels">Great World Hotels (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Huvafen Fushi
Ever wanted to master the art of doing absolutely nothing in panoramic surroundings? We know just the place.The Huvafen Fushi's tropical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 19:00:00" d="2020-05-23 19:15:00"><n u="Best From The Rest">Best From The Rest (31)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Oman 5 Must See Attractions
A stunning contrast of deserts, mountains and beaches, its unspoilt landscape, dotted with grand forts, exquisite palaces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 19:15:00" d="2020-05-23 19:30:00"><n u="Landmarks">Landmarks (14)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Vigeland Park
Vigeland sculpture park, covers an area of 300 thousand square meters. also known as the Frogner park, the sculptures here</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 19:30:00" d="2020-05-23 20:00:00"><n u="City Breaks">City Breaks (7)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Budapest
Other than New York, where else can you find the Statue of Liberty? Is the capital of Hungary actually two cities? If you’re intrigued</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 20:00:00" d="2020-05-23 20:45:00"><n u="Bliss">Bliss (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Lech, Austria
Home to some of the world’s best ski slopes, fine cuisines and described as one of the most luxurious Ski Chalets, you cannot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 20:45:00" d="2020-05-23 21:00:00"><n u="Best From The Rest">Best From The Rest (28)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dubai Arabic Adventure
Welcome to the city that has something to do at any given time, a destination that won't fail to keep you occupied and entertained</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 21:00:00" d="2020-05-23 21:30:00"><n u="Great World Hotels">Great World Hotels (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Huvafen Fushi
Maldives has yet another beautiful and mesmerizing wonder to offer. The Huvafen Fushi located in serene and beautiful island of Maldives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 21:30:00" d="2020-05-23 22:00:00"><n u="World Spas">World Spas (9)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mine Wellness, Malaysia
Mines Wellness features a floor where rooms are designed to offer a holistic wellness experience. A perfect spa resort that offers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 22:00:00" d="2020-05-23 22:15:00"><n u="Best From The Rest">Best From The Rest (31)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Oman 5 Must See Attractions
A stunning contrast of deserts, mountains and beaches, its unspoilt landscape, dotted with grand forts, exquisite palaces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 22:15:00" d="2020-05-23 22:30:00"><n u="Landmarks">Landmarks (14)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Vigeland Park
Vigeland sculpture park, covers an area of 300 thousand square meters. also known as the Frogner park, the sculptures here</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 22:30:00" d="2020-05-23 23:00:00"><n u="City Breaks">City Breaks (7)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Budapest
Other than New York, where else can you find the Statue of Liberty? Is the capital of Hungary actually two cities? If you’re intrigued</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 23:00:00" d="2020-05-23 23:45:00"><n u="Bliss">Bliss (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Lech, Austria
Home to some of the world’s best ski slopes, fine cuisines and described as one of the most luxurious Ski Chalets, you cannot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-23 23:45:00" d="2020-05-24 00:00:00"><n u="Best From The Rest">Best From The Rest (28)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Dubai Arabic Adventure
Welcome to the city that has something to do at any given time, a destination that won't fail to keep you occupied and entertained</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-24 00:00:00" d="2020-05-24 00:30:00"><n u="Great World Hotels">Great World Hotels (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Huvafen Fushi
Maldives has yet another beautiful and mesmerizing wonder to offer. The Huvafen Fushi located in serene and beautiful island of Maldives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-24 00:30:00" d="2020-05-24 01:00:00"><n u="World Spas">World Spas (9)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mine Wellness, Malaysia
Mines Wellness features a floor where rooms are designed to offer a holistic wellness experience. A perfect spa resort that offers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-24 01:00:00" d="2020-05-24 01:30:00"><n u="Backpack">Backpack (17)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mt. Bromo and Komodo National Park, Indonesia
Hannah visits the active volcano at the top of Mt. Bromo, and then travels to Komodo National</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-24 01:30:00" d="2020-05-24 02:00:00"><n u="Boarding Pass">Boarding Pass (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tromso
In Tromso, Jamie enjoys panoramic views of Tromso through a cable car ride, tries a reindeer burger, checks out the strong tidal currents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-24 02:00:00" d="2020-05-24 02:30:00"><n u="Xplore Sri Lanka">Xplore Sri Lanka (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Kandy
Legends believe that Princess Hemamala hid the sacred tooth of the Buddha in her hair and smuggled it out of Kalinga. Today, it rests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-24 02:30:00" d="2020-05-24 03:00:00"><n u="Quest">Quest (15)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Kolkata, India
Traveling on the banks of river Hooghly, preserving priceless vintage dishes. Treat yourself with the amazing food style of Sirampore, West Bengal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-24 03:00:00" d="2020-05-24 03:30:00"><n u="10 Days Korea">10 Days Korea (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Seoul
Andrew starts exploring Seoul by learning about its modern culture, visiting markets, palaces, a museum and ends with a visit to Korean war memorial</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-24 03:30:00" d="2020-05-24 04:00:00"><n u="XP Guide">XP Guide (50)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Singapore
Vibrant and dynamic, a mix of culture and people, an important port and industrial power house, cosmopolitan Singapore is nothing less than a dream destination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-24 04:00:00" d="2020-05-24 04:30:00"><n u="Backpack">Backpack (18)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Labuan Bajo and Bali, Indonesia
Hannah goes snorkeling at Pink beach on Komodo Island. While exploring Labuan Bajo, she visits Mello village and learns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1199" o="2020-05-24 04:30:00" d="2020-05-24 05:00:00"><n u="Boarding Pass">Boarding Pass (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Polar Park
In Polar Park, Jamie sees lynxes, faces his fears by befriending wolves, cuddles Alaskan huskies and goes out for an exciting dog sledging session</k>  </p>
</a>
