<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="73" t="2020-05-27 04:36:22"><p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 05:15:00" d="2020-06-03 05:40:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Robo Rusty / Rusty's Kitty Catastrophe
Rusty builds a robot version of himself, so he can do two things at once.

Rusty and Ruby build a robotic buddy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 05:40:00" d="2020-06-03 06:00:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Frankie's Botasaur / Rusty's Mega Stacker
New neighbor Frankie Fritz bot-naps Botasaur, making Rusty and Ruby go on a chase to get their friend back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 06:00:00" d="2020-06-03 06:25:00"><n u="Becca's Bunch">Becca's Bunch I (8)</n><t>L</t>    <k>Cute Lil' Bug / Eye of the Beholder
While the Bunch are minding Ringo's bug Sue, she changes in ways that none of them expected.

Wagtailers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 06:25:00" d="2020-06-03 06:50:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines III (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% The Polar Derby
Blaze and his friends head to VelocityVille and transform into racecars for the Polar Derby, a wintry race through the snow! But when racecar Crusher knocks them off-course, the pals must keep cool to stay on track (2016)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 06:50:00" d="2020-06-03 07:20:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rusty vs. the Robo Squirrel / Rusty's Day of the Drones
When the robotic squirrel Rusty made goes rogue - swiping things from all over town, Rusty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 07:20:00" d="2020-06-03 07:45:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol II (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Ryder calls Everest to save the day (2015)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 07:45:00" d="2020-06-03 08:15:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol II (25)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% Pups Save the Woof and Roll Show / Pups Save an Eagle
When a big pop star comes to town, a storm blows the whole town apart, including the stage! Can the PAW Patrol save the day?

While out in the woods, the pups rescue an eagle caught in twine and tied to her own nest (2015)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 08:15:00" d="2020-06-03 08:40:00"><n u="Blue's Clues &amp; You">Blue's Clues &amp; You I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Sad Day with Blue
Blue's feeling sad, so we play Blue's Clues to figure out why. Along the way to figuring out Blue's Clues, we help our Felt Friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 08:40:00" d="2020-06-03 09:00:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Rod and Brody's Jungle Adventure / Cadet for a Day
Rod and Brody try to earn a Jungle Exploring badge. They get lost and must work together to help Swift find them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 09:00:00" d="2020-06-03 09:30:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Hawaiian Luau! / Kitty-sitting!
Dazzle accidentally locks smoothies inside the Sweet Ride and can't find they key! Will she get them out before the luau?

Jasper thinks pet-sitting Cookie is going to be a piece of cake, until she gets lost (2017)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 09:30:00" d="2020-06-03 09:45:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Will she learn to ask for help? (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 09:45:00" d="2020-06-03 10:10:00"><n u="Abby Hatcher">Abby Hatcher I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Secret Basement Disco / Frazzled Fuzzly
Abby and Bozzly want to help Harriet overcome her shyness about her favorite activity.

Teeny Terry worries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 10:10:00" d="2020-06-03 10:35:00"><n u="Shimmer and Shine">Shimmer and Shine I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% How will Leah finish without any wishes left? (2015)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 10:35:00" d="2020-06-03 10:40:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (98)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Quarrel
Peppa and Suzy Sheep are having a quarrel and decide they are not best friends anymore. As time goes by they really miss each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 10:40:00" d="2020-06-03 10:45:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig I</n><t>O</t>    <k>Bouncy Ball
Peppa and George are playing in the garden with their bouncy ball when Suzy Sheep turns up with two tennis rackets. She uses the bouncy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 10:45:00" d="2020-06-03 10:55:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Powercut
One day all the lights suddenly go out and Peppa’s house is plunged into darkness. There has been a power cut</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 10:55:00" d="2020-06-03 11:00:00"><n u="Ready Set Dance">Ready Set Dance I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>What's My Jam?
An uplifting story about a kid who's just trying to fit in. It's a journey of self-discovery that brings the community together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 11:00:00" d="2020-06-03 11:25:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pup Pup Boogie / Pups in the Fog
The PAW Patrol must work quickly to fix the tracks and remove a train car at the Adventure Bay Train Station, before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 11:25:00" d="2020-06-03 11:55:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pup Pup Goose / Pup Pup and Away
Marshal gets a new BFF when a gosling he names “Fuzzy” takes a liking to him.

When Mayor Goodway accidentally takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 11:55:00" d="2020-06-03 12:20:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines IV (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Meatball Mayhem
When Crusher accidentally knocks a bottle of &quot;grow spice&quot; onto a meatball, it grows to an enormous size and rolls away! It's up to Blaze</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 12:20:00" d="2020-06-03 12:45:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines IV (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Robots in Space
When Space Commander Megan is marooned on Pluto, our robot heroes will race through wormholes, shoot past ice volcanoes, and blast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 12:45:00" d="2020-06-03 13:10:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies III (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% The Unidentified Flying Orchestra!
Strings! Brass! Woodwinds! Percussion! After Gil and Molly meet a conductor, the Guppies want to join an orchestra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 13:10:00" d="2020-06-03 13:20:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% A Turtely Awesome Adventure
Brody has to rescue his turbo-surfing pals when they get caught in the Shipwreck Cove whirlpool (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 13:20:00" d="2020-06-03 13:40:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Brody Goes Home
Brody and Team Top Wing VROOM to the rescue when Brody's little sister slips off the top of Puffin Peak (2017)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 13:40:00" d="2020-06-03 14:10:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol V (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save an Extreme Lunch / Pups Save a Cat Burglar
Daring Danny X is performing a new stunt! He is harnessed over a canyon eating an Extreme Lunch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 14:10:00" d="2020-06-03 14:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol V (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save the Butterflies / Pups Save an Underground Chicken
Chickaletta is stuck on a runaway drone and mysterious butterflies are causing chaos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 14:40:00" d="2020-06-03 15:05:00"><n u="Max &amp; Ruby">Max &amp; Ruby VI (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ruby’s Chocolate Chip Chaos / Max’s Kazoo
Ruby and Louise can’t decide what to sell, until Max’s rocket ship lands in the middle of their sales stand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 15:05:00" d="2020-06-03 15:10:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (62)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% George's Friend
George and Rebecca Rabbit's little brother Richard each have a toy dinosaur but they are not very good at sharing their toys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 15:10:00" d="2020-06-03 15:20:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (63)</n><t>Z</t>    <k>66% The Boat Pond
Peppa and her family and friends are playing at the pond with their toy boats. Everyone has a boat to play with except Rebecca Rabbit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 15:20:00" d="2020-06-03 15:30:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (64)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Mr Scarecrow
The birds keep eating the seeds from Grandpa Pig's flower garden. Peppa and George make a scarecrow, which stops the birds from eating</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 15:30:00" d="2020-06-03 15:55:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets III (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rusty's Raptor Race / Rusty's Triceratops
Rusty and Ruby build a raptor of their own to rescue Frankie Fritz on Dino Island!

When Brawny gets stuck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 15:55:00" d="2020-06-03 16:20:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets III (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Frankie's Super Shoes / Rusty's Rapid Ralph Return
Frankie's souped-up shoes malfunction during the basketball championship game and Rusty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 16:20:00" d="2020-06-03 16:45:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Top Wing Sting/Big Banana Break-In
Rod is super-excited to sing at Rhonda's, until Chomps and Rocco take the piano. The Cadets must get the piano back!

Margo the Monkey and the Banana Bandits break into Headquarters and try to take off with the HQ Command Flyer (2019)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 16:45:00" d="2020-06-03 17:15:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Top Wing Spring Fling / Dancing Daffodil Rescue
Spring means Commodore Smurkturkski gets a new little chick, but Sandy Stork loses the egg!

Big Swirl's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 17:15:00" d="2020-06-03 17:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol IV (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a Sleepover / Pups Save the Carnival
Farmer Al's animals go missing during a sleepover.

Cornelius has escaped from the</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 17:40:00" d="2020-06-03 18:10:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines III (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% The Great Animal Crown
When the Great Animal Crown is lost at the bottom of the ocean, Blaze transforms into a super-fast shark to retrieve</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 18:10:00" d="2020-06-03 18:35:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines III (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Fast Friends
Blaze, AJ, and Gabby meet a brand new monster machine named Watts - a super fast truck with electric tires! But when one of her special tires</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 18:35:00" d="2020-06-03 18:40:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% School Play
Peppa and her friends take part in a school play about Little Red Riding Hood, but Pedro Pony is nervous to be on the stage (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 18:40:00" d="2020-06-03 18:45:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (53)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Polly's Holiday
Granny and Grandpa’s pet, Polly Parrot comes to stay. Peppa and George love Polly Parrot. She is very funny and repeats everything anyone says</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 18:45:00" d="2020-06-03 18:55:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (54)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Windy Autumn Day
It is a cold and windy day. At the park, all the leaves have turned red and yellow. It is so windy that Peppa’s ball blows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 18:55:00" d="2020-06-03 19:00:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (55)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Mysteries
The family is watching “Detective Potato” on TV. Peppa and George want to be detectives too. So, Daddy Pig gives them a mystery to solve</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 19:00:00" d="2020-06-03 19:05:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (56)</n><t>O</t>    <k>66% Bubbles
Peppa and George are playing with bubbles. When the bubble mixture runs out, Daddy Pig shows them how to make really big bubbles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 19:05:00" d="2020-06-03 19:15:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (57)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Bedtime
It’s nearly time for bed and Peppa and George are called in for their bath. After that, they brush their teeth and get into bed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 19:15:00" d="2020-06-03 19:40:00"><n u="Blue's Clues &amp; You">Blue's Clues &amp; You I (4)</n><t>Z</t>    <k>71% Big News with Blue
Blue has something exciting to tell everybody! In this game of Blue's Clues, Josh and the viewer go on a note finding quest, solving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 19:40:00" d="2020-06-03 20:11:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Get Growing / Pups Save a Space Toy
Fertilizer causes Yumi’s crops to sprout huge veggies, so Ryder and the Paw Patrol must corral the stampeding produce!

The Paw Patrol draws a message on Farmer Al’s field to tell the space aliens the pups found their lost toy (2016)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 20:11:00" d="2020-06-03 20:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Get Skunked / Pups and a Whale of a Tale
When Everest gets sprayed by a skunk, the pups delicately try to tell her she needs a bath!

The</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 20:40:00" d="2020-06-03 21:02:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Lunch Box Rescue / Winging It
Timmy Turtle drops his new back-to-school lunch box in the river! The Cadets team up to save the lunch box - and Timmy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 21:02:00" d="2020-06-03 21:06:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (70)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Very good indeed (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 21:06:00" d="2020-06-03 21:10:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (71)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Foggy Day
Mummy and Daddy Pig are taking Peppa and George to play in the playground. On the way it gets a bit foggy, and soon it is so foggy they can’t see</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 21:10:00" d="2020-06-03 21:15:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (72)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% George's Birthday
Today is George’s birthday and Mummy and Daddy Pig have a special day planned. George gets a new Brontosaurus toy and the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 21:15:00" d="2020-06-03 21:25:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (73)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% Then Grandpa also shows them his beehive (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 21:25:00" d="2020-06-03 21:50:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Monkey Cookie Escape! / The New Neighbors!
When a magical mishap makes monkey cookies come alive, the crew has to stop the cookies' monkey business!

The fairy friends leave a welcome basket for their new neighbors. Will Ms. Marmalady take their warm welcome for herself? (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 21:50:00" d="2020-06-03 22:20:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Where's Cookie? / Jasper Learns to Bake!
Cricket accidentally overwhelms Cookie, the café's new kitty, and Cookie runs off. Will the fairy friends find her?

Poppy teaches Jasper how to make cinnamon buns, but when Jasper adds too much yeast, he has a BIG problem (2017)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 22:20:00" d="2020-06-03 22:25:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (79)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Long Grass
The grass has grown so long that Peppa and George's ball gets lost. Grandpa arrives with his fantastic, motorised lawnmower</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 22:25:00" d="2020-06-03 22:30:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (80)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Zoe Zebra
Mr. Zebra the Postman gets help from his daughter Zoë. Zoë has a very special letter for Peppa and George; an invitation to her birthday party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 22:30:00" d="2020-06-03 22:35:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (81)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% Painting
Peppa and George are painting. Daddy shows them how to mix paints and the three of them paint a beautiful picture of a cherry tree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 22:35:00" d="2020-06-03 22:45:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (82)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Cuckoo Clock
Daddy Pig winds up the old cuckoo clock. When a wooden cuckoo pops out singing “Cuckoo!”, Peppa thinks it is very funny, but George</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 22:45:00" d="2020-06-03 23:10:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% The Arctic Life!
Brrrr! The Arctic sure is cold—probably because it’s filled with so many cool animals! After meeting Arctic Dan, Gil embarks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 23:10:00" d="2020-06-03 23:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol IV (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a Sleepover / Pups Save the Carnival
Farmer Al's animals go missing during a sleepover.

Cornelius has escaped from the</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 23:40:00" d="2020-06-04 00:05:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol IV (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save Jake's Cake / Pups Save a Wild Ride
Ryder and the Pups need to help get a surprise birthday ice cream cake up to Jake's cabin.

Alex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 00:05:00" d="2020-06-04 00:30:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rusty's Spooky Adventure / Rusty Loses the Bits
Rusty and Liam love it when Mr. Higgins makes Sparkton Hills seem haunted with his 'Spooky Adventure'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 00:30:00" d="2020-06-04 00:55:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rusty's Plant Predicament / Rusty's Beach Day Delay
Super stinky weeds invade town but Botasaur thinks they’re delicious!

Rusty turns Botasaur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 00:55:00" d="2020-06-04 01:25:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save the Sea Turtles / Pups and the Very Big Baby
Ryder, Chase, and Rubble hatch a plan to help sea turtle hatchlings safely cross the</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 01:25:00" d="2020-06-04 01:55:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups and the Kitty-tastrophe / Pups Save a Train
Ryder and the PAW Patrol rescue a lost kitty from the bay, but who will save them from all the mayhem she causes?

Ryder, Rubble, and Rocky call in Chase to help them free Katie and Cali’s train from a rockslide (2013)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 01:55:00" d="2020-06-04 02:15:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines IV (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% The Chicken Circus!
Blaze, AJ, and Darington are in the front row for the amazing Chicken Circus! But when Crusher accidentally launches the chickens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 02:15:00" d="2020-06-04 02:40:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Darington to the Moon!
Today Darington will attempt his biggest stunt yet: rocketing to the moon! But his battery-powered rocket is out of energy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 02:40:00" d="2020-06-04 03:00:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines II (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Spark Bug
Blaze, Stripes, and AJ are racing through the jungle when Stripes discovers a lost little fire beetle named Sparky. Blaze and his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 03:00:00" d="2020-06-04 03:25:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies III (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% The Elephant Trunk-A-Dunk!
Gil's looking for elephants! He loves them all—African and Asian. He's in for a treat when the Guppies fill the stands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 03:25:00" d="2020-06-04 03:45:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies III (7)</n><t>O</t>    <k>68% The Super Ballet Bowl!
Jump! Leap! Relevé! Bubbletucky sports fans love ballet! Molly and the rest of the Guppies want to learn how to tell a story through dance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 03:45:00" d="2020-06-04 04:10:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines IV (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% The 100 Egg Challenge
The Great Egg Hunt has just begun, and Blaze and Crusher are racing all over town to see who can find the most eggs. Only the first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 04:10:00" d="2020-06-04 04:30:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines IV (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Midnight Mile
It may be nighttime in Axle City, but all the trucks are staying up super late for the ultimate all-night race: the Midnight Mile! And the first truck to cross the finish line will win the Glow-in-the-Dark trophy (2017)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 04:30:00" d="2020-06-04 04:55:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol VI (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups and the Stinky Bubble Trouble / Pups Save the Baby Ostriches
What's that smell? A strange odor is chasing the jungle animals away from their homes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 04:55:00" d="2020-06-04 05:15:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol VI (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save Gustavo's Guitar / Pups Save the Yoga Goats
Gustavo Goodway's guitar is missing. The pups need to find it before tonight's campfire concert!

Farmer Yumi's new Yoga Goat class is a hit, until her goats go missing! It's up to the Paw Patrol to find the goats and return them to Yumi's farm (2019)</k>  </p>
</a>
