<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="73" t="2020-05-28 04:42:58"><p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 05:15:00" d="2020-06-04 05:40:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ruby's Comet Adventure / Rusty's Messy Mishap
Ruby wants to see a comet fly by, and Rusty will do everything in his power to make sure his friend's wish comes true!

Rusty and Ruby race to fix a leaking underwater oil pipeline before it pollutes the lake and makes it uninhabitable (2018)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 05:40:00" d="2020-06-04 06:00:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Fix It 500 / Ice Ice Rusty
Frankie Fritz challenges Rusty and Ruby to a race around Sparkton Hills, with the Mobile Rivet Lab as the stakes.

Rusty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 06:00:00" d="2020-06-04 06:25:00"><n u="Becca's Bunch">Becca's Bunch I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Legendary Gill / Benny &amp; Shelly's Big Day Out
The Bunch remember their big adventure when they set out to prove that Legendary Gill, the giant fish, is real</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 06:25:00" d="2020-06-04 06:50:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines III (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Knighty Knights
In the kingdom of knight-trucks, Blaze discovers a machine his medieval pals use to recharge. When a dragon snatches the charging station</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 06:50:00" d="2020-06-04 07:20:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets II (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rusty and the Pirates of Sparkton Hills / Rusty's Mouse Problem
Rusty and Ruby set off on their pirate ship in a hunt for a buried treasure.

When</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 07:20:00" d="2020-06-04 07:45:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Time to call the PAW Patrol (2016)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 07:45:00" d="2020-06-04 08:15:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a Goldrush / Pups Save the Paw Patroller
When a grizzled old prospector discovers gold in Adventure Bay, it’s a bona fide, dog gone, gold rush!

When Mayor Humdinger and the Kit-tastrophe Crew try to steal the Paw Patroller, the chase becomes a rescue (2016)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 08:15:00" d="2020-06-04 08:40:00"><n u="Blue's Clues &amp; You">Blue's Clues &amp; You I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Laugh with Blue
Josh is being silly but still can't get Blue to laugh! We play Blue's Clues to figure out what will make Blue laugh</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 08:40:00" d="2020-06-04 09:00:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Penny Rescues A Treasure / Penny Rocks the Road Wing
Penny races to save the lost treasure of Shipwreck Cove - and Commodore Smurkturkski!

Rod</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 09:00:00" d="2020-06-04 09:30:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Towering Tower of Crepes!
Jasper wants to help Butterbean cook for her idol, Chef Belle Legume! Butterbean thinks his speedy skills would be perfect for the spatula</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 09:30:00" d="2020-06-04 09:45:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Will she &quot;ketch&quot; the culprit? (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 09:45:00" d="2020-06-04 10:10:00"><n u="Abby Hatcher">Abby Hatcher I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Trick or Treat Otis / Bedtime for Peepers
Otis gets mistaken for a real dog while trick or treating, and Abby and the group need to find him.

When</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 10:10:00" d="2020-06-04 10:35:00"><n u="Shimmer and Shine">Shimmer and Shine I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Dino Might!
After searching endlessly for Zac’s missing dinosaur toy, Leah asks her genies to wish up a replacement and gets stuck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 10:35:00" d="2020-06-04 10:40:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Daddy Pig Birthday
Today is Daddy Pig's birthday, but he has to go to work. While he is away, Mummy Pig, Peppa and George prepare a special birthday surprise (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 10:40:00" d="2020-06-04 10:45:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Sleepover
Peppa is going for a sleepover at Zoë Zebra’s house with Suzy Sheep, Rebecca Rabbit, Candy Cat and Emily Elephant. The girls stay up playing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 10:45:00" d="2020-06-04 10:55:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Stars
It is night time and the sky is full of stars. Mummy and Daddy Pig let Peppa and George put their coats on and they go outside to look at the stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 10:55:00" d="2020-06-04 11:00:00"><n u="Ready Set Dance">Ready Set Dance I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Get Down Granny
A groovy little story about a Granny who knows how to get down, if she would only, wake up (2019)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 11:00:00" d="2020-06-04 11:25:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups on Ice / Pups and the Snow Monster
Ryder and the PAW Patrol need to rescue Alex on Jakes mountain.

The pups find strange footprints</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 11:25:00" d="2020-06-04 11:55:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Ryder and the Paw Patrol search Adventure bay (2013)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 11:55:00" d="2020-06-04 12:20:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines IV (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Power Tires!
When his tires get popped, Blaze thinks he's out of the race for good. Luckily, Gabby is there with a new set of Power Tires - high-tech</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 12:20:00" d="2020-06-04 12:45:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines IV (12)</n><t>L</t>    <k>59% Snow Day Showdown
It's a snowy day in Axle City, and every truck in town is lining up for a delicious winter warm-up: hot chocolate! But when Crusher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 12:45:00" d="2020-06-04 13:10:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies III (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Come to Your Senses!
Oh no! Nonny broke his glasses! When they’re fixed, Nonny is determined to retrieve them on his own. But to do it, he’ll</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 13:10:00" d="2020-06-04 13:20:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Birthday Bandits!
The Monkey Bandits take Rod's birthday cake and Road-Wing. Can Swift rescue the party without ruining the surprise? (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 13:20:00" d="2020-06-04 13:40:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Rod and Brody's Jungle Adventure
Rod and Brody try to earn a Jungle Exploring badge. They get lost and must work together to help Swift find them (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 13:40:00" d="2020-06-04 14:10:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol V (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a Bookmobile / Pups Save Heady Humdinger
When Ms. Marjorie brings her bookmobile to Everest and the kids of the mountains, Maynard accidentally</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 14:10:00" d="2020-06-04 14:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol V (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save the PawPaws / Pups Save a Popped Top
Carlos and Tracker make PawPaw juice with the PAW Patrol when they find out Mayor Goodway and Chickaletta are in trouble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 14:40:00" d="2020-06-04 15:05:00"><n u="Max &amp; Ruby">Max &amp; Ruby VI (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Max and Ruby’s Museum Adventure
A trip to the museum sparks some debate over which exhibit the class would like to have their big sleepover in (2016)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 15:05:00" d="2020-06-04 15:10:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (65)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Time Capsule
Peppa and her school friends are making a time capsule. They each put one of their favourite things inside and bury it in the school garden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 15:10:00" d="2020-06-04 15:20:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (66)</n><t>Z</t>    <k>66% Recycling
Peppa and George help Mummy Pig tidy up the breakfast things. Mummy Pig tells them that bottles go into a special green box to be recycled Peppa and George have fun filling the boxes (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 15:20:00" d="2020-06-04 15:30:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (67)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Daddy Pig's Office
Peppa and George are visiting Daddy Pig’s office today. Daddy Pig works with Mr Rabbit and Mrs Cat. Mr. Rabbit’s job is all about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 15:30:00" d="2020-06-04 15:55:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets III (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rusty and the Search for Ozzy / Rusty's Dactyl Dilemma
Ozzy goes missing on Dino Island.

Dak is stranded off-shore with a busted wing (2019)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 15:55:00" d="2020-06-04 16:20:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets III (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Detective Rusty / Rusty's Chilling Rescue
Rusty and Ruby go into sleuth mode to discover why items are going missing from all around town.

When</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 16:20:00" d="2020-06-04 16:45:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Penny Rescues Survivor Bear / Penny's Jungle Adventure
Survivor Bear is headed UNDERWATER! Penny, and the rest of the team, have to rescue him using</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 16:45:00" d="2020-06-04 17:15:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Trouble With Treegoats / Rhonda's Rockin' Family Reunion
The Cadets are put to the test as they babysit some rambunctious tree goats who can climb anything!

Rhonda's very big family is coming for a reunion. The Cadets dance the excited Rhinos to the beach (2019)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 17:15:00" d="2020-06-04 17:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol IV (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save Jake's Cake / Pups Save a Wild Ride
Ryder and the Pups need to help get a surprise birthday ice cream cake up to Jake's cabin.

Alex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 17:40:00" d="2020-06-04 18:10:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines III (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Race for the Golden Treasure
Blaze and Pegwheel the Pirate have teamed up for the ultimate treasure hunt! Together they must find three keys to unlock a special chest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 18:10:00" d="2020-06-04 18:35:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines III (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Need for Blazing Speed
When Crusher tries to get Blazing Speed for himself, he accidentally sends Blaze's engine flying! Now it's Blaze vs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 18:35:00" d="2020-06-04 18:40:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (58)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% There’s enough for everyone in the traffic jam (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 18:40:00" d="2020-06-04 18:45:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (59)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Rock Pools
Granny and Grandpa Pig take Peppa and George to a beach with lots of rocks and little rock pools to explore. They all have fun with a little</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 18:45:00" d="2020-06-04 18:55:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (60)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Teddy's Day Out
Peppa and her family are having a picnic. Mr Zebra the Postman and Zoë Zebra are having a picnic too, so they decide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 18:55:00" d="2020-06-04 19:00:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (61)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Emily Elephant
There's a new pupil at the playgroup, Emily Elephant. Everybody wants to be her friend because she is very good at building blocks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 19:00:00" d="2020-06-04 19:05:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (62)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% George's Friend
George and Rebecca Rabbit's little brother Richard each have a toy dinosaur but they are not very good at sharing their toys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 19:05:00" d="2020-06-04 19:15:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (63)</n><t>Z</t>    <k>66% The Boat Pond
Peppa and her family and friends are playing at the pond with their toy boats. Everyone has a boat to play with except Rebecca Rabbit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 19:15:00" d="2020-06-04 19:40:00"><n u="Blue's Clues &amp; You">Blue's Clues &amp; You I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% ABC's with Blue
We are reading Blue's Clues to figure out what book Blue wants to read for story time. While looking for clues we practice letter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 19:40:00" d="2020-06-04 20:11:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Parroting Pups / Merpups Save the Turbots
Rocky loses his voice and can’t bark out his puppack tools, but Matea the parrot has no problem doing it for him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 20:11:00" d="2020-06-04 20:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save the Gliding Turbots / Pups Save a Plane
Francois and Cap’n Turbot become stranded on a remote island,Ryder and the pups fly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 20:40:00" d="2020-06-04 21:02:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Great Flash Wing Rescue / Turtle Train Rescue
The Cadets rescue Cheep, Chirp and Swift's Flash-Wing when Baddy McBat takes the jet with the chicks inside!

Falling rocks derail the Turtle Train! Swift must learn to pilot Penny's sub as they team up for the underwater rescue (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 21:02:00" d="2020-06-04 21:06:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (74)</n><t>O</t>    <k>66% The Sports Day
It is Sports Day at Peppa’s playgroup. There are lots of exciting events, including running, jumping and the “tug of war”. Daddy Pig tells</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 21:06:00" d="2020-06-04 21:10:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (75)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% GrandDad Dog's Garage
Peppa’s car runs out of petrol but thankfully Granddad Dog’s garage isn’t far away. With one phone call, Granddad Dog is on his way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 21:10:00" d="2020-06-04 21:15:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (76)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Balloon Ride
Peppa wins the top prize in a raffle at school: a trip in a hot air balloon. Mummy Pig, Daddy Pig, George and Peppa climb aboard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 21:15:00" d="2020-06-04 21:25:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (77)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% George Catches a Cold
Peppa and George love jumping in puddles, even when it’s raining – but when George takes off his rain hat, he catches a cold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 21:25:00" d="2020-06-04 21:50:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (16)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Surprise Cake! / Tic Tac Tomato!
Cricket wants to surprise Poppy with a cake! But can she finish it before Poppy returns from running errands?

Cricket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 21:50:00" d="2020-06-04 22:20:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Who will be crowned the Queen of Quiche? (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 22:20:00" d="2020-06-04 22:25:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (83)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Cycle Ride
Peppa and her family are going for a day’s cycle ride. Peppa loves cycling downhill but she’s not so keen on peddling uphill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 22:25:00" d="2020-06-04 22:30:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (84)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Peppa and George love ice-skating (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 22:30:00" d="2020-06-04 22:35:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (85)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Dentist
Peppa and George are at the dentist. Dr Elephant says that Peppa and George’s teeth are lovely and clean. But George’s plastic toy “Mr Dinosaur”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 22:35:00" d="2020-06-04 22:45:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (86)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Dens
Peppa is playing in the tree-house with the girls, and George and the boys stay in the castle that Grandpa Pig built for them. But when it starts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 22:45:00" d="2020-06-04 23:10:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies III (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Puppy Love!
Bubble Puppy’s got a cold! While Dr. Martin, the veterinarian, takes good care of him, the kids spend the day thinking about dogs—a Guppy’s best friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 23:10:00" d="2020-06-04 23:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol IV (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save the Flying Food / Pups Save a Ferris Wheel
Mr. Porter's delivery drones have gone out of control, and now they are air-dropping food everywhere!

Mayor Humdinger steals Adventure Bay's Ferris Wheel (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-04 23:40:00" d="2020-06-05 00:05:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol IV (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save A Sleepwalking Bear / Pups Save Dude Ranch Danny
The pups need to get a sleepwalking bear back home before he wakes up.

Daring Danny X takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-05 00:05:00" d="2020-06-05 00:30:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rusty's Dancing Suit / Rusty Bee Good
Mr. Higgins wants to go to the town dance, but thinks he's a terrible dancer. So Rusty and Ruby build</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-05 00:30:00" d="2020-06-05 00:55:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Robo Rusty / Rusty's Kitty Catastrophe
Rusty builds a robot version of himself, so he can do two things at once.

Rusty and Ruby build a robotic buddy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-05 00:55:00" d="2020-06-05 01:25:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pup Pup Boogie / Pups in the Fog
The PAW Patrol must work quickly to fix the tracks and remove a train car at the Adventure Bay Train Station, before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-05 01:25:00" d="2020-06-05 01:55:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pup Pup Goose / Pup Pup and Away
Marshal gets a new BFF when a gosling he names “Fuzzy” takes a liking to him.

When Mayor Goodway accidentally takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-05 01:55:00" d="2020-06-05 02:15:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines IV (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Ninja Blaze
Ninja Master Blackbelt is training Blaze and AJ to be powerful ninjas when Crusher and Pickle accidentally launch themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-05 02:15:00" d="2020-06-05 02:40:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines II (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Fire Alarm Blaze
There's a fire on the bridge, and it's too much for the Fire Chief and his team to handle. They need Firefighting Blaze to help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-05 02:40:00" d="2020-06-05 03:00:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Axle City Grand Prix
Gabby has the perfect tool to get Blaze ready to race: a special remote that can control any machine. But when Crusher takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-05 03:00:00" d="2020-06-05 03:25:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies III (8)</n><t>L</t>    <k>68% The Wizard of Oz-tralia
After Molly and Gil meet Bobby, a nature show host from Australia, they can't wait to learn all about Australian animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-05 03:25:00" d="2020-06-05 03:45:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% The Arctic Life!
Brrrr! The Arctic sure is cold—probably because it’s filled with so many cool animals! After meeting Arctic Dan, Gil embarks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-05 03:45:00" d="2020-06-05 04:10:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines V (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% AJ to the Rescue
Blaze and AJ are racing through the jungle when Blaze gets trapped in super sticky mud! Now it's up to AJ and his new animal friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-05 04:10:00" d="2020-06-05 04:30:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines V (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% The Trophy Chase
The Championship Race is about to start, and all the fastest trucks in town are ready to roll! But when Crusher steals the trophy before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-05 04:30:00" d="2020-06-05 04:55:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% But how can Chase help? (2013)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-05 04:55:00" d="2020-06-05 05:15:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save the Sea Turtles / Pups and the Very Big Baby
Ryder, Chase, and Rubble hatch a plan to help sea turtle hatchlings safely cross the</k>  </p>
</a>
