<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="91" t="2020-05-31 04:36:18"><p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 05:15:00" d="2020-06-07 05:40:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rusty's Piggy Bank Heist / Rusty's Whale of a Problem
Rusty forgets the code to his robotic piggy bank, activating its self-defense mode and turning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 05:40:00" d="2020-06-07 06:00:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rusty's Relaxing Recliner / Rusty and the Stinky Situation
Rusty builds his Mom the ultimate relaxing chair, but whenever it hears any noise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 06:00:00" d="2020-06-07 06:25:00"><n u="Becca's Bunch">Becca's Bunch I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mom's Day / Fogtail Woods
Becca thinks bigger is better when it comes to a gift for Moms' Day but she soon learns that it's the thought that counts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 06:25:00" d="2020-06-07 06:50:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines III (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Animal Island
Blaze and Stripes sail to Animal Island - an incredible place inhabited by monster truck animals! But when a greedy lizard puts the island</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 06:50:00" d="2020-06-07 07:20:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets II (11)</n><t>L</t>    <k>Rusty's Show Must Go On / Rusty and the S'mores Snatcher
Rusty, Ruby, and TigerBot help a stranded baby giraffe in the desert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 07:20:00" d="2020-06-07 07:45:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a Dragon / Pups Save the Three Little Pigs
A fantasy fire breathing dragon comes to life and won’t let Ryder and pups into the Lookout! Paw Patrol takes to the Air Patroller!

The Paw Patrol help three little pigs build new houses after theirs mysteriously disappear (2016)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 07:45:00" d="2020-06-07 08:15:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a Stinky Flower / Pups Save a Monkey-Naut
Mayor Humdinger drops off a ‘gift’ to Mayor Goodway, a flower that spreads a horrible stink when it blooms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 08:15:00" d="2020-06-07 09:00:00"><n>Shimmer and Shine</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The First Wish
A pair of fraternal twin genies-in-training unintentionally cause chaos in their attempts to grant wishes for their best friend, Leah (2015)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 09:00:00" d="2020-06-07 09:05:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pancakes
Mummy Pig makes pancakes, and Peppa and George help, but Daddy Pig flips his pancake so high it sticks to the ceiling (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 09:05:00" d="2020-06-07 09:10:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Ballet Lesson
Peppa goes to her first ballet lesson, and meets her friends there. She decides to teach Mummy Pig and Daddy Pig to dance but finds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 09:10:00" d="2020-06-07 09:20:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Cleaning the Car
Peppa and her family have to wash the car when it gets dirty (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 09:20:00" d="2020-06-07 09:45:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Will she tell her how she feels? (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 09:45:00" d="2020-06-07 10:10:00"><n u="Abby Hatcher">Abby Hatcher I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Princess Flug's Pet Slug / Fuzzly Photo Day
Princess Flug finds a slug and wants it to be her pet.

Abby wants to send a picture of her and the Fuzzlies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 10:10:00" d="2020-06-07 10:35:00"><n u="Shimmer and Shine">Shimmer and Shine I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Ahoy, Genies!
When Leah’s bucket full of beach treasures floats into the vast ocean, Leah summons Shimmer and Shine to help her retrieve the loot (2015)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 10:35:00" d="2020-06-07 10:40:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (6)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% The Playgroup
Peppa and George are going to daycare. It's George's first day at daycare, and he shows the class his interest in dinosaurs (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 10:40:00" d="2020-06-07 10:50:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Piggy in the Middle
Peppa teaches George how to catch a ball, and later, they play Monkey in the Middle with Mummy Pig (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 10:50:00" d="2020-06-07 10:55:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (71)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Foggy Day
Mummy and Daddy Pig are taking Peppa and George to play in the playground. On the way it gets a bit foggy, and soon it is so foggy they can’t see</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 10:55:00" d="2020-06-07 11:00:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (72)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% George's Birthday
Today is George’s birthday and Mummy and Daddy Pig have a special day planned. George gets a new Brontosaurus toy and the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 11:00:00" d="2020-06-07 11:10:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (76)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Balloon Ride
Peppa wins the top prize in a raffle at school: a trip in a hot air balloon. Mummy Pig, Daddy Pig, George and Peppa climb aboard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 11:10:00" d="2020-06-07 11:15:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The room doesn't stay tidy for long though (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 11:15:00" d="2020-06-07 11:20:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Playground
Peppa and George go to the playground. Peppa's friends are also there. Peppa likes going on the swings but George does not because</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 11:20:00" d="2020-06-07 11:30:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% At the Beach
Peppa and her family go to the beach, and they do lots of things there including burying Daddy Pig in the sand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 11:30:00" d="2020-06-07 11:35:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Mister Skinnylegs
George finds a spider in the bathroom sink, but Peppa is really frightened-until she realizes that it doesn't want to hurt her (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 11:35:00" d="2020-06-07 11:40:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Grandpa Pig's Boat
Peppa and George go for a ride in Grandpa Pig's boat. Danny Dog and Granddad Dog are also out sailing. Grandpa Pig and Granddad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 11:40:00" d="2020-06-07 11:45:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% My Birthday Party
It is Peppa's birthday, and Peppa has a party (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 11:45:00" d="2020-06-07 11:50:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (51)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% Daddy's Movie Camera
Daddy gets a new video camera. First, Peppa shows him how to work it, and then he records Peppa being silly (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 11:50:00" d="2020-06-07 11:55:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% School Play
Peppa and her friends take part in a school play about Little Red Riding Hood, but Pedro Pony is nervous to be on the stage (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 11:55:00" d="2020-06-07 12:00:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (53)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Polly's Holiday
Granny and Grandpa’s pet, Polly Parrot comes to stay. Peppa and George love Polly Parrot. She is very funny and repeats everything anyone says</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 12:00:00" d="2020-06-07 12:10:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (55)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Mysteries
The family is watching “Detective Potato” on TV. Peppa and George want to be detectives too. So, Daddy Pig gives them a mystery to solve</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 12:10:00" d="2020-06-07 12:15:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (56)</n><t>O</t>    <k>66% Bubbles
Peppa and George are playing with bubbles. When the bubble mixture runs out, Daddy Pig shows them how to make really big bubbles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 12:15:00" d="2020-06-07 12:20:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (57)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Bedtime
It’s nearly time for bed and Peppa and George are called in for their bath. After that, they brush their teeth and get into bed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 12:20:00" d="2020-06-07 12:30:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (59)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Rock Pools
Granny and Grandpa Pig take Peppa and George to a beach with lots of rocks and little rock pools to explore. They all have fun with a little</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 12:30:00" d="2020-06-07 12:35:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (60)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Teddy's Day Out
Peppa and her family are having a picnic. Mr Zebra the Postman and Zoë Zebra are having a picnic too, so they decide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 12:35:00" d="2020-06-07 12:40:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (61)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Emily Elephant
There's a new pupil at the playgroup, Emily Elephant. Everybody wants to be her friend because she is very good at building blocks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 12:40:00" d="2020-06-07 12:45:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (62)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% George's Friend
George and Rebecca Rabbit's little brother Richard each have a toy dinosaur but they are not very good at sharing their toys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 12:45:00" d="2020-06-07 12:50:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (63)</n><t>Z</t>    <k>66% The Boat Pond
Peppa and her family and friends are playing at the pond with their toy boats. Everyone has a boat to play with except Rebecca Rabbit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 12:50:00" d="2020-06-07 12:55:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (64)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Mr Scarecrow
The birds keep eating the seeds from Grandpa Pig's flower garden. Peppa and George make a scarecrow, which stops the birds from eating</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 12:55:00" d="2020-06-07 13:00:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (65)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Time Capsule
Peppa and her school friends are making a time capsule. They each put one of their favourite things inside and bury it in the school garden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 13:00:00" d="2020-06-07 13:11:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (67)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Daddy Pig's Office
Peppa and George are visiting Daddy Pig’s office today. Daddy Pig works with Mr Rabbit and Mrs Cat. Mr. Rabbit’s job is all about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 13:11:00" d="2020-06-07 13:16:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (68)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% Pirate Island
Grandpa and Granny Pig are taking Peppa, George and their friends to Pirate Island. Grandpa shows how to use his metal detector</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 13:16:00" d="2020-06-07 13:21:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (69)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Jumble Sale
Peppa’s playgroup is holding a jumble sale to raise money for a new roof and Madame Gazelle asks everyone to bring something to sell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 13:21:00" d="2020-06-07 13:26:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (71)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Foggy Day
Mummy and Daddy Pig are taking Peppa and George to play in the playground. On the way it gets a bit foggy, and soon it is so foggy they can’t see</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 13:26:00" d="2020-06-07 13:30:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (72)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% George's Birthday
Today is George’s birthday and Mummy and Daddy Pig have a special day planned. George gets a new Brontosaurus toy and the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 13:30:00" d="2020-06-07 13:40:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (73)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% Then Grandpa also shows them his beehive (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 13:40:00" d="2020-06-07 14:10:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol V (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% ULTIMATE RESCUE: Pups Save the Movie Monster!
Envious Humdinger tries to draw the Adventure Bay Monster Movie production to Foggy Bottom by commandeering</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 14:10:00" d="2020-06-07 14:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol V (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a Pluck-O-Matic / Pups Save a Mascot
Yumi's new Robo- Corn Plucker goes haywire, and Ryder and the Paw Patrol must get it under control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 14:40:00" d="2020-06-07 15:10:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Will her friends prove her wrong? (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 15:10:00" d="2020-06-07 15:40:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Who will deliver the Sneeze-Be-Gone soup? (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 15:40:00" d="2020-06-07 16:00:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Cheep, Chirp, and the Pirate's Treasure / Rod's amily Popcorn Party
Cap'n Dilly makes the chicks mini-pirates to find a treasure chest key</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 16:00:00" d="2020-06-07 16:30:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Top Wing Rescues the Academy
The Cadets must pass Inspector Eagle-Eye's test or Speedy and Bea will be sent back to teacher's school! Team Top Wing ace the test and rescue the Inspector using the Headquarters Command Flyer: a part of the HQ that can fly (2019)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 16:30:00" d="2020-06-07 17:00:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save the Gliding Turbots / Pups Save a Plane
Francois and Cap’n Turbot become stranded on a remote island,Ryder and the pups fly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 17:00:00" d="2020-06-07 17:25:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a Giant Plant / Pups Get Stuck
Buddy - Mayor Goodway’s gesture of goodwill gift grows wildly out of control when it’s planted in the wrong place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 17:25:00" d="2020-06-07 17:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a Robosaurus
When a homemade Robotic Dino named Earl comes to life, the pups need to find him, stop him, and bring him home (2016)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 17:40:00" d="2020-06-07 18:10:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines IV (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% The Chicken Circus!
Blaze, AJ, and Darington are in the front row for the amazing Chicken Circus! But when Crusher accidentally launches the chickens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 18:10:00" d="2020-06-07 18:35:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines IV (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Ninja Blaze
Ninja Master Blackbelt is training Blaze and AJ to be powerful ninjas when Crusher and Pickle accidentally launch themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 18:35:00" d="2020-06-07 18:40:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (76)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Balloon Ride
Peppa wins the top prize in a raffle at school: a trip in a hot air balloon. Mummy Pig, Daddy Pig, George and Peppa climb aboard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 18:40:00" d="2020-06-07 18:45:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (77)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% George Catches a Cold
Peppa and George love jumping in puddles, even when it’s raining – but when George takes off his rain hat, he catches a cold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 18:45:00" d="2020-06-07 18:55:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (78)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Eye Test
Pedro Pony wears glasses. Peppa thinks she might need glasses too, so Mummy Pig takes her to the optician. Peppa is a little disappointed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 18:55:00" d="2020-06-07 19:00:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (79)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Long Grass
The grass has grown so long that Peppa and George's ball gets lost. Grandpa arrives with his fantastic, motorised lawnmower</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 19:00:00" d="2020-06-07 19:05:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (80)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Zoe Zebra
Mr. Zebra the Postman gets help from his daughter Zoë. Zoë has a very special letter for Peppa and George; an invitation to her birthday party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 19:05:00" d="2020-06-07 19:15:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (81)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% Painting
Peppa and George are painting. Daddy shows them how to mix paints and the three of them paint a beautiful picture of a cherry tree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 19:15:00" d="2020-06-07 19:40:00"><n u="Blue's Clues &amp; You">Blue's Clues &amp; You I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Laugh with Blue
Josh is being silly but still can't get Blue to laugh! We play Blue's Clues to figure out what will make Blue laugh</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 19:40:00" d="2020-06-07 20:11:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol IV (2)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% Pups Save A Teeny Penguin / Pups Save the Cat Show
Everest and Jake try to rescue a little penguin and end up floating out to sea on a homemade bridge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 20:11:00" d="2020-06-07 20:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol IV (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a Playful Dragon / Pups Save the Critters
Buddy, the playful dragon from one of Alex's books, gets out and the pups</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 20:40:00" d="2020-06-07 21:02:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Beaver Dam Rescue / The Great Goat-Cart Race
When Ward Beaver accidently breaks the dam, Team Top Wing VROOM to the rescue.

It's time for the big &quot;goat cart&quot; race! But when a Treegoat races &quot;off-road&quot; into the river, Team Top Wing have to rescue the goat and the race (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 21:02:00" d="2020-06-07 21:06:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (86)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Dens
Peppa is playing in the tree-house with the girls, and George and the boys stay in the castle that Grandpa Pig built for them. But when it starts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 21:06:00" d="2020-06-07 21:10:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (87)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Grandpa's Little Train
Grandpa Pig has built a fantastic little train called “Gertrude” and he takes Peppa and George for a ride</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 21:10:00" d="2020-06-07 21:15:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (88)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% School Bus Trip
Madame Gazelle takes Peppa and her school friends on a school bus trip to the mountains. From the top of the mountains there</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 21:15:00" d="2020-06-07 21:25:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (89)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Rebecca Rabbit
Peppa and George are going to Rebecca Rabbit’s house today. It is a bit different to Peppa’s house; it is inside a hill, with tunnels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 21:25:00" d="2020-06-07 21:50:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Cricket's Forever Friend / Dazzle's Tea-riffic Teapot!
Cricket's friend is moving away! When they get in a fight, Cricket worries she's missed her chance to say goodbye</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 21:50:00" d="2020-06-07 22:20:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Cricket's Treasure Hunt! / The Puddlebrook Gold Rush!
Cricket goes on a treasure hunt for a mysterious, ruby red fruit. Will she find the treasure?

A</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 22:20:00" d="2020-06-07 22:25:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (95)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% School Camp
Peppa and her friends are going camping with Madame Gazelle. When it gets dark, they all sing a song around the campfire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 22:25:00" d="2020-06-07 22:30:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (96)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Toy Cupboard
Peppa and George's toy basket is full and their beds are covered in toys. Mummy Pig orders a new toy cupboard, but it needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 22:30:00" d="2020-06-07 22:35:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (97)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Captain Daddy Pig
Peppa and her family borrow Grandpa Pig’s boat for a day on the river. Daddy Pig is the captain, Peppa, George and Mummy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 22:35:00" d="2020-06-07 22:45:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (98)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Quarrel
Peppa and Suzy Sheep are having a quarrel and decide they are not best friends anymore. As time goes by they really miss each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 22:45:00" d="2020-06-07 23:10:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies III (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% The Unidentified Flying Orchestra!
Strings! Brass! Woodwinds! Percussion! After Gil and Molly meet a conductor, the Guppies want to join an orchestra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 23:10:00" d="2020-06-07 23:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol IV (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a Space Rock / Pups Save a Good Mayor
Everest, the Turbots and a Space Rock get trapped in a cave.

Mayor Goodway goes missing and Mayor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-07 23:40:00" d="2020-06-08 00:05:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol IV (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a City Kitty / Pups Save a Cloud Surfer
Cali gets lost in the woods.

Daring Danny X's harness loosens while kite-surfing (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-08 00:05:00" d="2020-06-08 00:30:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Frankie's Botasaur / Rusty's Mega Stacker
New neighbor Frankie Fritz bot-naps Botasaur, making Rusty and Ruby go on a chase to get their friend back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-08 00:30:00" d="2020-06-08 00:55:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Fix It 500 / Ice Ice Rusty
Frankie Fritz challenges Rusty and Ruby to a race around Sparkton Hills, with the Mobile Rivet Lab as the stakes.

Rusty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-08 00:55:00" d="2020-06-08 01:25:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Get a Rubble / Pups Save a Walrus
We see a flashback of how Rubble became a member of the Paw Patrol!

When Wally the Walrus gets tangled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-08 01:25:00" d="2020-06-08 01:55:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save the Bunnies / Puptacular
Farmer Yumi’s carrots are disappearing and she calls Ryder and the Paw Patrol for help.

Katie is excited</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-08 01:55:00" d="2020-06-08 02:15:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines IV (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Robots to the Rescue
When three big emergencies turn out to be too much for one truck alone, Blaze turns himself and his friends into super strong robots</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-08 02:15:00" d="2020-06-08 02:40:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines II (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Race Car Superstar
Blaze and AJ visit VelocityVille, a town full of race cars where everybody loves to go fast! When a snooty car named Speedrick traps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-08 02:40:00" d="2020-06-08 03:00:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines II (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Race to Eagle Rock
Blaze brings all of his monster truck pals to VelocityVille for a wild race to the top of Eagle Rock! But Crusher will stop at nothing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-08 03:00:00" d="2020-06-08 03:25:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies III (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Come to Your Senses!
Oh no! Nonny broke his glasses! When they’re fixed, Nonny is determined to retrieve them on his own. But to do it, he’ll</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-08 03:25:00" d="2020-06-08 03:45:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies III (16)</n><t>L</t>    <k>68% Puddleball!
When rain spoils a game of kickball, Gil invents a new game that shows how fun a little rain can be. But when the weather turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-08 03:45:00" d="2020-06-08 04:10:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Bouncy Tires
When Zeg the dinosaur truck accidentally puts on a set of “Super Bouncy Tires,” he bounces out of control! Now Blaze and AJ have to experiment to find a substance adhesive enough to stop their bouncing buddy (2014)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-08 04:10:00" d="2020-06-08 04:30:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines I (6)</n><t>L</t>    <k>59% Stuntmania!
Darington has built the ultimate stunt-track, and every Monster Machine in town is coming to see the show! But when a jealous Crusher tricks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-08 04:30:00" d="2020-06-08 04:55:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Ryder and the Paw Patrol search Adventure bay (2013)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-08 04:55:00" d="2020-06-08 05:15:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Pit Crew / Pups Fight Fire
Ryder and the PAW Patrol have to rescue Alex when he takes off on his new “super trike”.

Marshall proves</k>  </p>
</a>
