<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="71" t="2020-05-25 04:55:44"><p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 06:00:00" d="2020-06-01 06:25:00"><n u="Becca's Bunch">Becca's Bunch I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Wagtastic Four / Rock-A-Bye-Bunnies
Pops inspires Becca and the Bunch to play at being superheroes, and they create their own Super Bunch.

Lola's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 06:25:00" d="2020-06-01 06:50:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines II (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Race to Eagle Rock
Blaze brings all of his monster truck pals to VelocityVille for a wild race to the top of Eagle Rock! But Crusher will stop at nothing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 06:50:00" d="2020-06-01 07:20:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Frankie's Botasaur / Rusty's Mega Stacker
New neighbor Frankie Fritz bot-naps Botasaur, making Rusty and Ruby go on a chase to get their friend back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 07:20:00" d="2020-06-01 07:45:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save the Mayor's Race / Pups Save an Outlaw's Loot
It’s the annual Mayor’s Race, and Mayor Humdinger is planning his most devious cheating scheme yet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 07:45:00" d="2020-06-01 08:15:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol II (21)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% Pups Save Walinda / Pups Save a Big Bone
The PAW Patrol plan a special celebration for Wally the Walrus. When he doesn't show up, they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 08:15:00" d="2020-06-01 08:40:00"><n u="Blue's Clues &amp; You">Blue's Clues &amp; You I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% ABC's with Blue
We are reading Blue's Clues to figure out what book Blue wants to read for story time. While looking for clues we practice letter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 08:40:00" d="2020-06-01 09:00:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% A Turtely Awesome Adventure / Brody Goes Home
Brody has to rescue his turbo-surfing pals when they get caught in the Shipwreck Cove whirlpool.

Brody</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 09:00:00" d="2020-06-01 09:30:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Cricket's Treasure Hunt! / The Puddlebrook Gold Rush!
Cricket goes on a treasure hunt for a mysterious, ruby red fruit. Will she find the treasure?

A</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 09:30:00" d="2020-06-01 09:45:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fluttercakes!
Ms. Marmalady won't let the garbage man empty Butterbean's dumpster unless she beats her in a pancake-making contest (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 09:45:00" d="2020-06-01 10:10:00"><n u="Abby Hatcher">Abby Hatcher I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mo and Bo, in the Snow / Otis Out of Order
Mo and Bo are mistaken for a snow monster.

After taking a tumble, Otis suffers a fear of heights and becomes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 10:10:00" d="2020-06-01 10:35:00"><n u="Shimmer and Shine">Shimmer and Shine IV (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Zeashell Surprise / The Zahramay Zuffer-Puff
The girls help the Zeashell Genie make surprisefilled zeashells, but sneaky Uzma swaps the surprises inside with her own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 10:35:00" d="2020-06-01 10:40:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (92)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% But George feels a bit left out (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 10:40:00" d="2020-06-01 10:45:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (93)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pen Pal
Peppa has a French pen pal, a girl donkey, named Delphine. They also speak to each other on the telephone. Although Peppa speaks English</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 10:45:00" d="2020-06-01 10:55:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (94)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Granny and Granpa's Attic
Peppa and George are helping Granny and Grandpa Pig tidy their attic, but it's hard to decide what to throw out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 10:55:00" d="2020-06-01 11:00:00"><n u="Ready Set Dance">Ready Set Dance I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Do The Freeze
A super cool story about a snaggle toothed Snow Leopard and a city that's in awe of his ice cold moves (2019)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 11:00:00" d="2020-06-01 11:25:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol VI (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save Gustavo's Guitar / Pups Save the Yoga Goats
Gustavo Goodway's guitar is missing. The pups need to find it before tonight's campfire concert!

Farmer Yumi's new Yoga Goat class is a hit, until her goats go missing! It's up to the Paw Patrol to find the goats and return them to Yumi's farm (2019)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 11:25:00" d="2020-06-01 11:55:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% But how can Chase help? (2013)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 11:55:00" d="2020-06-01 12:20:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines IV (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% The Super-Size Prize
At the Axle City Fair, Blaze and AJ realize they don't have enough coins to use the new Supersize Prize Machine. So to earn money</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 12:20:00" d="2020-06-01 12:45:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines IV (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Breaking the Ice
When a little bunny gets trapped on top of a melting glacier, Blaze must put his new robot powers to the test as he races to the rescue (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 12:45:00" d="2020-06-01 13:10:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies III (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% The Amusement Parking Lot!
Beep beep! The Guppies love cars! But when Mr. Grouper’s car breaks down on the way to an amusement park, will the kids figure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 13:10:00" d="2020-06-01 13:20:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Great Goat-Cart Race
It's time for the big &quot;goat cart&quot; race! But when a Treegoat races &quot;off-road&quot; into the river, Team Top Wing have to rescue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 13:20:00" d="2020-06-01 13:40:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Banana Bandits
Monkey bandits hijack Rhonda's bananas! The Cadets rescue the bananas and Turtle Train when the monkeys strike again (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 13:40:00" d="2020-06-01 14:10:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol IV (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save the Mail / Pups Save a Frog Mayor
The postman's truck gets stuck in the mud and the mail gets stuck in a tree.

Mayor Goodway turns into a frog (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 14:10:00" d="2020-06-01 14:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol V (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save the Kitty Rescue Crew / Pups Save an Ostrich
Mayor Humdinger makes fake emergencies for his kitties to save so they appear better</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 14:40:00" d="2020-06-01 15:05:00"><n u="Max &amp; Ruby">Max &amp; Ruby VI (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Max and Winston / Grandma’s Bunny Sniffles
While Ruby and Valerie try to earn their bicycle safety Bunny Scout badge, Max and Winston hunt for parts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 15:05:00" d="2020-06-01 15:10:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (56)</n><t>O</t>    <k>66% Bubbles
Peppa and George are playing with bubbles. When the bubble mixture runs out, Daddy Pig shows them how to make really big bubbles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 15:10:00" d="2020-06-01 15:20:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (57)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Bedtime
It’s nearly time for bed and Peppa and George are called in for their bath. After that, they brush their teeth and get into bed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 15:20:00" d="2020-06-01 15:30:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (58)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% There’s enough for everyone in the traffic jam (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 15:30:00" d="2020-06-01 15:55:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets II (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Secret Agent Rusty / Moon Walkin' Rusty
When Frankie breaks into the Rivet Lab and takes control, Rusty and Ruby have to be &quot;secret agent&quot; sneaky to stop him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 15:55:00" d="2020-06-01 16:20:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets II (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rusty's Arctic Adventure / Super Liam
When Orbit crashes in the Arctic, it's up to Rusty and Ruby to get him back into space.

When Liam doesn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 16:20:00" d="2020-06-01 16:45:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing I (25)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% Junior Cadets Rescue / Sunken Treasure Race
Top Wing are training some friends to be &quot;junior Cadets&quot; When Baddy tries to show he can be a rescue hero</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 16:45:00" d="2020-06-01 17:15:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Flying Banana Bandits! / Penny's Chillin' Playdate
The Banana Bandits take Shirley's delivery fliers! The flying monkeys are headed for Commodore's balloon! Top Wing to the rescue!

Penny is heading to a play date with Anyu, but when Anyu's brother gets in trouble, it's all Cadets to the rescue (2017)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 17:15:00" d="2020-06-01 17:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol IV (2)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% Pups Save A Teeny Penguin / Pups Save the Cat Show
Everest and Jake try to rescue a little penguin and end up floating out to sea on a homemade bridge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 17:40:00" d="2020-06-01 18:10:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines III (11)</n><t>O</t>    <k>59% Toucan Do It!
Blaze, Starla, and Darington can’t wait to play every animal’s favorite sport: Jungle Ball! But when their teammate Tooks the Toucan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 18:10:00" d="2020-06-01 18:35:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines III (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% The Big Ant-venture
Blaze and Zeg are on Animal Island when they discover a world of tiny creatures right under their tires: Insect City! The friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 18:35:00" d="2020-06-01 18:40:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Fancy Dress Party
Peppa and George are having a costume party. Peppa is a fairy princess, and George is a dinosaur. Peppa has to pick which of her friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 18:40:00" d="2020-06-01 18:45:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Museum
Peppa and her family go to the museum. Peppa imagines herself as a Queen in the King and Queen's room. George imagines being a big dinosaur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 18:45:00" d="2020-06-01 18:55:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Very Hot Day
It is a super hot day, and all the mud puddles have dried up, so Peppa and George play in the wading pool (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 18:55:00" d="2020-06-01 19:00:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (41)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% Chloe's Puppet Show
Peppa and George visit their cousin Chloe's house, where they put on a puppet show about a pig who snores a lot. Daddy Pig and Uncle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 19:00:00" d="2020-06-01 19:05:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The room doesn't stay tidy for long though (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 19:05:00" d="2020-06-01 19:15:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Playground
Peppa and George go to the playground. Peppa's friends are also there. Peppa likes going on the swings but George does not because</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 19:15:00" d="2020-06-01 19:40:00"><n u="Blue's Clues &amp; You">Blue's Clues &amp; You I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Happy Birthday Blue
It's Blue's birthday! We're playing Blue's Clues to figure out what present Blue wants for her birthday. While we look for Clues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 19:40:00" d="2020-06-01 20:11:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a Robosaurus / Pups Save a Film Festival
When a homemade Robotic Dino named Earl comes to life, the pups need to find him, stop him, and bring him home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 20:11:00" d="2020-06-01 20:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Chase and Rocky to the rescue (2016)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 20:40:00" d="2020-06-01 21:02:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Lemon Pirates / Treasure Map Mission
When the island's precious lemons are taken by pirates, the Cadets swashbuckle the treasure back to the Lemon Shack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 21:02:00" d="2020-06-01 21:06:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (62)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% George's Friend
George and Rebecca Rabbit's little brother Richard each have a toy dinosaur but they are not very good at sharing their toys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 21:06:00" d="2020-06-01 21:10:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (63)</n><t>Z</t>    <k>66% The Boat Pond
Peppa and her family and friends are playing at the pond with their toy boats. Everyone has a boat to play with except Rebecca Rabbit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 21:10:00" d="2020-06-01 21:15:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (64)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Mr Scarecrow
The birds keep eating the seeds from Grandpa Pig's flower garden. Peppa and George make a scarecrow, which stops the birds from eating</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 21:15:00" d="2020-06-01 21:25:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (65)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Time Capsule
Peppa and her school friends are making a time capsule. They each put one of their favourite things inside and bury it in the school garden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 21:25:00" d="2020-06-01 21:50:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Starlight Cupcake Surprise! / Summer Slushies!
The crew accidentally delivers unfrosted cupcakes to a customer. Will Cricket's new piping skills save the party?

Butterbean has to borrow Ms. Marmalady's freezer for her fruitsicles, but Ms. Marmalady has her own plans for them (2017)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 21:50:00" d="2020-06-01 22:20:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (10)</n><t>L</t>    <k>Can Butterbean tell her without hurting her feelings? (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 22:20:00" d="2020-06-01 22:25:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (71)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Foggy Day
Mummy and Daddy Pig are taking Peppa and George to play in the playground. On the way it gets a bit foggy, and soon it is so foggy they can’t see</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 22:25:00" d="2020-06-01 22:30:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (72)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% George's Birthday
Today is George’s birthday and Mummy and Daddy Pig have a special day planned. George gets a new Brontosaurus toy and the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 22:30:00" d="2020-06-01 22:35:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (73)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% Then Grandpa also shows them his beehive (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 22:35:00" d="2020-06-01 22:45:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (74)</n><t>O</t>    <k>66% The Sports Day
It is Sports Day at Peppa’s playgroup. There are lots of exciting events, including running, jumping and the “tug of war”. Daddy Pig tells</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 22:45:00" d="2020-06-01 23:10:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies III (7)</n><t>O</t>    <k>68% The Super Ballet Bowl!
Jump! Leap! Relevé! Bubbletucky sports fans love ballet! Molly and the rest of the Guppies want to learn how to tell a story through dance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 23:10:00" d="2020-06-01 23:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save Floating Friends / Pups Save a Satellite
The alien’s spaceship is on the fritz and shooting out anti-gravity rays</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-01 23:40:00" d="2020-06-02 00:05:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol IV (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Porter's stove explodes right before the Chilli cook-off (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 00:05:00" d="2020-06-02 00:30:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rusty's Alien Invasion / Rusty's Running Car
The comic book action figures Rusty created for Liam come alive and behave just like their conquering characters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 00:30:00" d="2020-06-02 00:55:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rusty Feels Peachy / Rusty's Monkey Mayhem
While helping Chef Betty and Sammy compete for the Peachy Keen tasting contest, Rusty and Ruby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 00:55:00" d="2020-06-02 01:25:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol VI (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Along with its precious cargo - Chickaletta (2019)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 01:25:00" d="2020-06-02 01:55:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol VI (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups and the Stinky Bubble Trouble / Pups Save the Baby Ostriches
What's that smell? A strange odor is chasing the jungle animals away from their homes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 01:55:00" d="2020-06-02 02:15:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines IV (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Robot Power
When Crusher unleashes three of his most destructive creations on Axle City, there's only one hero strong enough to save the day: Robot Blaze (2017)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 02:15:00" d="2020-06-02 02:40:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Dino Dash
Blaze and AJ are playing with their friend Zeg when he accidentally gets blasted by a geyser into a far away mud pit. It’s up to Blaze</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 02:40:00" d="2020-06-02 03:00:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Piggy 500
Starla is excited to race with her prize pig Zippy in the Piggy 500! But when her competitor Crusher and his rude pig Slop cheat and send Zippy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 03:00:00" d="2020-06-02 03:25:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Have a Cow
With an 'oink, oink' here and a 'moo, moo' there, the Bubble Guppies learn all about farm animals, and discover that a lot of their favorite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 03:25:00" d="2020-06-02 03:45:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies III (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Good Morning, Mr. Grumpfish!
The Bubble Guppies have a substitute teacher: Mr. Grumpfish. He doesn’t seem to like anything! It’ll take</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 03:45:00" d="2020-06-02 04:10:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines IV (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% The Flying Lion
Blaze and AJ are excited to play with their new friend Roarian, the Flying Lion! But when Roarian loses his magical sunstone, he turns into a statue! Now it's up to Blaze and AJ to find the sunstone and restore Roarian's powers (2017)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 04:10:00" d="2020-06-02 04:30:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines IV (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Ninja Soup
Blackbelt isn't the only Ninja Master in his family- his Grandma Ninja has awesome moves too! But when she gets a nasty cold, Blaze</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 04:30:00" d="2020-06-02 04:55:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol V (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a Frozen Camp-out / Pups Save the Fizzy Pickles
Alex and Mr. Porter are on a tropical Island camping trip when a freak snowstorm hits!

Mr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 04:55:00" d="2020-06-02 05:15:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol V (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a Pluck-O-Matic / Pups Save a Mascot
Yumi's new Robo- Corn Plucker goes haywire, and Ryder and the Paw Patrol must get it under control</k>  </p>
</a>
