<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="73" t="2020-05-26 04:41:04"><p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 05:15:00" d="2020-06-02 05:40:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rusty's Dancing Suit / Rusty Bee Good
Mr. Higgins wants to go to the town dance, but thinks he's a terrible dancer. So Rusty and Ruby build</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 05:40:00" d="2020-06-02 06:00:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rusty's Piggy Bank Heist / Rusty's Whale of a Problem
Rusty forgets the code to his robotic piggy bank, activating its self-defense mode and turning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 06:00:00" d="2020-06-02 06:25:00"><n u="Becca's Bunch">Becca's Bunch I (7)</n><t>L</t>    <k>Wow Me Wagtail / Wishing Stone
Becca plans to wow at the talent show with her spectacular ballet troupe but soon realises Ringo needs to dance to his own tune</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 06:25:00" d="2020-06-02 06:50:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% The Wishing Wheel
Blaze, AJ, and Stripes are searching for the Wishing Wheel: a magical treasure that will grant a wish for one lucky race car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 06:50:00" d="2020-06-02 07:20:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Fix It 500 / Ice Ice Rusty
Frankie Fritz challenges Rusty and Ruby to a race around Sparkton Hills, with the Mobile Rivet Lab as the stakes.

Rusty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 07:20:00" d="2020-06-02 07:45:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol II (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Time to call the PAW Patrol (2015)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 07:45:00" d="2020-06-02 08:15:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol II (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a Snowboard Competition / Pups Save a Chicken of the Sea
Jake and Everest are excited for the Snowboard Competition, until they see the course</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 08:15:00" d="2020-06-02 08:40:00"><n u="Blue's Clues &amp; You">Blue's Clues &amp; You I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% 123's with Blue
Count along with Josh &amp; Blue in this game of Blue's Clues to find out what Blue wants to buy at the store. We help Shovel &amp; Pail learn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 08:40:00" d="2020-06-02 09:00:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Birthday Bandits! / The Mystery of the Haunted Cave
The Monkey Bandits take Rod's birthday cake and Road-Wing. Can Swift rescue the party without ruining the surprise?

As Bea helps Brody and Rod earn their Overnight Badge, Baddy McBat tries to scare them, but the Cadets rescue him (2017)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 09:00:00" d="2020-06-02 09:30:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Missing Veggies! / Cricket the Flower Girl!
All the veggies are disappearing from Poppy's garden, and the Bean Team thinks Ms. Marmalady is behind it! Is she to blame?

Cricket stains her flower girl dress! Will she be able to fix it before the wedding? (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 09:30:00" d="2020-06-02 09:45:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Will Cricket's scout skills save the picnic? (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 09:45:00" d="2020-06-02 10:10:00"><n u="Abby Hatcher">Abby Hatcher I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Teeny Terry's Gift / Peeper Time Blues
Teeny Terry wants to surprise Lex by finishing everything on his to do list.

The Peepers are over-the-top</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 10:10:00" d="2020-06-02 10:35:00"><n u="Shimmer and Shine">Shimmer and Shine IV (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Zeacorn Cove / Lights of Oceanea
When Uzma takes the magic jewel that powers Zeacorn Cove, the girls and their new Zeacorns friends set out to retrieve it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 10:35:00" d="2020-06-02 10:40:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (95)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% School Camp
Peppa and her friends are going camping with Madame Gazelle. When it gets dark, they all sing a song around the campfire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 10:40:00" d="2020-06-02 10:45:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (96)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Toy Cupboard
Peppa and George's toy basket is full and their beds are covered in toys. Mummy Pig orders a new toy cupboard, but it needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 10:45:00" d="2020-06-02 10:55:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (97)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Captain Daddy Pig
Peppa and her family borrow Grandpa Pig’s boat for a day on the river. Daddy Pig is the captain, Peppa, George and Mummy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 10:55:00" d="2020-06-02 11:00:00"><n u="Ready Set Dance">Ready Set Dance I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Heel Tow Hoedown
A tooting, hooting, back slapping story about a town that's lost a vital move to its hoedown and a Kid Crew member</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 11:00:00" d="2020-06-02 11:25:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save the Sea Turtles / Pups and the Very Big Baby
Ryder, Chase, and Rubble hatch a plan to help sea turtle hatchlings safely cross the</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 11:25:00" d="2020-06-02 11:55:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups and the Kitty-tastrophe / Pups Save a Train
Ryder and the PAW Patrol rescue a lost kitty from the bay, but who will save them from all the mayhem she causes?

Ryder, Rubble, and Rocky call in Chase to help them free Katie and Cali’s train from a rockslide (2013)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 11:55:00" d="2020-06-02 12:20:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines IV (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Robots to the Rescue
When three big emergencies turn out to be too much for one truck alone, Blaze turns himself and his friends into super strong robots</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 12:20:00" d="2020-06-02 12:45:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines IV (8)</n><t>L</t>    <k>59% T. Rex Trouble
Blaze and Zeg are in Dinosaur Valley, showing off their amazing robot powers to their dinosaur friends. But when they discover three</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 12:45:00" d="2020-06-02 13:10:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies III (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Party at Sea!
Anchor’s away! It’s time to celebrate boats with a party at sea! But when a giant ball of snow cone ice threatens to sink the party ship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 13:10:00" d="2020-06-02 13:20:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Top Wing's Eggcellent Rescue
Sandy Stork loses her glasses and mixes up the eggs in her delivery. Top Wing race to get the right eggs back home before they hatch (2017)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 13:20:00" d="2020-06-02 13:40:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Great Pearl-A-Palooza Caper
When Chomps and Rocco take Big Swirl's famous pearls, Top Wing must get them back in time for Pearl-A-Palooza (2017)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 13:40:00" d="2020-06-02 14:10:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol V (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save Big Paw / Pups Save a Hum-Mover
When an ancient relic goes missing from Carlos' archeological dig, Tracker and Skye must track down the creature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 14:10:00" d="2020-06-02 14:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol V (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a High Flying Skye / Pups Go for the Gold
When Corny runs away from Farmer Al's Farm during a blackout, the pups need to light</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 14:40:00" d="2020-06-02 15:05:00"><n u="Max &amp; Ruby">Max &amp; Ruby VI (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>You Can't Catch Me / Max's Bubbles
While playing, Max accidentally creates an obstacle course that’s the perfect activity for Ruby and her Bunny Scout group</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 15:05:00" d="2020-06-02 15:10:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (59)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Rock Pools
Granny and Grandpa Pig take Peppa and George to a beach with lots of rocks and little rock pools to explore. They all have fun with a little</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 15:10:00" d="2020-06-02 15:20:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (60)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Teddy's Day Out
Peppa and her family are having a picnic. Mr Zebra the Postman and Zoë Zebra are having a picnic too, so they decide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 15:20:00" d="2020-06-02 15:30:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (61)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Emily Elephant
There's a new pupil at the playgroup, Emily Elephant. Everybody wants to be her friend because she is very good at building blocks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 15:30:00" d="2020-06-02 15:55:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets III (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rusty's Dino Island
Rusty and Ruby discover a secret island where dinosaurs still exist, but they must find a way to stop a volcano from erupting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 15:55:00" d="2020-06-02 16:20:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets III (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rusty's Tiny Adventure / Rusty's Warm Winter Games
Rusty and Ruby use a shrink ray to help Tigerbot recover Mrs. Rivets' special ring after it falls down the drain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 16:20:00" d="2020-06-02 16:45:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Cheep, Chirp, and the Pirate's Treasure / Rod's amily Popcorn Party
Cap'n Dilly makes the chicks mini-pirates to find a treasure chest key</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 16:45:00" d="2020-06-02 17:15:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Top Wing Rescues the Academy
The Cadets must pass Inspector Eagle-Eye's test or Speedy and Bea will be sent back to teacher's school! Team Top Wing ace the test and rescue the Inspector using the Headquarters Command Flyer: a part of the HQ that can fly (2019)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 17:15:00" d="2020-06-02 17:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol IV (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a Playful Dragon / Pups Save the Critters
Buddy, the playful dragon from one of Alex's books, gets out and the pups</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 17:40:00" d="2020-06-02 18:10:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines III (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Falcon Quest
In the sky above Animal Island, a remarkable race is about to begin. But before Blaze can join, he must spread his wings! Challenged by a tough-talking falcon, Blaze takes off on a journey to earn his place with the fast fliers (2016)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 18:10:00" d="2020-06-02 18:35:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines III (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Can they claw their way to victory? (2016)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 18:35:00" d="2020-06-02 18:40:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Daddy Puts Up a Picture
Daddy Pig offers to put up a picture of Peppa and George on the wall while Mummy Pig is out. He accidentally cracks the wall while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 18:40:00" d="2020-06-02 18:45:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% At the Beach
Peppa and her family go to the beach, and they do lots of things there including burying Daddy Pig in the sand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 18:45:00" d="2020-06-02 18:55:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Mister Skinnylegs
George finds a spider in the bathroom sink, but Peppa is really frightened-until she realizes that it doesn't want to hurt her (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 18:55:00" d="2020-06-02 19:00:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Grandpa Pig's Boat
Peppa and George go for a ride in Grandpa Pig's boat. Danny Dog and Granddad Dog are also out sailing. Grandpa Pig and Granddad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 19:00:00" d="2020-06-02 19:05:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% My Birthday Party
It is Peppa's birthday, and Peppa has a party (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 19:05:00" d="2020-06-02 19:15:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (51)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% Daddy's Movie Camera
Daddy gets a new video camera. First, Peppa shows him how to work it, and then he records Peppa being silly (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 19:15:00" d="2020-06-02 19:40:00"><n u="Blue's Clues &amp; You">Blue's Clues &amp; You I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Playdate with Magenta
Blue's friend Magenta is coming over today! We play Blue's Clues to figure out what Blue wants to do with Magenta. During our search</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 19:40:00" d="2020-06-02 20:11:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (17)</n><t>O</t>    <k>66% All Star Pups! / Pups Save Sports Day
It’s monkey mayhem as pups play kickball against Raimondo’s team, until an eagle steals the ball.

The</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 20:11:00" d="2020-06-02 20:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups in a Jam / Pups Save a Windsurfing Pig
It’s the annual Jamboree Jamfest, but all of the fruit is carried off by ants! It's up to the</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 20:40:00" d="2020-06-02 21:02:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Goose on the Loose / Red Cockadoodle Didn't
Swift and Brody have to rely on each other, and their &quot;buddy navigating&quot; skills, to lead the geese to safety in the fog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 21:02:00" d="2020-06-02 21:06:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (66)</n><t>Z</t>    <k>66% Recycling
Peppa and George help Mummy Pig tidy up the breakfast things. Mummy Pig tells them that bottles go into a special green box to be recycled Peppa and George have fun filling the boxes (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 21:06:00" d="2020-06-02 21:10:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (67)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Daddy Pig's Office
Peppa and George are visiting Daddy Pig’s office today. Daddy Pig works with Mr Rabbit and Mrs Cat. Mr. Rabbit’s job is all about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 21:10:00" d="2020-06-02 21:15:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (68)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% Pirate Island
Grandpa and Granny Pig are taking Peppa, George and their friends to Pirate Island. Grandpa shows how to use his metal detector</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 21:15:00" d="2020-06-02 21:25:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (69)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Jumble Sale
Peppa’s playgroup is holding a jumble sale to raise money for a new roof and Madame Gazelle asks everyone to bring something to sell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 21:25:00" d="2020-06-02 21:50:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Switchin' in the Kitchen! / The Breadstick Bicycle!
Dazzle and Poppy each think that the other's job is easier, so they switch jobs to see!

Cricket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 21:50:00" d="2020-06-02 22:20:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Butterbean Babysits! / Fairy Cozy Cocoa!
Butterbean offers to babysit a toddler for the day, but it turns out to be harder than she thought!

Butterbean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 22:20:00" d="2020-06-02 22:25:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (75)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% GrandDad Dog's Garage
Peppa’s car runs out of petrol but thankfully Granddad Dog’s garage isn’t far away. With one phone call, Granddad Dog is on his way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 22:25:00" d="2020-06-02 22:30:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (76)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Balloon Ride
Peppa wins the top prize in a raffle at school: a trip in a hot air balloon. Mummy Pig, Daddy Pig, George and Peppa climb aboard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 22:30:00" d="2020-06-02 22:35:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (77)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% George Catches a Cold
Peppa and George love jumping in puddles, even when it’s raining – but when George takes off his rain hat, he catches a cold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 22:35:00" d="2020-06-02 22:45:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (78)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Eye Test
Pedro Pony wears glasses. Peppa thinks she might need glasses too, so Mummy Pig takes her to the optician. Peppa is a little disappointed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 22:45:00" d="2020-06-02 23:10:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies III (8)</n><t>L</t>    <k>68% The Wizard of Oz-tralia
After Molly and Gil meet Bobby, a nature show host from Australia, they can't wait to learn all about Australian animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 23:10:00" d="2020-06-02 23:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol IV (2)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% Pups Save A Teeny Penguin / Pups Save the Cat Show
Everest and Jake try to rescue a little penguin and end up floating out to sea on a homemade bridge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-02 23:40:00" d="2020-06-03 00:05:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol IV (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a Playful Dragon / Pups Save the Critters
Buddy, the playful dragon from one of Alex's books, gets out and the pups</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 00:05:00" d="2020-06-03 00:30:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rusty's Pet Project / Rusty Gets Stuck
When Botasaur gets tired from playing, Rusty builds him a bigger battery - but with it comes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 00:30:00" d="2020-06-03 00:55:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rusty's Mysterious Mystery / Rusty's Yard-Cade Game
Officer Carl loses his lucky sculpture, Rusty and Ruby must find it and convince Officer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 00:55:00" d="2020-06-03 01:25:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol VI (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save Gustavo's Guitar / Pups Save the Yoga Goats
Gustavo Goodway's guitar is missing. The pups need to find it before tonight's campfire concert!

Farmer Yumi's new Yoga Goat class is a hit, until her goats go missing! It's up to the Paw Patrol to find the goats and return them to Yumi's farm (2019)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 01:25:00" d="2020-06-03 01:55:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% But how can Chase help? (2013)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 01:55:00" d="2020-06-03 02:15:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines IV (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Pickle Family Campout
When all the members of Pickle's family get lost in the woods, Pickle teams up with Tow Truck Blaze to come to their rescue (2017)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 02:15:00" d="2020-06-03 02:40:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Fired Up!
When Blaze smells smoke at Axle City’s garage, he calmly and courageously leads his friends outside to safety. Axle City’s fire chief</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 02:40:00" d="2020-06-03 03:00:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Knight Riders
Blaze and Crusher discover a medieval kingdom holding a Royal Race! They become knights to compete in the race across the realm. Even though</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 03:00:00" d="2020-06-03 03:25:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies III (4)</n><t>L</t>    <k>68% Get Ready for School!
Oona's worried about her little friend Avi! It's his first day of school and he's nervous. From cubbies to free play, the Guppies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 03:25:00" d="2020-06-03 03:45:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies III (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% The Police Cop-etition!
Stop, in the name of fun! Officer Miranda teaches Gil and the other kids how police officers use laws to keep us safe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 03:45:00" d="2020-06-03 04:10:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines IV (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Royal Rescue
A visit to the King's castle goes awry when the King accidentally catapults himself far, far away! To bring him home, Blaze</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 04:10:00" d="2020-06-03 04:30:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines IV (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Blaze and the Magic Genie
Blaze and AJ are driving through the desert when they meet a magical Genie who loves to grant wishes! But when the Genie loses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 04:30:00" d="2020-06-03 04:55:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol V (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save Ace's Birthday Surprise / Pups Save a Tower of Pizza
Rocky and the Pups are fixing an Old-Timey Junk Car for Ace Sorensen's Birthday!

Adventure Bay is working hard to earn the record for having the world's highest tower of pizzas (2018)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-06-03 04:55:00" d="2020-06-03 05:15:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol VI (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Along with its precious cargo - Chickaletta (2019)</k>  </p>
</a>
