<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="72" t="2020-05-17 04:36:10"><p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 05:20:00" d="2020-05-24 05:40:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rusty’s Mechanical Animal / Rusty's Spaceship
Rusty and Ruby make Ranger Anna a robotic pet, but it goes haywire when they try to program it.

Rusty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 05:40:00" d="2020-05-24 06:00:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rusty Feels Peachy / Rusty's Monkey Mayhem
While helping Chef Betty and Sammy compete for the Peachy Keen tasting contest, Rusty and Ruby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 06:00:00" d="2020-05-24 06:25:00"><n u="Becca's Bunch">Becca's Bunch I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Up In The Air / Super Sour Power
When Russell wants to fly like his squirrel cousin Sammy, the Bunch help make him wings.

Becca and the Bunch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 06:25:00" d="2020-05-24 06:50:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Dragon Island Duel
It’s the day of the Dragon Island Duel, a one-on-one race between Blaze and Crusher around tropical Dragon Island! When Crusher cheats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 06:50:00" d="2020-05-24 07:20:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rusty's Spooky Adventure / Rusty Loses the Bits
Rusty and Liam love it when Mr. Higgins makes Sparkton Hills seem haunted with his &quot;Spooky Adventure&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 07:20:00" d="2020-05-24 07:45:00"><n u="Paw Patrol">Paw Patrol I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Great Race / Pups Take the Cake
It’s Race Day and the pups are about to race across the town to see who is the fastest.

Mr. Porter enters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 07:45:00" d="2020-05-24 08:15:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save the Penguins / Pups Save a Dolphin Pup
Someone has been swiping fish off Cap’n Turbot’s boat, so he calls Ryder and the PAW Patrol</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 08:15:00" d="2020-05-24 09:00:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% The Puppy and the Ring
In the mythical land of Bubbledom, the evil Night Wizard has taken the magical Ring of the Sun! Someone needs to save the daytime! Will Molly and Gil return the Ring to the Sun King, or will it be nighttime in Bubbledom forever? (2013)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 09:00:00" d="2020-05-24 09:05:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Treasure Hunt
Grandpa Pig hides some treasure in his garden, and when Peppa and George come, they have to look for it (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 09:05:00" d="2020-05-24 09:10:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Cleaning the Car
Peppa and her family have to wash the car when it gets dirty (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 09:10:00" d="2020-05-24 09:20:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Lunch
Peppa and George visit Granny Pig and Grandpa Pig's house for lunch. Granny Pig has made a salad but George doesn't like vegetables, so Grandpa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 09:20:00" d="2020-05-24 09:45:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Where's Cookie? / Jasper Learns to Bake!
Cricket accidentally overwhelms Cookie, the café's new kitty, and Cookie runs off. Will the fairy friends find her?

Poppy teaches Jasper how to make cinnamon buns, but when Jasper adds too much yeast, he has a BIG problem (2017)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 09:45:00" d="2020-05-24 10:10:00"><n u="Abby Hatcher">Abby Hatcher I (2)</n><t>L</t>    <k>Princess Flug's Flower Float / The Fuzzlies Talent Show
When roses of all kinds go missing at the hotel, Abby discovers Princess Flug, a regal monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 10:10:00" d="2020-05-24 10:35:00"><n u="Shimmer and Shine">Shimmer and Shine IV (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Zeta Sleeps Over / Genie Babies
A stinky bug infestation in Zeta's secret lair forces her to spend the night at Shimmer and Shine's Palace.

Zeta</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 10:35:00" d="2020-05-24 10:40:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Tree House
Peppa and George visit Granny Pig and Grandpa Pig's house. Grandpa Pig has built a tree house for them (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 10:40:00" d="2020-05-24 10:45:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (41)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% Chloe's Puppet Show
Peppa and George visit their cousin Chloe's house, where they put on a puppet show about a pig who snores a lot. Daddy Pig and Uncle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 10:45:00" d="2020-05-24 10:55:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Mister Skinnylegs
George finds a spider in the bathroom sink, but Peppa is really frightened-until she realizes that it doesn't want to hurt her (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 10:55:00" d="2020-05-24 11:00:00"><n u="Ready Set Dance">Ready Set Dance IX (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>I Love The Rain
A joyful little story about a rainy day in Ready Set City and the Kid Crew's mission to have fun, whatever the weather (2019)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 11:00:00" d="2020-05-24 11:25:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol V (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a High Flying Skye / Pups Go for the Gold
When Corny runs away from Farmer Al's Farm during a blackout, the pups need to light</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 11:25:00" d="2020-05-24 11:55:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol V (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save an Extreme Lunch / Pups Save a Cat Burglar
Daring Danny X is performing a new stunt! He is harnessed over a canyon eating an Extreme Lunch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 11:55:00" d="2020-05-24 12:20:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Catch That Cake!
It’s Darington’s birthday! Crusher uses a robot plate to try and steal the birthday cake, but his plan goes awry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 12:20:00" d="2020-05-24 12:45:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines III (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Animal Island
Blaze and Stripes sail to Animal Island - an incredible place inhabited by monster truck animals! But when a greedy lizard puts the island</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 12:45:00" d="2020-05-24 13:10:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies III (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Good Morning, Mr. Grumpfish!
The Bubble Guppies have a substitute teacher: Mr. Grumpfish. He doesn’t seem to like anything! It’ll take</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 13:10:00" d="2020-05-24 13:20:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Big Banana Break-In
Margo the Monkey and the Banana Bandits break into Headquarters and try to take off with the HQ Command Flyer (2019)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 13:20:00" d="2020-05-24 13:40:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Top Wing Spring Fling
Spring means Commodore Smurkturkski gets a new little chick, but Sandy Stork loses the egg!

Big Swirl's amazing Dancing Daffodils</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 13:40:00" d="2020-05-24 14:10:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a Giant Plant / Pups Get Stuck
Buddy - Mayor Goodway’s gesture of goodwill gift grows wildly out of control when it’s planted in the wrong place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 14:10:00" d="2020-05-24 14:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Raise the Paw Patroller / Pups Save the Crows
Daring Danny’s at it again, luckily the Pups are able to raise their rig after Danny sinks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 14:40:00" d="2020-05-24 15:10:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Hawaiian Luau! / Kitty-sitting!
Dazzle accidentally locks smoothies inside the Sweet Ride and can't find they key! Will she get them out before the luau?

Jasper thinks pet-sitting Cookie is going to be a piece of cake, until she gets lost (2017)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 15:10:00" d="2020-05-24 15:40:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Towering Tower of Crepes!
Jasper wants to help Butterbean cook for her idol, Chef Belle Legume! Butterbean thinks his speedy skills would be perfect for the spatula</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 15:40:00" d="2020-05-24 16:00:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Shirley's Sleep-Over Adventure / A Little Off Track
A falling tree threatens Shirley's home. The Cadets invite her to sleep over, and she helps guide their rescue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 16:00:00" d="2020-05-24 16:30:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Turtle Train Clean Up / Anya's Friendship Party
The Cadets go green and clean-up Big Swirl. When the train loaded with recycling rolls out of control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 16:30:00" d="2020-05-24 17:00:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save Old Trusty / Pups Save a Pony
Ryder and the pups need to unplug Old Trusty the geyser to stop water sprouting up all over town.

Priscilla</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 17:00:00" d="2020-05-24 17:25:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a Robosaurus / Pups Save a Film Festival
When a homemade Robotic Dino named Earl comes to life, the pups need to find him, stop him, and bring him home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 17:25:00" d="2020-05-24 17:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save the Songbirds
When the famous singing songbirds of Adventure Bay go missing, it's PAW Patrol to the rescue (2016)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 17:40:00" d="2020-05-24 18:10:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Dinosaur Parade
Blaze, AJ, and lots of spectators have gathered to watch herds of dinosaurs march through Axle City! But Crusher pushes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 18:10:00" d="2020-05-24 18:39:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines II (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Pickle Power
Crusher builds a super-powered vacuum to clean up his big mess – but the machine goes haywire, sucking up Crusher and everything in its path! Now Pickle must team up with Blaze and AJ to stop the vacuum and save Crusher (2015)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 18:39:00" d="2020-05-24 18:43:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Powercut
One day all the lights suddenly go out and Peppa’s house is plunged into darkness. There has been a power cut</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 18:43:00" d="2020-05-24 18:48:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Daddy Pig Birthday
Today is Daddy Pig's birthday, but he has to go to work. While he is away, Mummy Pig, Peppa and George prepare a special birthday surprise (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 18:48:00" d="2020-05-24 18:55:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Sleepover
Peppa is going for a sleepover at Zoë Zebra’s house with Suzy Sheep, Rebecca Rabbit, Candy Cat and Emily Elephant. The girls stay up playing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 18:55:00" d="2020-05-24 19:00:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Stars
It is night time and the sky is full of stars. Mummy and Daddy Pig let Peppa and George put their coats on and they go outside to look at the stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 19:00:00" d="2020-05-24 19:05:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Cold Winter's Day
It is a cold winter day. Peppa and George want to jump in muddy puddles, but the puddles are all frozen and slippery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 19:05:00" d="2020-05-24 19:15:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Muddy Puddles
It's raining and Peppa is sad because she can't go out to play. When the rain stops, Peppa feels better and she and George get ready</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 19:15:00" d="2020-05-24 19:40:00"><n u="Blue's Clues &amp; You">Blue's Clues &amp; You I (4)</n><t>Z</t>    <k>71% Big News with Blue
Blue has something exciting to tell everybody! In this game of Blue's Clues, Josh and the viewer go on a note finding quest, solving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 19:40:00" d="2020-05-24 20:10:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol II (21)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% Pups Save Walinda / Pups Save a Big Bone
The PAW Patrol plan a special celebration for Wally the Walrus. When he doesn't show up, they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 20:10:00" d="2020-05-24 20:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol II (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Time to call the PAW Patrol (2015)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 20:40:00" d="2020-05-24 21:01:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Top Wing Sting/Big Banana Break-In
Rod is super-excited to sing at Rhonda's, until Chomps and Rocco take the piano. The Cadets must get the piano back!

Margo the Monkey and the Banana Bandits break into Headquarters and try to take off with the HQ Command Flyer (2019)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 21:01:00" d="2020-05-24 21:06:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (28)</n><t>L</t>    <k>66% My Cousin Chloé
Peppa and George's cousin Chloe comes to their house. Peppa tries to show Chloe that she is a big girl, but it is very hard (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 21:06:00" d="2020-05-24 21:10:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pancakes
Mummy Pig makes pancakes, and Peppa and George help, but Daddy Pig flips his pancake so high it sticks to the ceiling (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 21:10:00" d="2020-05-24 21:15:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Babysitting
Granny Pig and Grandpa Pig look after Peppa and George while Mummy Pig and Daddy Pig go out for the evening. Peppa and George are too excited</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 21:15:00" d="2020-05-24 21:25:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Ballet Lesson
Peppa goes to her first ballet lesson, and meets her friends there. She decides to teach Mummy Pig and Daddy Pig to dance but finds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 21:25:00" d="2020-05-24 21:50:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Will she tell her how she feels? (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 21:50:00" d="2020-05-24 22:20:00"><n u="Butterbean's Cafe">Butterbean's Cafe I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A Kitty for Marmalady's! / Slumber Party!
When a kitty makes mischief in the café, everyone is convinced it's Cookie! But is it?

Cricket's friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 22:20:00" d="2020-05-24 22:25:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Tree House
Peppa and George visit Granny Pig and Grandpa Pig's house. Grandpa Pig has built a tree house for them (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 22:25:00" d="2020-05-24 22:30:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Fancy Dress Party
Peppa and George are having a costume party. Peppa is a fairy princess, and George is a dinosaur. Peppa has to pick which of her friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 22:30:00" d="2020-05-24 22:35:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The Museum
Peppa and her family go to the museum. Peppa imagines herself as a Queen in the King and Queen's room. George imagines being a big dinosaur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 22:35:00" d="2020-05-24 22:45:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Very Hot Day
It is a super hot day, and all the mud puddles have dried up, so Peppa and George play in the wading pool (2004)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 22:45:00" d="2020-05-24 23:10:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Bubble Puppy
Gil wants to adopt a puppy! But before he can bring the puppy home, the Bubble Guppies must learn how to take care of pets (2010)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 23:10:00" d="2020-05-24 23:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save Daring Danny X / Pups in a Fix
Daring Danny X takes his ambitions too far when he attempts a jump over Rattle Snake Canyon! The Paw Patrol</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-24 23:40:00" d="2020-05-25 00:05:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save a Dragon / Pups Save the Three Little Pigs
A fantasy fire breathing dragon comes to life and won’t let Ryder and pups into the Lookout! Paw Patrol takes to the Air Patroller!

The Paw Patrol help three little pigs build new houses after theirs mysteriously disappear (2016)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-25 00:05:00" d="2020-05-25 00:30:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rusty's Penguin Problem / Rusty's Sand Castle Hassle
Rusty and the gang must get some penguins to the Nature Park on the hottest day of the year.

Liam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-25 00:30:00" d="2020-05-25 00:55:00"><n u="Rusty Rivets">Rusty Rivets I (4)</n><t>L</t>    <k>Ruby Rocks / Rusty's Balloon Blast
With help from Rusty and the Bits, Ruby performs at the Sprocketville Talent Show.

When Liam accidentally launches</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-25 00:55:00" d="2020-05-25 01:25:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol IV (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save Francois the Penguin / Pups Save Daring Danny's Hippo
Francois and a baby penguin get caught on the other side of a carvasse.

Daring Danny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-25 01:25:00" d="2020-05-25 01:55:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol IV (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save Baby Humdinger / Pups Save a Pinata
Tracker has a dream that Mayor Humginder turns into a baby! Now it's up to the pups to find the special</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-25 01:55:00" d="2020-05-25 02:15:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines III (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Falcon Quest
In the sky above Animal Island, a remarkable race is about to begin. But before Blaze can join, he must spread his wings! Challenged by a tough-talking falcon, Blaze takes off on a journey to earn his place with the fast fliers (2016)!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-25 02:15:00" d="2020-05-25 02:40:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Bouncy Tires
When Zeg the dinosaur truck accidentally puts on a set of “Super Bouncy Tires,” he bounces out of control! Now Blaze and AJ have to experiment to find a substance adhesive enough to stop their bouncing buddy (2014)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-25 02:40:00" d="2020-05-25 03:00:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines I (6)</n><t>L</t>    <k>59% Stuntmania!
Darington has built the ultimate stunt-track, and every Monster Machine in town is coming to see the show! But when a jealous Crusher tricks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-25 03:00:00" d="2020-05-25 03:25:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies IV (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Guppy Movers!
When their friend Skip's moving day doesn’t go as planned, Molly, Gil, and the rest of the Guppy Movers roll in to set things right</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-25 03:25:00" d="2020-05-25 03:45:00"><n u="Bubble Guppies">Bubble Guppies IV (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Temple of the Lost Puppy!
Bubble Puppy disappears after he bites down on ancient magic bone, so the Guppies must embark on an epic booby-trapped adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-25 03:45:00" d="2020-05-25 04:10:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines III (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Defeat the Cheat
It's the second ever Team Truck Challenge - a big race that pairs trucks together in racing teams. And this time Blaze's teammate is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-25 04:10:00" d="2020-05-25 04:30:00"><n u="Blaze and the Monster Machines">Blaze and the Monster Machines III (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Raceday Rescue
It's race day, and Crusher is cheating twice as hard to beat Blaze and Watts - sending both drivers far, far away! But Blaze and Watts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-25 04:30:00" d="2020-05-25 04:55:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol IV (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Save the Runaway Kitties / Pups Save Tiny Marshall
The Kit-trastrophe crew get into the poufy shampoo and blow away.

Marshall dreams he gets shrunk (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1201" o="2020-05-25 04:55:00" d="2020-05-25 05:20:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol IV (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Pups Chill Out / Pups Save Farmer Alex
Roger's frozen food delivery truck gets stuck in a ditch.

Farmer Yumi's animals are stampeding towards town (2017)</k>  </p>
</a>
