<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="113" t="2020-04-15 04:37:59"><p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 05:00:00" d="2020-04-22 05:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% It's Mother's Day, and Gumball and Darwin discover that Tobias and Banana Joe have both made a card for &quot;The Best Mum in the World&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 05:15:00" d="2020-04-22 05:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Mum has forced Dad to install a password on the computer…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 05:25:00" d="2020-04-22 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin are offended when Mom calls them “procrastinators”, once she’s told them what it means</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 05:35:00" d="2020-04-22 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin help Rocky land an office job so that his dad, Mr Robinson, will be proud of him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 05:45:00" d="2020-04-22 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball confronts Clayton about his fabled Seven Pressure Point Heart Exploding Technique, assuming it’s another one of his outlandish claims</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 06:00:00" d="2020-04-22 06:11:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben, Gwen and Grandpa Max find themselves killing time at the local town library but soon scramble to out manoeuvre Hex as he searches for a hidden ancient artefact</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 06:11:00" d="2020-04-22 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Team Tennyson enjoy a convention in town but when a costume store employee finds a familiar-looking helmet and tries it on, Ben is faced with the return of Forever Knight!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 06:25:00" d="2020-04-22 06:35:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When Mao Mao gets hungry for the perfect adventure Adorabat tells a white lie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 06:35:00" d="2020-04-22 06:50:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Mao Mao's desire to be a legend drives him to keep topping himself. But how much is enough?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 06:50:00" d="2020-04-22 07:01:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>Jessica Cruz is convinced she can find the purr-fect forever home for Dexter, a cat who has been deemed unadoptable because he’s basically the worst cat in the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 07:01:00" d="2020-04-22 07:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>When mean-girl Leslie Willis becomes a social media sensation by posting mean videos, Wonder Woman questions the moral integrity of the World of Man</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 07:15:00" d="2020-04-22 07:25:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>JP leads his friends on a voyage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 07:25:00" d="2020-04-22 07:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>The kids meet a mysterious kid from the future</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 07:45:00" d="2020-04-22 07:55:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin finally teaches the other Titans a very valuable lesson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 07:55:00" d="2020-04-22 08:04:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% When her teammates turns evil it's up to Lady Legasus to stop the League of Legs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 08:04:00" d="2020-04-22 08:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans start speaking Pig Latin to prevent Robin from eavesdropping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 08:15:00" d="2020-04-22 08:24:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% It's Movie Night and the Titans have a hard time deciding who gets to choose which movie they watch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 08:24:00" d="2020-04-22 08:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% It's back to school as the Titans teach each other about science and grammar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 08:34:00" d="2020-04-22 08:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Beast Boy writes a song to tell Raven his feelings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 08:50:00" d="2020-04-22 09:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>When the Bears attend Chloe’s family reunion, they fall victim to the mischievous pranks of Chloe’s cousin, Jon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 09:00:00" d="2020-04-22 09:10:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>On a day out with just Chloe and Ice Bear, she realises that Ice Bear only runs errands for his brothers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 09:10:00" d="2020-04-22 09:25:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>Ice Bear has a Korean-style cooking show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 09:25:00" d="2020-04-22 09:35:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% The AO return home to learn that no time has passed but they soon discover their knowledge of brawling has gotten years more advanced</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 09:35:00" d="2020-04-22 09:50:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% After Strata is sent packing the AO discover that they have picked up a hitch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 09:50:00" d="2020-04-22 09:59:00"><n>Total Dramarama</n>    <k>Noah tries to rescue the chocolates Owen forgot outside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 09:59:00" d="2020-04-22 10:09:00"><n>Total Dramarama</n>    <k>Leshawna creates a paint balloon fight to decide who gets to come with her to an amusement park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 10:09:00" d="2020-04-22 10:18:00"><n>Total Dramarama</n>    <k>Courtney must go all day without correcting her friends which is hard because they do everything wrong!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 10:18:00" d="2020-04-22 10:26:00"><n>Total Dramarama</n>    <k>Owen and Noah unwittingly become cookie moguls and must hide the secret ingredient which is Owen's spit from licking the sprinkles off the cookies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 10:26:00" d="2020-04-22 10:35:00"><n>Total Dramarama</n>    <k>In order to earn her final Girl Campers badge Courtney must earn Gwen's friendship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 10:35:00" d="2020-04-22 10:45:00"><n>Total Dramarama</n>    <k>Owen wants everyone to love his new snowsuit and envy him but it's just not working out that way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 10:45:00" d="2020-04-22 10:54:00"><n>Total Dramarama</n>    <k>Duncan stages a small coup to oust Courtney as their official class firefighter so that he can wear the shiny firefighter helmet - until he smells smoke</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 10:54:00" d="2020-04-22 11:03:00"><n>Total Dramarama</n>    <k>Courtney becomes a toy tester but forgets that the most important thing is to have fun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 11:03:00" d="2020-04-22 11:40:00"><n>Total Dramarama</n>    <k>Gwen accidentally brings a pink stuffed pony she loves to daycare and spends the day denying it's hers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 11:40:00" d="2020-04-22 11:50:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>After getting rejected by a photography club, Val tries to get a picture of the legendary Chupacabra in order to prove himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 11:50:00" d="2020-04-22 12:10:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>After faking an injury to get out of work, Vic gains sympathy from everyone while unknowingly attracting attention from a dangerous mythical creature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 12:10:00" d="2020-04-22 12:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Tobias tries to be Gumball's best friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 12:20:00" d="2020-04-22 12:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin just want to veg out all day but end up having to save the rest of the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 12:40:00" d="2020-04-22 12:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% The kids try to help Dad bond with Frankie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 12:50:00" d="2020-04-22 13:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball and Hotdog Kid discover why they're so awkward with each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 13:10:00" d="2020-04-22 13:21:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>Everything is going well for Kara Danvers both as a teen and a superhero until she starts taking the blame for things she didn't do</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 13:21:00" d="2020-04-22 13:35:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>When the local mall is attached by the monstrous supervillain Giganta, Karen Beecher discovers that tiny Bumblebee might be the only one small enough to save the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 13:35:00" d="2020-04-22 13:45:00"><n>Adventure Time - Elements</n>    <k>Finn and Jake help Princess Bubblegum sneak into Wizard City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 13:45:00" d="2020-04-22 14:05:00"><n>Adventure Time - Elements</n>    <k>Jake is tired of Finn using his body as armour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 14:05:00" d="2020-04-22 14:15:00"><n>Adventure Time - Elements</n>    <k>Finn and Jake are on a mission to save BMO from malfunctioning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 14:15:00" d="2020-04-22 14:30:00"><n>Adventure Time - Elements</n>    <k>Finn finds Flame Princess battling Ice King exciting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 14:30:00" d="2020-04-22 14:40:00"><n>Adventure Time - Elements</n>    <k>Marceline is tracking Maja the Sky Witch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 14:40:00" d="2020-04-22 14:55:00"><n>Adventure Time - Elements</n>    <k>Jake's delicious sandwich is stolen by magic man</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 14:55:00" d="2020-04-22 15:05:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When Mao Mao's old partner threatens the kingdom, his friends will need to learn about his past in order to protect the present</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 15:05:00" d="2020-04-22 15:25:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When the Sheriff's Dept fights a monster that copies their every move they'll have to find a way to fight without fighting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 15:25:00" d="2020-04-22 15:33:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% When Beast Boy's head starts to rattle, Robin suggests that he should find a hobby so that his brain will stop shrinking. Beast Boy and his brain agree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 15:33:00" d="2020-04-22 15:55:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Gizmo convinces the Titans he's kidnapped Cyborg./Raven is cursed to be nice; meanwhile Starfire is about to marry a pot of chili</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 15:55:00" d="2020-04-22 16:04:00"><n>Total Dramarama</n>    <k>Noah tries to rescue the chocolates Owen forgot outside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 16:04:00" d="2020-04-22 16:20:00"><n>Total Dramarama</n>    <k>Leshawna creates a paint balloon fight to decide who gets to come with her to an amusement park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 16:20:00" d="2020-04-22 16:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin are offended when Mom calls them “procrastinators”, once she’s told them what it means</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 16:30:00" d="2020-04-22 16:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% While performing a school play, Gumball is so nervous about kissing Penny that he accidentally head-butts her and cracks open her shell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 16:50:00" d="2020-04-22 17:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball receives a scare-email from a freaky ghost and decides to ignore it, despite Darwin's advice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 17:00:00" d="2020-04-22 17:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Vice Principal Brown gives Gumball and Darwin the ancient school hamster, Chris Morris, to look after for the weekend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 17:20:00" d="2020-04-22 17:30:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>Craig, Kelsey and JP run afoul of some teenage witches</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 17:30:00" d="2020-04-22 17:50:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>Kelsey leads her friends on the most important quest ever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 17:50:00" d="2020-04-22 18:00:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>When Vic accidentally loses one of Val's prized coins Val makes a deal with a mysterious antiques collector to replace it, but the deal has terrible consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 18:00:00" d="2020-04-22 18:15:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>Val holds a grudge against Vic, unwittingly attracting an evil cadejo, a mythological wolf-like beast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 18:15:00" d="2020-04-22 18:24:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% A glimpse inside each Titan's dream world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 18:24:00" d="2020-04-22 18:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Using a grandma voice, Cyborg makes the others dress warmly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 18:34:00" d="2020-04-22 18:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin dabbles with magic, ignoring Raven's warning that he will anger the magic god</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 18:50:00" d="2020-04-22 18:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% When Robin gets frustrated with the Titans' disobedience he turns to. uppets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 18:59:00" d="2020-04-22 19:09:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% After Starfire is set up by Blackfire and sent to prison, the Titans work to make Blackfire a better sister while Starfire plots her revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 19:09:00" d="2020-04-22 19:30:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Despite the Titans' protests, Beast Boy becomes convinced that replacing his body parts with robotic limbs makes him more manly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 19:30:00" d="2020-04-22 19:40:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When Mao Mao's old partner threatens the kingdom, his friends will need to learn about his past in order to protect the present</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 19:40:00" d="2020-04-22 20:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When the Sheriff's Dept fights a monster that copies their every move they'll have to find a way to fight without fighting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 20:00:00" d="2020-04-22 20:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>The Tennysons come across a naturally formed pit with no bottom. Ben fights his better judgment to jump in until Kevin 11 shows up and goads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 20:10:00" d="2020-04-22 20:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Team Tennyson trade campfire stories in an anthology-style series that pits Ben against his arch-rival, Kevin 11, and teaches him the power of imagination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 20:30:00" d="2020-04-22 20:40:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% The AO return home to learn that no time has passed but they soon discover their knowledge of brawling has gotten years more advanced</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 20:40:00" d="2020-04-22 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% After Strata is sent packing the AO discover that they have picked up a hitch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 21:00:00" d="2020-04-22 21:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% Lloyd turns the tables on Harumi to take his father’s power away, and the Ninja learn what it takes to be a Dragon Hunter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 21:25:00" d="2020-04-22 21:55:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% Lloyd and his team plot to take control of the Oni Titan. Meanwhile in the First Realm, the Ninja fall into Iron Baron’s clutches and an old master returns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 21:55:00" d="2020-04-22 22:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo shares his tips and tricks for trading favors and then cashing them all in to create “a perfect day.”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 22:05:00" d="2020-04-22 22:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% When his family go on vacation Angelo sets all kinds of traps in his house for potential thieves. Problem is when they return home Angelo lost his guide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 22:20:00" d="2020-04-22 22:30:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and friends attempt to negotiate a deal for Peter and Cooper’s nonsensical home-made comic book with a famous comic book publisher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 22:30:00" d="2020-04-22 22:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo attempts to rack up the high score on an online business rating service to win free dinner at a fancy Japanese Steak House</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 22:45:00" d="2020-04-22 22:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% When Dad surprises the family with a brand new Electra smart home device everyone loves it at first, then Dad gets hooked and Angelo and Elena</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 22:55:00" d="2020-04-22 23:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% After failing an online “best friends” quiz Sherwood and Angelo drift apart. Angelo discovers the quiz was fake and tries to repair his relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 23:15:00" d="2020-04-22 23:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo enters a pie baking contest with his Dad as his partner until the two have creative differences and go it alone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 23:25:00" d="2020-04-22 23:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and Lola start a campaign to help Sherwood get voted “most likely to succeed” by his classmates instead of Tracy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 23:35:00" d="2020-04-22 23:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Elena and Angelo are grounded for fighting with each other. They have to put aside their differences and work together to escape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 23:45:00" d="2020-04-22 23:56:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin challenge Dad to a “lazy-off”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-22 23:56:00" d="2020-04-23 00:07:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball must learn to say “no” when Carrie the Ghost uses his body against his will</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 00:07:00" d="2020-04-23 00:16:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball sets out to solve the mystery of who stuffed Principal Brown into his locker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 00:16:00" d="2020-04-23 00:20:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>Vambre and Prohyas are hired by Old Man Oldman to walk his new stray dog. The problem is: it's a stray dinosaur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 00:20:00" d="2020-04-23 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% The Wattersons fear the worst when they are summoned to a Town Hall meeting, but are surprised when they're offered a new house. Until they discover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 00:30:00" d="2020-04-23 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% No matter what Gumball does, Carmen thinks she knows better. Gumball attempts to gain the moral high ground but fails. The only option left is to bring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 00:40:00" d="2020-04-23 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% The Wattersons compete over who has the worst life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 00:50:00" d="2020-04-23 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% When the kids find out that Mom's life hasn't panned out as she'd hoped, they start taking on her chores. However, they accidentally grab her bucket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 01:00:00" d="2020-04-23 01:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo shares his tips and tricks for trading favors and then cashing them all in to create “a perfect day.”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 01:10:00" d="2020-04-23 01:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% When his family go on vacation Angelo sets all kinds of traps in his house for potential thieves. Problem is when they return home Angelo lost his guide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 01:25:00" d="2020-04-23 01:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and friends attempt to negotiate a deal for Peter and Cooper’s nonsensical home-made comic book with a famous comic book publisher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 01:35:00" d="2020-04-23 01:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo attempts to rack up the high score on an online business rating service to win free dinner at a fancy Japanese Steak House</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 01:45:00" d="2020-04-23 01:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% When Dad surprises the family with a brand new Electra smart home device everyone loves it at first, then Dad gets hooked and Angelo and Elena</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 01:55:00" d="2020-04-23 02:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% After failing an online “best friends” quiz Sherwood and Angelo drift apart. Angelo discovers the quiz was fake and tries to repair his relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 02:05:00" d="2020-04-23 02:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo enters a pie baking contest with his Dad as his partner until the two have creative differences and go it alone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 02:15:00" d="2020-04-23 02:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and Lola start a campaign to help Sherwood get voted “most likely to succeed” by his classmates instead of Tracy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 02:25:00" d="2020-04-23 02:35:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 02:35:00" d="2020-04-23 02:55:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% Lloyd turns the tables on Harumi to take his father’s power away, and the Ninja learn what it takes to be a Dragon Hunter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 02:55:00" d="2020-04-23 03:15:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% Lloyd and his team plot to take control of the Oni Titan. Meanwhile in the First Realm, the Ninja fall into Iron Baron’s clutches and an old master returns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 03:15:00" d="2020-04-23 03:25:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>Vambre can't get her brain to go to sleep and it takes control of her body</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 03:25:00" d="2020-04-23 03:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% While performing a school play, Gumball is so nervous about kissing Penny that he accidentally head-butts her and cracks open her shell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 03:35:00" d="2020-04-23 03:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball receives a scare-email from a freaky ghost and decides to ignore it, despite Darwin's advice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 03:45:00" d="2020-04-23 03:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Vice Principal Brown gives Gumball and Darwin the ancient school hamster, Chris Morris, to look after for the weekend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 03:55:00" d="2020-04-23 04:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% When Darwin and Gumball reveal how they’d spend their perfect day, Gumball confesses that he would spend it with Penny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 04:05:00" d="2020-04-23 04:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Granny Jojo has brought a boyfriend to her birthday meal and Dad isn’t happy about it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 04:15:00" d="2020-04-23 04:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% The Wattersons complain about their day and order a pizza from Larry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 04:30:00" d="2020-04-23 04:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% The citizens of Elmore are feeling down because it’s January, so Gumball and Anais invent a new holiday called Sluzzle Tag</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 04:40:00" d="2020-04-23 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% In Biology class, Gumball and Darwin are waiting for a butterfly to emerge from its chrysalis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-23 04:50:00" d="2020-04-23 05:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% After Gumball and Darwin have too much sugary cereal they begin thinking about the mysteries of the universe</k>  </p>
</a>
