<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="116" t="2020-05-26 04:41:22"><p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 05:00:00" d="2020-06-02 05:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When Mom sees Darwin gazing longingly at a fish-tank she thinks their mammalian lifestyle isn’t fulfilling her adopted son and deep down he longs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 05:10:00" d="2020-06-02 05:15:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>The Warriors go to Grup’s workplace and must resist the temptation to steal the sword that is Grup’s job to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 05:15:00" d="2020-06-02 05:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The Parent Teacher Association of Elmore Junior High ban video games, so the kids try and prove that games aren’t a bad influence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 05:25:00" d="2020-06-02 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Anais arrives in the bedroom to find a messy crime-scene and her Daisy doll missing. She realises that Gumball and Darwin are the chief suspects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 05:35:00" d="2020-06-02 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% A mysterious figure from Nicole’s past shows up and challenges her to a fight, but the kids are surprised when she refuses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 05:45:00" d="2020-06-02 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% A compilation of some of the funniest, most bizarre clips uploaded onto the internet by the people of Elmore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 06:00:00" d="2020-06-02 06:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>In a peaceful coastal town, Ben must not only face the archaic antagonist Steam Smythe and his latest creation, the Clocktopus, but also his deepest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 06:10:00" d="2020-06-02 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben and Gwen are transformed into babies by nanny-gone-nuts Nanny Nightmare who will stop at nothing to reshape the world in the image of her day-care</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 06:25:00" d="2020-06-02 06:35:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When Rufus and Reg come to swindle the town, Sheriff Mao Mao teaches them a lesson in justice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 06:35:00" d="2020-06-02 06:50:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>The gang decide to compete in the annual Thumb War competition, but a surprise forces Mao Mao to deal with the unthinkable. losing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 06:50:00" d="2020-06-02 07:00:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>Having just moved to the boring Metropolis suburbs Batgirl is thrilled when she intercepts a call from Batman asking for help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 07:00:00" d="2020-06-02 07:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>Supergirl always relies on her strength, but she’ll need more than brawn to stop brainy Catwoman from stealing valuable gems from the local science museum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 07:15:00" d="2020-06-02 07:25:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>70% An unusually hot day at the Creek melts all of Kit's ice pops, so Craig helps her find a short cut to her frozen snack supplier before everyone else melts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 07:25:00" d="2020-06-02 07:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>70% The Trio finds gold in the muddy depths of the Creek so Craig builds a rig to recover it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 07:45:00" d="2020-06-02 07:54:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The prize jewel on the Secret Joyful Burger menu is a mysterious burger, but to order it you need to know its name. And Larry refuses to tell the guys what it's called</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 07:54:00" d="2020-06-02 08:03:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When Gumball finds out that their 8-bit friend Ocho has an Italian plumber called Mario for an uncle, he assumes it’s ‘that’ Mario and says he’ll do anything to meet him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 08:03:00" d="2020-06-02 08:14:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Richard discovers that going into a bank whilst wearing a motorcycle helmet can land you in a lot of trouble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 08:14:00" d="2020-06-02 08:24:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When Leslie's petals begin falling off he feels like his good looks are fading, Gumball and Darwin use everything they know about style and beauty to try and help him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 08:24:00" d="2020-06-02 08:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The Wattersons fear the worst when they are summoned to a Town Hall meeting, but are surprised when they're offered a new house. Until they discover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 08:35:00" d="2020-06-02 08:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% No matter what Gumball does, Carmen thinks she knows better. Gumball attempts to gain the moral high ground but fails. The only option left is to bring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 08:45:00" d="2020-06-02 08:56:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The Wattersons compete over who has the worst life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 08:56:00" d="2020-06-02 09:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When the kids find out that Mom's life hasn't panned out as she'd hoped, they start taking on her chores. However, they accidentally grab her bucket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 09:25:00" d="2020-06-02 09:35:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>Dan and Wynton stumble on both a possible hidden location of the Mind Core Cell and Colonel Tripp./After a falling out with Dan, Wynton is mind-controlled by Tripp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 09:35:00" d="2020-06-02 09:50:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>Dan and Wynton stumble on both a possible hidden location of the Mind Core Cell and Colonel Tripp./After a falling out with Dan, Wynton is mind-controlled by Tripp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 09:50:00" d="2020-06-02 10:01:00"><n>Power Players</n>    <k>Axel must wrangle Galileo and Bobbie to shut down a rogue thermostat - improperly upgraded by Slobot - as it plunges the house into extreme hot and cold zones</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 10:01:00" d="2020-06-02 10:20:00"><n>Power Players</n>    <k>After a Porcupunk sighting Axel leads a recon mission that slowly but surely proves to be a wild goose chase devised by Sarge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 10:20:00" d="2020-06-02 10:29:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin takes the Titans on an educational trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 10:29:00" d="2020-06-02 10:39:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Aqualad uses shrimps and prime rib to win back Raven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 10:39:00" d="2020-06-02 10:48:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans have Raven give them new super powers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 10:48:00" d="2020-06-02 10:58:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin tries to tell the origin story of the Teen Titans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 10:58:00" d="2020-06-02 11:08:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans want to be the scariest trick-or-treaters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 11:08:00" d="2020-06-02 11:18:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Justice League holds another talent competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 11:18:00" d="2020-06-02 11:28:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans must find a way to beat the Hive Five</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 11:28:00" d="2020-06-02 11:37:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin throws his own party with a special guest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 11:37:00" d="2020-06-02 11:47:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin tries to tell some tall tales</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 11:47:00" d="2020-06-02 11:56:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Teen Titans Go takes a look at the superheroes' lives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 11:56:00" d="2020-06-02 12:06:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans have to stop Darkseid's latest scheme</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 12:06:00" d="2020-06-02 12:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans time travel back to the 1980s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 12:15:00" d="2020-06-02 12:24:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Starfire dreams of becoming a successful business alien princess and joins a cookie-selling organization to learn the proper skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 12:24:00" d="2020-06-02 13:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% When the Big Game is threatened the Titans must infiltrate the football stadium and stop the attack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 13:10:00" d="2020-06-02 13:21:00"><n>Power Players</n>    <k>Axel and the team juggle not waking Uncle Andrew from his nap and stopping Orangutank from stealing Andrew's latest invention: the Knockout Box!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 13:21:00" d="2020-06-02 13:35:00"><n>Power Players</n>    <k>At a rummage sale with Uncle Andrew Axel and Zoe must stop Madcap from turning her long-lost tank toy Joyride into an agent of mayhem!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 13:35:00" d="2020-06-02 13:46:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin challenge Dad to a “lazy-off”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 13:46:00" d="2020-06-02 14:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball must learn to say “no” when Carrie the Ghost uses his body against his will</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 14:05:00" d="2020-06-02 14:16:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball sets out to solve the mystery of who stuffed Principal Brown into his locker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 14:16:00" d="2020-06-02 14:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin’s harmless pranks on Dad spiral hopelessly out of control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 14:30:00" d="2020-06-02 14:41:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin’s martial arts costumes make them a laughing stock at school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 14:41:00" d="2020-06-02 14:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball is traumatised when accidentally kissed on the mouth by his Grandma JoJo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 14:55:00" d="2020-06-02 15:05:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When Mao Mao discovers that he is not as popular as Badgerclops and Adorabat, they decide to reinvent him as a kinder, cuddlier hero</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 15:05:00" d="2020-06-02 15:25:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When Mao Mao underestimates enemy and friend alike, it almost costs him the entire kingdom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 15:25:00" d="2020-06-02 15:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% When Blackfire begins her plan to conquer Earth, the girls must pull out all the stops to defeat her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 15:34:00" d="2020-06-02 15:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans make Robin give them a tour of Wayne Manor and discover how fun it is to be rich</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 15:50:00" d="2020-06-02 16:01:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O and the other ThunderCats are thrilled to meet a new Thunderian! She’s good at fighting robots and most importantly thinks Lion-O and his Sword</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 16:01:00" d="2020-06-02 16:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Snarf leaves the Cats' Lair to get a needed vacation by transforming into a normal cat and hanging out with a nice old lady on a farm! But his relaxing day is threatened</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 16:15:00" d="2020-06-02 16:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The Wattersons transform their house into The Big House</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 16:25:00" d="2020-06-02 16:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The Wattersons discover a family of cartoon copycats who mimic their every move</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 16:35:00" d="2020-06-02 16:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Grandpa Louie has a new online friend - the only problem is she isn’t real</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 16:55:00" d="2020-06-02 17:06:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin accidentally create a loveable monster that eats their family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 17:06:00" d="2020-06-02 17:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball is embarrassed when Mum comes to school to spend some “quality time”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 17:20:00" d="2020-06-02 17:30:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>70% When a kid claims dibs on the Stump, Craig has no choice but to take them to court. Dibs Court</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 17:30:00" d="2020-06-02 17:50:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>70% JP finds a fossil in the Creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 17:50:00" d="2020-06-02 18:00:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Hawkodile admits his love for Dr. Fox</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 18:00:00" d="2020-06-02 18:15:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>It's Christmas Eve and Brock is excited for Santa to come and visit as he settles down for a bedtime story from Master Frown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 18:15:00" d="2020-06-02 18:24:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% When Blackfire begins her plan to conquer Earth, the girls must pull out all the stops to defeat her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 18:24:00" d="2020-06-02 18:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin ignores the rules for a game of jinx</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 18:34:00" d="2020-06-02 18:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% When drinking tea turns the other Titans English, it's up to Robin to save America from another British invasion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 18:50:00" d="2020-06-02 18:58:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Easter Bunny is missing and it's up to the Titans to find him before Easter is ruined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 18:58:00" d="2020-06-02 19:08:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% After seeing a pair of cool dudes on rollerblades Robin tries to be just like them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 19:08:00" d="2020-06-02 19:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin tries to teach the Titans valuable history lessons but the others co-opt his stories and spin them into their own twisted yarns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 19:25:00" d="2020-06-02 19:36:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O and the other ThunderCats are thrilled to meet a new Thunderian! She’s good at fighting robots and most importantly thinks Lion-O and his Sword</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 19:36:00" d="2020-06-02 19:50:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Snarf leaves the Cats' Lair to get a needed vacation by transforming into a normal cat and hanging out with a nice old lady on a farm! But his relaxing day is threatened</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 19:50:00" d="2020-06-02 20:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Team Tennyson visits Adrenaland Jr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 20:00:00" d="2020-06-02 20:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>When Kevin convinces Steam Smythe to adopt a modern approach in fighting Ben our young hero must resort to old-fashioned thinking to save the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 20:10:00" d="2020-06-02 20:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben and Gwen's social media battle with Kevin 11 quickly escalates into an all-out war in real life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 20:30:00" d="2020-06-02 20:40:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>Dan and Wynton stumble on both a possible hidden location of the Mind Core Cell and Colonel Tripp./After a falling out with Dan, Wynton is mind-controlled by Tripp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 20:40:00" d="2020-06-02 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>Dan and Wynton stumble on both a possible hidden location of the Mind Core Cell and Colonel Tripp./After a falling out with Dan, Wynton is mind-controlled by Tripp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 21:00:00" d="2020-06-02 21:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% In honor of older sisters, Slobber offers free tickets to whomever can make the best short film about their older sister. Angelo is all set</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 21:10:00" d="2020-06-02 21:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo searches for the ultimate object to bring to show and tell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 21:25:00" d="2020-06-02 21:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo’s photo bombs make him a big hit on the internet and he is loving his newfound popularity. Until, Butterfingers starts getting more “likes”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 21:35:00" d="2020-06-02 21:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% The equipment in Coach Zonka’s gym class is deemed a safety hazard so gym class is canceled permanently. Angelo attempts to rally the school to bring back gym class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 21:50:00" d="2020-06-02 22:00:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Everyone’s favorite skater, Ollie Van Dunk, crashes out in a big contest, loses his mojo, and quits skating. Angelo and friends try to raise his spirits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 22:00:00" d="2020-06-02 22:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% When Angelo gets stuck with the chore of painting Geezer’s old broken down fence, he channels his inner Tom Sawyer and manages to convince everyone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 22:20:00" d="2020-06-02 22:30:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and friends make a TV show pilot called “Angelo Rules,” with Lola producing, Sherwood directing, Angelo writing, and Butterfingers playing Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 22:30:00" d="2020-06-02 22:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% After Mom cuts off Angelo’s videogame time Angelo attempts to change her mind. He sets out to prove to her that gaming is an important skillset</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 22:45:00" d="2020-06-02 23:10:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>66% As Lloyd and Harumi search the Oni Temple for the last mask, the ninja are taken hostage and discover Princess Harumi's true intentions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 23:10:00" d="2020-06-02 23:40:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>66% The ninja appeal to the police commissioner of Ninjago in an effort to help save Lloyd and thwart Harumi's efforts to resurrect the evil Lord Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 23:40:00" d="2020-06-02 23:51:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Tobias compete for Penny's affection by putting on the lamest duel in history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-02 23:51:00" d="2020-06-03 00:02:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin learn that it isn't wise to upset Hector, Elmore's resident Giant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 00:02:00" d="2020-06-03 00:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Nicole seeks to develop a sense of ambition in Gumball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 00:10:00" d="2020-06-03 00:20:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>Trying to cheer Vambre up, Prohyas recalls when they were just kids on their parents broccoli Farm</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 00:20:00" d="2020-06-03 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The Wattersons complain about their day and order a pizza from Larry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 00:30:00" d="2020-06-03 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The citizens of Elmore are feeling down because it’s January, so Gumball and Anais invent a new holiday called Sluzzle Tag</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 00:40:00" d="2020-06-03 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% In Biology class, Gumball and Darwin are waiting for a butterfly to emerge from its chrysalis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 00:50:00" d="2020-06-03 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% After Gumball and Darwin have too much sugary cereal they begin thinking about the mysteries of the universe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 01:00:00" d="2020-06-03 01:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and Lola are stuck with Manetti as a science project partner. The only way to complete the project is turn Manetti into the science project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 01:10:00" d="2020-06-03 01:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Tracy claims Angelo broke her arm. Angelo’s punishment—become Tracy’s slave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 01:25:00" d="2020-06-03 01:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo discovers Cathy cat and Joe Mama have been accidentally switched at the Vet. And no one believes Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 01:35:00" d="2020-06-03 01:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo creates a fake Guatemalan pen pal so he doesn’t fail Mr. Foot’s class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 01:45:00" d="2020-06-03 01:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo becomes an intern at Adventureparkland. But, his dream job isn’t all it’s cracked up to be because he has to actually… work!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 01:55:00" d="2020-06-03 02:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Miss Perla turns detention time into art therapy where Angelo makes cool bobble-head sculptures which become all the rage in school. Result:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 02:05:00" d="2020-06-03 02:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% When Cathy hikes the price of her famous cupcake the “Brooklyn Blackout,” Lola goes undercover in search of the secret recipe. Angelo and the gang discover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 02:15:00" d="2020-06-03 02:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo shares his tips and tricks for delaying a test</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 02:25:00" d="2020-06-03 02:35:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>53% The Warriors are hired to &quot;vanquish&quot; a dragon, who turns out to be confoundingly sweet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 02:35:00" d="2020-06-03 02:55:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>66% As Lloyd and Harumi search the Oni Temple for the last mask, the ninja are taken hostage and discover Princess Harumi's true intentions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 02:55:00" d="2020-06-03 03:16:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>66% The ninja appeal to the police commissioner of Ninjago in an effort to help save Lloyd and thwart Harumi's efforts to resurrect the evil Lord Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 03:16:00" d="2020-06-03 03:20:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>The Warriors seek a secret book in the Library of Shhh! and their best friend from warrior school &quot;Witchy Simone&quot; follows them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 03:20:00" d="2020-06-03 03:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When Rob purchases a universal remote from the Awesome Store, he discovers he can control the universe. He rewinds into the past and remembers Gumball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 03:30:00" d="2020-06-03 03:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball saved himself from being trapped in The Void, just in time. The remote has now taken Gumball back to the beginning of that disastrous day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 03:40:00" d="2020-06-03 03:45:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>Trying to cheer Vambre up, Prohyas recalls when they were just kids on their parents broccoli Farm</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 03:45:00" d="2020-06-03 03:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Fed up with having to listen to Molly's long, tedious anecdotes, Gumball and Darwin try to teach her how to make them sound more exciting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 03:55:00" d="2020-06-03 04:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin put Anais' new friend, Josh, through a series of tests, to see if he's good enough for their sister</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 04:05:00" d="2020-06-03 04:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are convinced it's a day when nothing interesting is happening. But as they walk around Elmore, it is apparent exciting things</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 04:15:00" d="2020-06-03 04:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When Gumball and Darwin accidentally find a sinister secret manifesto on Alan's memory stick, they decide they have to foil his plan for total world domination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 04:30:00" d="2020-06-03 04:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Nicole remembers the day she first met Richard, and the different choices she could have made</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 04:40:00" d="2020-06-03 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball learns that the Wattersons have been stealing Mr Robinson’s wi-fi for years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-03 04:50:00" d="2020-06-03 05:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball is livid when an online test keeps telling him that his character-type is &quot;The Loser&quot;</k>  </p>
</a>
