<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="116" t="2020-05-29 04:36:44"><p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 05:00:00" d="2020-06-05 05:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Richard decides that his work around the house is underappreciated by Nicole and goes on strike to prove it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 05:10:00" d="2020-06-05 05:15:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>53% The Warriors are hired to &quot;vanquish&quot; a dragon, who turns out to be confoundingly sweet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 05:15:00" d="2020-06-05 05:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The Wattersons will do whatever it takes to get into the first screening of the latest Stellar Odyssey sequel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 05:25:00" d="2020-06-05 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Join the citizens of Elmore for a song and dance spectacular that will have you covering your ears with joy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 05:35:00" d="2020-06-05 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Darwin is delighted when they discover their old childhood toys, but soon realises that some things are best left in the past</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 05:45:00" d="2020-06-05 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Darwin ends up in detention with the Bomb Kid, who decides to make Darwin his new target. However, it backfires when Darwin ruins his life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 06:00:00" d="2020-06-05 06:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben stumbles into Dr. Animo’s secret lab, now ruled by his superior mutants the Alphas, and must help the lesser animals escape while stuck as Stinkfly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 06:10:00" d="2020-06-05 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben and Gwen’s camping trip is interrupted by the emotionless Weatherheads but a malfunctioning Omnitrix firing out a mishmash of aliens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 06:25:00" d="2020-06-05 06:35:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>After struggling to keep up, Adorabat gets a cybernetic &quot;Mega-Mech.&quot; But can fancy new powers make up for experience?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 06:35:00" d="2020-06-05 06:50:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When the Sweetypies think the mythical Torbaclaun has come to Pure Heart Valley, Mao Mao tries to prove to them that it isn't real</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 06:50:00" d="2020-06-05 07:00:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>A fun day for Barbara Gordon and her bestie Harleen Quinzel is turned on its head when out of nowhere the villainous Harley Quinn shows up to wreak havoc!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 07:00:00" d="2020-06-05 07:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>Jessica Cruz &amp; Pam Isley bond over protecting an ancient tree - without realizing who the other’s alter ego is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 07:15:00" d="2020-06-05 07:25:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>70% A terrible haircut forces Craig to go undercover at the Creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 07:25:00" d="2020-06-05 07:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>70% When the Time Keeper goes missing, Craig and his friends take up the task of helping kids get home in time for dinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 07:45:00" d="2020-06-05 07:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The Watterson kids come up with a fool-proof plan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 07:55:00" d="2020-06-05 08:06:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball decides to put Mr. Small's eco-friendly principles to the test but it doesn't quite go as planned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 08:06:00" d="2020-06-05 08:16:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Leslie calls Gumball's bluff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 08:16:00" d="2020-06-05 08:27:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Nicole and her parents have it out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 08:27:00" d="2020-06-05 08:38:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When Nicole decides to pay the cable bill in person at Chanax, she leaves specific instructions for Richard to stay in the car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 08:38:00" d="2020-06-05 08:48:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are at the convenience store considering playing truant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 08:48:00" d="2020-06-05 08:59:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin argue with the Internet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 08:59:00" d="2020-06-05 09:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Hector is unhappy with his height</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 09:25:00" d="2020-06-05 09:35:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>After defeating Magnus, the AO get an offer of employment from Philomena Dusk!/Dan and the AO rebel before they sell-out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 09:35:00" d="2020-06-05 09:50:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>After defeating Magnus, the AO get an offer of employment from Philomena Dusk!/Dan and the AO rebel before they sell-out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 09:50:00" d="2020-06-05 10:01:00"><n>Power Players</n>    <k>After a screening of the King Arthur tale Axel holds out his sword and declares himself king but when Dynamo uses his magnetism to steal the weapon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 10:01:00" d="2020-06-05 10:20:00"><n>Power Players</n>    <k>Axel must 'save' Bobbie Blobby after she defects to Madcap's team tempted by Porcupunk and his assertion that she belongs with the bad toys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 10:20:00" d="2020-06-05 10:30:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Beast Boy has to get a job at a pie shop to earn enough money to buy Cyborg a birthday gift, only his job interferes with being able to attend the actual party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 10:30:00" d="2020-06-05 10:40:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin is inadvertently the getaway driver for a bank robbery in the midst of his driver's ed exam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 10:40:00" d="2020-06-05 10:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Raven's supervillain father comes to visit and the rest of the team thinks he's the coolest~a5~until he steals their souls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 10:50:00" d="2020-06-05 11:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Cyborg and Beast Boy create clones of themselves to do their chores and the clones create more clones until the situation grows out of control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 11:00:00" d="2020-06-05 11:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin poses as Speedy to sabotage his upcoming date with Starfire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 11:10:00" d="2020-06-05 11:20:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin's distracting the team so they put him on forced hiatus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 11:20:00" d="2020-06-05 11:30:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin's distracting the team so they put him on forced hiatus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 11:30:00" d="2020-06-05 11:40:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Starfire mistakenly thinks she's killed Beast Boy, leading him to pose as a ghost and torment her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 11:40:00" d="2020-06-05 11:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The gang agrees to babysit Silkie, but then loses him; meanwhile, Silkie has a telenovela adventure south of the border</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 11:50:00" d="2020-06-05 12:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Beast Boy and Cyborg try their best to slow the pizza delivery boy so they can get free pizza</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 12:00:00" d="2020-06-05 12:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Beast Boy takes over as Alpha male of the Titans when he is in Gorilla-mode and Robin has to figure out how to get back on top</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 12:10:00" d="2020-06-05 12:20:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% When the guys plan a guys night out, Starfire drags Raven out on a wild adventure of their own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 12:20:00" d="2020-06-05 12:30:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Beast Boy gets fired from the team and the Wonder Twins take his place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 12:30:00" d="2020-06-05 13:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin wish comes true and he finally gets superpowers - but at what cost?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 13:10:00" d="2020-06-05 13:21:00"><n>Power Players</n>    <k>Bearbarian helps Axel get in touch with his wild side as Orangutank liberates nature from an apartment building - tossing potted plants of all sizes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 13:21:00" d="2020-06-05 13:35:00"><n>Power Players</n>    <k>Madcap's latest creation the Ice Crusher puts the whole city in a deep freeze forcing Axel and the team to face him in a game of high-stakes hockey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 13:35:00" d="2020-06-05 13:46:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Ms Simian sets out to “befriend” Gumball in order to win a Favourite Teacher Award</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 13:46:00" d="2020-06-05 14:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin give Mr Robinson a home and end up saving his marriage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 14:05:00" d="2020-06-05 14:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin help Anais rescue her doll from Tina Rex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 14:15:00" d="2020-06-05 14:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are unwitting accomplices in a gas station robbery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 14:30:00" d="2020-06-05 14:41:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin accidentally destroy Mr Robinson’s new car… or do they?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 14:41:00" d="2020-06-05 14:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball experiences an impossibly unfortunate chain of events</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 14:55:00" d="2020-06-05 15:05:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Badgerclops adopts an abandoned monster, but some things are better left in the wild</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 15:05:00" d="2020-06-05 15:25:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Mao Mao's legendary, gigantic and critical father visits his son at his new job as sheriff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 15:25:00" d="2020-06-05 15:33:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin surprises the Titans with a trip to the opera, but they soon fall asleep, and all dream about starring in their own operas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 15:33:00" d="2020-06-05 15:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans are outraged when their favourite cartoon is rebooted, so they come up with a plan to get this new show off the air</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 15:50:00" d="2020-06-05 16:01:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Third Earth is being overrun by super tough, super buff Warrior Maidens and it looks like the ThunderCats are next on their hit list!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 16:01:00" d="2020-06-05 16:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O wants to prove to the ThunderKittens that he’s not just some boring old adult like Tygra even if it means ignoring his instincts and messing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 16:15:00" d="2020-06-05 16:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Carrie takes Gumball, Darwin and Anais to a real haunted house party on Halloween</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 16:25:00" d="2020-06-05 16:36:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Darwin is too polite to speak his mind, so Gumball teaches him to be direct</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 16:36:00" d="2020-06-05 16:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% For once in his life Gumball is the one who's owed an apology</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 16:55:00" d="2020-06-05 17:06:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Tobias compete for Penny's affection by putting on the lamest duel in history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 17:06:00" d="2020-06-05 17:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The kids find out that Richard has been being picked on by the same person since high school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 17:20:00" d="2020-06-05 17:30:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>70% Craig discovers that the Honeysuckle Rangers have snuck into his side of the Creek to steal his most prized possession</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 17:30:00" d="2020-06-05 17:50:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>70% When Craig can't go to the Creek, he and his mom decide to build the biggest blanket fort in the world!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 17:50:00" d="2020-06-05 18:00:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Unikitty and gang have ordered some delicious Thai food for dinner. Unfortunately the wait for the delivery is proving too much, time itself seems to have slowed down</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 18:00:00" d="2020-06-05 18:15:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>When the Score creeper traps Unikitty and the gang in his laser tag arena the gang must defeat the house team or be imprisoned forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 18:15:00" d="2020-06-05 18:23:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin surprises the Titans with a trip to the opera, but they soon fall asleep, and all dream about starring in their own operas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 18:23:00" d="2020-06-05 18:33:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Justice League holds a talent competition to find a superhero worthy of joining the team</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 18:33:00" d="2020-06-05 18:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The competition heats up as Robin tries everything to win</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 18:50:00" d="2020-06-05 18:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans get into the pioneer spirit as they head west on the Oregon Trail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 18:59:00" d="2020-06-05 19:09:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% When yet another crime alert interrupts their relaxation the Titans decide to become villains and do whatever they want</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 19:09:00" d="2020-06-05 19:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Cyborg tells the other Titans that TV wrestling is fake and tries to teach them about real wrestling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 19:25:00" d="2020-06-05 19:36:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Third Earth is being overrun by super tough, super buff Warrior Maidens and it looks like the ThunderCats are next on their hit list!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 19:36:00" d="2020-06-05 19:50:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O wants to prove to the ThunderKittens that he’s not just some boring old adult like Tygra even if it means ignoring his instincts and messing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 19:50:00" d="2020-06-05 20:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben, Gwen and Grandpa Max arrive in Bismarck for its annual celebration of bee pollination, bringing them face-to-face with Queen Bee and a bold new scheme</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 20:00:00" d="2020-06-05 20:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Team Tennyson look to take in the sights of the Shoshone Falls but when they find Steam Smythe siphoning off the water, it is up to Ben, Grandpa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 20:10:00" d="2020-06-05 20:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>While visiting Lake Erie, a relaxing day at the beach gets all washed up when Ben, Gwen and Grandpa Max come face-to-face with Hex. and his summer intern, Kevin!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 20:30:00" d="2020-06-05 20:40:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>After defeating Magnus, the AO get an offer of employment from Philomena Dusk!/Dan and the AO rebel before they sell-out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 20:40:00" d="2020-06-05 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>After defeating Magnus, the AO get an offer of employment from Philomena Dusk!/Dan and the AO rebel before they sell-out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 21:00:00" d="2020-06-05 21:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% After Angelo trashes Burst’s stage set, his punishment is that he must star in Burst’s unusual, arty play. With Sherwood and Lola helping backstage, Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 21:10:00" d="2020-06-05 21:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% After accidentally breaking a window, Angelo and friends complete a series of chores at the rec center as pay back. But it’s all good because Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 21:25:00" d="2020-06-05 21:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% To convince his parents to buy him a phone Angelo must turn his text addicted sister into a smart phone role model</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 21:35:00" d="2020-06-05 21:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% After Mr. Foot confiscates all electronics before class, Angelo and friends have to kick it old school and pass hand written notes to communicate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 21:50:00" d="2020-06-05 22:00:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Dreams do come true and Angelo and friends turn Angelo’s Dad into a rock star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 22:00:00" d="2020-06-05 22:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo attempts to join the secretive “school council” and learns-- never become a member of a group that will have you has a member</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 22:20:00" d="2020-06-05 22:30:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo gives us his tips and tricks for the most awesome sleepover ever. Until, the “prank call” trick ruins the night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 22:30:00" d="2020-06-05 22:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo stupidly boasts that his Dad used to be a stuntman. And the next day Dad has been invited to speak to Angelo’s class for career day. Gah!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 22:45:00" d="2020-06-05 23:10:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% Lloyd must find his voice as he leads a small resistance to capture the airwaves in Ninjago City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 23:10:00" d="2020-06-05 23:40:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% Lloyd and the rebels celebrate their successful strike against Emperor Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 23:40:00" d="2020-06-05 23:51:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin spice up their friendship by introducing a third best friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-05 23:51:00" d="2020-06-06 00:02:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball has to save Mr Robinson’s life during Elmore’s Senior Talent Show!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 00:02:00" d="2020-06-06 00:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball tries to save Darwin from being kissed by a girl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 00:10:00" d="2020-06-06 00:20:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>53% Tired of their local public swimming pool, the Warriors travel to the Dinosaur Kingdom to sneak in their pool</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 00:20:00" d="2020-06-06 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball refuses to get out of bed because he is in a lousy mood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 00:30:00" d="2020-06-06 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Nicole arranges a playdate for Anais with the son of a classy lady she met at the supermarket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 00:40:00" d="2020-06-06 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Darwin joins the school marching band, and his tin-whistle talent lands him the solo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 00:50:00" d="2020-06-06 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Richard has lost all of the family’s money. Nicole is happy for the Wattersons to appear in a Joyful Burger commercial for some much needed cash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 01:00:00" d="2020-06-06 01:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and friends attempt to negotiate a deal for Peter and Cooper’s nonsensical home-made comic book with a famous comic book publisher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 01:10:00" d="2020-06-06 01:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo attempts to rack up the high score on an online business rating service to win free dinner at a fancy Japanese Steak House</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 01:25:00" d="2020-06-06 01:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% When Dad surprises the family with a brand new Electra smart home device everyone loves it at first, then Dad gets hooked and Angelo and Elena</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 01:35:00" d="2020-06-06 01:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% After failing an online “best friends” quiz Sherwood and Angelo drift apart. Angelo discovers the quiz was fake and tries to repair his relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 01:45:00" d="2020-06-06 01:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo enters a pie baking contest with his Dad as his partner until the two have creative differences and go it alone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 01:55:00" d="2020-06-06 02:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and Lola start a campaign to help Sherwood get voted “most likely to succeed” by his classmates instead of Tracy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 02:05:00" d="2020-06-06 02:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Dad takes a parenting class which works! Now he has more control of his kids. Angelo infiltrates the parenting class (posing as an adult) to learn Dad’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 02:15:00" d="2020-06-06 02:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo comes up with unique inventions to win “Snake Pit” a TV show where you pitch your business idea to local “business tycoons” hoping to get them to invest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 02:25:00" d="2020-06-06 02:35:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>The Warriors are treated to a banquet by the grateful Kotassians and Vambre accidentally eats their king</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 02:35:00" d="2020-06-06 02:55:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% Lloyd must find his voice as he leads a small resistance to capture the airwaves in Ninjago City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 02:55:00" d="2020-06-06 03:16:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% Lloyd and the rebels celebrate their successful strike against Emperor Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 03:16:00" d="2020-06-06 03:20:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 03:20:00" d="2020-06-06 03:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The kids convince Mr Corneille to become a cage fighter and set up a fight against a fearsome Russian fighter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 03:30:00" d="2020-06-06 03:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are jealous of a sparking a baby war</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 03:40:00" d="2020-06-06 03:45:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>53% Tired of their local public swimming pool, the Warriors travel to the Dinosaur Kingdom to sneak in their pool</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 03:45:00" d="2020-06-06 03:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Tobias tries to be Gumball's best friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 03:55:00" d="2020-06-06 04:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin just want to veg out all day but end up having to save the rest of the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 04:05:00" d="2020-06-06 04:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The kids try to help Dad bond with Frankie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 04:15:00" d="2020-06-06 04:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Hotdog Kid discover why they're so awkward with each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 04:30:00" d="2020-06-06 04:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin try to find out the name of their neighbour, Antlers Guy, but accidentally blow his witness protection cover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 04:40:00" d="2020-06-06 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Pr Brown make a pact to tell each other's girlfriends about problems they have</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 04:50:00" d="2020-06-06 05:01:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin babysit Anais “responsibly”, whilst “irresponsibly” flooding the house</k>  </p>
</a>
