<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="103" t="2021-07-09 07:32:05"><p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 05:00:00" d="2021-07-15 05:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (12)</n>    <k>The Routine
Mum and the kids depart for their hard day's work, leaving a seemingly lazy Dad half-asleep on the sofa. Mum has given him one very simple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 05:10:00" d="2021-07-15 05:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (13)</n>    <k>The Parking
When the Wattersons arrive at the mall for a day of shopping, they struggle to find a space in the parking lot. They search for a space</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 05:20:00" d="2021-07-15 05:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (14)</n>    <k>The Upgrade
Gumball and Darwin see an advert for the latest cutting-edge Bobert operating system and excitedly talk Bobert into downloading it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 05:35:00" d="2021-07-15 05:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (15)</n>    <k>The Comic
Gumball is the star of his own comic but struggles to match up to his heroic alter-ego</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 05:45:00" d="2021-07-15 06:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (16)</n>    <k>The Romantic
After Gumball convinces himself that Penny doesn't love him as much as she used to, he decides to put together a romantic quest to remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 06:00:00" d="2021-07-15 06:10:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! II (3)</n>    <k>Brian
When The Brain captures the Titans to fuel Project B.R.I.A.N. the Titan's little buddies are the only heroes who can save them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 06:10:00" d="2021-07-15 06:25:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! II (3)</n>    <k>Nature
In order to get his powers back Beast Boy returns to nature and finds it much harsher than he expects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 06:25:00" d="2021-07-15 06:35:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! II (4)</n>    <k>Salty Codgers
Raven is delighted when the other Titans are magically turned into old people during a battle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 06:35:00" d="2021-07-15 06:50:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! II (4)</n>    <k>Knowledge
Starfire wants to learn more but will knowledge make her a bummer?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 06:50:00" d="2021-07-15 07:00:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (1)</n>    <k>Robo Teacher
When a substitute teacher fills in for Chef, Duncan thinks it's going to be the best day ever. He's wrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 07:00:00" d="2021-07-15 07:15:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (2)</n>    <k>Glove Glove Me Do
Owen's newly found gloves make him great at everything. But this greatness comes at a high price</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 07:15:00" d="2021-07-15 07:25:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (83)</n>    <k>Everett's Trap
Shun and Masato head to Tokyo’s Battle Island to discuss plans for hosting public Bakugan battles. Upon landing, they quickly learn it’s a set up! The two are now stranded and face with heaps of brawlers, who are all looking to bring them down!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 07:25:00" d="2021-07-15 07:40:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (84)</n>    <k>Kazami vs. Mc Q
Shun and Masato manage to fend off a horde of brawlers on Battle Island, but they quickly learn that was only a diversion- One of Kazami’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 07:40:00" d="2021-07-15 07:50:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (1)</n>    <k>The Knights
The Colossus: Gumball and Darwin learn that it isn't wise to upset Hector Elmore's resident Giant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 07:50:00" d="2021-07-15 08:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (1)</n>    <k>The Knights
The Knights: Gumball and Tobias compete for Penny's affection by putting on the lamest duel in history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 08:00:00" d="2021-07-15 08:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (2)</n>    <k>81% The Remote
The Remote: The Wattersons' battle for possession of the TV remote gets dirty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 08:20:00" d="2021-07-15 08:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (2)</n>    <k>81% The Remote
The Fridge: When Mom discovers Gumball has no ambition she is determined to turn him into a winner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 08:30:00" d="2021-07-15 08:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (3)</n>    <k>The Flower
Gumball seeks justice when Banana Joe chews Darwin's pen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 08:40:00" d="2021-07-15 09:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (3)</n>    <k>The Flower
Gumball is determined to drive Penny away from Leslie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 09:00:00" d="2021-07-15 09:25:00"><n u="The Looney Tunes Show">The Looney Tunes Show II (5)</n>    <k>73% Semper Lie
When Bugs tells a small lie to Porky, it gathers steam to make everything far worse -- and inadvertently prompts Daffy to join the U.S. Marines</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 09:25:00" d="2021-07-15 09:55:00"><n u="The Looney Tunes Show">The Looney Tunes Show II (6)</n>    <k>73% Father Figures
Volunteering in the Father Figure program, Porky is matched up with the troubled Henry Hawk and Foghorn is paired up with Daffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 09:55:00" d="2021-07-15 10:25:00"><n u="The Looney Tunes Show">The Looney Tunes Show II (7)</n>    <k>73% Customer Service
When Cecil Turtle, a customer service representative, intentionally cuts off Bugs' cable TV, Bugs declares war and gets revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 10:25:00" d="2021-07-15 10:35:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (14)</n>    <k>Monster Squad!
The Titans want to be the scariest trick-or-treaters in town so Raven casts a spell to turn them into real monsters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 10:35:00" d="2021-07-15 10:50:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (17)</n>    <k>54% BBRBDAY
When he isn't invited to Beast Boy's birthday party Robin throws his own party with special guest Bob Uecker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 10:50:00" d="2021-07-15 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (18)</n>    <k>Tall Titan Tales
Robin tries to tell some tall tales but the other Titans give their own fractured versions instead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 11:00:00" d="2021-07-15 11:20:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (21)</n>    <k>54% Nostalgia Is Not a Substitute For. 
The Titans time travel back to the 1980s to determine whether or not it was the best decade ever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 11:20:00" d="2021-07-15 11:30:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (22)</n>    <k>Business Ethics Wink Wink
Starfire dreams of becoming a successful business alien princess and joins a cookie-selling organization to learn the proper skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 11:30:00" d="2021-07-15 11:45:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (23)</n>    <k>Slapping Butts and Celebrating For No Reason
When the Big Game is threatened the Titans must infiltrate the football stadium and stop the attack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 11:45:00" d="2021-07-15 11:55:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (24)</n>    <k>I Used To Be A Peoples
Robin feels the other Titans are spending too much time together so he encourages them to spend some time alone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 11:55:00" d="2021-07-15 12:10:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (25)</n>    <k>The Metric System vs. Freedom
Robin teaches the other Titans about the difference between the Imperial System and the Metric System</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 12:10:00" d="2021-07-15 12:20:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (28)</n>    <k>Them Soviet Boys
In order to quickly get through their chores and karate lessons the Titans learn how to montage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 12:20:00" d="2021-07-15 12:40:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (29)</n>    <k>Lil' Dimples
Thinking it's a way to reconnect with her father Raven enters a beauty pageant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 12:40:00" d="2021-07-15 12:50:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (3)</n>    <k>45% The Tooth About Zombies
When Gwen's favorite event, the Zombie March, falls on the same day as Beth's nightmare event, dental hygienist check upday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 12:50:00" d="2021-07-15 13:10:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (4)</n>    <k>45% Lie-Ranosaurus Wrecked
Owen pretends to be Izzy's pet dinosaur after leading her to believe she dug him up in the school playground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 13:10:00" d="2021-07-15 13:20:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (5)</n>    <k>Swing Set Jet Set
Axel and the team battle Princess SugarSalt for possession of Bearbarian's hammer traded to her by one of their own - Galileo!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 13:20:00" d="2021-07-15 13:35:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (6)</n>    <k>That Slobot is No Bot of Mine
Axel and the team compete against themselves in tests of skill, strength and stamina, but when SloBot gets belittled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 13:35:00" d="2021-07-15 13:50:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (21)</n>    <k>The Traitor
When Alan ditches Gumball to do something more fun Gumball is desperate to track him down and make him pay for his betrayal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 13:50:00" d="2021-07-15 14:05:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (22)</n>    <k>The Advice
To make Mr Small feel like he's inspired the students, Gumball and Darwin try to follow every piece of advice Mr Small gives them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 14:05:00" d="2021-07-15 14:15:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (23)</n>    <k>The Signal
When Darwin asks for his advice on hats, Gumball suddenly can't speak and offends Darwin. Darwin is convinced Gumball said he had a fat head</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 14:15:00" d="2021-07-15 14:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (24)</n>    <k>The Girlfriend
When she has no one to share her lunch with, Jamie realises she needs a sweetheart. Darwin is the only one who doesn't flee immediately</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 14:30:00" d="2021-07-15 14:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (25)</n>    <k>81% The Parasite
Anais has made a new friend but Gumball and Darwin aren't sure their relationship is equal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 14:40:00" d="2021-07-15 14:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (26)</n>    <k>81% The Love
When Bobert finds he's infected with a virus called love.exe he asks Gumball and Darwin to give him a definition for the word 'love'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 14:55:00" d="2021-07-15 15:05:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (3)</n>    <k>Chata's Quinta Quinceanera
Vic and Val want to go to a friend's pool party on the same day as their grandma's quinceanera, so they use a magical flute</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 15:05:00" d="2021-07-15 15:25:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (5)</n>    <k>Brotherly Love
After breaking Chata's plant, Vic and Val must accomplish the seemingly easy task of replacing it; this proves difficult when their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 15:25:00" d="2021-07-15 15:35:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (3)</n>    <k>54% Booby Trap House
After being left alone at home Cyborg and Starfire booby trap the tower for safety</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 15:35:00" d="2021-07-15 15:55:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (4)</n>    <k>54% Fish Water
Starfire wins a goldfish at the carnival and vows to keep it alive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 15:55:00" d="2021-07-15 16:05:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (5)</n>    <k>54% TV Knight
Batman and Commissioner Gordon check in on various happenings around Jump City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 16:05:00" d="2021-07-15 16:20:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (6)</n>    <k>54% BBSFBDAY!
Beast Boy agrees to share his birthday with Starfire after learning she's never had one on Earth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 16:20:00" d="2021-07-15 16:30:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (3)</n>    <k>45% The Tooth About Zombies
When Gwen's favorite event, the Zombie March, falls on the same day as Beth's nightmare event, dental hygienist check upday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 16:30:00" d="2021-07-15 16:40:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (4)</n>    <k>45% Lie-Ranosaurus Wrecked
Owen pretends to be Izzy's pet dinosaur after leading her to believe she dug him up in the school playground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 16:40:00" d="2021-07-15 16:55:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (27)</n>    <k>45% All Up in Your Drill
Duncan stages a small coup to oust Courtney as their official class firefighter so that he can wear the shiny firefighter helmet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 16:55:00" d="2021-07-15 17:05:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek II (29)</n>    <k>The End Was Here
Craig tries to figure out how an ancient war that decimated the Creek began in hopes of stopping history from repeating itself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 17:05:00" d="2021-07-15 17:25:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek II (30)</n>    <k>72% The Children Of…
Craig has tried to convince his family to get a dog for years but has never been successful, but he may have a chance if he follows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 17:25:00" d="2021-07-15 17:35:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (22)</n>    <k>Churro Kings
When Vic &amp; Val start making good money from selling churros at the taco stand, their lust for stuff makes them do dirty tricks to take out their competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 17:35:00" d="2021-07-15 17:55:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (23)</n>    <k>Know It All
When Vic accidently unleashes evil bats from a cave, it's up to the boys and Don to protect the town, but Vic's know-it-all attitude keeps getting in the way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 17:55:00" d="2021-07-15 19:10:00"><n>Scooby-Doo! Frankencreepy</n>    <k>Velma discovers she's inherited her great great-uncle Dr. Von Dinkenstein's cursed castle in the terrifying town of Transylvania Pennsylvania, that is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 19:10:00" d="2021-07-15 19:30:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! VI (45)</n>    <k>Real Art
After Starfire buys an ugly painting, the Titans take her to the museum so she can experience real art</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 19:30:00" d="2021-07-15 19:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (13)</n>    <k>The Hero
Richard overhears Gumball and Darwin making fun of him which hurts his feelings and he has to regain his reputation as a hero</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 19:40:00" d="2021-07-15 20:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (13)</n>    <k>81% The Photo
Gumball tries to look good in the school photo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 20:00:00" d="2021-07-15 20:10:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (5)</n>    <k>Swing Set Jet Set
Axel and the team battle Princess SugarSalt for possession of Bearbarian's hammer traded to her by one of their own - Galileo!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 20:10:00" d="2021-07-15 20:30:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (6)</n>    <k>That Slobot is No Bot of Mine
Axel and the team compete against themselves in tests of skill, strength and stamina, but when SloBot gets belittled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 20:30:00" d="2021-07-15 20:40:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (85)</n>    <k>The Awesome Burger Brawl
The Burger Joint is hosting a hamburger eating contest to promote their new Bakugan themed burger! This contest gets underway</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 20:40:00" d="2021-07-15 21:00:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (86)</n>    <k>Master and Apprentice
A wealthy man, Mr Gold, has duped Storm and Ajit, and trapped them in his personal prison. but no prison can hold the cunning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 21:00:00" d="2021-07-15 21:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (29)</n>    <k>60% Geezer's Nephew
Angelo and friends are stuck hanging out with Geezer’s Nephew -- a terrible horrible no good delinquent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 21:10:00" d="2021-07-15 21:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (30)</n>    <k>Enter The Karate Kid
Angelo and friends attempt to raise Butterfingers flagging self-esteem by training him in the art of Angelo-fu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 21:25:00" d="2021-07-15 21:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (31)</n>    <k>60% A Perfect Day
Angelo shares his tips and tricks for trading favors and then cashing them all in to create “a perfect day.”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 21:35:00" d="2021-07-15 21:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (32)</n>    <k>60% Home Security
When his family go on vacation Angelo sets all kinds of traps in his house for potential thieves. Problem is when they return home Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 21:55:00" d="2021-07-15 22:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (33)</n>    <k>60% Pow!
Angelo and friends attempt to negotiate a deal for Peter and Cooper’s nonsensical home-made comic book with a famous comic book publisher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 22:05:00" d="2021-07-15 22:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (34)</n>    <k>60% Better Call Angelo
Angelo attempts to rack up the high score on an online business rating service to win free dinner at a fancy Japanese Steak House</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 22:25:00" d="2021-07-15 22:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (35)</n>    <k>60% Electra
When Dad surprises the family with a brand new Electra smart home device everyone loves it at first then Dad gets hooked and Angelo and Elena</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 22:35:00" d="2021-07-15 22:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (36)</n>    <k>60% Best Friends Forever
After failing an online “best friends” quiz Sherwood and Angelo drift apart. Angelo discovers the quiz was fake and tries to repair his relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 22:50:00" d="2021-07-15 23:00:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (29)</n>    <k>The Trojan Bear
When Axel opens a subscription gift-box he didn't even order the team finds their ranks divided by a robotic bear - or Princess SugarSalt in disguise!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 23:00:00" d="2021-07-15 23:20:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (30)</n>    <k>Porcupunk Rock
Madcap turns to Axel and his team for help after a sonic upgrade to Porcupunk threatens to bring down the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 23:20:00" d="2021-07-15 23:30:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (31)</n>    <k>Saving Private Masko
Masko takes Axel's call for more discipline too seriously and loses sight of his own identity in the process, becoming a no-nonsense</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 23:30:00" d="2021-07-15 23:45:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (32)</n>    <k>Out of My Head
Axel must help Sarge and Bobbie learn to walk in each other's shoes - literally - after Luka unwittingly switches the toys' heads!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 23:45:00" d="2021-07-16 00:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (26)</n>    <k>The Diet
Gumball and Darwin discover the reason Dad's diet wasn't working was that he was actually on ten diets: and eating a meal for each of them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 00:00:00" d="2021-07-16 00:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (27)</n>    <k>The Ex
Gumball discovers that Rob, his old nemesis, is &quot;neme-seeing&quot; someone else now. Devastated that Rob has fallen out of hate with him, Gumball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 00:10:00" d="2021-07-16 00:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (28)</n>    <k>The Weirdo
When they see the school bullies making fun of Sussie Gumball and Darwin decide to try and help her act less weird. They carefully observe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 00:25:00" d="2021-07-16 00:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (29)</n>    <k>The Menu
The prize jewel on the Secret Joyful Burger menu is a mysterious burger but to order it you need to know its name. When Larry refuses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 00:35:00" d="2021-07-16 00:50:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (30)</n>    <k>The Uncle
When Gumball finds out that their 8-bit friend Ocho has an Italian plumber called Mario for an uncle, he assumes it's 'that' Mario</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 00:50:00" d="2021-07-16 01:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (31)</n>    <k>The Heist
Richard's got a motorcycle helmet stuck on his head, so when he goes into a bank the terrified staff all assume he's there to rob the place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 01:00:00" d="2021-07-16 01:15:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (32)</n>    <k>The Petals
When Leslie's petals begin falling off he feels like his good looks are fading, Gumball and Darwin use everything they know about style</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 01:15:00" d="2021-07-16 01:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (15)</n>    <k>60% Secret Recipe
When Cathy hikes the price of her famous cupcake the “Brooklyn Blackout” Lola goes undercover in search of the secret recipe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 01:25:00" d="2021-07-16 01:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (16)</n>    <k>60% Angelo vs. The Test
Angelo shares his tips and tricks for delaying a test</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 01:40:00" d="2021-07-16 01:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (17)</n>    <k>60% What Now?
Because of his cunning and tenacity Angelo always gets what he wants. Is this the way life is always going to be? Angelo has an existential crisis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 01:50:00" d="2021-07-16 02:00:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (18)</n>    <k>60% Grounded
Elena and Angelo are grounded for fighting with each other. They have to put aside their differences and work together to escape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 02:00:00" d="2021-07-16 02:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (19)</n>    <k>60% The Pigeons
Lola has a pigeon phobia. Paging Dr. Angelo and Dr. Sherwood to cure her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 02:10:00" d="2021-07-16 02:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (20)</n>    <k>Best Sister Ever
In honor of older sisters Slobber offers free tickets to whomever can make the best short film about their older sister</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 02:20:00" d="2021-07-16 02:30:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (20)</n>    <k>60% Cupcake War
A new hipster cupcake shop opens across the street from Cathy’s siphoning off all the customers. Angelo and friends come up with strategies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 02:30:00" d="2021-07-16 02:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (21)</n>    <k>Snow And Tell
Angelo searches for the ultimate object to bring to show and tell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 02:40:00" d="2021-07-16 02:55:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (1)</n>    <k>Unboxing Part 1
Axel ventures into his uncle's strictly off-limits basement lab in hopes of fixing a broken toy and ends up unleashing living</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 02:55:00" d="2021-07-16 03:05:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (2)</n>    <k>Unboxing Part 2
Axel discovers that he can transform into a toy and teams up with his new team of toys to stop Madcap from stealing a Minergy battery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 03:05:00" d="2021-07-16 03:15:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (4)</n>    <k>Knockout
Axel and the team juggle not waking Uncle Andrew from his nap and stopping Orangutank from stealing Andrew's latest invention: the Knockout Box!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 03:15:00" d="2021-07-16 03:25:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (5)</n>    <k>Swing Set Jet Set
Axel and the team battle Princess SugarSalt for possession of Bearbarian's hammer traded to her by one of their own - Galileo!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 03:25:00" d="2021-07-16 03:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (17)</n>    <k>The Uploads
Gumball and Darwin try to tear themselves away from the internet but end up falling down the Elmore Stream-hole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 03:35:00" d="2021-07-16 03:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (18)</n>    <k>81% The Wicked
After being framed for feeding coffee to the squirrels in the park, Gumball proclaims that Mrs Robinson is pure evil. Darwin tells</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 03:45:00" d="2021-07-16 03:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (19)</n>    <k>81% The Origins
When Mom and Dad struggle to keep hyperactive toddler-aged Gumball from trashing the house and exhausting them they decide to buy him a pet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 03:55:00" d="2021-07-16 04:05:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (20)</n>    <k>81% The Origins Part Two
Via the sewers Darwin finds himself flushed out to sea. He is terrified but determined to make his way back to the Wattersons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 04:05:00" d="2021-07-16 04:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (21)</n>    <k>The Traitor
When Alan ditches Gumball to do something more fun Gumball is desperate to track him down and make him pay for his betrayal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 04:20:00" d="2021-07-16 04:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (22)</n>    <k>The Advice
To make Mr Small feel like he's inspired the students, Gumball and Darwin try to follow every piece of advice Mr Small gives them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 04:30:00" d="2021-07-16 04:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (23)</n>    <k>The Signal
When Darwin asks for his advice on hats, Gumball suddenly can't speak and offends Darwin. Darwin is convinced Gumball said he had a fat head</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 04:40:00" d="2021-07-16 04:50:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (24)</n>    <k>The Girlfriend
When she has no one to share her lunch with, Jamie realises she needs a sweetheart. Darwin is the only one who doesn't flee immediately</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-16 04:50:00" d="2021-07-16 05:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (25)</n>    <k>81% The Parasite
Anais has made a new friend but Gumball and Darwin aren't sure their relationship is equal</k>  </p>
</a>
