<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="105" t="2021-07-09 07:31:28"><p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 05:00:00" d="2021-07-14 05:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (19)</n>    <k>The Egg
Nicole arranges a playdate for Anais with the son of a classy lady she met at the supermarket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 05:10:00" d="2021-07-14 05:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (20)</n>    <k>The Triangle
Darwin joins the school marching band and his tin-whistle talent lands him the solo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 05:20:00" d="2021-07-14 05:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (20)</n>    <k>The Money
Richard has lost all of the family’s money. Nicole is happy for the Wattersons to appear in a Joyful Burger commercial for some much needed cash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 05:35:00" d="2021-07-14 05:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (1)</n>    <k>81% The Return
Dad has to make the kids on time for their first day back at school. But he's overslept and now he can't find Gumball, Darwin or Anais anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 05:45:00" d="2021-07-14 06:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (2)</n>    <k>81% The Nemesis
Gumball and Darwin discover that Rob, who once swore to wreak vengeance on them, has been trying to destroy them for some time. But his traps never work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 06:00:00" d="2021-07-14 06:10:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! II (1)</n>    <k>54% Mr. Butt
After Starfire is set up by Blackfire and sent to prison the Titans work to make Blackfire a better sister while Starfire plots her revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 06:10:00" d="2021-07-14 06:25:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! II (1)</n>    <k>Man Person
Despite the Titans' protests Beast Boy becomes convinced that replacing his body parts with robotic limbs makes him more manly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 06:25:00" d="2021-07-14 06:35:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! II (2)</n>    <k>Pirates
When Aqualad and Raven fall for each other Beast Boy fights this match - with intensity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 06:35:00" d="2021-07-14 06:50:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! II (2)</n>    <k>I See You
Robin brings Starfire on a fake stakeout in an attempt to get a kiss while Cyborg and Beast Boy hold their own stakeout to discover Raven's dark secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 06:50:00" d="2021-07-14 07:00:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (25)</n>    <k>The Upside of Hunger
Owen has a mishap while baking an upside-down cake and is transported to an upside-down world where he is forced tooutwit himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 07:00:00" d="2021-07-14 07:15:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (26)</n>    <k>Fire in the Hole
Duncan cooks up a nuclear hot sauce to mess with Chef, but accidentally summons Terry Spice, King of the Underworld!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 07:15:00" d="2021-07-14 07:25:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (81)</n>    <k>Bakugan Battle Circus
Shun and Dan head to the Bakugan circus for a little fun, but the fun is interrupted when the star Bakugan are too exhausted to perform</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 07:25:00" d="2021-07-14 07:40:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (82)</n>    <k>Ebony Manor
Lightning reunites with an old frenemy – Ebony. This time the kitty queen of the streets has a new home and is living a life of luxury with her new master</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 07:40:00" d="2021-07-14 07:50:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (38)</n>    <k>The Heart
When Mr Robinson accidentally lets slip how little he cares for Gumball and Darwin, they react by giving him the cold shoulder. Surprisingly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 07:50:00" d="2021-07-14 08:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (39)</n>    <k>The Ghouls
It's Halloween in Elmore. As the kids go trick or treating we see what everyone in town is up to. The ghosts and ghouls are finding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 08:00:00" d="2021-07-14 08:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (40)</n>    <k>The BFFS
Gumball's old BFF, Fuzzy, turns up on his doorstep. Darwin struggles to accept that there was someone before him and fails to contain his jealousy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 08:20:00" d="2021-07-14 08:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (41)</n>    <k>The Agent
Gumball and Darwin's clothes go missing after a swimming lesson, and Gumball is forced to wear a tuxedo from the lost and found office</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 08:30:00" d="2021-07-14 08:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (42)</n>    <k>81% The Decisions
When everything goes wrong in Darwin's life, he begins to suspect that Gumball's bad influence might be to blame. Darwin decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 08:40:00" d="2021-07-14 09:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (43)</n>    <k>The Web
Gumball and Darwin realize that the adult residents of Elmore are dangerously naive when it comes to being safe online</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 09:00:00" d="2021-07-14 09:25:00"><n u="The Looney Tunes Show">The Looney Tunes Show II (1)</n>    <k>73% Bobcats On Three!
Daffy coaches Gossamer's water polo team despite having no experience or discernible skill for the job. Meanwhile, Bugs becomes addicted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 09:25:00" d="2021-07-14 09:50:00"><n u="The Looney Tunes Show">The Looney Tunes Show II (3)</n>    <k>73% Itsy Bitsy Gopher
When one of the Gophers is reported missing, Daffy and Lola take the case to look for him. Meanwhile, Bugs nearly destroys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 09:50:00" d="2021-07-14 10:10:00"><n u="The Looney Tunes Show">The Looney Tunes Show II (4)</n>    <k>73% Rebel Without a Glove
When Bugs loses his gloves, he also loses part of his identity, and the motorcycle gloves he gets as a temporary replacement prompt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 10:10:00" d="2021-07-14 10:25:00"><n u="Mighty Magiswords">Mighty Magiswords III (12)</n>    <k>52% Do We Decimal System?
The Warriors seek a secret book in the Library of Shhh! and their best friend from warrior school Witchy Simone follows them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 10:25:00" d="2021-07-14 10:35:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (2)</n>    <k>54% Chicken in the Cradle
Beast Boy neglects his responsibilities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 10:35:00" d="2021-07-14 10:50:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (5)</n>    <k>54% Tower Renovation
The Titans go house hunting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 10:50:00" d="2021-07-14 11:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (6)</n>    <k>Quantum Fun
Robin takes the other Titans on a trip through the dizzying world of quantum physics</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 11:00:00" d="2021-07-14 11:20:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (7)</n>    <k>The Fight
Robin tries to teach the other Titans about real estate but they're only interested in finding a villain to fight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 11:20:00" d="2021-07-14 11:30:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (8)</n>    <k>Genie President
Robin hatches a plan to get rich off pennies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 11:30:00" d="2021-07-14 11:45:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (9)</n>    <k>Little Elvis
The Titans team up with Shazam to defeat Mr. Mind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 11:45:00" d="2021-07-14 11:55:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (10)</n>    <k>The Groover
Robin takes the Titans on an educational trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 11:55:00" d="2021-07-14 12:10:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (11)</n>    <k>The Power of Shrimps
Aqualad uses shrimps and prime rib to win back Raven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 12:10:00" d="2021-07-14 12:20:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (12)</n>    <k>My Name is Jose
The Titans have Raven give them new super powers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 12:20:00" d="2021-07-14 12:40:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (13)</n>    <k>54% The Real Orangins!
Robin tries again to tell the real origin story of the Teen Titans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 12:40:00" d="2021-07-14 12:50:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (1)</n>    <k>Robo Teacher
When a substitute teacher fills in for Chef, Duncan thinks it's going to be the best day ever. He's wrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 12:50:00" d="2021-07-14 13:10:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (2)</n>    <k>Glove Glove Me Do
Owen's newly found gloves make him great at everything. But this greatness comes at a high price</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 13:10:00" d="2021-07-14 13:20:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (3)</n>    <k>Bowling for Ballers
Axel and the team must intervene when Zoe's not-so-friendly bowling competition with Cleo LeBall gets interrupted by Madcap Porcupunk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 13:20:00" d="2021-07-14 13:35:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (4)</n>    <k>Knockout
Axel and the team juggle not waking Uncle Andrew from his nap and stopping Orangutank from stealing Andrew's latest invention: the Knockout Box!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 13:35:00" d="2021-07-14 13:50:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (15)</n>    <k>The Comic
Gumball is the star of his own comic but struggles to match up to his heroic alter-ego</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 13:50:00" d="2021-07-14 14:05:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (16)</n>    <k>The Romantic
After Gumball convinces himself that Penny doesn't love him as much as she used to, he decides to put together a romantic quest to remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 14:05:00" d="2021-07-14 14:15:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (17)</n>    <k>The Uploads
Gumball and Darwin try to tear themselves away from the internet but end up falling down the Elmore Stream-hole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 14:15:00" d="2021-07-14 14:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (18)</n>    <k>81% The Wicked
After being framed for feeding coffee to the squirrels in the park, Gumball proclaims that Mrs Robinson is pure evil. Darwin tells</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 14:30:00" d="2021-07-14 14:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (19)</n>    <k>81% The Origins
When Mom and Dad struggle to keep hyperactive toddler-aged Gumball from trashing the house and exhausting them they decide to buy him a pet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 14:40:00" d="2021-07-14 14:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (20)</n>    <k>81% The Origins Part Two
Via the sewers Darwin finds himself flushed out to sea. He is terrified but determined to make his way back to the Wattersons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 14:55:00" d="2021-07-14 15:05:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (1)</n>    <k>Folk Art Foes
When Vic accidently unleashes the lord of mischief from an ancient relic, V and V have to work together to trap it back inside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 15:05:00" d="2021-07-14 15:25:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (2)</n>    <k>Dead Ringer
When Vic doesn't pick Val for his soccer team, Val vows to win with his own squad. But when his team doesn't match up, he resorts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 15:25:00" d="2021-07-14 15:35:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (51)</n>    <k>The Overbite
Raven teaches the other Titans how to dance properly but soon they are captured by the Dance Demon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 15:35:00" d="2021-07-14 15:55:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! III (52)</n>    <k>The Cape
The Titans reminisce about a surprise party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 15:55:00" d="2021-07-14 16:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (1)</n>    <k>54% Shrimps and Prime Rib
The Titans try to remember how to be superheroes in order to stop The Brain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 16:00:00" d="2021-07-14 16:20:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (2)</n>    <k>54% Halloween v Christmas
When Santa tries to take over Halloween it's up to the Titans and a few ghouls to stop him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 16:20:00" d="2021-07-14 16:30:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (1)</n>    <k>Robo Teacher
When a substitute teacher fills in for Chef, Duncan thinks it's going to be the best day ever. He's wrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 16:30:00" d="2021-07-14 16:40:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (2)</n>    <k>Glove Glove Me Do
Owen's newly found gloves make him great at everything. But this greatness comes at a high price</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 16:40:00" d="2021-07-14 16:55:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (26)</n>    <k>Snow Way Out
Owen wants everyone to love his new snowsuit and envy him, but it's just not working out that way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 16:55:00" d="2021-07-14 17:05:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek II (27)</n>    <k>72% Crisis At Elder…
Tragedy strikes the Creek when the Elders get trapped under Elder Rock, and it's up to Craig, Kelsey and JP to rescue them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 17:05:00" d="2021-07-14 17:25:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek II (28)</n>    <k>Kelsey The Worthy
When Kelsey demolishes a wall at Craig's house, her father takes away her sword. So she enlists Craig and JP to help prove to her father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 17:25:00" d="2021-07-14 17:35:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (20)</n>    <k>It Grows
As everyone celebrates Valentino for growing his first facial hair, a jealous Vic resorts to magical methods to grow a mustache and compete for attention</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 17:35:00" d="2021-07-14 17:55:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (21)</n>    <k>A New Don
When Vic &amp; Val discover that Don isn't really himself, it's up to them to use his kooky codex of conspiracies to save him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 17:55:00" d="2021-07-14 18:50:00"><n>Tom and Jerry Meet Sherlock Holmes</n>    <k>Fun is elementary when everyone's favorite cat-and-mouse cutups try to outsleuth the great detective Sherlock Holmes! With jewel heists around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 18:50:00" d="2021-07-14 19:10:00"><n>Lego DC Super Hero Girls: Galactic Wonder</n>    <k>Wonder Woman has won student of the month at Super Hero High again! As a special surprise Principal Waller has flown in Wonder Woman’s mother, Queen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 19:10:00" d="2021-07-14 19:30:00"><n u="DC Super Hero Girls">DC Super Hero Girls I (34)</n>    <k>#CrashCourse
When a high-speed chase breaks out during her driver's test, Diana Prince's desire to fight evil clashes with her desire to undergo a World</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 19:30:00" d="2021-07-14 19:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (12)</n>    <k>The Dream
Darwin kisses Penny in one of Gumball's dreams and gets mad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 19:40:00" d="2021-07-14 20:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (12)</n>    <k>The Sidekick
Gumball and Darwin try to get a game back from Tobias but Darwin starts to feel like a sidekick to Gumball and refuses to follow his orders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 20:00:00" d="2021-07-14 20:10:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (3)</n>    <k>Bowling for Ballers
Axel and the team must intervene when Zoe's not-so-friendly bowling competition with Cleo LeBall gets interrupted by Madcap Porcupunk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 20:10:00" d="2021-07-14 20:30:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (4)</n>    <k>Knockout
Axel and the team juggle not waking Uncle Andrew from his nap and stopping Orangutank from stealing Andrew's latest invention: the Knockout Box!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 20:30:00" d="2021-07-14 20:40:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (83)</n>    <k>Everett's Trap
Shun and Masato head to Tokyo’s Battle Island to discuss plans for hosting public Bakugan battles. Upon landing, they quickly learn it’s a set up! The two are now stranded and face with heaps of brawlers, who are all looking to bring them down!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 20:40:00" d="2021-07-14 21:00:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (84)</n>    <k>Kazami vs. Mc Q
Shun and Masato manage to fend off a horde of brawlers on Battle Island, but they quickly learn that was only a diversion- One of Kazami’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 21:00:00" d="2021-07-14 21:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (20)</n>    <k>60% Cupcake War
A new hipster cupcake shop opens across the street from Cathy’s siphoning off all the customers. Angelo and friends come up with strategies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 21:10:00" d="2021-07-14 21:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (21)</n>    <k>Snow And Tell
Angelo searches for the ultimate object to bring to show and tell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 21:25:00" d="2021-07-14 21:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (22)</n>    <k>Photobomb
Angelo’s photo bombs make him a big hit on the internet and he is loving his newfound popularity. Until Butterfingers starts getting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 21:35:00" d="2021-07-14 21:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (23)</n>    <k>Not Gym Class
The equipment in Coach Zonka’s gym class is deemed a safety hazard so gym class is canceled permanently. Angelo attempts to rally the school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 21:55:00" d="2021-07-14 22:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (25)</n>    <k>60% Van Dunk's Mojo
Everyone’s favorite skater Ollie Van Dunk crashes out in a big contest loses his mojo and quits skating. Angelo and friends try to raise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 22:05:00" d="2021-07-14 22:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (26)</n>    <k>60% Das Fence
When Angelo gets stuck with the chore of painting Geezer’s old broken down fence he channels his inner Tom Sawyer and manages to convince</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 22:25:00" d="2021-07-14 22:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (27)</n>    <k>60% The World According To Angelo
Angelo and friends make a TV show pilot called “Angelo Rules” with Lola producing Sherwood directing Angelo writing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 22:35:00" d="2021-07-14 22:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (28)</n>    <k>In The Game
After Mom cuts off Angelo’s videogame time Angelo attempts to change her mind. He sets out to prove to her that gaming is an important</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 22:50:00" d="2021-07-14 23:00:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (25)</n>    <k>Bringing Up Baby
Zoe leaves Axel in charge of the school project - watching over an infant simulator doll - but when MadCap brings the</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 23:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:20:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (26)</n>    <k>Spies Like Us
Uncle Andrew warns Axel that his vintage Agent Danger action figure is off-limits only to have the toy escape on its own! Axel and the team must return Danger to its rightful place before Uncle Andrew finds out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 23:20:00" d="2021-07-14 23:30:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (27)</n>    <k>Iced Out
Madcap's latest creation, the Ice Crusher, puts the whole city in a deep freeze forcing Axel and the team to face him in a game of high-stakes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 23:30:00" d="2021-07-14 23:45:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (28)</n>    <k>Stretched Too Thin
After a new combo-move leaves Masko permanently limp Axel and the team must help the fallen luchador get his stretch back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-14 23:45:00" d="2021-07-15 00:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (19)</n>    <k>The Copycats
Gumball and Darwin are confused when they meet Kiki and Quack, a pair of siblings that copy everything they do and say</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 00:00:00" d="2021-07-15 00:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (20)</n>    <k>81% The Catfish
When Gumball and Darwin realise Grandpa Louie has no friends on Elmore Plus, they feel bad. So they create one - called Muriel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 00:10:00" d="2021-07-15 00:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (21)</n>    <k>81% The Cycle
Gumball, Darwin and Anais discover that Mr Wilson has been picking on their dad for most of his life: ever since he humiliated Richard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 00:25:00" d="2021-07-15 00:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (22)</n>    <k>81% The Stars
When Dad gives Larry's Hairdressers a bad review for saying he's bald, he gets offered a free haircut. This inspires Gumball and Darwin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 00:35:00" d="2021-07-15 00:50:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (23)</n>    <k>The Box
The Wattersons receive an unmarked package in the mail. To distract themselves from the urge to open it, they all take turns to imagine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 00:50:00" d="2021-07-15 01:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (24)</n>    <k>The Matchmaker
Darwin likes a girl in his class so Gumball decides it’s time to play cupid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 01:00:00" d="2021-07-15 01:15:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (25)</n>    <k>The Grades
Miss Simian discovers a failed test from Gumball's past that brings down his grade point average. This means he has to retake kindergarten</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 01:15:00" d="2021-07-15 01:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (7)</n>    <k>60% The Balance Of Nature
Angelo makes Tracy cry and feels terrible about it. He declares a truce. Problem is… their growing friendship throws off the balance of nature!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 01:25:00" d="2021-07-15 01:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (8)</n>    <k>60% Cat Burglar
Joe Mama has been stealing stuff from around town and storing it under Angelo’s bed. Angelo and friends embark on a reverse scavenger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 01:40:00" d="2021-07-15 01:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (9)</n>    <k>Here Comes The Science
Angelo and Lola are stuck with Manetti as a science project partner. The only way to complete the project is turn Manetti into the science project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 01:50:00" d="2021-07-15 02:00:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (10)</n>    <k>60% The Arm
Tracy claims Angelo broke her arm. Angelo’s punishment—become Tracy’s slave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 02:00:00" d="2021-07-15 02:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (11)</n>    <k>60% Catnapped
Angelo discovers Cathy cat and Joe Mama have been accidentally switched at the Vet. And no one believes Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 02:10:00" d="2021-07-15 02:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (12)</n>    <k>60% Pen Pal
Angelo creates a fake Guatemalan pen pal so he doesn’t fail Mr. Foot’s class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 02:20:00" d="2021-07-15 02:30:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (13)</n>    <k>60% Employee Of The Month
Angelo becomes an intern at Adventureparkland. But his dream job isn’t all it’s cracked up to be because he has to actually… work!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 02:30:00" d="2021-07-15 02:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (14)</n>    <k>60% Bobbleheads Are Gonna Roll
Miss Perla turns detention time into art therapy where Angelo makes cool bobble-head sculptures which become</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 02:40:00" d="2021-07-15 02:55:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players II (24)</n>    <k>The Toy Knight returns!
Axel is sick of being the nice, enthusiastic little boy that everyone likes. He dreams of being an unsung hero, cold and lonesome</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 02:55:00" d="2021-07-15 03:05:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (3)</n>    <k>Bowling for Ballers
Axel and the team must intervene when Zoe's not-so-friendly bowling competition with Cleo LeBall gets interrupted by Madcap Porcupunk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 03:05:00" d="2021-07-15 03:15:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players II (25)</n>    <k>Big Mad Part 1
While Axel dreams of being bigger so people take him seriously, Madcap designs a giant body for himself that gives him immeasurable strength</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 03:15:00" d="2021-07-15 03:25:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players II (26)</n>    <k>Big Mad Part 2
Action Axel will try everything to defeat the now giant and super powerful Madcap. What if he asked for Uncle Andre's help?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 03:25:00" d="2021-07-15 03:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (3)</n>    <k>81% The Crew
When Gumball and Darwin decide it's time they join a crew, they agree that the coolest posse in Elmore is the senior citizens. They do everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 03:35:00" d="2021-07-15 03:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (4)</n>    <k>81% The Others
When Anais reveals she's in the grade above them at school, Gumball's and Darwin's eyes are suddenly opened to a whole new world of other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 03:45:00" d="2021-07-15 03:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (5)</n>    <k>81% The Signature
Dad discovers that Granny Jojo and Louie are planning to get married and move to Florida. To stop this happening he adopts Louie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 03:55:00" d="2021-07-15 04:05:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (6)</n>    <k>The Gift
After they receive an extravagant invitation to Masami's birthday party, Gumball and Darwin are anxious to find just the right gift for her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 04:05:00" d="2021-07-15 04:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (7)</n>    <k>The Apprentice
Gumball decides that the best way to show Mr Fitzgerald that he's good enough for Penny, is to become his apprentice for the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 04:20:00" d="2021-07-15 04:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (8)</n>    <k>The Check
Gumball, Darwin and Anais are delighted when Grandpa Louie gives them a check for $5,000. They immediately start fantasising over what to spend it on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 04:30:00" d="2021-07-15 04:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (9)</n>    <k>The Pest
When they find Anais training herself for a brutal showdown Gumball and Darwin realise that their sister is being pestered at school by an annoying kid: Billy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 04:40:00" d="2021-07-15 04:50:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (10)</n>    <k>The Hug
When Darwin taunts Gumball about how predictable he is Gumball tries to prove that he can still surprise his buddy. He thinks that greeting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2021-07-15 04:50:00" d="2021-07-15 05:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (11)</n>    <k>The Sale
Gumball and Darwin are devastated to learn that Mr Robinson - their favourite person in the world - is selling his house and leaving town</k>  </p>
</a>
