<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="109" t="2020-05-12 04:39:58"><p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 05:15:00" d="2020-05-19 05:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Richard discovers that going into a bank whilst wearing a motorcycle helmet can land you in a lot of trouble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 05:25:00" d="2020-05-19 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When Leslie's petals begin falling off he feels like his good looks are fading, Gumball and Darwin use everything they know about style and beauty to try and help him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 05:35:00" d="2020-05-19 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The Wattersons fear the worst when they are summoned to a Town Hall meeting, but are surprised when they're offered a new house. Until they discover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 05:45:00" d="2020-05-19 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% No matter what Gumball does, Carmen thinks she knows better. Gumball attempts to gain the moral high ground but fails. The only option left is to bring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 06:00:00" d="2020-05-19 06:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Kevin 11 gives Xingo a power up, setting him loose to wreak havoc on other TV shows, and it is up to Ben to stop them both</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 06:10:00" d="2020-05-19 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Team Tennyson stops in at a fringe family reunion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 06:25:00" d="2020-05-19 06:35:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When Rufus and Reg come to swindle the town, Sheriff Mao Mao teaches them a lesson in justice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 06:35:00" d="2020-05-19 06:50:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>The gang decide to compete in the annual Thumb War competition, but a surprise forces Mao Mao to deal with the unthinkable. losing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 06:50:00" d="2020-05-19 07:01:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>In an attempt to make Karen feel better about a pimple, Zee recounts her embarrassing transition into magichood, and the rift it created between her and her father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 07:01:00" d="2020-05-19 07:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>Having just moved to the boring Metropolis suburbs Batgirl is thrilled when she intercepts a call from Batman asking for help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 07:15:00" d="2020-05-19 07:25:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>Craig Kelsey and JP become smugglers to sneak candy to kids in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 07:25:00" d="2020-05-19 07:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>When Craig can't go to the Creek he and his mom decide to build the biggest blanket fort in the world!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 07:45:00" d="2020-05-19 07:55:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans are determined to find out what happened to the missing 2'oclock hour during Daylight Saving Time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 07:55:00" d="2020-05-19 08:04:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% It's St. Patrick's Day and after wishing to become a leprechaun Beast Boy becomes obsessed with gold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 08:04:00" d="2020-05-19 08:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin uses his skills as a master detective</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 08:15:00" d="2020-05-19 08:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans go to an amusement park to see LeBron James but instead help solve a mystery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 08:25:00" d="2020-05-19 08:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% It's Valentine's Day and Cyborg goes to great lengths to make it special for his girlfriend Jinx</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 08:34:00" d="2020-05-19 08:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% When the Titans get trapped in a giant bottle in their living room they pass the time by reminiscing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 08:50:00" d="2020-05-19 09:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>A storm rolls in while the Bears are separated. Grizz looks after the Poppy Rangers. Panda is stuck with Charlie in his car. Chloe and Ice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 09:00:00" d="2020-05-19 09:10:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>Charlie meets a creature just like him named Ralph</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 09:10:00" d="2020-05-19 09:25:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>Charlie meets a creature just like him named Ralph</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 09:25:00" d="2020-05-19 09:35:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% Philomena Dusk from AAAnimus Corp. hires Magnus and gives him a control implant to bolster the power of his Bakugan to defeat Dan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 09:35:00" d="2020-05-19 09:50:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% A cryptic call leads the AO in search of a missing Bakugan but they soon realize the call was</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 09:50:00" d="2020-05-19 10:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% A mysterious package shows up at the Watterson’s house and they do their best to avoid opening it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 10:00:00" d="2020-05-19 10:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Darwin likes a girl in his class so Gumball decides it’s time to play cupid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 10:20:00" d="2020-05-19 10:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Unikitty finds an old, beatup recliner on the curb, but sees its inner beauty and brings it home to introduce to the gang!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 10:30:00" d="2020-05-19 10:50:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Puppycorn wants to impress his skater friends with his sweet skills, except he has none</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 10:50:00" d="2020-05-19 10:58:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin surprises the Titans with a trip to the opera but they soon fall asleep and all dream about starring in their own operas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 10:58:00" d="2020-05-19 11:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans are outraged when their favorite cartoon is rebooted so they come up with a plan to get this new show off the air</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 11:15:00" d="2020-05-19 11:25:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Panthro is getting a little fed up with having to fix things around the Cats' Lair constantly which is unfortunate because the ThunderCats are about to be attacked</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 11:25:00" d="2020-05-19 11:40:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O is reminded that he needs to plug the Sword of Omens into the Cats' Lair each night or else the base will run out of power. That's fine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 11:40:00" d="2020-05-19 11:50:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>After getting rejected by a photography club, Val tries to get a picture of the legendary Chupacabra in order to prove himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 11:50:00" d="2020-05-19 12:10:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>After faking an injury to get out of work, Vic gains sympathy from everyone while unknowingly attracting attention from a dangerous mythical creature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 12:10:00" d="2020-05-19 12:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Sarah, the new kid in school, is Gumball and Darwin's number one, slightly obsessive, fan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 12:20:00" d="2020-05-19 12:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The new coach at Elmore High stands up to Jamie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 12:40:00" d="2020-05-19 12:51:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Darwin is sent away to a government institute for geniuses. Yes. Really</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 12:51:00" d="2020-05-19 13:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The secret behind Anton's immortality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 13:10:00" d="2020-05-19 13:21:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>Jessica Cruz is convinced she can find the purr-fect forever home for Dexter, a cat who has been deemed unadoptable because he’s basically the worst cat in the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 13:21:00" d="2020-05-19 13:35:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>Diana Prince is absolutely crushing it in every single aspect of life as a student at Metropolis High… until someone shows up who threatens to throw</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 13:35:00" d="2020-05-19 13:45:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>As Max attempts to get Ben and Gwen to the Four Corners Monument before sunset, an ominous fog bank engulfs the roadway</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 13:45:00" d="2020-05-19 14:05:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>After Ben gets too much publicity for his alien antics in Fort Knox a jealous Gwen feels unappreciated but she soon must prove she's a worthy member of Team Tennyson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 14:05:00" d="2020-05-19 14:15:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>After a lull in alien antics a restless Ben suggests to Max and Gwen that he might be a better hero if he went solo. Ben soon finds out he must rethink his strategy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 14:15:00" d="2020-05-19 14:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>The Weatherheads set their sights on Winter Wonderland as their next target and Ben must become one with his emotion if he is to save the town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 14:30:00" d="2020-05-19 14:40:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>When Ben and Max get into an argument, Ben goes Heatblast to blow off steam against Max's wishes; but Dr. Animo spots him and subsequently turns Max into a chicken</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 14:40:00" d="2020-05-19 14:55:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>After Ben stumbles upon a video of Cannonbolt ripping up a computer lab on the internet, Team Tennyson must race to State U where Ben discovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 14:55:00" d="2020-05-19 15:05:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When Mao Mao discovers that he is not as popular as Badgerclops and Adorabat, they decide to reinvent him as a kinder, cuddlier hero</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 15:05:00" d="2020-05-19 15:25:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When Mao Mao underestimates enemy and friend alike, it almost costs him the entire kingdom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 15:25:00" d="2020-05-19 15:37:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans are at Super Hero Summer Camp for the week and they may need to add another teammate to win the big canoe race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 15:37:00" d="2020-05-19 15:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% In order to quickly get through their chores and karate lessons the Titans learn how to montage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 15:50:00" d="2020-05-19 16:01:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Third Earth is being overrun by super tough, super buff Warrior Maidens and it looks like the ThunderCats are next on their hit list!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 16:01:00" d="2020-05-19 16:20:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O wants to prove to the ThunderKittens that he’s not just some boring old adult like Tygra even if it means ignoring his instincts and messing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 16:20:00" d="2020-05-19 16:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball is embarrassed when Mum comes to school to spend some “quality time”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 16:31:00" d="2020-05-19 16:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball’s magic tinfoil helmet threatens to tear the Watterson family apart!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 16:50:00" d="2020-05-19 17:01:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Anais is convinced that Gumball is being bullied by Tina Rex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 17:01:00" d="2020-05-19 17:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are convinced that the world will end in 24 hours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 17:20:00" d="2020-05-19 17:30:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>JP invites his friends over for a sleepover but it happens to be on the night of a huge game of Flashlight Tag in the Creek!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 17:30:00" d="2020-05-19 17:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>A spat between the Elders of the Creek leaves an opening in their tabletop role playing game so Kelsey joins the campaign!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 17:45:00" d="2020-05-19 17:55:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Richard's prepared one of the tastiest desserts ever, but he's locked it up tight until the friends have their boring dinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 17:55:00" d="2020-05-19 18:15:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>You're watching the Unikingdom News Show Super Good Morning Time Program Action Information Show, a variety news program put on (badly) by Unikitty and the gang!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 18:15:00" d="2020-05-19 18:27:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans are at Super Hero Summer Camp for the week and they may need to add another teammate to win the big canoe race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 18:27:00" d="2020-05-19 18:36:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% After being left alone at home Cyborg and Starfire booby trap the tower for safety</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 18:36:00" d="2020-05-19 18:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Starfire wins a goldfish at the carnival and vows to keep it alive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 18:50:00" d="2020-05-19 18:58:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% When Beast Boy gets a stack of cash from the Tooth Fairy against Raven's advice the other Titans start knocking out their own teeth to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 18:58:00" d="2020-05-19 19:07:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% A giant cocoon mysteriously appears in the Titans' living room and no one can find Beast Boy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 19:07:00" d="2020-05-19 19:30:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Tired of Robin's bland cooking the other Titans try their hand at spicing up their food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 19:30:00" d="2020-05-19 19:41:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Third Earth is being overrun by super tough, super buff Warrior Maidens and it looks like the ThunderCats are next on their hit list!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 19:41:00" d="2020-05-19 20:00:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O wants to prove to the ThunderKittens that he’s not just some boring old adult like Tygra even if it means ignoring his instincts and messing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 20:00:00" d="2020-05-19 20:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>After a series of reoccurring nightmares affect his sleep, Ben refuses to open up to Max and Gwen about what's bothering him. But they realize Zombozo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 20:10:00" d="2020-05-19 20:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Kevin 11 gives Xingo a power up, setting him loose to wreak havoc on other TV shows, and it is up to Ben to stop them both</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 20:30:00" d="2020-05-19 20:40:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% Philomena Dusk from AAAnimus Corp. hires Magnus and gives him a control implant to bolster the power of his Bakugan to defeat Dan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 20:40:00" d="2020-05-19 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% A cryptic call leads the AO in search of a missing Bakugan but they soon realize the call was</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 21:00:00" d="2020-05-19 21:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% To convince his parents to buy him a phone Angelo must turn his text addicted sister into a smart phone role model</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 21:10:00" d="2020-05-19 21:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% After Mr. Foot confiscates all electronics before class, Angelo and friends have to kick it old school and pass hand written notes to communicate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 21:25:00" d="2020-05-19 21:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Dreams do come true and Angelo and friends turn Angelo’s Dad into a rock star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 21:35:00" d="2020-05-19 21:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo attempts to join the secretive “school council” and learns-- never become a member of a group that will have you has a member</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 21:55:00" d="2020-05-19 22:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo gives us his tips and tricks for the most awesome sleepover ever. Until, the “prank call” trick ruins the night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 22:05:00" d="2020-05-19 22:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo stupidly boasts that his Dad used to be a stuntman. And the next day Dad has been invited to speak to Angelo’s class for career day. Gah!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 22:20:00" d="2020-05-19 22:30:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo makes Tracy cry and feels terrible about it. He declares a truce. Problem is… their growing friendship throws off the balance of nature!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 22:30:00" d="2020-05-19 22:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Joe Mama has been stealing stuff from around town and storing it under Angelo’s bed. Angelo and friends embark on a reverse scavenger hunt to figure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 22:45:00" d="2020-05-19 23:15:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% While Princess Harumi adjusts to life with the ninja, Lloyd and Jay search for answers about the Oni Masks, while Cole and Zane attempt to infiltrate the Sons of Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 23:15:00" d="2020-05-19 23:45:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% In order to join the Sons of Garmadon, Zane (aka Snake Jaguar) participates in a deadly motorcycle initiation race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 23:45:00" d="2020-05-19 23:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When everyone in the Watterson household wants to watch their favourite show at the same time, a massive fight breaks out over control of the television remote</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-19 23:55:00" d="2020-05-20 00:06:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball is determined to drive Penny away from Leslie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 00:06:00" d="2020-05-20 00:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball seeks justice when Banana Joe chews Darwin's pen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 00:20:00" d="2020-05-20 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When the Wattersons arrive at the mall for a day of shopping, they struggle to find a space in the parking lot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 00:30:00" d="2020-05-20 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin see an advert for the latest, cutting-edge Bobert operating system and excitedly talk Bobert into downloading it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 00:40:00" d="2020-05-20 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball is the star of his own comic, but struggles to match up to his heroic alter-ego</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 00:50:00" d="2020-05-20 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% After Gumball convinces himself that Penny doesn't love him as much as she used to, he decides to put together a romantic quest to remind her of their good times together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 01:00:00" d="2020-05-20 01:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% To convince his parents to buy him a phone Angelo must turn his text addicted sister into a smart phone role model</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 01:10:00" d="2020-05-20 01:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% After Mr. Foot confiscates all electronics before class, Angelo and friends have to kick it old school and pass hand written notes to communicate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 01:25:00" d="2020-05-20 01:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Dreams do come true and Angelo and friends turn Angelo’s Dad into a rock star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 01:35:00" d="2020-05-20 01:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo attempts to join the secretive “school council” and learns-- never become a member of a group that will have you has a member</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 01:45:00" d="2020-05-20 01:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo gives us his tips and tricks for the most awesome sleepover ever. Until, the “prank call” trick ruins the night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 01:55:00" d="2020-05-20 02:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo stupidly boasts that his Dad used to be a stuntman. And the next day Dad has been invited to speak to Angelo’s class for career day. Gah!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 02:05:00" d="2020-05-20 02:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo makes Tracy cry and feels terrible about it. He declares a truce. Problem is… their growing friendship throws off the balance of nature!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 02:15:00" d="2020-05-20 02:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Joe Mama has been stealing stuff from around town and storing it under Angelo’s bed. Angelo and friends embark on a reverse scavenger hunt to figure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 02:25:00" d="2020-05-20 02:35:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>The Warriors seek a secret book in the Library of Shhh! and their best friend from warrior school &quot;Witchy Simone&quot; follows them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 02:35:00" d="2020-05-20 02:55:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% While Princess Harumi adjusts to life with the ninja, Lloyd and Jay search for answers about the Oni Masks, while Cole and Zane attempt to infiltrate the Sons of Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 02:55:00" d="2020-05-20 03:15:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% In order to join the Sons of Garmadon, Zane (aka Snake Jaguar) participates in a deadly motorcycle initiation race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 03:15:00" d="2020-05-20 03:25:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>The Warriors go to Grup’s workplace and must resist the temptation to steal the sword that is Grup’s job to protect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 03:25:00" d="2020-05-20 03:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The Wattersons compete over who has the worst life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 03:35:00" d="2020-05-20 03:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When the kids find out that Mom's life hasn't panned out as she'd hoped, they start taking on her chores. However, they accidentally grab her bucket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 03:45:00" d="2020-05-20 03:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Richard decides that his work around the house is underappreciated by Nicole and goes on strike to prove it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 03:55:00" d="2020-05-20 04:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The Wattersons will do whatever it takes to get into the first screening of the latest Stellar Odyssey sequel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 04:05:00" d="2020-05-20 04:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Join the citizens of Elmore for a song and dance spectacular that will have you covering your ears with joy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 04:15:00" d="2020-05-20 04:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Darwin is delighted when they discover their old childhood toys, but soon realises that some things are best left in the past</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 04:30:00" d="2020-05-20 04:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Darwin ends up in detention with the Bomb Kid, who decides to make Darwin his new target. However, it backfires when Darwin ruins his life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 04:40:00" d="2020-05-20 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The kids convince Mr Corneille to become a cage fighter and set up a fight against a fearsome Russian fighter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 04:50:00" d="2020-05-20 05:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are jealous of a sparking a baby war</k>  </p>
</a>
