<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="113" t="2020-04-09 04:36:22"><p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 05:01:00" d="2020-04-16 05:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball is traumatised when accidentally kissed on the mouth by his Grandma JoJo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 05:15:00" d="2020-04-16 05:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are invited to a high school party, and have to bring a date!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 05:25:00" d="2020-04-16 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin unsuccessfully attempt to get a refund for their computer game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 05:35:00" d="2020-04-16 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Whilst Gumball and Darwin make fun of Mum and Dad for being old, their voices start to break</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 05:45:00" d="2020-04-16 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Sarah, the new kid in school, is Gumball and Darwin's number one, slightly obsessive, fan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 06:00:00" d="2020-04-16 06:11:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>While in Tokyo, Team Tennyson learn that Japan's hottest new restaurant is being run by the Bugg Brothers as a nefarious scheme to make loads of money</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 06:11:00" d="2020-04-16 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Team Tennyson watched a sumo wrestling match when the Twain Twins crash the event. Ben must think things through if he is to stop the polarizing family!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 06:25:00" d="2020-04-16 06:36:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>The gang struggles to get rid of the King when he joins them as their new deputy-for-a-day!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 06:36:00" d="2020-04-16 06:50:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Worried that his sword is a glorified consolation prize, Mao Mao sets out to prove the worth of his weapon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 06:50:00" d="2020-04-16 07:01:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>What begins as a simple vandalism investigation becomes an all-out turf war when the team encounters a powerful trio of Kryptonians bent on world domination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 07:01:00" d="2020-04-16 07:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>When Zee (Zatanna) asks Kara to look after her two magical bunnies, they quickly start to multiply, wreaking havoc all across Metropolis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 07:15:00" d="2020-04-16 07:25:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>The circle game wreaks havoc on the Creek so Craig forms a council to restore order</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 07:25:00" d="2020-04-16 07:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>Craig Kelsey and JP team up with an intergalactic hero named Sparkle Cadet hoping to save the Creek from negativity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 07:45:00" d="2020-04-16 07:55:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Beast Boy invites Tara to the Titan's Valentine's Day dance and she accepts in order to destroy all of the Titans and exact revenge on Beast Boy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 07:55:00" d="2020-04-16 08:05:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% BB avoids being &quot;the dumb one&quot; by making the rest of the Titans dumber, which leaves only Silkie to save the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 08:05:00" d="2020-04-16 08:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin goes undercover to destroy the Hive. ight after he enjoys some of their perks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 08:15:00" d="2020-04-16 08:24:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Raven teaches the other Titans how to dance properly but soon they are captured by the Dance Demon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 08:24:00" d="2020-04-16 08:33:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans reminisce about a surprise party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 08:33:00" d="2020-04-16 08:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans try to remember how to be superheroes in order to stop The Brain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 08:50:00" d="2020-04-16 09:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>Pet Shop tells the tale of where the Baby Bears once lived</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 09:00:00" d="2020-04-16 09:11:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>Chloe, a child prodigy, finds it difficult to connect with her much older classmates. The Bears take her under their wing and show her how to make great college friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 09:11:00" d="2020-04-16 09:25:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>When Grizz comes home with a live crab, he thinks it can become a pet for the brothers to share. However, the crab pinches Ice Bear's ear and won't let go…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 09:25:00" d="2020-04-16 09:35:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% The AO meet Benton Dusk discovering that their quiet little corner of the world is about to become much, much larger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 09:35:00" d="2020-04-16 09:50:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% Benton Dusk reveals that the AO have been indentified as persons of interest by power</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 09:50:00" d="2020-04-16 10:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans are excited to see the movie version of their favourite show &quot;Babies vs Dogs&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 10:00:00" d="2020-04-16 10:09:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Inspired by the &quot;Babies vs Dogs&quot; movie, the Titans decide to make a big Hollywood film of their own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 10:09:00" d="2020-04-16 10:19:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans go house hunting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 10:19:00" d="2020-04-16 10:29:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin takes the other Titans on a trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 10:29:00" d="2020-04-16 10:39:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin tries to teach the other Titans about real estate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 10:39:00" d="2020-04-16 10:48:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin hatches a plan to get rich off pennies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 10:48:00" d="2020-04-16 10:58:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans team up with Shazam to defeat Mr. Mind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 10:58:00" d="2020-04-16 11:07:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin takes the Titans on an educational trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 11:07:00" d="2020-04-16 11:40:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Aqualad uses shrimps and prime rib to win back Raven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 11:40:00" d="2020-04-16 11:50:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>Vic and Val use a magical flute to teleport</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 11:50:00" d="2020-04-16 12:10:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>After breaking Chata's plant, Vic and Val must accomplish the seemingly easy task of replacing it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 12:10:00" d="2020-04-16 12:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When Darwin asks for his advice on hats, Gumball suddenly can’t speak and offends Darwin. Darwin is convinced Gumball said he had a fat head</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 12:20:00" d="2020-04-16 12:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When she has no one to share her lunch with, Jamie realises she needs a sweetheart. Darwin's the only one who doesn’t flee immediately, so he and Jamie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 12:40:00" d="2020-04-16 12:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are reading Anais’ diary when they discover that her relationship with her new friend seems a bit one-sided</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 12:50:00" d="2020-04-16 13:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When Bobert finds he is infected with a virus called love.exe he asks Gumball and Darwin to give him a definition for the word ‘love’</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 13:10:00" d="2020-04-16 13:21:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>The girls must track down Katana a mysterious warrior who’s stealing the souls of Metropolis’s villains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 13:21:00" d="2020-04-16 13:35:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>When she stumbles across a villainous plot - and all the other heroes are indisposed - Bumblebee must rise to the occasion… despite being the smallest of the bunch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 13:35:00" d="2020-04-16 13:45:00"><n>Adventure Time - Elements</n>    <k>Jake and Finn are attacked by marauders from the crystal dimension</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 13:45:00" d="2020-04-16 14:05:00"><n>Adventure Time - Elements</n>    <k>Jake pretends to be a rainicorn in order to make Lady’s parents like him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 14:05:00" d="2020-04-16 14:15:00"><n>Adventure Time - Elements</n>    <k>Finn needs to find a princess willing to give up a lock of her hair</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 14:15:00" d="2020-04-16 14:30:00"><n>Adventure Time - Elements</n>    <k>Finn has to give a speech at Princess Bubblegum’s Science BBQ</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 14:30:00" d="2020-04-16 14:40:00"><n>Adventure Time - Elements</n>    <k>Finn and Jake go into Beemo to defeat an evil Big Boss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 14:40:00" d="2020-04-16 14:55:00"><n>Adventure Time - Elements</n>    <k>Finn and Jake must go inside Giant’s belly to help him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 14:55:00" d="2020-04-16 15:06:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>After struggling to keep up, Adorabat gets a cybernetic &quot;Mega-Mech.&quot; But can fancy new powers make up for experience?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 15:06:00" d="2020-04-16 15:25:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Feeling left out Adorabat wishes Mao Mao and Badgerclops would spend less time with each other and more time with her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 15:25:00" d="2020-04-16 15:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% When Cyborg and Starfire find a baby bird, it awakens their inner child</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 15:34:00" d="2020-04-16 15:55:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% After Young Justice easily takes out the HIVE while the other Titans make silly jokes Robin decides the team needs to get serious./ The Titans visit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 15:55:00" d="2020-04-16 16:04:00"><n>Total Dramarama</n>    <k>Duncan Leshawna and Jude all want corner pieces of Izzy's Birthday Cake… But are they prepared to go to any length to get one?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 16:04:00" d="2020-04-16 16:20:00"><n>Total Dramarama</n>    <k>Courtney refuses to share her valuable collectors item toy with her classmates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 16:20:00" d="2020-04-16 16:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The Wattersons will do whatever it takes to get into the first screening of the latest Stellar Odyssey sequel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 16:30:00" d="2020-04-16 16:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Join the citizens of Elmore for a song and dance spectacular that will have you covering your ears with joy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 16:50:00" d="2020-04-16 17:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball accidentally uploads a video of himself and wants it gone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 17:00:00" d="2020-04-16 17:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The Watterson kids come up with a fool-proof plan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 17:20:00" d="2020-04-16 17:30:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>Craig's phone gets stuck in the tallest tree in the creek!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 17:30:00" d="2020-04-16 17:50:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>JP leads his friends on a voyage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 17:50:00" d="2020-04-16 18:00:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>While searching for a hidden skate park, V and V happen upon a tribe of wild kids, who live in a society without rules or adults</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 18:00:00" d="2020-04-16 18:15:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>Victor &amp; Valentino gain a newfound respect for cleanliness after Chata's house traps them inside its labyrinth of ancient, magical walls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 18:15:00" d="2020-04-16 18:24:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Starfire's new pet is a horribly dangerous parasite, but Robin is the only one who is suspicious of the beast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 18:24:00" d="2020-04-16 18:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Beast Boy teaches Starfire how to lie and it backfires as her lies get more and more outrageous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 18:35:00" d="2020-04-16 18:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Raven eats a bad meatball that causes tentacles to spring from her teeth and devour the other Titans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 18:50:00" d="2020-04-16 19:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% When the gang breaks Robin's beloved staff, Robin is forced to find a replacement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 19:00:00" d="2020-04-16 19:09:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Beast Boy falls for Terra despite clear signs that she is more interested in destroying the Titans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 19:09:00" d="2020-04-16 19:30:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans revert to creative game-playing in order to have a chance at beating the undefeated supervillain dodgeball team</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 19:30:00" d="2020-04-16 19:41:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>After struggling to keep up, Adorabat gets a cybernetic &quot;Mega-Mech.&quot; But can fancy new powers make up for experience?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 19:41:00" d="2020-04-16 20:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Feeling left out Adorabat wishes Mao Mao and Badgerclops would spend less time with each other and more time with her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 20:00:00" d="2020-04-16 20:11:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben, Gwen and Grandpa Max arrive in Bismarck for its annual celebration of bee pollination, bringing them face-to-face with Queen Bee and a bold new scheme</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 20:11:00" d="2020-04-16 20:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Team Tennyson look to take in the sights of the Shoshone Falls but when they find Steam Smythe siphoning off the water, it is up to Ben, Grandpa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 20:30:00" d="2020-04-16 20:40:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% The AO meet Benton Dusk discovering that their quiet little corner of the world is about to become much, much larger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 20:40:00" d="2020-04-16 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% Benton Dusk reveals that the AO have been indentified as persons of interest by power</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 21:00:00" d="2020-04-16 21:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% Zane’s near demise at the hands of Mr. E forces the ninja to flee aboard the Bounty, where they discover a message Zane intercepted may reveal the hidden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 21:25:00" d="2020-04-16 21:55:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% As Lloyd and Harumi venture deep into Primeval’s Eye in search of the third Oni Mask, the ninja attempt to fix the Bounty and make a startling discovery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 21:55:00" d="2020-04-16 22:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and friends are stuck hanging out with Geezer’s Nephew -- a terrible, horrible, no good delinquent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 22:05:00" d="2020-04-16 22:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and friends attempt to raise Butterfingers flagging self-esteem by training him in the art of Angelo-fu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 22:20:00" d="2020-04-16 22:30:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo shares his tips and tricks for trading favors and then cashing them all in to create “a perfect day.”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 22:30:00" d="2020-04-16 22:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% When his family go on vacation Angelo sets all kinds of traps in his house for potential thieves. Problem is when they return home Angelo lost his guide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 22:45:00" d="2020-04-16 22:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and friends attempt to negotiate a deal for Peter and Cooper’s nonsensical home-made comic book with a famous comic book publisher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 22:55:00" d="2020-04-16 23:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo attempts to rack up the high score on an online business rating service to win free dinner at a fancy Japanese Steak House</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 23:15:00" d="2020-04-16 23:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% When Dad surprises the family with a brand new Electra smart home device everyone loves it at first, then Dad gets hooked and Angelo and Elena</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 23:25:00" d="2020-04-16 23:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% After failing an online “best friends” quiz Sherwood and Angelo drift apart. Angelo discovers the quiz was fake and tries to repair his relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 23:35:00" d="2020-04-16 23:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo discovers Cathy cat and Joe Mama have been accidentally switched at the Vet. And no one believes Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 23:45:00" d="2020-04-16 23:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball decides that the best way to prove to Mr. Fitzgerald that he's good enough for Penny is to become his apprentice for the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-16 23:55:00" d="2020-04-17 00:06:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball, Darwin and Anais are delighted when Grandpa Louie gives them a check for $5000. They immediately start fantasizing over what to spend it on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 00:06:00" d="2020-04-17 00:16:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When they find Anais training herself for a brutal showdown, Gumball and Darwin realise that their sister is being pestered at school by an annoying kid: Billy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 00:16:00" d="2020-04-17 00:20:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>The Warriors are treated to a banquet by the grateful Kotassians and Vambre accidentally eats their king</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 00:20:00" d="2020-04-17 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Rocky is trying to find love with the help of the latest dating app…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 00:30:00" d="2020-04-17 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin give Bobert specific instructions to ensure he acts in a safe and responsible manner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 00:40:00" d="2020-04-17 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Nicole is angry at Richard for forgetting her special day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 00:50:00" d="2020-04-17 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Channel 6 Elmore News has all the top hard-hitting local stories. Newscaster Kip Schlezinger is the man to bring you the latest news, even when there is nothing to report</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 01:00:00" d="2020-04-17 01:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and friends are stuck hanging out with Geezer’s Nephew -- a terrible, horrible, no good delinquent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 01:10:00" d="2020-04-17 01:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and friends attempt to raise Butterfingers flagging self-esteem by training him in the art of Angelo-fu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 01:25:00" d="2020-04-17 01:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo shares his tips and tricks for trading favors and then cashing them all in to create “a perfect day.”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 01:35:00" d="2020-04-17 01:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% When his family go on vacation Angelo sets all kinds of traps in his house for potential thieves. Problem is when they return home Angelo lost his guide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 01:45:00" d="2020-04-17 01:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and friends attempt to negotiate a deal for Peter and Cooper’s nonsensical home-made comic book with a famous comic book publisher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 01:55:00" d="2020-04-17 02:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo attempts to rack up the high score on an online business rating service to win free dinner at a fancy Japanese Steak House</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 02:05:00" d="2020-04-17 02:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% When Dad surprises the family with a brand new Electra smart home device everyone loves it at first, then Dad gets hooked and Angelo and Elena</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 02:15:00" d="2020-04-17 02:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% After failing an online “best friends” quiz Sherwood and Angelo drift apart. Angelo discovers the quiz was fake and tries to repair his relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 02:25:00" d="2020-04-17 02:35:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>Vambre and Prohyas are hired by Old Man Oldman to walk his new stray dog. The problem is: it's a stray dinosaur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 02:35:00" d="2020-04-17 02:55:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% Zane’s near demise at the hands of Mr. E forces the ninja to flee aboard the Bounty, where they discover a message Zane intercepted may reveal the hidden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 02:55:00" d="2020-04-17 03:15:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% As Lloyd and Harumi venture deep into Primeval’s Eye in search of the third Oni Mask, the ninja attempt to fix the Bounty and make a startling discovery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 03:15:00" d="2020-04-17 03:25:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>Vambre and Prohyas encounter the Keeper of the &quot;Mask Magi-Sword&quot; who challenges them to a contest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 03:25:00" d="2020-04-17 03:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball discovers that Bobert is planning to take over his identity and replace him!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 03:35:00" d="2020-04-17 03:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin barely survive a school picnic in the Forest of Doom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 03:45:00" d="2020-04-17 03:56:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball sets out to win his Dad back by winning a blindfolded “dumb” race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 03:56:00" d="2020-04-17 04:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball almost loses his mind trying to guess Darwin’s secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 04:05:00" d="2020-04-17 04:16:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are taught confusing lessons about honesty by the school councillor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 04:16:00" d="2020-04-17 04:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Darwin is sent away to a government institute for geniuses. Yes. Really</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 04:30:00" d="2020-04-17 04:41:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin’s wish comes true when they suddenly turn into men</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 04:41:00" d="2020-04-17 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball discovers the difference between a “date” and a “pet’s funeral”. he hard way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 04:50:00" d="2020-04-17 05:01:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When Gumball rejects “The Rejects Club”, the rejects wreak their revenge</k>  </p>
</a>
