<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="110" t="2020-05-15 05:00:54"><p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 05:00:00" d="2020-05-22 05:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Darwin asks Gumball to teach him how to skate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 05:15:00" d="2020-05-22 05:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin follow Nicole to the Rainbow Factory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 05:25:00" d="2020-05-22 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The kids find out Dad has been dressing as a woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 05:35:00" d="2020-05-22 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The boys manage to lose Polly in the blink of an eye</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 05:45:00" d="2020-05-22 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Nicole has decided it's time to throw out the family's refrigerator</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 06:00:00" d="2020-05-22 06:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>All Ben wants to do is stop Queen Bee from robbing a bank</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 06:10:00" d="2020-05-22 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Hex uses a miscommunication spell to drive a wedge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 06:25:00" d="2020-05-22 06:35:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Badgerclops gets huge to destroy a towering monster but when he refuses to shrink down the kingdom faces a new terror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 06:35:00" d="2020-05-22 06:50:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When the Sweetypies think the mythical Torbaclaun has come to Pure Heart Valley, Mao Mao tries to prove to them that it isn't real</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 06:50:00" d="2020-05-22 07:01:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>After an embarrassing incident ruins Barbara Gordon’s reputation, rather than owning it, she decides it’s easier to harness The Flash’s ability to travel back in time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 07:01:00" d="2020-05-22 07:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>Desperate to emerge from her father’s shadow, Zee Zatara performs for her own audience, but loses her cool when her act is dismissed as fakery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 07:15:00" d="2020-05-22 07:25:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>Craig dines at the restaurant where his older brother works and orders up a plate of REVENGE. and lots of breadsticks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 07:25:00" d="2020-05-22 07:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>A runaway from a summer camp ends up at the Stump but Craig suspects her story may not be what it seems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 07:45:00" d="2020-05-22 07:55:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The team goes on a series of epic quests in order to create the world's perfect sandwich</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 07:55:00" d="2020-05-22 08:05:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Beast Boy has to get a job at a pie shop to earn enough money to buy Cyborg a birthday gift, only his job interferes with being able to attend the actual party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 08:05:00" d="2020-05-22 08:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin is inadvertently the getaway driver for a bank robbery in the midst of his driver's ed exam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 08:15:00" d="2020-05-22 08:24:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans have Raven give them new super powers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 08:24:00" d="2020-05-22 08:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin tries to tell the origin story of the Teen Titans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 08:34:00" d="2020-05-22 08:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans want to be the scariest trick-or-treaters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 08:50:00" d="2020-05-22 09:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>The Bears win a tour of the infamous Googs corporate headquarters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 09:00:00" d="2020-05-22 09:10:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>While on a fishing trip, the Bears get attacked by a giant legendary fish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 09:10:00" d="2020-05-22 09:25:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>The Bears travel to the video game store</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 09:25:00" d="2020-05-22 09:35:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% The AO meet Benton Dusk discovering that their quiet little corner of the world is about to become much, much larger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 09:35:00" d="2020-05-22 09:50:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% Benton Dusk reveals that the AO have been indentified as persons of interest by power</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 09:50:00" d="2020-05-22 09:59:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The prize jewel on the Secret Joyful Burger menu is a mysterious burger, but to order it you need to know its name. And Larry refuses to tell the guys what it's called</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 09:59:00" d="2020-05-22 10:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When Gumball finds out that their 8-bit friend Ocho has an Italian plumber called Mario for an uncle, he assumes it’s ‘that’ Mario and says he’ll do anything to meet him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 10:20:00" d="2020-05-22 10:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Unikitty plans a parade to celebrate being unique!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 10:30:00" d="2020-05-22 10:50:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>There's a mishap in the lab causing tiny problems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 10:50:00" d="2020-05-22 10:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin tells the Titans to stop being reckless teens or the Creepy Catcher will get them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 10:59:00" d="2020-05-22 11:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans must find a way to keep all the Jump City residents from moving to Stockton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 11:15:00" d="2020-05-22 11:26:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Tygra's feeling unappreciated by the other ThunderCats so he starts hanging out with Mumm-Ra and cleaning his Black Pyramid?! Whaaaaaaat?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 11:26:00" d="2020-05-22 11:40:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Every time Mumm-Ra gets a hold of a magic artefact to restore his powers the ThunderCats just smash it and turn him into a dinky skeleton again. Until today that is!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 11:40:00" d="2020-05-22 11:50:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>After Vic loses a wrestling match, V&amp;V journey to the underworld to seek advice from their uncle, a famous wrestler named El Toro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 11:50:00" d="2020-05-22 12:10:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>When Chata lets Vic be the boss of the taco stand for the day Vic decides to fire Val, which has disastrous consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 12:10:00" d="2020-05-22 12:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball confronts Clayton about his fabled Seven Pressure Point Heart Exploding Technique, assuming it’s another one of his outlandish claims</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 12:20:00" d="2020-05-22 12:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball jaywalks and is pulled over by Donut Cop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 12:40:00" d="2020-05-22 12:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Darwin starts sneezing repeatedly and it seems he can't stop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 12:50:00" d="2020-05-22 13:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% It's Mother's Day, and Gumball and Darwin discover that Tobias and Banana Joe have both made a card for &quot;The Best Mum in the World&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 13:10:00" d="2020-05-22 13:21:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>When Supergirl is presumed dead after a battle with Livewire, Kara Danvers decides to reinvent herself with a new look, a new personality, and a new name. Power Girl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 13:21:00" d="2020-05-22 13:35:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>When Babs and Kara spar over whose dog is better at the Metropolis Dog Show, Ace the Bat-Hound and Krypto the Superdog must find a way to save the day themselves!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 13:35:00" d="2020-05-22 13:45:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben finds a rare Sumo Slammers card during a tour of historic Oldeville. But when Billy Billions comes to claim the same card, Ben has to battle Billy’s high-tech drones</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 13:45:00" d="2020-05-22 14:05:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>In a peaceful coastal town, Ben must not only face the archaic antagonist Steam Smythe and his latest creation, the Clocktopus, but also his deepest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 14:05:00" d="2020-05-22 14:14:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben and Gwen are transformed into babies by nanny-gone-nuts Nanny Nightmare who will stop at nothing to reshape the world in the image of her day-care</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 14:14:00" d="2020-05-22 14:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben must go alien to save the Hoover Dam from disaster but when tough guy hero Tim Buktu swoops in to &quot;help&quot; Ben must figure out if Tim is friend… or foe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 14:30:00" d="2020-05-22 14:40:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben, Gwen and Max go on a tour of the impervious Fort Knox when Dr. Animo sicks a hungry ani-mutate on the Fort</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 14:40:00" d="2020-05-22 14:55:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben and Gwen are excited to attend an Earth Day EDM concert in Portland until the show is hijacked by the sound-manipulating baddy Lord Decibel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 14:55:00" d="2020-05-22 15:05:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Badgerclops adopts an abandoned monster, but some things are better left in the wild</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 15:05:00" d="2020-05-22 15:25:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Mao Mao's legendary, gigantic and critical father visits his son at his new job as sheriff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 15:25:00" d="2020-05-22 15:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans put on a show but Robin warns that the performance must be boring or else they'll wake up the wolves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 15:34:00" d="2020-05-22 15:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% After the other Titans are turned into collectibles and disappear Robin must search yard sales and stores to find them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 15:50:00" d="2020-05-22 16:01:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Vultureman has got a brand new invention but there's one big problem: he stole the idea from Panthro! Oh, also Vultureman is using his invention to take over Third Earth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 16:01:00" d="2020-05-22 16:20:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Tygra takes Lion-O climbing up the peak of Hook Mountain to teach him a lesson about trust. But they get trapped by a snowstorm and take refuge in a creepy cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 16:20:00" d="2020-05-22 16:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Hotdog Kid discover why they're so awkward with each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 16:30:00" d="2020-05-22 16:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin try to find out the name of their neighbour, Antlers Guy, but accidentally blow his witness protection cover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 16:50:00" d="2020-05-22 17:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Pr Brown make a pact to tell each other's girlfriends about problems they have</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 17:00:00" d="2020-05-22 17:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Alan has lost faith in humanity and turned the world black and white. Gumball has to get over his hatred of Alan to bring the color back by singing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 17:20:00" d="2020-05-22 17:30:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>Craig and Stacks help Kelsey become a real author turning her story into a book!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 17:30:00" d="2020-05-22 17:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>Craig takes his cousin, Bryson, to the Creek, and accidentally starts a water balloon war</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 17:45:00" d="2020-05-22 17:55:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>When Unikitty has a little auto incident with Master Frown, he insists on taking it to court! Frown's thrilled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 17:55:00" d="2020-05-22 18:15:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Dr. Fox is proud to unveil her new ultimate combat machine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 18:15:00" d="2020-05-22 18:24:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans put on a show but Robin warns that the performance must be boring or else they'll wake up the wolves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 18:24:00" d="2020-05-22 18:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% It's Crime Season and Robin is determined to continue his streak of stopping 52 crimes every year</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 18:34:00" d="2020-05-22 18:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin's streak of stopping 52 crimes every year is in jeopardy when members of his team are poached by Kid Flash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 18:50:00" d="2020-05-22 18:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Brother Blood takes the Titans to trial for their recent destruction of Jump City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 18:59:00" d="2020-05-22 19:08:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% After the other Titans are injured Beast Boy donates his blood to save them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 19:08:00" d="2020-05-22 19:30:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans' Halloween party is interupted by the Hive Five robbing a candy factory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 19:30:00" d="2020-05-22 19:41:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Vultureman has got a brand new invention but there's one big problem: he stole the idea from Panthro! Oh, also Vultureman is using his invention to take over Third Earth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 19:41:00" d="2020-05-22 20:00:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Tygra takes Lion-O climbing up the peak of Hook Mountain to teach him a lesson about trust. But they get trapped by a snowstorm and take refuge in a creepy cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 20:00:00" d="2020-05-22 20:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben's jealousy has him convinced he has to out-do Kevin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 20:10:00" d="2020-05-22 20:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>All Ben wants to do is stop Queen Bee from robbing a bank</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 20:30:00" d="2020-05-22 20:40:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% The AO meet Benton Dusk discovering that their quiet little corner of the world is about to become much, much larger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 20:40:00" d="2020-05-22 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% Benton Dusk reveals that the AO have been indentified as persons of interest by power</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 21:00:00" d="2020-05-22 21:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Everyone’s favorite skater, Ollie Van Dunk, crashes out in a big contest, loses his mojo, and quits skating. Angelo and friends try to raise his spirits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 21:10:00" d="2020-05-22 21:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% When Angelo gets stuck with the chore of painting Geezer’s old broken down fence, he channels his inner Tom Sawyer and manages to convince everyone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 21:25:00" d="2020-05-22 21:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and friends make a TV show pilot called “Angelo Rules,” with Lola producing, Sherwood directing, Angelo writing, and Butterfingers playing Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 21:35:00" d="2020-05-22 21:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% After Mom cuts off Angelo’s videogame time Angelo attempts to change her mind. He sets out to prove to her that gaming is an important skillset</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 21:55:00" d="2020-05-22 22:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and friends are stuck hanging out with Geezer’s Nephew -- a terrible, horrible, no good delinquent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 22:05:00" d="2020-05-22 22:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and friends attempt to raise Butterfingers flagging self-esteem by training him in the art of Angelo-fu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 22:20:00" d="2020-05-22 22:30:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo shares his tips and tricks for trading favors and then cashing them all in to create “a perfect day.”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 22:30:00" d="2020-05-22 22:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% When his family go on vacation Angelo sets all kinds of traps in his house for potential thieves. Problem is when they return home Angelo lost his guide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 22:45:00" d="2020-05-22 23:15:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% Lord Garmadon returns and frees Harumi, who encourages him to “achieve his true potential” by conquering the one thing that has always stood in his way… his son, Lloyd</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 23:15:00" d="2020-05-22 23:45:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% The ninja race to save Lloyd, as a more powerful-than-ever Lord Garmadon creates an enormous Colossi to help him rule Ninjago and defeat the ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 23:45:00" d="2020-05-22 23:56:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Principal Brown tries to “fix” Gumball’s dysfunctional family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 23:56:00" d="2020-05-23 00:07:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin babysit Anais “responsibly”, whilst “irresponsibly” flooding the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 00:07:00" d="2020-05-23 00:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball goes to school in a dress and becomes the darling of Elmore High</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 00:20:00" d="2020-05-23 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are reading Anais’ diary when they discover that her relationship with her new friend seems a bit one-sided</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 00:30:00" d="2020-05-23 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When Bobert finds he is infected with a virus called love.exe he asks Gumball and Darwin to give him a definition for the word ‘love’</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 00:40:00" d="2020-05-23 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% At Halloween show and tell, the class isn’t buying Gumball’s story about Gargaroth The Devourer until Carrie fakes a terrifying haunting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 00:50:00" d="2020-05-23 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball is walking in the same direction as Hot Dog Guy, and with each step it becomes increasingly awkward</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 01:00:00" d="2020-05-23 01:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Everyone’s favorite skater, Ollie Van Dunk, crashes out in a big contest, loses his mojo, and quits skating. Angelo and friends try to raise his spirits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 01:10:00" d="2020-05-23 01:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% When Angelo gets stuck with the chore of painting Geezer’s old broken down fence, he channels his inner Tom Sawyer and manages to convince everyone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 01:25:00" d="2020-05-23 01:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and friends make a TV show pilot called “Angelo Rules,” with Lola producing, Sherwood directing, Angelo writing, and Butterfingers playing Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 01:35:00" d="2020-05-23 01:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% After Mom cuts off Angelo’s videogame time Angelo attempts to change her mind. He sets out to prove to her that gaming is an important skillset</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 01:45:00" d="2020-05-23 01:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and friends are stuck hanging out with Geezer’s Nephew -- a terrible, horrible, no good delinquent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 01:55:00" d="2020-05-23 02:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and friends attempt to raise Butterfingers flagging self-esteem by training him in the art of Angelo-fu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 02:05:00" d="2020-05-23 02:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo shares his tips and tricks for trading favors and then cashing them all in to create “a perfect day.”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 02:15:00" d="2020-05-23 02:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% When his family go on vacation Angelo sets all kinds of traps in his house for potential thieves. Problem is when they return home Angelo lost his guide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 02:25:00" d="2020-05-23 02:35:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 02:35:00" d="2020-05-23 02:55:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% Lord Garmadon returns and frees Harumi, who encourages him to “achieve his true potential” by conquering the one thing that has always stood in his way… his son, Lloyd</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 02:55:00" d="2020-05-23 03:15:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% The ninja race to save Lloyd, as a more powerful-than-ever Lord Garmadon creates an enormous Colossi to help him rule Ninjago and defeat the ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 03:15:00" d="2020-05-23 03:25:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>53% The Warriors are hired to &quot;vanquish&quot; a dragon, who turns out to be confoundingly sweet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 03:25:00" d="2020-05-23 03:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Mr. Robinson accidentally lets his feelings slip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 03:35:00" d="2020-05-23 03:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% It's Halloween in Elmore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 03:45:00" d="2020-05-23 03:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball's old BFF Fuzzy, turns up on his doorstep</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 03:55:00" d="2020-05-23 04:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin's clothes go missing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 04:05:00" d="2020-05-23 04:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When everything goes wrong in Darwin's life, he begins to suspect that Gumball's bad influence might be to blame</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 04:15:00" d="2020-05-23 04:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Darwin asks Gumball to teach him how to skate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 04:30:00" d="2020-05-23 04:41:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The students find their world turned upside down</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 04:41:00" d="2020-05-23 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin spice up their friendship by introducing a third best friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-23 04:50:00" d="2020-05-23 05:01:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball has to save Mr Robinson’s life during Elmore’s Senior Talent Show!</k>  </p>
</a>
