<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="110" t="2020-05-13 04:36:34"><p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 05:00:00" d="2020-05-20 05:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Tobias tries to be Gumball's best friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 05:15:00" d="2020-05-20 05:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin just want to veg out all day but end up having to save the rest of the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 05:25:00" d="2020-05-20 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The kids try to help Dad bond with Frankie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 05:35:00" d="2020-05-20 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Hotdog Kid discover why they're so awkward with each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 05:45:00" d="2020-05-20 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin try to find out the name of their neighbour, Antlers Guy, but accidentally blow his witness protection cover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 06:00:00" d="2020-05-20 06:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Zombozo hypnotizes Grandpa Max's entire baking class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 06:10:00" d="2020-05-20 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Team Tennyson's thrift store shopping is ruined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 06:25:00" d="2020-05-20 06:35:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When Mao Mao discovers that he is not as popular as Badgerclops and Adorabat, they decide to reinvent him as a kinder, cuddlier hero</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 06:35:00" d="2020-05-20 06:50:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When Mao Mao underestimates enemy and friend alike, it almost costs him the entire kingdom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 06:50:00" d="2020-05-20 07:01:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>Jessica Cruz is convinced she can find the purr-fect forever home for Dexter, a cat who has been deemed unadoptable because he’s basically the worst cat in the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 07:01:00" d="2020-05-20 07:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>Diana Prince is absolutely crushing it in every single aspect of life as a student at Metropolis High… until someone shows up who threatens to throw</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 07:15:00" d="2020-05-20 07:25:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>JP invites his friends over for a sleepover but it happens to be on the night of a huge game of Flashlight Tag in the Creek!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 07:25:00" d="2020-05-20 07:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>A spat between the Elders of the Creek leaves an opening in their tabletop role playing game so Kelsey joins the campaign!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 07:45:00" d="2020-05-20 07:54:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% It's Easter and the Tooth Fairy is trying to take over the holiday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 07:54:00" d="2020-05-20 08:04:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin learns that avocados are a super food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 08:04:00" d="2020-05-20 08:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin vows to never wash his hand again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 08:15:00" d="2020-05-20 08:24:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin takes the other Titans on a trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 08:24:00" d="2020-05-20 08:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin tries to teach the other Titans about real estate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 08:34:00" d="2020-05-20 08:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin hatches a plan to get rich off pennies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 08:50:00" d="2020-05-20 09:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>The Bears help Chloe present her project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 09:00:00" d="2020-05-20 09:10:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>Grizz pitches his Crowbar Jones prequel film to Nom Nom, hoping Nom Nom will agree to appear in the movie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 09:10:00" d="2020-05-20 09:25:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>The Bears travel to the video game store</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 09:25:00" d="2020-05-20 09:35:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% We are introduced to Shun's mysterious backstory, his relationship with his industrialist father and desire for a closer knit family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 09:35:00" d="2020-05-20 09:50:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% Dan and Shun butt heads on how best to make the AO a real team amidst growing threats includin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 09:50:00" d="2020-05-20 10:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Miss Simian discovers a failed test from Gumball's past that brings down his grade point average. This means he has to retake kindergarten all over again!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 10:00:00" d="2020-05-20 10:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin discover the reason Dad's diet wasn't working was that he was actually on ten diets and eating a meal for each of them!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 10:20:00" d="2020-05-20 10:29:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Unikitty and Hawkodile are &quot;lost at sea&quot;, stranded on a raft together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 10:29:00" d="2020-05-20 10:50:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>When Unikitty has a little auto incident with Master Frown, he insists on taking it to court! Frown's thrilled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 10:50:00" d="2020-05-20 11:02:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans are at Super Hero Summer Camp for the week and they may need to add another teammate to win the big canoe race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 11:02:00" d="2020-05-20 11:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% In order to quickly get through their chores and karate lessons the Titans learn how to montage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 11:15:00" d="2020-05-20 11:26:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Third Earth is being overrun by super tough, super buff Warrior Maidens and it looks like the ThunderCats are next on their hit list!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 11:26:00" d="2020-05-20 11:40:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O wants to prove to the ThunderKittens that he’s not just some boring old adult like Tygra even if it means ignoring his instincts and messing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 11:40:00" d="2020-05-20 11:50:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>When Vic accidentally loses one of Val's prized coins Val makes a deal with a mysterious antiques collector to replace it, but the deal has terrible consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 11:50:00" d="2020-05-20 12:10:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>Val holds a grudge against Vic, unwittingly attracting an evil cadejo, a mythological wolf-like beast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 12:10:00" d="2020-05-20 12:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The kids finally get the puppy they always wanted, except it’s a turtle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 12:20:00" d="2020-05-20 12:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When Mum reveals that Gumball's real name is &quot;Zach&quot;, Gumball adopts a cheesy, annoying persona to match the name</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 12:40:00" d="2020-05-20 12:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Nothing much is happening for Gumball and Darwin and the background characters in Elmore seize their moment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 12:50:00" d="2020-05-20 13:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball is in such a bad mood that it spreads to Darwin, who joins him in complaining about everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 13:10:00" d="2020-05-20 13:21:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>Everything is going well for Kara Danvers both as a teen and a superhero until she starts taking the blame for things she didn't do</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 13:21:00" d="2020-05-20 13:35:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>Jessica Cruz &amp; Pam Isley bond over protecting an ancient tree - without realizing who the other's alter ego is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 13:35:00" d="2020-05-20 13:45:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>When a forest fire interrupts their fun, Team Tennyson must hurry if they are to save the bird population and discover who is behind the growing fire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 13:45:00" d="2020-05-20 14:05:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>As Team Tennyson admires the efficiency of a super modern train station Ben is quick to sniff out one of Steam Smythe's robots holding up the line</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 14:05:00" d="2020-05-20 14:15:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>After Billy Billions' efforts to carve his face onto Mount Rushmore with a laser are thwarted by Ben the billionaire brat turns his focus on removing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 14:15:00" d="2020-05-20 14:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben accidentally creates a giant sink hole and frees King Koil and his Kimodo Dragon from below</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 14:30:00" d="2020-05-20 14:40:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>After a series of reoccurring nightmares affect his sleep, Ben refuses to open up to Max and Gwen about what's bothering him. But they realize Zombozo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 14:40:00" d="2020-05-20 14:55:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Gwen drags Ben along on a hike in search of the legendary Forgeti, a yeti that makes people forget they ever saw it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 14:55:00" d="2020-05-20 15:05:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>The gang struggles to get rid of the King when he joins them as their new deputy-for-a-day!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 15:05:00" d="2020-05-20 15:25:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Worried that his sword is a glorified consolation prize, Mao Mao sets out to prove the worth of his weapon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 15:25:00" d="2020-05-20 15:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans give Robin advice to guide him through his camp romance with Wonder Girl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 15:34:00" d="2020-05-20 15:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Thinking it's a way to reconnect with her father Raven enters a beauty pageant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 15:50:00" d="2020-05-20 16:01:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O has gotten a hold of the last jar of Thundersnaps! But a difficult to open cookie jar is gonna send Lion-O and Cheetara chasing down a legend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 16:01:00" d="2020-05-20 16:20:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>A crying unicorn appears at the Cats' Lair and weepily tells the ThunderCats that all of her unicorn friends have been captured!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 16:20:00" d="2020-05-20 16:31:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball is desperate to avoid a late fee on the rented dvd he accidentally destroyed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 16:31:00" d="2020-05-20 16:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Tobias compete for Penny's affection by putting on the lamest duel in history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 16:50:00" d="2020-05-20 17:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Darwin ends up in detention with the Bomb Kid, who decides to make Darwin his new target. However, it backfires when Darwin ruins his life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 17:00:00" d="2020-05-20 17:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The kids convince Mr Corneille to become a cage fighter and set up a fight against a fearsome Russian fighter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 17:20:00" d="2020-05-20 17:30:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>Craig rescues a tadpole and decides to raise him into a level 100 frog!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 17:30:00" d="2020-05-20 17:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>Craig goes on a mind-bending journey as he tries to eat the most sour candy in the Creek!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 17:45:00" d="2020-05-20 17:55:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>When Unikitty and the gang discover a gross bug in the castle, they desperately want it gone for good, but Unikitty refuses to allow them to squish it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 17:55:00" d="2020-05-20 18:15:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Unikitty finds an old, beatup recliner on the curb, but sees its inner beauty and brings it home to introduce to the gang!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 18:15:00" d="2020-05-20 18:24:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans give Robin advice to guide him through his camp romance with Wonder Girl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 18:24:00" d="2020-05-20 18:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Batman and Commissioner Gordon check in on various happenings around Jump City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 18:34:00" d="2020-05-20 18:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Beast Boy agrees to share his birthday with Starfire after learning she's never had one on Earth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 18:50:00" d="2020-05-20 18:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Stuck inside because of bad weather the Titans play rainy day games after Robin convinces them that indoor activites will cheer up the clouds and make the rain stop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 18:59:00" d="2020-05-20 19:09:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin refuses to give the Titans any more orders so that they'll learn to think for themselves. Instead the Titans start taking their cues from fortune cookies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 19:09:00" d="2020-05-20 19:30:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin convinces the Titans to go back to school with him so he can finally become the all-American class president-type he's dreamt of being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 19:30:00" d="2020-05-20 19:41:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>A crying unicorn appears at the Cats' Lair and weepily tells the ThunderCats that all of her unicorn friends have been captured!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 19:41:00" d="2020-05-20 20:00:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O has gotten a hold of the last jar of Thundersnaps! But a difficult to open cookie jar is gonna send Lion-O and Cheetara chasing down a legend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 20:00:00" d="2020-05-20 20:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Team Tennyson stops in at a fringe family reunion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 20:10:00" d="2020-05-20 20:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Zombozo hypnotizes Grandpa Max's entire baking class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 20:30:00" d="2020-05-20 20:40:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% We are introduced to Shun's mysterious backstory, his relationship with his industrialist father and desire for a closer knit family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 20:40:00" d="2020-05-20 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% Dan and Shun butt heads on how best to make the AO a real team amidst growing threats includin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 21:00:00" d="2020-05-20 21:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and Lola are stuck with Manetti as a science project partner. The only way to complete the project is turn Manetti into the science project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 21:10:00" d="2020-05-20 21:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Tracy claims Angelo broke her arm. Angelo’s punishment—become Tracy’s slave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 21:25:00" d="2020-05-20 21:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo discovers Cathy cat and Joe Mama have been accidentally switched at the Vet. And no one believes Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 21:35:00" d="2020-05-20 21:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo creates a fake Guatemalan pen pal so he doesn’t fail Mr. Foot’s class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 21:55:00" d="2020-05-20 22:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo becomes an intern at Adventureparkland. But, his dream job isn’t all it’s cracked up to be because he has to actually… work!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 22:05:00" d="2020-05-20 22:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Miss Perla turns detention time into art therapy where Angelo makes cool bobble-head sculptures which become all the rage in school. Result:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 22:20:00" d="2020-05-20 22:30:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% When Cathy hikes the price of her famous cupcake the “Brooklyn Blackout,” Lola goes undercover in search of the secret recipe. Angelo and the gang discover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 22:30:00" d="2020-05-20 22:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo shares his tips and tricks for delaying a test</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 22:45:00" d="2020-05-20 23:15:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% Zane’s near demise at the hands of Mr. E forces the ninja to flee aboard the Bounty, where they discover a message Zane intercepted may reveal the hidden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 23:15:00" d="2020-05-20 23:45:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% As Lloyd and Harumi venture deep into Primeval’s Eye in search of the third Oni Mask, the ninja attempt to fix the Bounty and make a startling discovery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 23:45:00" d="2020-05-20 23:56:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Darwin develops a texting addiction when he and Gumball get their first cell phone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-20 23:56:00" d="2020-05-21 00:06:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Carrie takes Gumball, Darwin and Anais to a real haunted house party on Halloween</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 00:06:00" d="2020-05-21 00:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Darwin is too polite to speak his mind, so Gumball teaches him to be direct</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 00:20:00" d="2020-05-21 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Everyone knows you can never watch just one video on the internet but Gumball and Darwin think they are the exception to the rule</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 00:30:00" d="2020-05-21 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% After being framed for feeding coffee to the squirrels in the park, Gumball proclaims that Mrs Robinson is pure evil</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 00:40:00" d="2020-05-21 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When Mom and Dad struggle to keep hyperactive, toddler-aged Gumball from trashing the house and exhausting them, they decide to buy him a pet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 00:50:00" d="2020-05-21 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Via the sewers, Darwin finds himself flushed out to sea. He is terrified, but determined to make his way back to the Wattersons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 01:00:00" d="2020-05-21 01:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and Lola are stuck with Manetti as a science project partner. The only way to complete the project is turn Manetti into the science project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 01:10:00" d="2020-05-21 01:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Tracy claims Angelo broke her arm. Angelo’s punishment—become Tracy’s slave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 01:25:00" d="2020-05-21 01:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo discovers Cathy cat and Joe Mama have been accidentally switched at the Vet. And no one believes Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 01:35:00" d="2020-05-21 01:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo creates a fake Guatemalan pen pal so he doesn’t fail Mr. Foot’s class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 01:45:00" d="2020-05-21 01:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo becomes an intern at Adventureparkland. But, his dream job isn’t all it’s cracked up to be because he has to actually… work!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 01:55:00" d="2020-05-21 02:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Miss Perla turns detention time into art therapy where Angelo makes cool bobble-head sculptures which become all the rage in school. Result:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 02:05:00" d="2020-05-21 02:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% When Cathy hikes the price of her famous cupcake the “Brooklyn Blackout,” Lola goes undercover in search of the secret recipe. Angelo and the gang discover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 02:15:00" d="2020-05-21 02:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo shares his tips and tricks for delaying a test</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 02:25:00" d="2020-05-21 02:35:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 02:35:00" d="2020-05-21 02:55:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% Zane’s near demise at the hands of Mr. E forces the ninja to flee aboard the Bounty, where they discover a message Zane intercepted may reveal the hidden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 02:55:00" d="2020-05-21 03:15:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% As Lloyd and Harumi venture deep into Primeval’s Eye in search of the third Oni Mask, the ninja attempt to fix the Bounty and make a startling discovery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 03:15:00" d="2020-05-21 03:25:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>Trying to cheer Vambre up, Prohyas recalls when they were just kids on their parents broccoli Farm</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 03:25:00" d="2020-05-21 03:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Pr Brown make a pact to tell each other's girlfriends about problems they have</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 03:35:00" d="2020-05-21 03:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Alan has lost faith in humanity and turned the world black and white. Gumball has to get over his hatred of Alan to bring the color back by singing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 03:45:00" d="2020-05-21 03:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% A group of kids get locked in the school after their parents have a charity gala. They appoint Gumball as leader to get them out but it leads to chaos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 03:55:00" d="2020-05-21 04:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Clayton shapeshifts into people to take their detentions for money. He starts framing people for misdemeanors so GB and DW must track him down to stop him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 04:05:00" d="2020-05-21 04:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Sarah finds a notebook from an awesome store!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 04:15:00" d="2020-05-21 04:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball receives a scare-email from a freaky ghost and decides to ignore it, despite Darwin's advice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 04:30:00" d="2020-05-21 04:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball decides to put Mr. Small's eco-friendly principles to the test but it doesn't quite go as planned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 04:40:00" d="2020-05-21 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Leslie calls Gumball's bluff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 04:50:00" d="2020-05-21 05:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Nicole and her parents have it out</k>  </p>
</a>
