<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="113" t="2020-04-10 04:38:44"><p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 05:01:00" d="2020-04-17 05:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin make their Dad believe in magic again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 05:15:00" d="2020-04-17 05:26:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Ms Simian sets out to “befriend” Gumball in order to win a Favourite Teacher Award</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 05:26:00" d="2020-04-17 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin give Mr Robinson a home and end up saving his marriage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 05:35:00" d="2020-04-17 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% The new coach at Elmore High stands up to Jamie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 05:45:00" d="2020-04-17 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Mr. Robinson accidentally lets his feelings slip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 06:00:00" d="2020-04-17 06:11:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben, Gwen and Grandpa Max arrive in Bismarck for its annual celebration of bee pollination, bringing them face-to-face with Queen Bee and a bold new scheme</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 06:11:00" d="2020-04-17 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Team Tennyson look to take in the sights of the Shoshone Falls but when they find Steam Smythe siphoning off the water, it is up to Ben, Grandpa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 06:25:00" d="2020-04-17 06:36:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>After struggling to keep up, Adorabat gets a cybernetic &quot;Mega-Mech.&quot; But can fancy new powers make up for experience?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 06:36:00" d="2020-04-17 06:50:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Feeling left out Adorabat wishes Mao Mao and Badgerclops would spend less time with each other and more time with her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 06:50:00" d="2020-04-17 07:01:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>The girls must track down Katana a mysterious warrior who’s stealing the souls of Metropolis’s villains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 07:01:00" d="2020-04-17 07:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>When she stumbles across a villainous plot - and all the other heroes are indisposed - Bumblebee must rise to the occasion… despite being the smallest of the bunch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 07:15:00" d="2020-04-17 07:25:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>An accidental stink bomb explosion causes the kids to evacuate the Creek but Craig takes it upon himself to rescue those left behind in the stench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 07:25:00" d="2020-04-17 07:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>When Craig decides to keep a lightning bug in a jar he disrupts the delicate balance of Summer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 07:45:00" d="2020-04-17 07:55:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Cyborg wants Pain Bot to be his “little buddy” but is the destructive robot too dangerous to be a sidekick?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 07:55:00" d="2020-04-17 08:05:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Killer Moth offers a reward for Silkie's return, but will Silkier be happier away from the Titans?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 08:05:00" d="2020-04-17 08:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% BB and Cyborg invite Starfire to join in their fun as long as she avoids dreaded uncle jokes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 08:15:00" d="2020-04-17 08:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Santa tries to take over Halloween</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 08:25:00" d="2020-04-17 08:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% After being left alone at home Cyborg and Starfire booby trap the tower for safety</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 08:34:00" d="2020-04-17 08:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Starfire wins a goldfish at the carnival and vows to keep it alive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 08:50:00" d="2020-04-17 09:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>When the Bears' beloved laptop breaks, they finally have the need to do something they've never done before: get jobs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 09:00:00" d="2020-04-17 09:11:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>The Baby Bears have an adventure in the sky while aboard a plane to Sweden. But when they are forced to sit in different sections of the plane, things</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 09:11:00" d="2020-04-17 09:25:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>Panda becomes the alpha bear, and he and Grizz have to deal with the consequences of an emotional Panda being the leader of the three Bears</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 09:25:00" d="2020-04-17 09:35:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% The AO embark on a mission into the mysterious labyrinth world of Vestroia to find Strata the Hunter and free the Bakugan he has imprisoned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 09:35:00" d="2020-04-17 09:50:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% Lost in the maze of Vestroia the AO encounter powerful forces that seem to be struggling fo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 09:50:00" d="2020-04-17 09:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans have Raven give them new super powers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 09:59:00" d="2020-04-17 10:09:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin tries to tell the origin story of the Teen Titans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 10:09:00" d="2020-04-17 10:18:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans want to be the scariest trick-or-treaters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 10:18:00" d="2020-04-17 10:29:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Justice League holds another talent competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 10:29:00" d="2020-04-17 10:38:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans must find a way to beat the Hive Five</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 10:38:00" d="2020-04-17 10:48:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin throws his own party with a special guest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 10:48:00" d="2020-04-17 10:58:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin tries to tell some tall tales</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 10:58:00" d="2020-04-17 11:07:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Teen Titans Go takes a look at the superheroes' lives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 11:07:00" d="2020-04-17 11:40:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans have to stop Darkseid's latest scheme</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 11:40:00" d="2020-04-17 11:50:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>While searching for a hidden skate park, V and V happen upon a tribe of wild kids, who live in a society without rules or adults</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 11:50:00" d="2020-04-17 12:10:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>Victor &amp; Valentino gain a newfound respect for cleanliness after Chata's house traps them inside its labyrinth of ancient, magical walls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 12:10:00" d="2020-04-17 12:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% At Halloween show and tell, the class isn’t buying Gumball’s story about Gargaroth The Devourer until Carrie fakes a terrifying haunting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 12:20:00" d="2020-04-17 12:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball is walking in the same direction as Hot Dog Guy, and with each step it becomes increasingly awkward</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 12:40:00" d="2020-04-17 12:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Elmore residents are going missing, and the cause of these disappearances may be closer to home than Gumball and Darwin think</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 12:50:00" d="2020-04-17 13:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin discover that Tobias is doing way better than them in an online game called Galatrek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 13:10:00" d="2020-04-17 13:21:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>The girls must track down Katana a mysterious warrior who's stealing the souls of Metropolis's villains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 13:21:00" d="2020-04-17 13:35:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>Overwhelmed by Superman coverage in Metropolis, Supergirl decides to really show the city what she can do. But is she helping people or her ego?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 13:35:00" d="2020-04-17 13:45:00"><n>Adventure Time - Elements</n>    <k>Finn and Jake must risk it all to see all their dreams come true</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 13:45:00" d="2020-04-17 14:05:00"><n>Adventure Time - Elements</n>    <k>Finn and Jake are making the best home movie ever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 14:05:00" d="2020-04-17 14:15:00"><n>Adventure Time - Elements</n>    <k>Marceline messes with Finn and Jake and tells them they’re vampires</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 14:15:00" d="2020-04-17 14:30:00"><n>Adventure Time - Elements</n>    <k>King Snuggadoodle and the Huggaboopies invade Finn and Jake’s tree house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 14:30:00" d="2020-04-17 14:40:00"><n>Adventure Time - Elements</n>    <k>Finn and Jake must survive the tests of the Fight King</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 14:40:00" d="2020-04-17 14:55:00"><n>Adventure Time - Elements</n>    <k>Finn and Jake have to enter Marceline’s mind and retrieve the wake spell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 14:55:00" d="2020-04-17 15:06:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When the Sweetypies think the mythical Torbaclaun has come to Pure Heart Valley, Mao Mao tries to prove to them that it isn't real</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 15:06:00" d="2020-04-17 15:25:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Mao Mao's legendary, gigantic and critical father visits his son at his new job as sheriff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 15:25:00" d="2020-04-17 15:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% After Young Justice easily takes out the HIVE while the other Titans make silly jokes Robin decides the team needs to get serious./ The Titans visit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 15:34:00" d="2020-04-17 15:55:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Raven and Beast Boy are shocked to discover that their exes, Terra and Aqualad, are now dating each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 15:55:00" d="2020-04-17 16:04:00"><n>Total Dramarama</n>    <k>Owen and Beth try to save an ant hill that Courtney and Leshawna want to destroy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 16:04:00" d="2020-04-17 16:20:00"><n>Total Dramarama</n>    <k>After Owen gets ripped off at the ice cream truck the kids unite to right that wrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 16:20:00" d="2020-04-17 16:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% The life of the background objects of Elmore are shown in a series of short skits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 16:30:00" d="2020-04-17 16:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% The Wattersons are surprised to discover that their past actions have consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 16:50:00" d="2020-04-17 17:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Whilst Gumball and Darwin make fun of Mum and Dad for being old, their voices start to break</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 17:00:00" d="2020-04-17 17:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Sarah, the new kid in school, is Gumball and Darwin's number one, slightly obsessive, fan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 17:20:00" d="2020-04-17 17:30:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>The kids meet a mysterious kid from the future</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 17:30:00" d="2020-04-17 17:50:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>Craig's fed up with losing in video games to his Dad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 17:50:00" d="2020-04-17 18:00:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>Vic &amp; Val want to sneak out to a secret fireworks show but are thwarted when their new babysitter, Xochi, outsmarts them at every turn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 18:00:00" d="2020-04-17 18:15:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>When V &amp; V discover that Chata's emotions control the water in the lake, they use it to their advantage and start their own wave pool business</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 18:15:00" d="2020-04-17 18:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Cyborg and Beast Boy face off about which is better, burgers or burritos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 18:25:00" d="2020-04-17 18:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% When a computer dating program matches Beast Boy to Raven, he tries wooing her to disastrous effect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 18:35:00" d="2020-04-17 18:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% A magical prism causes Raven to fragment into five distinct personalities which wreak havoc around town until the other Titans can figure out how to rejoin her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 18:50:00" d="2020-04-17 19:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% When the gang bands together to form a giant robot, Robin is relegated to the left leg - but he makes the left leg count!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 19:00:00" d="2020-04-17 19:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Beast Boy and Cyborg decide to make a yearbook for the Titans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 19:10:00" d="2020-04-17 19:30:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Raven and Beast Boy are shocked to discover that their exes, Terra and Aqualad, are now dating each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 19:30:00" d="2020-04-17 19:41:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When the Sweetypies think the mythical Torbaclaun has come to Pure Heart Valley, Mao Mao tries to prove to them that it isn't real</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 19:41:00" d="2020-04-17 20:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Mao Mao's legendary, gigantic and critical father visits his son at his new job as sheriff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 20:00:00" d="2020-04-17 20:11:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>While visiting Lake Erie, a relaxing day at the beach gets all washed up when Ben, Gwen and Grandpa Max come face-to-face with Hex and his summer intern, Kevin!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 20:11:00" d="2020-04-17 20:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben gets a tough lesson on knowing his limits when he competes in a gruelling obstacle race, made even worse by the Weatherheads!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 20:30:00" d="2020-04-17 20:40:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% The AO embark on a mission into the mysterious labyrinth world of Vestroia to find Strata the Hunter and free the Bakugan he has imprisoned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 20:40:00" d="2020-04-17 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% Lost in the maze of Vestroia the AO encounter powerful forces that seem to be struggling fo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 21:00:00" d="2020-04-17 21:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% As Lloyd and Harumi search the Oni Temple for the last mask, the ninja are taken hostage and discover Princess Harumi’s true intentions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 21:25:00" d="2020-04-17 21:55:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% The ninja appeal to the police commissioner of Ninjago in an effort to help save Lloyd and thwart Harumi’s efforts to resurrect the evil Lord Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 21:55:00" d="2020-04-17 22:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo enters a pie baking contest with his Dad as his partner until the two have creative differences and go it alone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 22:05:00" d="2020-04-17 22:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and Lola start a campaign to help Sherwood get voted “most likely to succeed” by his classmates instead of Tracy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 22:20:00" d="2020-04-17 22:30:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Dad takes a parenting class which works! Now he has more control of his kids. Angelo infiltrates the parenting class (posing as an adult) to learn Dad’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 22:30:00" d="2020-04-17 22:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo comes up with unique inventions to win “Snake Pit” a TV show where you pitch your business idea to local “business tycoons” hoping to get them to invest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 22:45:00" d="2020-04-17 22:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% After making a bet that their life is harder, Angelo and Mr. Foot trade places. Angelo becomes the teacher, and Mr. Foot the unruly student</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 22:55:00" d="2020-04-17 23:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% After taking a career test that claims to predict your future and receiving disappointing results, Angelo and friends set out to change their destinies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 23:15:00" d="2020-04-17 23:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% The line for Adventureparkland’s newest ride is way too long so Angelo and the gang decide to spread rumors of wolves attacking people at the park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 23:25:00" d="2020-04-17 23:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% With Lola and Sherwood away Angelo interviews and auditions potential replacements</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 23:35:00" d="2020-04-17 23:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Miss Perla turns detention time into art therapy where Angelo makes cool bobble-head sculptures which become all the rage in school. Result:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 23:45:00" d="2020-04-17 23:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% When Darwin taunts Gumball about how predictable he is, Gumball tries to prove that he can still surprise his buddy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-17 23:55:00" d="2020-04-18 00:06:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin are devastated to learn that Mr. Robinson -- their favourite person in the world -- is selling his house and leaving town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 00:06:00" d="2020-04-18 00:16:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Mom and the kids depart for their hard day's work, leaving a seemingly lazy Dad half-asleep on the sofa. Mom has given him one very simple job: buy mayonnaise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 00:16:00" d="2020-04-18 00:20:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>Vambre gives Prohyas the silent treatment, only to have her voice stolen away by a ventriloquist dummy Frankenstein</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 00:20:00" d="2020-04-18 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Nicole encourages Gumball to do what comes naturally. reak stuff!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 00:30:00" d="2020-04-18 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball kind of teaches Darwin how to be a skater…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 00:40:00" d="2020-04-18 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Darwin finds it harder than expected to give up his favourite foodstuff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 00:50:00" d="2020-04-18 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin try to find out the name of their neighbour, Antlers Guy, but accidentally blow his witness protection cover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 01:00:00" d="2020-04-18 01:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo enters a pie baking contest with his Dad as his partner until the two have creative differences and go it alone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 01:10:00" d="2020-04-18 01:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and Lola start a campaign to help Sherwood get voted “most likely to succeed” by his classmates instead of Tracy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 01:25:00" d="2020-04-18 01:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Dad takes a parenting class which works! Now he has more control of his kids. Angelo infiltrates the parenting class (posing as an adult) to learn Dad’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 01:35:00" d="2020-04-18 01:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo comes up with unique inventions to win “Snake Pit” a TV show where you pitch your business idea to local “business tycoons” hoping to get them to invest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 01:45:00" d="2020-04-18 01:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% After making a bet that their life is harder, Angelo and Mr. Foot trade places. Angelo becomes the teacher, and Mr. Foot the unruly student</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 01:55:00" d="2020-04-18 02:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% After taking a career test that claims to predict your future and receiving disappointing results, Angelo and friends set out to change their destinies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 02:05:00" d="2020-04-18 02:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% The line for Adventureparkland’s newest ride is way too long so Angelo and the gang decide to spread rumors of wolves attacking people at the park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 02:15:00" d="2020-04-18 02:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% With Lola and Sherwood away Angelo interviews and auditions potential replacements</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 02:25:00" d="2020-04-18 02:35:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>The Warriors seek a secret book in the Library of Shhh! and their best friend from warrior school &quot;Witchy Simone&quot; follows them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 02:35:00" d="2020-04-18 02:55:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% As Lloyd and Harumi search the Oni Temple for the last mask, the ninja are taken hostage and discover Princess Harumi’s true intentions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 02:55:00" d="2020-04-18 03:15:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% The ninja appeal to the police commissioner of Ninjago in an effort to help save Lloyd and thwart Harumi’s efforts to resurrect the evil Lord Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 03:15:00" d="2020-04-18 03:25:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>The Warriors are treated to a banquet by the grateful Kotassians and Vambre accidentally eats their king</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 03:25:00" d="2020-04-18 03:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin help Anais rescue her doll from Tina Rex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 03:35:00" d="2020-04-18 03:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin are unwitting accomplices in a gas station robbery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 03:45:00" d="2020-04-18 03:56:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin accidentally destroy Mr Robinson’s new car… or do they?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 03:56:00" d="2020-04-18 04:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball experiences an impossibly unfortunate chain of events</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 04:05:00" d="2020-04-18 04:16:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin accidentally create a loveable monster that eats their family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 04:16:00" d="2020-04-18 04:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball is embarrassed when Mum comes to school to spend some “quality time”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 04:30:00" d="2020-04-18 04:41:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball’s magic tinfoil helmet threatens to tear the Watterson family apart!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 04:41:00" d="2020-04-18 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Anais is convinced that Gumball is being bullied by Tina Rex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-04-18 04:50:00" d="2020-04-18 05:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin are convinced that the world will end in 24 hours</k>  </p>
</a>
