<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="115" t="2020-05-30 04:41:40"><p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 05:01:00" d="2020-06-06 05:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% A group of kids get locked in the school after their parents have a charity gala. They appoint Gumball as leader to get them out but it leads to chaos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 05:10:00" d="2020-06-06 05:15:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>53% Tired of their local public swimming pool, the Warriors travel to the Dinosaur Kingdom to sneak in their pool</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 05:15:00" d="2020-06-06 05:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Clayton shapeshifts into people to take their detentions for money. He starts framing people for misdemeanors so GB and DW must track him down to stop him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 05:25:00" d="2020-06-06 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Sarah finds a notebook from an awesome store!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 05:35:00" d="2020-06-06 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The Watterson kids come up with a fool-proof plan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 05:45:00" d="2020-06-06 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball decides to put Mr. Small's eco-friendly principles to the test but it doesn't quite go as planned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 06:00:00" d="2020-06-06 06:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>In a peaceful coastal town, Ben must not only face the archaic antagonist Steam Smythe and his latest creation, the Clocktopus, but also his deepest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 06:10:00" d="2020-06-06 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben and Gwen are transformed into babies by nanny-gone-nuts Nanny Nightmare who will stop at nothing to reshape the world in the image of her day-care</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 06:25:00" d="2020-06-06 06:35:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>An explosive loner and his slacker best friend are waylaid from their journey into legend, only to find that their story is just beginning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 06:35:00" d="2020-06-06 06:50:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When Mao Mao gets hungry for the perfect adventure Adorabat tells a white lie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 06:50:00" d="2020-06-06 06:59:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>When six ordinary girls meet and discover that they each have extraordinary powers they decide to join forces to take on one of Metropolis’s most sinister villains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 06:59:00" d="2020-06-06 07:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>When six ordinary girls discover they each have extraordinary powers, they decide to join forces to take on one of Metropolis’s most sinister villains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 07:15:00" d="2020-06-06 07:25:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>70% Craig discovers that the Honeysuckle Rangers have snuck into his side of the Creek to steal his most prized possession</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 07:25:00" d="2020-06-06 07:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>70% When Craig can't go to the Creek, he and his mom decide to build the biggest blanket fort in the world!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 07:45:00" d="2020-06-06 07:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin just want to veg out all day but end up having to save the rest of the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 07:55:00" d="2020-06-06 08:06:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The kids try to help Dad bond with Frankie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 08:06:00" d="2020-06-06 08:16:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Hotdog Kid discover why they're so awkward with each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 08:16:00" d="2020-06-06 08:27:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>After an excessive spending spree, the Golden Goose tells the gang it won't give them any more golden eggs until they learn the value of money</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 08:27:00" d="2020-06-06 08:38:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>The moon is bored of taking the nightshift, since everyone's always asleep. So Unikitty leads the gang in putting on an over-the-top late night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 08:38:00" d="2020-06-06 08:49:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Badgerclops smells, but Mao Mao and Adorabat don't know how to tell him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 08:49:00" d="2020-06-06 08:59:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When the Sweetypies think the mythical Torbaclaun has come to Pure Heart Valley, Mao Mao tries to prove to them that it isn't real</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 08:59:00" d="2020-06-06 09:10:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>When the local Burger Joint is being threatened by a rogue Bakugan, Dan steps up to save the day and the burgers!/The AO stop neighbourhood kids from copycat behaviour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 09:10:00" d="2020-06-06 09:20:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>When the local Burger Joint is being threatened by a rogue Bakugan, Dan steps up to save the day and the burgers!/The AO stop neighbourhood kids from copycat behaviour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 09:20:00" d="2020-06-06 09:29:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans discover how hard cartoons are to produce when they make one about Michael and Aaron</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 09:29:00" d="2020-06-06 10:20:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Trigon makes Raven attend her prom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 10:20:00" d="2020-06-06 10:29:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Cyborg plugs into the control panel of the Titans tower and drives the others crazy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 10:29:00" d="2020-06-06 10:39:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Starfire's new pet is a horribly dangerous parasite, but Robin is the only one who is suspicious of the beast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 10:39:00" d="2020-06-06 10:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Beast Boy teaches Starfire how to lie and it backfires as her lies get more and more outrageous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 10:50:00" d="2020-06-06 10:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Raven eats a bad meatball that causes tentacles to spring from her teeth and devour the other Titans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 10:59:00" d="2020-06-06 11:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% When the gang breaks Robin's beloved staff, Robin is forced to find a replacement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 11:10:00" d="2020-06-06 11:19:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Beast Boy falls for Terra despite clear signs that she is more interested in destroying the Titans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 11:19:00" d="2020-06-06 11:29:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans revert to creative game-playing in order to have a chance at beating the undefeated supervillain dodgeball team</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 11:29:00" d="2020-06-06 11:39:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Cyborg and Beast Boy face off about which is better, burgers or burritos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 11:39:00" d="2020-06-06 11:49:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% When a computer dating program matches Beast Boy to Raven, he tries wooing her to disastrous effect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 11:49:00" d="2020-06-06 11:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% A magical prism causes Raven to fragment into five distinct personalities which wreak havoc around town until the other Titans can figure out how to rejoin her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 11:59:00" d="2020-06-06 12:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% When the gang bands together to form a giant robot, Robin is relegated to the left leg - but he makes the left leg count!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 12:10:00" d="2020-06-06 12:20:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Raven shows the rest of the Titans that books can be fun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 12:20:00" d="2020-06-06 12:30:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% When the Titans replace the couch with a treadmill, Cyborg and Beast Boy must get guidance from the couch spirit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 12:30:00" d="2020-06-06 13:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% When Robin needs an archenemy, Starfire generously offers to fill the role and she exceeds expectations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 13:10:00" d="2020-06-06 13:21:00"><n>Power Players</n>    <k>Axel finds himself at the center of a disagreement between Sarge and Masko over what's more important in battle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 13:21:00" d="2020-06-06 13:35:00"><n>Power Players</n>    <k>Zoe builds her own battle suit in hopes of joining Axel's team. The only problem? She can't shrink!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 13:35:00" d="2020-06-06 13:46:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin accidentally create a loveable monster that eats their family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 13:46:00" d="2020-06-06 14:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball is embarrassed when Mum comes to school to spend some “quality time”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 14:05:00" d="2020-06-06 14:16:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball’s magic tinfoil helmet threatens to tear the Watterson family apart!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 14:16:00" d="2020-06-06 14:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Anais is convinced that Gumball is being bullied by Tina Rex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 14:30:00" d="2020-06-06 14:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are convinced that the world will end in 24 hours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 14:40:00" d="2020-06-06 14:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball is desperate to avoid a late fee on the rented dvd he accidentally destroyed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 14:55:00" d="2020-06-06 15:05:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When Rufus and Reg come to swindle the town, Sheriff Mao Mao teaches them a lesson in justice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 15:05:00" d="2020-06-06 15:25:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>The gang decide to compete in the annual Thumb War competition, but a surprise forces Mao Mao to deal with the unthinkable. losing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 15:25:00" d="2020-06-06 15:37:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Bumblebee offers to help Robin with his leadership skills by teaching him how to act like a queen bee</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 15:37:00" d="2020-06-06 15:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Needing a hero with shrinking powers, but forgetting about Bumblebee, Robin invites The Atom to join their fight against the Brain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 15:50:00" d="2020-06-06 16:00:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Vultureman has got a brand new invention but there's one big problem: he stole the idea from Panthro! Oh, also Vultureman is using his invention to take over Third Earth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 16:00:00" d="2020-06-06 16:15:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Tygra takes Lion-O climbing up the peak of Hook Mountain to teach him a lesson about trust. But they get trapped by a snowstorm and take refuge in a creepy cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 16:15:00" d="2020-06-06 16:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin befriend Clayton, who is a compulsive liar and begins contaminating them with lies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 16:25:00" d="2020-06-06 16:36:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% It's Mother's Day, and Gumball and Darwin discover that Tobias and Banana Joe have both made a card for &quot;The Best Mum in the World&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 16:36:00" d="2020-06-06 16:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Mum has forced Dad to install a password on the computer…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 16:55:00" d="2020-06-06 17:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin decide to use online reviews to wrangle free stuff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 17:05:00" d="2020-06-06 17:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% A mysterious package shows up at the Watterson’s house and they do their best to avoid opening it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 17:20:00" d="2020-06-06 17:30:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>70% A spat between the Elders of the Creek leaves an opening in their tabletop roleplaying game, so Kelsey joins the campaign!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 17:30:00" d="2020-06-06 17:50:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>70% Craig goes on a mind-bending journey as he tries to eat the most sour candy in the Creek!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 17:50:00" d="2020-06-06 18:00:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>The gang are at the local laundromat cleaning their clothes, when Unikitty finds Batman's uniform mixed in with her clothes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 18:00:00" d="2020-06-06 18:15:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Puppycorn's birthday wish is stolen by Master Frown, the biggest downer in the kingdom!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 18:15:00" d="2020-06-06 18:27:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Bumblebee offers to help Robin with his leadership skills by teaching him how to act like a queen bee</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 18:27:00" d="2020-06-06 18:36:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Needing a hero with shrinking powers, but forgetting about Bumblebee, Robin invites The Atom to join their fight against the Brain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 18:36:00" d="2020-06-06 18:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Zapped into an episode of Pretty Pretty Pegasus the Titans must fight their way out./ The Titans try vegetarianism but learn that not everyone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 18:50:00" d="2020-06-06 18:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% It's Movie Night and the Titans have a hard time deciding who gets to choose which movie they watch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 18:59:00" d="2020-06-06 19:09:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% It's back to school as the Titans teach each other about science and grammar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 19:09:00" d="2020-06-06 19:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Beast Boy writes a song to tell Raven his feelings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 19:25:00" d="2020-06-06 19:35:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Vultureman has got a brand new invention but there's one big problem: he stole the idea from Panthro! Oh, also Vultureman is using his invention to take over Third Earth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 19:35:00" d="2020-06-06 19:50:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Tygra takes Lion-O climbing up the peak of Hook Mountain to teach him a lesson about trust. But they get trapped by a snowstorm and take refuge in a creepy cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 19:50:00" d="2020-06-06 20:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben gets a tough lesson on knowing his limits when he competes in a grueling obstacle race-- made even worse by the Weatherheads!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 20:00:00" d="2020-06-06 20:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben learns about the possible existence of a mythical creature, the Quetzalcoatl, and takes it upon himself to find the feathered serpent on his own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 20:10:00" d="2020-06-06 20:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Team Tennyson help transport a caged Quetzalcoatl through the Yucatan jungle only to encounter a saboteur, LaGrange, who hijacks the precious cargo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 20:30:00" d="2020-06-06 20:40:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>The AO are attacked by Masato Kazami and his Body Guards./Philomena's attempt to refocus the Mind Core Cell's power backfires and the AO must fight their fellow employees</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 20:40:00" d="2020-06-06 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>The AO are attacked by Masato Kazami and his Body Guards./Philomena's attempt to refocus the Mind Core Cell's power backfires and the AO must fight their fellow employees</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 21:00:00" d="2020-06-06 21:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo makes Tracy cry and feels terrible about it. He declares a truce. Problem is… their growing friendship throws off the balance of nature!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 21:10:00" d="2020-06-06 21:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Joe Mama has been stealing stuff from around town and storing it under Angelo’s bed. Angelo and friends embark on a reverse scavenger hunt to figure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 21:25:00" d="2020-06-06 21:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo and Lola are stuck with Manetti as a science project partner. The only way to complete the project is turn Manetti into the science project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 21:35:00" d="2020-06-06 21:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Tracy claims Angelo broke her arm. Angelo’s punishment—become Tracy’s slave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 21:50:00" d="2020-06-06 22:00:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo discovers Cathy cat and Joe Mama have been accidentally switched at the Vet. And no one believes Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 22:00:00" d="2020-06-06 22:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo creates a fake Guatemalan pen pal so he doesn’t fail Mr. Foot’s class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 22:20:00" d="2020-06-06 22:30:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo becomes an intern at Adventureparkland. But, his dream job isn’t all it’s cracked up to be because he has to actually… work!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 22:30:00" d="2020-06-06 22:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Miss Perla turns detention time into art therapy where Angelo makes cool bobble-head sculptures which become all the rage in school. Result:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 22:45:00" d="2020-06-06 23:10:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% The headquarters to the resistance is breached and Lloyd scrambles to avoid capture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 23:10:00" d="2020-06-06 23:40:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% As Lloyd unmasks Mystake for who she truly is Emperor Garmadon embraces Harumi as his daughter of darkness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 23:40:00" d="2020-06-06 23:51:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Principal Brown tries to “fix” Gumball’s dysfunctional family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-06 23:51:00" d="2020-06-07 00:02:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin babysit Anais “responsibly”, whilst “irresponsibly” flooding the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 00:02:00" d="2020-06-07 00:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball goes to school in a dress and becomes the darling of Elmore High</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 00:10:00" d="2020-06-07 00:20:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>Vambre and Prohyas encounter the Keeper of the &quot;Mask Magi-Sword&quot; who challenges them to a contest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 00:20:00" d="2020-06-07 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Dad is in charge of getting the kids to their first day back at school on time, but he's overslept and now he can't find Gumball, Darwin, or Anais anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 00:30:00" d="2020-06-07 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin discover that Rob, who once swore to wreak vengeance on them, has been trying to destroy them for some time. but his traps never work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 00:40:00" d="2020-06-07 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When Gumball and Darwin decide it's time they join a crew, they agree that the coolest posse in Elmore is the Senior Citizens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 00:50:00" d="2020-06-07 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When Anais reveals that she's in the grade above them at school, Gumball and Darwin's eyes are suddenly opened to a whole new world of other students</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 01:00:00" d="2020-06-07 01:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% After making a bet that their life is harder, Angelo and Mr. Foot trade places. Angelo becomes the teacher, and Mr. Foot the unruly student</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 01:10:00" d="2020-06-07 01:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% After taking a career test that claims to predict your future and receiving disappointing results, Angelo and friends set out to change their destinies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 01:25:00" d="2020-06-07 01:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% The line for Adventureparkland’s newest ride is way too long so Angelo and the gang decide to spread rumors of wolves attacking people at the park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 01:35:00" d="2020-06-07 01:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% With Lola and Sherwood away Angelo interviews and auditions potential replacements</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 01:45:00" d="2020-06-07 01:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% After Angelo trashes Burst’s stage set, his punishment is that he must star in Burst’s unusual, arty play. With Sherwood and Lola helping backstage, Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 01:55:00" d="2020-06-07 02:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% After accidentally breaking a window, Angelo and friends complete a series of chores at the rec center as pay back. But it’s all good because Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 02:05:00" d="2020-06-07 02:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% To convince his parents to buy him a phone Angelo must turn his text addicted sister into a smart phone role model</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 02:15:00" d="2020-06-07 02:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% After Mr. Foot confiscates all electronics before class, Angelo and friends have to kick it old school and pass hand written notes to communicate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 02:25:00" d="2020-06-07 02:35:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>Vambre gives Prohyas the silent treatment, only to have her voice stolen away by a ventriloquist dummy Frankenstein</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 02:35:00" d="2020-06-07 02:55:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% The headquarters to the resistance is breached and Lloyd scrambles to avoid capture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 02:55:00" d="2020-06-07 03:16:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% As Lloyd unmasks Mystake for who she truly is Emperor Garmadon embraces Harumi as his daughter of darkness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 03:16:00" d="2020-06-07 03:20:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 03:20:00" d="2020-06-07 03:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Leslie calls Gumball's bluff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 03:30:00" d="2020-06-07 03:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Nicole and her parents have it out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 03:40:00" d="2020-06-07 03:45:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>Vambre and Prohyas encounter the Keeper of the &quot;Mask Magi-Sword&quot; who challenges them to a contest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 03:45:00" d="2020-06-07 03:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When Nicole decides to pay the cable bill in person at Chanax, she leaves specific instructions for Richard to stay in the car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 03:55:00" d="2020-06-07 04:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are at the convenience store considering playing truant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 04:05:00" d="2020-06-07 04:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin argue with the Internet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 04:15:00" d="2020-06-07 04:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Hector is unhappy with his height</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 04:30:00" d="2020-06-07 04:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball decides it’s time to play cupid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 04:40:00" d="2020-06-07 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Channel 6 Elmore News has all the top local stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-06-07 04:50:00" d="2020-06-07 05:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin find themselves in serious trouble when they agree to everything the new kid in school says. The truth is they can't understand a word that he says</k>  </p>
</a>
