<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="110" t="2020-05-14 05:01:10"><p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 05:00:00" d="2020-05-21 05:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When Nicole decides to pay the cable bill in person at Chanax, she leaves specific instructions for Richard to stay in the car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 05:15:00" d="2020-05-21 05:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are at the convenience store considering playing truant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 05:25:00" d="2020-05-21 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin argue with the Internet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 05:35:00" d="2020-05-21 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Hector is unhappy with his height</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 05:45:00" d="2020-05-21 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball decides it’s time to play cupid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 06:00:00" d="2020-05-21 06:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Team Tennyson travels to a ski resort for some fun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 06:10:00" d="2020-05-21 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben's jealousy has him convinced he has to out-do Kevin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 06:25:00" d="2020-05-21 06:35:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>The gang struggles to get rid of the King when he joins them as their new deputy-for-a-day!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 06:35:00" d="2020-05-21 06:50:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Worried that his sword is a glorified consolation prize, Mao Mao sets out to prove the worth of his weapon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 06:50:00" d="2020-05-21 07:01:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>Everything is going well for Kara Danvers both as a teen and a superhero until she starts taking the blame for things she didn't do</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 07:01:00" d="2020-05-21 07:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>Jessica Cruz &amp; Pam Isley bond over protecting an ancient tree - without realizing who the other's alter ego is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 07:15:00" d="2020-05-21 07:25:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>Craig rescues a tadpole and decides to raise him into a level 100 frog!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 07:25:00" d="2020-05-21 07:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>Craig goes on a mind-bending journey as he tries to eat the most sour candy in the Creek!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 07:45:00" d="2020-05-21 07:54:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The other Titans are trying to stop a cow-stealing UFO</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 07:54:00" d="2020-05-21 08:03:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans tell their slightly inaccurate origin stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 08:03:00" d="2020-05-21 08:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin ignores the rules for a game of jinx</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 08:15:00" d="2020-05-21 08:24:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans team up with Shazam to defeat Mr. Mind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 08:24:00" d="2020-05-21 08:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin takes the Titans on an educational trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 08:34:00" d="2020-05-21 08:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Aqualad uses shrimps and prime rib to win back Raven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 08:50:00" d="2020-05-21 09:00:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>Ice Bear has a Korean-style cooking show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 09:00:00" d="2020-05-21 09:10:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>Ice Bear has a Korean-style cooking show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 09:10:00" d="2020-05-21 09:25:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n>    <k>Charlie meets a creature just like him named Ralph</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 09:25:00" d="2020-05-21 09:35:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% Osamu Kazami comes to take his son Shun back home and finds a defiance he hadn't co</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 09:35:00" d="2020-05-21 09:50:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% Drago and the other AO Bakugan face an unseen threat with earth shattering power only to be left wondering if it was all a dream</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 09:50:00" d="2020-05-21 10:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball discovers that Rob, his old nemesis, is &quot;neme-seeing&quot; someone else. Devastated that Rob has fallen out of hate with him, Gumball refuses to accept</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 10:00:00" d="2020-05-21 10:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When they see the school bullies making fun of Sussie, Gumball and Darwin decide to try and help her act less weird</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 10:20:00" d="2020-05-21 10:30:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Dr. Fox is proud to unveil her new ultimate combat machine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 10:30:00" d="2020-05-21 10:50:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Unikitty and the gang gear up for a fun day at the beach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 10:50:00" d="2020-05-21 10:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans give Robin advice to guide him through his camp romance with Wonder Girl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 10:59:00" d="2020-05-21 11:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Thinking it's a way to reconnect with her father Raven enters a beauty pageant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 11:15:00" d="2020-05-21 11:26:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>A crying unicorn appears at the Cats' Lair and weepily tells the ThunderCats that all of her unicorn friends have been captured!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 11:26:00" d="2020-05-21 11:40:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Lion-O has gotten a hold of the last jar of Thundersnaps! But a difficult to open cookie jar is gonna send Lion-O and Cheetara chasing down a legend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 11:40:00" d="2020-05-21 11:50:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>After being told by Chata that they can't get a pet, Vic &amp; Val adopt a wild lizard, unaware of its magical properties, and decide to keep it secret from Chata</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 11:50:00" d="2020-05-21 12:10:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n>    <k>After Vic loses a wrestling match, V&amp;V journey to the underworld to seek advice from their uncle, a famous wrestler named El Toro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 12:10:00" d="2020-05-21 12:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The Wattersons are swapping scary stories on a family vacation, when their car breaks down in the middle of the desert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 12:20:00" d="2020-05-21 12:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When Gumball and Darwin discover his diploma is fake, Principal Brown is determined to keep their discovery a secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 12:40:00" d="2020-05-21 12:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin start noticing small details around Elmore High that don't add up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 12:50:00" d="2020-05-21 13:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin help Rocky land an office job so that his dad, Mr Robinson, will be proud of him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 13:10:00" d="2020-05-21 13:21:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>After an embarrassing incident ruins Barbara Gordon’s reputation, rather than owning it, she decides it’s easier to harness The Flash’s ability to travel back in time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 13:21:00" d="2020-05-21 13:35:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n>    <k>Desperate to emerge from her father’s shadow, Zee Zatara performs for her own audience, but loses her cool when her act is dismissed as fakery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 13:35:00" d="2020-05-21 13:45:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben has to clean the Rust Bucket but when he is tricked into letting the vile Fly Guys steal it he must chase them down before they create an unstoppable maggot monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 13:45:00" d="2020-05-21 14:05:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>While tailgating at a homecoming football game, Ben teams up with Grandpa Max’s old college buddies to keep the crazy clown Zombozo from robbing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 14:05:00" d="2020-05-21 14:15:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>While winning big on a Sumo Slammers video game, Ben gets the idea to win a wrestling match for real until an intimidating wrestler Kyle decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 14:15:00" d="2020-05-21 14:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>While trying to film his own indie film, Ben accidentally allows the Bug Gang to go free</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 14:30:00" d="2020-05-21 14:40:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>When Ben attempts to stay up all night for Adrenaland, he not only fails to utilize his alien powers to stay awake but his &quot;sleep-alien-ing&quot; causes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 14:40:00" d="2020-05-21 14:55:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>When Ben interferes with malicious magician Hex’s quest for the earth-moving Titan Gloves at a swap meet, he inadvertently switches bodies with Gwen!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 14:55:00" d="2020-05-21 15:05:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>Badgerclops gets huge to destroy a towering monster but when he refuses to shrink down the kingdom faces a new terror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 15:05:00" d="2020-05-21 15:25:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n>    <k>When the Sweetypies think the mythical Torbaclaun has come to Pure Heart Valley, Mao Mao tries to prove to them that it isn't real</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 15:25:00" d="2020-05-21 15:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin tells the Titans to stop being reckless teens or the Creepy Catcher will get them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 15:34:00" d="2020-05-21 15:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans must find a way to keep all the Jump City residents from moving to Stockton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 15:50:00" d="2020-05-21 16:01:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Tygra's feeling unappreciated by the other ThunderCats so he starts hanging out with Mumm-Ra and cleaning his Black Pyramid?! Whaaaaaaat?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 16:01:00" d="2020-05-21 16:20:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Every time Mumm-Ra gets a hold of a magic artefact to restore his powers the ThunderCats just smash it and turn him into a dinky skeleton again. Until today that is!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 16:20:00" d="2020-05-21 16:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are jealous of a sparking a baby war</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 16:30:00" d="2020-05-21 16:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Tobias tries to be Gumball's best friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 16:50:00" d="2020-05-21 17:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin just want to veg out all day but end up having to save the rest of the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 17:00:00" d="2020-05-21 17:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The kids try to help Dad bond with Frankie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 17:20:00" d="2020-05-21 17:30:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>Craig dines at the restaurant where his older brother works and orders up a plate of REVENGE. and lots of breadsticks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 17:30:00" d="2020-05-21 17:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n>    <k>A runaway from a summer camp ends up at the Stump but Craig suspects her story may not be what it seems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 17:45:00" d="2020-05-21 17:55:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Puppycorn wants to impress his skater friends with his sweet skills, except he has none</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 17:55:00" d="2020-05-21 18:15:00"><n>Unikitty</n>    <k>Unikitty and Hawkodile are &quot;lost at sea&quot;, stranded on a raft together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 18:15:00" d="2020-05-21 18:24:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin tells the Titans to stop being reckless teens or the Creepy Catcher will get them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 18:24:00" d="2020-05-21 18:33:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Santa calls it quits so the Titans must pitch in to save the holiday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 18:33:00" d="2020-05-21 18:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% The Titans play Spin The Bottle as Starfire tries to improve her vocabulary through kissing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 18:50:00" d="2020-05-21 18:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Control Freak informs the Titans that they are on a TV show he created and demands they earn him an award</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 18:59:00" d="2020-05-21 19:09:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Cyborg's real strength comes not from his robot parts, but from his favourite song</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 19:09:00" d="2020-05-21 19:30:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n>    <k>52% Robin tries to teach the Titans valuable life lessons by reading them fairytales but the others co-opt his stories and spin them into their own twisted yarns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 19:30:00" d="2020-05-21 19:41:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Tygra's feeling unappreciated by the other ThunderCats so he starts hanging out with Mumm-Ra and cleaning his Black Pyramid?! Whaaaaaaat?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 19:41:00" d="2020-05-21 20:00:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n>    <k>Every time Mumm-Ra gets a hold of a magic artefact to restore his powers the ThunderCats just smash it and turn him into a dinky skeleton again. Until today that is!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 20:00:00" d="2020-05-21 20:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Team Tennyson's thrift store shopping is ruined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 20:10:00" d="2020-05-21 20:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Team Tennyson travels to a ski resort for some fun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 20:30:00" d="2020-05-21 20:40:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% Osamu Kazami comes to take his son Shun back home and finds a defiance he hadn't co</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 20:40:00" d="2020-05-21 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n>    <k>48% Drago and the other AO Bakugan face an unseen threat with earth shattering power only to be left wondering if it was all a dream</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 21:00:00" d="2020-05-21 21:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Because of his cunning and tenacity Angelo always gets what he wants. Is this the way life is always going to be? Angelo has an existential crisis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 21:10:00" d="2020-05-21 21:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Elena and Angelo are grounded for fighting with each other. They have to put aside their differences and work together to escape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 21:25:00" d="2020-05-21 21:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Lola has a pigeon phobia. Paging Dr. Angelo and Dr. Sherwood to cure her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 21:35:00" d="2020-05-21 21:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% A new hipster cupcake shop opens across the street from Cathy’s siphoning off all the customers. Angelo and friends come up with strategies to help Cathy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 21:55:00" d="2020-05-21 22:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% In honor of older sisters, Slobber offers free tickets to whomever can make the best short film about their older sister. Angelo is all set</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 22:05:00" d="2020-05-21 22:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo searches for the ultimate object to bring to show and tell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 22:20:00" d="2020-05-21 22:30:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo’s photo bombs make him a big hit on the internet and he is loving his newfound popularity. Until, Butterfingers starts getting more “likes”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 22:30:00" d="2020-05-21 22:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% The equipment in Coach Zonka’s gym class is deemed a safety hazard so gym class is canceled permanently. Angelo attempts to rally the school to bring back gym class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 22:45:00" d="2020-05-21 23:15:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% As Lloyd and Harumi search the Oni Temple for the last mask, the ninja are taken hostage and discover Princess Harumi’s true intentions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 23:15:00" d="2020-05-21 23:45:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% The ninja appeal to the police commissioner of Ninjago in an effort to help save Lloyd and thwart Harumi’s efforts to resurrect the evil Lord Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 23:45:00" d="2020-05-21 23:56:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin spice up their friendship by introducing a third best friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-21 23:56:00" d="2020-05-22 00:07:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball has to save Mr Robinson’s life during Elmore’s Senior Talent Show!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 00:07:00" d="2020-05-22 00:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball tries to save Darwin from being kissed by a girl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 00:20:00" d="2020-05-22 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When Alan ditches Gumball to do something more fun, Gumball is desperate to track him down and make him pay for his betrayal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 00:30:00" d="2020-05-22 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% To try and make Mr Small feel like he’s inspired the students, Gumball and Darwin try to follow every piece of advice Mr Small gives them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 00:40:00" d="2020-05-22 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When Darwin asks for his advice on hats, Gumball suddenly can’t speak and offends Darwin. Darwin is convinced Gumball said he had a fat head</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 00:50:00" d="2020-05-22 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% When she has no one to share her lunch with, Jamie realises she needs a sweetheart. Darwin's the only one who doesn’t flee immediately, so he and Jamie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 01:00:00" d="2020-05-22 01:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Because of his cunning and tenacity Angelo always gets what he wants. Is this the way life is always going to be? Angelo has an existential crisis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 01:10:00" d="2020-05-22 01:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Elena and Angelo are grounded for fighting with each other. They have to put aside their differences and work together to escape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 01:25:00" d="2020-05-22 01:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Lola has a pigeon phobia. Paging Dr. Angelo and Dr. Sherwood to cure her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 01:35:00" d="2020-05-22 01:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% A new hipster cupcake shop opens across the street from Cathy’s siphoning off all the customers. Angelo and friends come up with strategies to help Cathy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 01:45:00" d="2020-05-22 01:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% In honor of older sisters, Slobber offers free tickets to whomever can make the best short film about their older sister. Angelo is all set</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 01:55:00" d="2020-05-22 02:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo searches for the ultimate object to bring to show and tell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 02:05:00" d="2020-05-22 02:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% Angelo’s photo bombs make him a big hit on the internet and he is loving his newfound popularity. Until, Butterfingers starts getting more “likes”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 02:15:00" d="2020-05-22 02:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n>    <k>59% The equipment in Coach Zonka’s gym class is deemed a safety hazard so gym class is canceled permanently. Angelo attempts to rally the school to bring back gym class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 02:25:00" d="2020-05-22 02:35:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>Vambre gets on Prohyas for playing the same song too much, and he exacts revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 02:35:00" d="2020-05-22 02:55:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% As Lloyd and Harumi search the Oni Temple for the last mask, the ninja are taken hostage and discover Princess Harumi’s true intentions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 02:55:00" d="2020-05-22 03:15:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n>    <k>67% The ninja appeal to the police commissioner of Ninjago in an effort to help save Lloyd and thwart Harumi’s efforts to resurrect the evil Lord Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 03:15:00" d="2020-05-22 03:25:00"><n>Mighty Magiswords - 5 Minute Shorts</n>    <k>53% Prohyas and Vambre's Warrior service is open for business as they are tasked to unclog a royal sink</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 03:25:00" d="2020-05-22 03:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Channel 6 Elmore News has all the top local stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 03:35:00" d="2020-05-22 03:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin find themselves in serious trouble when they agree to everything the new kid in school says. The truth is they can't understand a word that he says</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 03:45:00" d="2020-05-22 03:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The Wattersons are forced to rent out their house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 03:55:00" d="2020-05-22 04:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The kids find out Dad has been dressing as a woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 04:05:00" d="2020-05-22 04:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Everyone assumes Darwin &amp; Carrie's relationship is doomed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 04:15:00" d="2020-05-22 04:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Anais and psycho Jamie are accused of the same crime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 04:30:00" d="2020-05-22 04:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Dad decides to resolve the Watterson family's differences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 04:40:00" d="2020-05-22 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% The kids find out Dad has been dressing as a woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="1204" o="2020-05-22 04:50:00" d="2020-05-22 05:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n>    <k>81% Gumball, Darwin and Banana Joe investigate Banana Barbara's mysterious disappearance and uncover an old rival's shadowy scheme in the process</k>  </p>
</a>
