<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a><n>First Porno for Degenerate Daddy’s Girl - Estella Bathory</n><g><o>http://gonet.cz/~tri65dnigalerie/zanr/600/e/efc6b3a9778b23f57e2efb8b6f1ce61f.jpg</o></g><o>http://gonet.cz/~tri65dnigalerie/zanr/250/e/efc6b3a9778b23f57e2efb8b6f1ce61f.jpg</o><s o="2020-05-17 10:18:00" d="2020-05-17 11:02:00" n="Passion XXX" id_tv="1317"></s><p><k>1st Porno 4 Degenerate Daddy’s Girl. She may look sweet and innocent but she’s anything but. Estella Bathory is into hardcore BDSM, this is her very first porn shoot and this</k><d>1st Porno 4 Degenerate Daddy’s Girl. She may look sweet and innocent but she’s anything but. Estella Bathory is into hardcore BDSM, this is her very first porn shoot and this is what she does in it: - Vaginal fucking - Physical domination &amp; verbal abuse - Orgasms - Deepthroat &amp; face-fucking - Squirting - Spanking - Face-slapping - Face-spitting - Masturbation - Cumshot There’s no set-up to the scene. We just play it straight. It’s worth bearing in mind the sequence of events though because we didn’t shoot things in the order we usually do. The first chunk of sex is actually the photoshoot, which we won’t be publishing until Saturday. So bear in mind when you watch that that what you’re seeing is Estella getting fucked for the very first time on camera. She’s absolutely soaking and really wanted to cum but we wouldn’t let her. Next came the solo vid, when she came twice. And next comes the scene. Estella is a seriously kinky little madam. She’s into the Daddy stuff big time, adores a proper spanking and has a fetish for feet. She’s also got an endearing habit of opening her mouth and sticking her tongue out all the time. When asked during the fuck scene why she does this, she replies: “So dirty old men will come and stick their cocks in my mouth”. You’ve got to love her.</d></p><i><w>http://tv.sms.cz/televize/passion-xxx/20200517/1400270208-First-porno-for-degenerate-daddy-s-girl-estella-bathory</w></i><x></x></a>
