<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a><n>The War of the Roses</n><s o="2020-06-08 02:55:00" d="2020-06-08 04:50:00" n="TCM (v UPC)" id_tv="163"></s><p><k>Few things are sadder, sillier, or scarier than what can happen to a long-married couple when love dies. In THE WAR OF THE ROSES, director Danny DeVito and writer Michael Leeson (adapting a novel by Warren Adler) have captured just such a fiasco in its full ingloriousness, making their film the smartest, most sophisticated, and funniest American comedy of 1989. After 17 years of wedlock, the love Barbara Rose (Turner) once felt for her husband, Oliver (Douglas), has curdled into hate. She hates his phony laugh. She hates the way he patronizes her when she decides to start a catering business. She hates his dog (she's a cat person). She just hates him. He still loves her--as much as he can love anybody--but he loves their big, beautiful, antique-filled house more. And therein lies the cautionary tale, told by Gavin D'Amato (director DeVito himself), a divorce lawyer and associate in Oliver's firm who begins to recount the story (to a prospective client) in the film's prolog. Gavin has decided to represent Oliver in the divorce action; Barbara's attorney is Harry Thurmont. (He's played by G.D. Spradlin, whom viewers may remember as the military commander who sent Martin Sheen on his mission to terminate Marlon Brando in APOCALYPSE NOW. If you think the casting here is arbitrary, take note of the helicopter that begins buzzing by Gavin's office window as his tale gets progressively crazier.) Barbara wants no money, only the house. Oliver is ready to give up anything but the house. To help Oliver assert his claim and protect his assets, Gavin finds an obscure legal precedent that allows his client to remain in the house with Barbara until final deposition of assets is made. Stuck in legally binding close proximity--a dark reversal of their legally binding marriage--the Roses escalate tensions until the hostilities erupt into the full-scale war of the title. And no prisoners are taken. Barbara nails the door to Oliver's b</k></p><i><w>http://tv.sms.cz/televize/tcm-v-upc/20200608/1410331646-The-war-of-the-roses</w></i><x></x></a>
