<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a><n>The Specialist</n><s o="2020-05-17 23:40:00" d="2020-05-18 01:50:00" n="TCM (v UPC)" id_tv="163"></s><p><k>More like a direct-to-video exploitation movie on a grand scale than a major theatrical release, THE SPECIALIST is a glossy but surpassingly tacky movie. Its only appeal is to viewers who take the so-bad-it's-good approach to films in which the plot, dialogue, and mise-en-scene conspire at every turn to defeat their suspension of disbelief. In 1984, Ray Quick (Sylvester Stallone) and Ned Trent (James Woods), CIA explosives experts, are in the middle of a mission to blow up a South American drug dealer. But when the dealer's car appears, there's a little girl in it. Ray wants to abort the mission, but Ned intends to see it through, and the sequence ends with Ray and Ned at one another's throats. Flash forward to present-day Miami, where Ray is making a living as a freelance hitman. Desperate people contact him by computer, and he only takes the cases he wants. Ray's work is distinguished by its precision; he specializes in building and planting bombs that blow up only the intended target, leaving innocent bystanders shaken but unharmed. Against his better judgment, Ray is persuaded to take the case of May Munro (Sharon Stone), a sleek, panty-less temptress whose parents were killed by Miami drug lord Joe Leon (Rod Steiger). May wants revenge, and loner Ray agrees to help, even though she's determined to stay close by so she can savor her revenge. Complicating matters, Ned, who is now working for Leon, immediately recognizes Ray's signature explosive style. Ned is jockeying for power within the family, particularly in relation to Joe's son Tomas (Eric Roberts), and intends to use the situation to curry favor with Leon, while also exacting personal revenge (Ray, we learn, got him fired after that last mission). Meanwhile, Ray and May are falling in love, despite her insistence that she's no good for him. Betrayal follows betrayal: May turns out to be a pawn in Ned's plan for vengeance on Ray.</k></p><i><w>http://tv.sms.cz/televize/tcm-v-upc/20200517/1400494553-The-specialist</w></i><x></x></a>
