<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="15" t="2020-05-14 04:59:20"><p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-21 05:15:00" d="2020-05-21 05:35:00"><n u="The Detour - Season">The Detour - Season 2</n>    <k>The family reunites, but this time Robin makes a huge mistake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-21 05:35:00" d="2020-05-21 06:05:00"><n u="The Detour - Season">The Detour - Season 3</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-21 06:05:00" d="2020-05-21 08:50:00"><n>The Young Philadelphians</n>    <k>Drama of a young lawyer, from humble means, who grows to become a prominent figure in Philadelphia's high-society</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-21 08:50:00" d="2020-05-21 10:55:00"><n u="Major League">Major League II</n>    <k>This sequel finds the members of the championship Cleveland Indians team headed towards finishing the season in last place after their off-season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-21 10:55:00" d="2020-05-21 12:45:00"><n>Daniel Defoe's Robinson Crusoe</n>    <k>A British seaman, the sole survivor of a shipwreck, finds himself stranded on a remote island. Battling both nature and extreme isolation, Crusoe fights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-21 12:45:00" d="2020-05-21 14:50:00"><n>Edward Scissorhands</n>    <k>A kindly inventor creates a synthetic young man, but dies before completing his creation, leaving him stuck with scissors for hands, which ultimately</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-21 14:50:00" d="2020-05-21 16:50:00"><n>Mr. Nice Guy</n>    <k>Jackie is a well-known television chef who is drawn into a war between two rival gangs by a TV reporter, Diana, who has videotaped Giancarlo murdering a rival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-21 16:50:00" d="2020-05-21 18:50:00"><n>Dennis</n>    <k>Live-action film version of the comic strip, created in the early 1950s, about a young boy and his unusual view of the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-21 18:50:00" d="2020-05-21 21:00:00"><n>Wild Wild West</n>    <k>Special government agent James West and his co-hort Artemus Gordon, team up to thwart Dr Arliss Loveless who is plotting to assassinate the President of the United States</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-21 21:00:00" d="2020-05-21 23:00:00"><n>Hard to Kill</n>    <k>Upon awakening from a long coma, Agent Storm (Steven Seagal) must protect his loved ones from those who tried to kill him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-21 23:00:00" d="2020-05-22 01:05:00"><n>Tango &amp; Cash</n>    <k>Arch rival cops Sylvester Stallone and Kurt Russell are framed by a drug baron and must team up to clear their names</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-22 01:05:00" d="2020-05-22 02:30:00"><n>Destruction: Las Vegas</n>    <k>Discovering that an ancient Egyptian curse has been awakened, Nelson and Olive work together to stop it before it destroys Las Vegas!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-22 02:30:00" d="2020-05-22 04:30:00"><n>3000 Miles to Graceland</n>    <k>Fresh out of prison, seasoned criminal Michael Zane wastes no time setting up his next big heist by joining up with a new gang led by his old friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-22 04:30:00" d="2020-05-22 04:50:00"><n u="Miracle Workers - Season">Miracle Workers - Season 1</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-22 04:50:00" d="2020-05-22 05:15:00"><n u="Search Party - Season">Search Party - Season 1</n>    <k>When Dory discovers that her friend, Chantal has gone missing, she becomes obsessed with finding out what happened, even though her boyfriend</k>  </p>
</a>
