<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="11" t="2019-07-11 00:21:09"><p id_tv="163" o="2019-07-15 05:35:00" d="2019-07-15 06:00:00"><n u="Search Party - Season">Search Party - Season 2</n>    <k>After finding the not-so-missing Chantal and killing the not-so-villainous Keith, the gang is faced with the horrifying task of trying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2019-07-15 06:00:00" d="2019-07-15 08:30:00"><n>The Birdcage</n>    <k>Armand and Albert have a home life many would envy. They share a long-term committed relationship encompassing their lives and careers and have together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2019-07-15 08:30:00" d="2019-07-15 10:15:00"><n>Collision Course</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2019-07-15 10:15:00" d="2019-07-15 13:05:00"><n>The Shawshank Redemption</n>    <k>Andy Dufresne, a mild mannered New England banker, is convicted of murdering his wife and her lover. Despised at first by the other inmates because</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2019-07-15 13:05:00" d="2019-07-15 16:15:00"><n>There Will Be Blood</n>    <k>On the frontier of California's turn-of-the-century petroleum boom, Daniel Plainview transforms himself from a down-and-out silver miner raising</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2019-07-15 16:15:00" d="2019-07-15 18:50:00"><n>The Fugitive</n>    <k>A man is forced to go on the run after being falsely accused of killing his wife</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2019-07-15 18:50:00" d="2019-07-15 21:00:00"><n>Thunderbolt</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2019-07-15 21:00:00" d="2019-07-15 23:00:00"><n>Freddy vs. Jason</n>    <k>Freddy Krueger is in hell--literally. It's been nearly ten years since Krueger invaded peoples' dreams to exact his deadly form of revenge and murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2019-07-15 23:00:00" d="2019-07-16 01:05:00"><n>Scream</n>    <k>Iconic Wes Craven slasher, where a group of teens are terrorised by a serial-killer obsessed by horror movie cliché</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2019-07-16 01:05:00" d="2019-07-16 03:40:00"><n>The Departed</n>    <k>In South Boston the state police force is waging war on organized crime. Young undercover cop Billy Costigan is assigned to infiltrate the mob syndicate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2019-07-16 03:40:00" d="2019-07-16 05:35:00"><n>Once Upon a Honeymoon</n>    <k>This was a flawed attempt at the TO BE OR NOT TO BE genre, mixing comedy with Nazis. The two are as compatible as escargot and sauerkraut</k>  </p>
</a>
