<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="13" t="2019-08-13 02:29:36"><p id_tv="163" o="2019-08-20 05:35:00" d="2019-08-20 06:00:00"><n u="Those Who Can't - Season">Those Who Can't - Season 1</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2019-08-20 06:00:00" d="2019-08-20 08:30:00"><n>Citizen Kane</n>    <k>A psychological study of Charles Foster Kane, a powerful newspaper tycoon whose idealism was corrupted as he rose to enourmous wealth and power</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2019-08-20 08:30:00" d="2019-08-20 10:45:00"><n>Unknown</n>    <k>Oscar nominee Liam Neeson (Taken, Schindler's List) stars as Dr. Martin Harris, who awakens after a car accident in Berlin to discover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2019-08-20 10:45:00" d="2019-08-20 11:20:00"><n u="Action Zone - Season">Action Zone - Season 1</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2019-08-20 11:20:00" d="2019-08-20 13:45:00"><n>The Brothers Grimm</n>    <k>Legendary fairytale scribes, brothers Will and Jake Grimm, travel around the Napoleonic countryside vanquishing monsters and demons in exchange for quick money</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2019-08-20 13:45:00" d="2019-08-20 16:35:00"><n>The Abyss</n>    <k>Picture the opening scene of JAWS, except that, in THE ABYSS, it's not a great white shark but an underwater UFO that propels the movie into action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2019-08-20 16:35:00" d="2019-08-20 18:20:00"><n>Getaway</n>    <k>Brent Magna (Ethan Hawke) is a burned out race car driver who is thrust into a do-or-die mission behind the wheel when h is wife is kidnapped. With Brent’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2019-08-20 18:20:00" d="2019-08-20 21:00:00"><n>Outbreak</n>    <k>A deadly virus from the African rainforest quickly begins infecting the entire population of a small town in Northern California</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2019-08-20 21:00:00" d="2019-08-20 22:40:00"><n>The Final Destination</n>    <k>On what should have been a fun-filled day at the races, Nick O'Bannon has a horrific premonition in which a bizarre sequence of events causes multiple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2019-08-20 22:40:00" d="2019-08-21 00:30:00"><n u="Final Destination">Final Destination 5</n>    <k>Death returns for another wild ride in the latest &quot;5nal Destination.&quot; With the series' original producers on board, a script by the red-hot writer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2019-08-21 00:30:00" d="2019-08-21 02:50:00"><n>Starship Troopers</n>    <k>Upon graduating school, Johnny Rico volunteers for the Mobile Infantry to do his Federal Service. Far from having patriotic motives, Johnny has joined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2019-08-21 02:50:00" d="2019-08-21 04:20:00"><n>Mad Max</n>    <k>In a dystopian future Australia, Mel Gibson's cult antihero Max is a steely cop patrolling the lawless highways as the world slips slowly into chaos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2019-08-21 04:20:00" d="2019-08-21 05:35:00"><n>The Saint In London</n>    <k>The Saint's investigation of a counterfeiting ring uncovers a nest of spies</k>  </p>
</a>
