<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a><n>The Big Sky</n><s o="2019-08-18 03:55:00" d="2019-08-18 06:00:00" n="TCM (v UPC)" id_tv="163"></s><p><k>A stirring but overlong northwest frontier epic from Hawks which depicts the adventures of two young Kentuckians at the turn of the 19th century. Douglas and Martin search for Martin's uncle, Hunnicutt, a noted trapper and frontiersman, finding him in a St. Louis jail (into which they are thrown for brawling). All are bailed out by riverboat captain and trader Geray who needs Hunnicutt to guide his French company more than 1,000 miles into Blackfoot Indian territory where he intends to trade for fur pelts. On board the boat is a Blackfoot princess, Threatt, to whom Martin is attracted. In her silent response (he does not speak the language and their brief conversations must be interpreted by uncle Hunnicut) it is apparent that she loves him. A band of renegades, led by Davis, attack the boat, trying to eliminate the fur-trading competitors. They are defeated and the travelers reach Blackfoot country, where they are greeted as heroes for returning Threatt safely. (It is never explained what the Indian lady was doing so far east in the first place.) Martin is reluctant to stay with the woman he loves but, at the last minute, he bids farewell to Douglas and friends and settles with the Blackfoot tribe. Douglas was the only star in this languid, leisurely Hawks film which is superbly written by Nichols. The scenery is magnificent, even in black and white, shot on location in the Grand Teton National Park. Tiomkin's score is lyrical and haunting, on occasion full of his typical stirring bombast. (He had recently won two Oscars for score and song for HIGH NOON.) The Russian-born composer also created the score for Hawks' epic western RED RIVER. Aside from the fascinating upriver struggle where the men must pull the boat by rope while hostile Indians lurk nearby, the most interesting aspect of the film is the wizened Hunnicutt as the old trapper; he manages to steal almost every scene.</k></p><i><w>http://tv.sms.cz/televize/tcm-v-upc/20190818/1310241724-The-big-sky</w></i><x></x></a>
