<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="14" t="2020-04-09 04:36:08"><p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-16 05:15:00" d="2020-04-16 05:35:00"><n u="The Detour - Season">The Detour - Season 1</n>    <k>Having driven their van, 'Blue Thunder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-16 05:35:00" d="2020-04-16 06:00:00"><n u="The Detour - Season">The Detour - Season 1</n>    <k>Nate gets pulled over for driving under the influence, even though he's completely sober</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-16 06:00:00" d="2020-04-16 07:40:00"><n>Cold Zone</n>    <k>A storm is coming. No one could predict it. No one can measure it. Now one family must survive it. You can't come in from the cold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-16 07:40:00" d="2020-04-16 10:55:00"><n>The Last Emperor</n>    <k>The story of the last imperial ruler of China</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-16 10:55:00" d="2020-04-16 12:35:00"><n>The Seven Magnificent Gladiators</n>    <k>Swordsmen and archers. they were seven against an army. Warrior heroes on a mission of liberation, they're armed for action and ready for the conflict</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-16 12:35:00" d="2020-04-16 14:45:00"><n>Clash of the Titans</n>    <k>The ultimate struggle for power pits men against kings and kings against gods. But the war between the gods themselves could destroy the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-16 14:45:00" d="2020-04-16 16:50:00"><n>Step Up</n>    <k>Two dancers get paired up reluctantly for a showcase and set aside their differences to be successful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-16 16:50:00" d="2020-04-16 18:55:00"><n>Step Up 2: The Streets</n>    <k>When rebellious street dancer Andie lands at the elite Maryland School of the Arts, she finds herself fighting to fit in</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-16 18:55:00" d="2020-04-16 21:00:00"><n>The Mask</n>    <k>After discovering an ancient mask with strange powers, a timid bank clerk is instantly transformed into an indestructible superhero, able to fulfill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-16 21:00:00" d="2020-04-16 22:45:00"><n>Halloween 4: The Return of Michael Myers</n>    <k>Ten years ago, he changed the face of Halloween. Tonight. e's back!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-16 22:45:00" d="2020-04-17 00:45:00"><n>Halloween 5: The Revenge of Michael Myers</n>    <k>The citizens of Haddonfield, Illinois are about to endure the revenge of Michael Myers, as the presumed-dead killer returns to kill and kill again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-17 00:45:00" d="2020-04-17 02:25:00"><n>Halloween: H2O</n>    <k>Two decades after the first film, maniacal killer Michael Myers reappears to terrorise Jamie Lee Curtis one last time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-17 02:25:00" d="2020-04-17 04:05:00"><n>Godsend</n>    <k>A couple agree to have their deceased son cloned, under the supervision of an enigmatic doctor, but bizarre things start to happen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-17 04:05:00" d="2020-04-17 05:35:00"><n>Hercules, Samson &amp; Ulysses</n>    <k>When two legendary Greek heroes are marooned, they're pushed into conflict with the famed Biblical strongman</k>  </p>
</a>
