<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2020-06-01 04:35:57"><p id_tv="163" o="2020-06-08 05:15:00" d="2020-06-08 05:35:00"><n u="The Detour - Season">The Detour - Season 4</n>    <k>The Detour is an all-too-honest look at the family dynamic starring Jason Jones, Natalie Zea, Ashley Gerasimovich and Liam Carroll. Season four finds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-06-08 05:35:00" d="2020-06-08 06:00:00"><n u="The Detour - Season">The Detour - Season 4</n>    <k>The Detour is an all-too-honest look at the family dynamic starring Jason Jones, Natalie Zea, Ashley Gerasimovich and Liam Carroll. Season four finds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-06-08 06:00:00" d="2020-06-08 08:00:00"><n>Accidental Love</n>    <k>A small-town waitress gets a nail accidentally lodged in her head causing unpredictable behaviour that leads her to Washington, D.C., where sparks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-06-08 08:00:00" d="2020-06-08 09:55:00"><n>Major League</n>    <k>The Cleveland Indians are the worst baseball team on the national league. It's new owner, a former show girl, wants the team to lose in order</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-06-08 09:55:00" d="2020-06-08 11:50:00"><n>Dirty Dancing</n>    <k>Spending the summer at a Catskills resort with her family, Frances &quot;Baby&quot; Houseman falls in love with the camp's dance instructor, Johnny Castle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-06-08 11:50:00" d="2020-06-08 13:45:00"><n>Starsky &amp; Hutch</n>    <k>Detective David Starsky is the most dedicated undercover cop working the mean streets of Bay City, California. Maniacally devoted to his</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-06-08 13:45:00" d="2020-06-08 15:40:00"><n>The In-Laws</n>    <k>Right before his daughter's wedding, a mild-mannered foot doctor discovers that his future son-in-law's father is a free-wheeling international spy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-06-08 15:40:00" d="2020-06-08 17:55:00"><n>Around the World in 80 Days</n>    <k>An eccentric London inventor, Phileas Fogg, has come up with the secrets to flight, electricity, and even in-line skates, but the establishment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-06-08 17:55:00" d="2020-06-08 21:00:00"><n>The Guns of Navarone</n>    <k>A team of Allied saboteurs fight their way behind enemy lines to destroy a pair of Nazi guns on the Aegean island of Navarone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-06-08 21:00:00" d="2020-06-09 01:15:00"><n>Lawrence of Arabia</n>    <k>Sweeping epic about the real life adventures of T.E. Lawrence, a British major who unified Arab tribes and led them in the fight for independence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-06-09 01:15:00" d="2020-06-09 03:00:00"><n>Predator</n>    <k>A team of commandos on a mission in a Central American jungle find themselves hunted by an extraterrestrial warrior</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-06-09 03:00:00" d="2020-06-09 05:10:00"><n>The Young Philadelphians</n>    <k>Drama of a young lawyer, from humble means, who grows to become a prominent figure in Philadelphia's high-society</k>  </p>
</a>
