<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="15" t="2020-05-17 04:35:59"><p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-24 05:10:00" d="2020-05-24 05:35:00"><n u="Those Who Can't - Season">Those Who Can't - Season 3</n>    <k>When a Smoot student becomes a viral sensation, Shoemaker gets a brush with fame, and Loren and Abbey try to out-viral everyone with a video of their own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-24 05:35:00" d="2020-05-24 06:00:00"><n u="Those Who Can't - Season">Those Who Can't - Season 3</n>    <k>Out in the woods for a cross-country race, the gang stumbles upon a hermit they believe is a legendary serial killer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-24 06:00:00" d="2020-05-24 07:45:00"><n>Madeline</n>    <k>Horrified at the prospect of her beloved school being sold, a young French girl uses her wit and craftiness to attempt to save it, making an unlikely</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-24 07:45:00" d="2020-05-24 09:40:00"><n>Legally Blonde</n>    <k>Elle Woods is the president of her sorority and a natural blonde, but when her boyfriend heads to Harvard with an old flame, Elle heads there</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-24 09:40:00" d="2020-05-24 11:30:00"><n>Police Academy 5: Assignment Miami Beach</n>    <k>Fourth sequel to the original &quot;Police Academy&quot; takes place at a Police Chief's Convention with the typical hijinks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-24 11:30:00" d="2020-05-24 13:10:00"><n>Police Academy 6: City Under Siege</n>    <k>The latest &quot;Police Academy&quot; sequel is a mystery about a mob boss who orchestrates a massive crime wave in Los Angeles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-24 13:10:00" d="2020-05-24 14:50:00"><n>Police Academy VII: Mission to Moscow</n>    <k>While on a training mission in Moscow, the Police Academy gang get caught up in, and try to foil, a plan by Russian mafia boss to gain power via a hand held computer game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-24 14:50:00" d="2020-05-24 16:40:00"><n>Daniel Defoe's Robinson Crusoe</n>    <k>A British seaman, the sole survivor of a shipwreck, finds himself stranded on a remote island. Battling both nature and extreme isolation, Crusoe fights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-24 16:40:00" d="2020-05-24 18:30:00"><n>Legally Blonde 2: Red White and Blonde</n>    <k>Elle Woods has conquered Harvard law school, and now she’s heading to Washington D.C. to legally face down a cosmetics firm using her pet dog’s family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-24 18:30:00" d="2020-05-24 21:00:00"><n>Hellboy</n>    <k>Born in the flames of hell and brought to earth to perpetrate evil, Hellboy was rescued from sinister forces by the benevolent Professor Bruttenholm</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-24 21:00:00" d="2020-05-24 23:10:00"><n u="Predator">Predator 2</n>    <k>Set in Los Angeles in the year 1997 when the streets are ruled by Jamaican and Colombian drug dealers. A federal agent assists the LAPD in their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-24 23:10:00" d="2020-05-25 01:25:00"><n>Blade: Trinity</n>    <k>Deep in a remote desert, vampire leaders are resurrecting Dracula, the horrific creature who spawned their race. Now known as Drake, this awesome vampire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-25 01:25:00" d="2020-05-25 03:00:00"><n>From Dusk Till Dawn 3: The Hangman's Daughter</n>    <k>Story traces the early days of Santanico Pandemonium and Texas Ranger Earl McGraw</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-25 03:00:00" d="2020-05-25 04:45:00"><n>Roxanne</n>    <k>A modern-day Cyrano romances his Roxanne</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-05-25 04:45:00" d="2020-05-25 05:10:00"><n u="Search Party - Season">Search Party - Season 1</n>    <k>It's the dinner party from Hell when Dory and Drew invite Portia and Chantal's intense ex-boyfriend over in an effort to get some answers out of him</k>  </p>
</a>
