<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2020-04-10 04:37:31"><p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-17 05:35:00" d="2020-04-17 06:05:00"><n u="The Detour - Season">The Detour - Season 1</n>    <k>The Parkers begrudgingly stop to eat at a culturally insensitive roadside restaurant and dinner theater</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-17 06:05:00" d="2020-04-17 07:50:00"><n>Flight of the Navigator</n>    <k>An earth-born boy boards an alien spacecraft and embarks on a series of adventures with a crew of extraterrestrial creatures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-17 07:50:00" d="2020-04-17 10:25:00"><n>Big Fish</n>    <k>Will Bloom returns to his hometown and the sickbed of his estranged father, a famous teller of tall tales. But to connect with his father, Will tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-17 10:25:00" d="2020-04-17 12:25:00"><n>The Incredible Adventures of Marco Polo</n>    <k>In this globe-trotting adventure about the famous 13th Century explorer, Marco Polo sets out from Italy to find his missing father, and along</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-17 12:25:00" d="2020-04-17 14:20:00"><n>Bridge to Terabithia</n>    <k>Jess Aarons is an outsider at school and even in his own family. Jess has trained all summer to become the fastest kid in his middle school class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-17 14:20:00" d="2020-04-17 17:40:00"><n>The Aviator</n>    <k>A biographical chronicle which charts the early years of famous tycoon, Howard Hughes (1905-1976), whose eclectic career spanned across everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-17 17:40:00" d="2020-04-17 21:00:00"><n>Dune</n>    <k>Sweeping adaptation of Frank Herbert's epic Sci-Fi novel. Kyle MacLachlan stars as Paul Atreides, heir to a noble House on the planet Dune</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-17 21:00:00" d="2020-04-17 23:30:00"><n>Bram Stoker's Dracula</n>    <k>Based on the Victorian horror novel written by Bram Stoker in 1897, about the vampire Dracula, who is on a quest to be eternally reunited</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-17 23:30:00" d="2020-04-18 01:25:00"><n>Dragon</n>    <k>Liu Jin-xi (Donnie Yen) is a village craftsman whose quiet life is irrevocably shattered by the arrival of two notorious gangsters in the local general store</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-18 01:25:00" d="2020-04-18 03:10:00"><n>Snake in the Eagle's Shadow</n>    <k>A young orphan, bullied by school mates, befriends an old beggar and is rewarded by being taught a new form of martial arts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-18 03:10:00" d="2020-04-18 04:50:00"><n>Drive Angry</n>    <k>Firepower, Horsepower and Hellpower charge this 3D high-octane revenge actioner starring Oscar® winner Nicolas Cage. As a tougher-than-nails escapee</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-18 04:50:00" d="2020-04-18 05:15:00"><n u="The Detour - Season">The Detour - Season 1</n>    <k>Nate gets pulled over for driving under the influence, even though he's completely sober</k>  </p>
</a>
