<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="12" t="2020-04-14 04:33:20"><p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-21 05:30:00" d="2020-04-21 06:00:00"><n u="Those Who Can't - Season">Those Who Can't - Season 2</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-21 06:00:00" d="2020-04-21 07:55:00"><n>Lafayette Escadrille</n>    <k>Early in World War I, a young American joins the French air force</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-21 07:55:00" d="2020-04-21 09:40:00"><n>Flight of the Navigator</n>    <k>An earth-born boy boards an alien spacecraft and embarks on a series of adventures with a crew of extraterrestrial creatures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-21 09:40:00" d="2020-04-21 12:15:00"><n>Big Fish</n>    <k>Will Bloom returns to his hometown and the sickbed of his estranged father, a famous teller of tall tales. But to connect with his father, Will tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-21 12:15:00" d="2020-04-21 14:00:00"><n>Police Academy 2: Their First Assignment</n>    <k>After graduating from Police Academy, Mahoney and his friends are ready to deal with true crime. but their nasty new lieutenant at the station is setting them up to fail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-21 14:00:00" d="2020-04-21 16:45:00"><n>Dune</n>    <k>Sweeping adaptation of Frank Herbert's epic Sci-Fi novel. Kyle MacLachlan stars as Paul Atreides, heir to a noble House on the planet Dune</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-21 16:45:00" d="2020-04-21 19:20:00"><n>The Fugitive</n>    <k>A man is forced to go on the run after being falsely accused of killing his wife</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-21 19:20:00" d="2020-04-21 21:00:00"><n u="National Lampoon's Loaded Weapon">National Lampoon's Loaded Weapon 1</n>    <k>Take off on the &quot;Lethal Weapon&quot; series of films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-21 21:00:00" d="2020-04-21 23:25:00"><n u="Lethal Weapon">Lethal Weapon 3</n>    <k>When a crooked ex-cop forms a brutal ring of arms dealers, it's up to mis-matched cops Riggs and Murtaugh to fire off a bullet or fifty in pursuit of fast-paced justice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-21 23:25:00" d="2020-04-22 01:55:00"><n u="Lethal Weapon">Lethal Weapon 4</n>    <k>LAPD Detectives Martin Riggs, Roger Murtaugh, and Lorna Cole return to battle a the head of a Chinese Triad crime ring specialising in counterfeiting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-22 01:55:00" d="2020-04-22 03:50:00"><n>The Beach</n>    <k>In an age when all sensation seems to come digitally via the cell phone, video screen, pager and Internet, a young American backpacker named Richard yearns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="163" o="2020-04-22 03:50:00" d="2020-04-22 05:35:00"><n>Damon And Pythias</n>    <k>This spear and sandal epic was shot on location in Italy, and stars Don Burnett and Guy Williams as the title characters. The story is based on the Damon</k>  </p>
</a>
