<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a><n>A Fish Called Wanda</n><s o="2019-08-17 03:25:00" d="2019-08-17 05:10:00" n="TCM (v UPC)" id_tv="163"></s><p><k>Combining the talents of Monty Python stalwart Cleese and Ealing Studios veteran Crichton, this hilariously offbeat post-caper comedy benefits from two of British film comedy's most accomplished traditions. Cleese, who wrote the screenplay, stars as an emotionally and sexually repressed English barrister whose life is thrown into upheaval by the appearance of Wanda--not the fish of the title, but a sexy American thief played by Curtis. She and her gang--Cockney tough guy Georgeson, stuttering animal rights advocate Palin, and ex-CIA assassin Kline--pull off a well-executed jewel heist, but in the thieves' subsequent rush to double-cross one another and grab all the loot, Georgeson ends up in jail, and the booty remains hidden in a safety deposit box (the location of which is known only to him). Curtis has been dishing out sexual favors to her cohorts (save to Palin, whose heart apparently belongs to the finned Wanda) but hides her lovemaking with fellow American Kline from Georgeson by claiming that he is her brother. Deciding that the best way to learn the whereabouts of the jewels is through Georgeson's barrister, Cleese, Curtis poses as an American law student studying the British system (and idolizing Cleese) and sweeps the uptight Englishman off his feet. In so doing she liberates him from a stuffy suburban existence dominated by his nagging wife, Aitken, and his demanding, selfish daughter, Caylor (Cleese's real-life daughter). Their furtive affair is plagued by the insanely jealous, explosively violent Kline, who pops up and pops off at the most unexpected moments. Meanwhile, Georgeson has assigned the loyal Palin the task of eliminating Hayes, the old woman who saw them fleeing from the scene of their crime. Palin's attempts to do her in become increasingly painful for him (both physically and psychically), as he accidentally brings about the destruction (in Wile E. Coyote fashion) of her three lapdogs.</k></p><i><w>http://tv.sms.cz/televize/tcm-v-upc/20190817/1310241709-A-fish-called-wanda</w></i><x></x></a>
