<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2021-07-09 06:34:17"><p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-16 06:00:00" d="2021-07-16 07:00:00"><n>Best of Bloomberg Markets: Middle East</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Highlights of the week's most important business and financial issues shaping global markets, with a focus on the Middle East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-16 07:00:00" d="2021-07-16 08:00:00"><n>Bloomberg Daybreak: Europe</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Live market reports from London and overnight news from Wall Street. Markets never sleep and neither does Bloomberg News. Track investments 24 hours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-16 08:00:00" d="2021-07-16 10:00:00"><n>Bloomberg Markets: European Open</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Live from London, Bloomberg Markets: European Open is focused on bringing you the most important global business and breaking markets news and information as it happens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-16 10:00:00" d="2021-07-16 11:00:00"><n>Bloomberg Surveillance: Early Edition</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Bloomberg Surveillance: Early Edition with Francine Lacqua live from London, bringing insight on global markets and the top business stories of the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-16 11:00:00" d="2021-07-16 12:00:00"><n>Bloomberg Surveillance: Early Edition</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Bloomberg Surveillance: Early Edition with Francine Lacqua, Matt Miller and Kailey Leinz live from London, Berlin and New York, bringing insight on markets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-16 12:00:00" d="2021-07-16 13:00:00"><n>Bloomberg Surveillance</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Bloomberg Surveillance with Tom Keene, Jonathan Ferro and Lisa Abramowicz live from New York, bringing insight on global markets and the top business stories of the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-16 13:00:00" d="2021-07-16 14:00:00"><n>Bloomberg Surveillance</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Bloomberg Surveillance with Tom Keene, Jonathan Ferro and Lisa Abramowicz live from New York, bringing insight on global markets and the top business stories of the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-16 14:00:00" d="2021-07-16 15:00:00"><n>Bloomberg Surveillance</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Bloomberg Surveillance with Tom Keene, Jonathan Ferro and Lisa Abramowicz live from New York, bringing insight on global markets and the top business stories of the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-16 15:00:00" d="2021-07-16 16:00:00"><n>Bloomberg: The Open</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Jonathan Ferro hosts this programme showcasing the most insightful and informative Bloomberg charts to help position a global audience for the trading day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-16 16:00:00" d="2021-07-16 17:00:00"><n>Bloomberg Markets: Americas</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Live from New York, Bloomberg Markets: Americas is focused on bringing you the most important global business and breaking markets news and information as it happens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-16 17:00:00" d="2021-07-16 18:00:00"><n>Bloomberg Markets: European Close</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Bloomberg Markets: European Close analyses the major market moving stories across the day in Europe, hears from the biggest newsmakers and showcases</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-16 18:00:00" d="2021-07-16 19:00:00"><n>Bloomberg: Balance of Power</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Bloomberg: Balance of Power focuses on the politics and policies being shaped by the agenda of President Biden's administration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-16 19:00:00" d="2021-07-16 20:00:00"><n>Bloomberg Technology</n><t>Z</t>    <k>The only daily news programme focused exclusively on technology, innovation and the future of business. Hosted by Emily Chang in San Francisco</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-16 20:00:00" d="2021-07-16 22:30:00"><n>Bloomberg Markets: The Close</n><t>Z</t>    <k>This fast-paced programme is the quintessential market close show leading up to the final minutes and seconds before the closing bell on Wall Street</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-16 22:30:00" d="2021-07-16 23:00:00"><n>Bloomberg Markets: What'd You Miss?</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Bloomberg TV's flagship markets programme, providing key insights, analysis and context at the market close. It's a highly intelligent look at the markets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-16 23:00:00" d="2021-07-17 00:00:00"><n>Bloomberg Technology</n><t>Z</t>    <k>The only daily news programme focused exclusively on technology, innovation and the future of business. Hosted by Emily Chang in San Francisco</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-17 00:00:00" d="2021-07-17 01:00:00"><n>Bloomberg Wall Street Week</n><t>Z</t>    <k>David Westin speaks with top names in finance about the week's biggest issues on Wall Street</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-17 01:00:00" d="2021-07-17 01:30:00"><n>Money and Equality</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Many financial institutions have pledged to help reduce racial and gender inequality in the US. We speak with leaders in banking and finance, and academic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-17 01:30:00" d="2021-07-17 02:00:00"><n>Bloomberg Studio 1.0</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Jennifer Doudna. Biochemist Jennifer Doudna, co-winner of the 2020 Nobel Prize in Chemistry, talks about her work on the co-development of the genome</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-17 02:00:00" d="2021-07-17 03:00:00"><n>Best of Bloomberg Daybreak: Middle East</n><t>Z</t>    <k>A look at the week's most important business and financial issues shaping global markets, with a focus on the Middle East</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-17 03:00:00" d="2021-07-17 03:30:00"><n u="The David Rubenstein Show">The David Rubenstein Show VI (21)</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Secretary Gina Raimondo. Philanthropist and financier David Rubenstein uncovers inside stories from the most influential minds in business</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-17 03:30:00" d="2021-07-17 04:00:00"><n>Bloomberg Front Row</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Dan Pinto, JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. Bloomberg talks with Co-President and COO of JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co, Dan Pinto, about his career and his work at the global</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="167" o="2021-07-17 04:00:00" d="2021-07-17 05:00:00"><n>Bloomberg Wall Street Week</n><t>Z</t>    <k>David Westin speaks with top names in finance about the week's biggest issues on Wall Street</k>  </p>
</a>
