<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2019-08-13 01:53:34"><p id_tv="193" o="2019-08-19 05:00:00" d="2019-08-19 05:10:00"><n>Arirang News</n>    <k>The Arirang NEWS quickly delivered the news about National/Politics, North Korea, Economy, IT/Science, Foreign Policy, World, Life/Culture of the Korea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="193" o="2019-08-19 05:10:00" d="2019-08-19 05:20:00"><n>Arirang Special</n>    <k>Arirang Special features a variety of unique and special programs produced by Arirang TV. These exciting programs will open your eyes to a new part of the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="193" o="2019-08-19 05:20:00" d="2019-08-19 06:00:00"><n>Heart to Heart</n>    <k>The talk show invites personalities making names for themselves in various fields and holds in-depth conversations about their values and future plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="193" o="2019-08-19 06:00:00" d="2019-08-19 07:00:00"><n>Arirang Prime</n>    <k>Arirang Prime is about different social and cultural topics between Korea and the international community. It is a fun and informative documentary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="193" o="2019-08-19 07:00:00" d="2019-08-19 07:50:00"><n>Seeking Korean Treasures</n>    <k>Seeking Korean Treasures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="193" o="2019-08-19 07:50:00" d="2019-08-19 08:00:00"><n>NOW</n>    <k>This up close and personal look gives weekly insights into what is happening around Korea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="193" o="2019-08-19 08:00:00" d="2019-08-19 09:00:00"><n>Simply K-Pop</n>    <k>Kpop fans around the world get up close with this unique music program! Watch Kpop stars as they perform on-stage and interact with the audience</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="193" o="2019-08-19 09:00:00" d="2019-08-19 09:30:00"><n>PromiSINGER</n>    <k>PromiSINGER is a show-mentary (variety show + mini-docu) starring the rookie idols of K-Pop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="193" o="2019-08-19 09:30:00" d="2019-08-19 10:00:00"><n>Peace Insight</n>    <k>A program that restores the homogeneity of North and South Korea by finding a common culture between the two countries and enhances the international</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="193" o="2019-08-19 10:00:00" d="2019-08-19 10:30:00"><n>The Chamber</n>    <k>&quot;The Chamber&quot; offers comprehensive and in-depth coverage of economic issues both in Korea and around the world with top economic experts, ultimately</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="193" o="2019-08-19 10:30:00" d="2019-08-19 11:00:00"><n u="Travel Agency">Travel Agency 2</n>    <k>Global content Creators from all around the world will create a brand new map, introducing every inch of Korea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="193" o="2019-08-19 11:00:00" d="2019-08-19 11:10:00"><n>Arirang News</n>    <k>The Arirang NEWS quickly delivered the news about National/Politics, North Korea, Economy, IT/Science, Foreign Policy, World, Life/Culture of the Korea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="193" o="2019-08-19 11:10:00" d="2019-08-19 11:20:00"><n>Arirang Special</n>    <k>Arirang Special features a variety of unique and special programs produced by Arirang TV. These exciting programs will open your eyes to a new part of the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="193" o="2019-08-19 11:20:00" d="2019-08-19 12:00:00"><n>Heart to Heart</n>    <k>The talk show invites personalities making names for themselves in various fields and holds in-depth conversations about their values and future plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="193" o="2019-08-19 12:00:00" d="2019-08-19 13:00:00"><n>Showbiz Korea</n>    <k>Showbiz Korea aired its first episode in 2002 and kept its viewers all over the world up to date on the news about Korean celebrities and the entertainment industry!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="193" o="2019-08-19 13:00:00" d="2019-08-19 13:30:00"><n>NOW</n>    <k>This up close and personal look gives weekly insights into what is happening around Korea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="193" o="2019-08-19 13:30:00" d="2019-08-19 14:00:00"><n>I'm Live</n>    <k>?I'm Live is a live concert program featuring Korea's top musicians ?Musicians and fans interact with one another in close proximity, becoming one in the name of music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="193" o="2019-08-19 14:00:00" d="2019-08-19 14:30:00"><n>Money Monster</n>    <k>Money Monster presents a variety of future-oriented perspectives on the fourth industrial revolution and its impact on the industries as well as the consumption patterns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="193" o="2019-08-19 14:30:00" d="2019-08-19 15:00:00"><n u="Architecture">Architecture 101</n>    <k>New living space trends! Home is more than an investment and more than a place to sleep! From house-building know-how and tips to architectural theories from pros! Everything there is to know about house-building. Architecture 101, a program on unique homes, begins now!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="193" o="2019-08-19 15:00:00" d="2019-08-19 15:30:00"><n>The Point : World Affairs</n>    <k>&quot;The Point: World Affairs&quot; is a weekly current affairs program that sheds light on one of the key issues affecting South Korea and the globe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="193" o="2019-08-19 15:30:00" d="2019-08-19 16:00:00"><n>Arts Avenue</n>    <k>Arts Avenue is a culture and arts magazine program, featuring the diverse and dynamic world of Korean Arts or 'K-Arts' from its past to present</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="193" o="2019-08-19 16:00:00" d="2019-08-19 19:00:00"><n>Arirang Special</n>    <k>Arirang Special features a variety of unique and special programs produced by Arirang TV. These exciting programs will open your eyes to a new part of the world</k>  </p>
</a>
