<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="120" t="2021-07-13 04:56:53"><p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 05:05:00" d="2021-07-20 05:15:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 2016 II (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Super-Villain Team-Up
After a lull in alien antics, a restless Ben suggests to Max and Gwen that he might be a better hero if he went solo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 05:15:00" d="2021-07-20 05:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 2016 II (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>30% The Feels
While Max and Gwen revel in the holiday spirit of Winter Wonderland, Ben couldn't be more unamused and focused on the toys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 05:25:00" d="2021-07-20 05:35:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Phantom Thief Comes to Call
An archeological discovery is made in Los Volmos. Exploration at the site is cut short, when a master thief</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 05:35:00" d="2021-07-20 05:50:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Phantom Thief Ajit
An Ancient Bakugon artifact from an archeological discovery is placed in the Los Volmos Museum. The Awesome Brawlers are charged</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 05:50:00" d="2021-07-20 05:55:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dances with Walruses
Magoo thinks he’s herding cattle through the desert but is in fact on an ice floe with walruses. He takes Fizz and Weasel for cattle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 05:55:00" d="2021-07-20 06:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Bodyguard
Fizz has dressed Weasel up as a supervillain in order to pretend to save the city. Magoo mistakes his disguised neighbor for an actress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 06:05:00" d="2021-07-20 06:10:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Not Without My Hamster
Fizz and Weasel are at the supermarket buying ingredients to make the world’s best cake. They bump into Magoo who thinks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 06:10:00" d="2021-07-20 06:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Curse of the Pyramid
Magoo thinks that he is lost in a pyramid but he is in fact in a big conference room where Fizz is about to perform a stand-up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 06:25:00" d="2021-07-20 06:30:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Deep Sea Diving
Magoo thinks he’s underwater scooting and has discovered Atlantis. In fact he’s in New York riding Fizz’s latest invention:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 06:30:00" d="2021-07-20 06:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Shaaaaaark!
Magoo thinks he’s a beach lifeguard but is actually on an ice floe and the swimmers are penguins! When Fizz shows up in a submarine to kidnap</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 06:40:00" d="2021-07-20 06:45:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Magoo the Sorcerer
Fizz and Weasel are trying to steal the president’s jokebook. Magoo thinking he is visiting a museum of sorcery mistakes Weasel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 06:45:00" d="2021-07-20 07:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Concrete Jungle
Fizz has invented a machine which turns spoiled brats into perfect children. Weasel accidentally launches Fizz next to Magoo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 07:00:00" d="2021-07-20 07:25:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Worst in Show
While on a trip to New York Scooby and the gang find themselves taking part in a dog show competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 07:25:00" d="2021-07-20 07:55:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Mysteries on the Disorient Express
Scooby and his friends decide to go on a train trip. But they learn that pets are not allowed in the main carriages</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 07:55:00" d="2021-07-20 08:05:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Too Many Treasures
Hoping to fix their fort, Craig enlists the 10 Speeds to give them a ride to the legendary Junk Pile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 08:05:00" d="2021-07-20 08:20:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Final Book
The last book of Kelsey's favorite fantasy series goes missing from the library, so Craig decides to help her solve the mystery of who took it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 08:20:00" d="2021-07-20 08:30:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% Wildernessa
An encounter with Wildernessa, guardian of the wilderness, inspires Kelsey to take up a cause</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 08:30:00" d="2021-07-20 08:50:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% Sunday Clothes
JP dirties his last clean clothes and he must wear his Sunday best to the creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 08:50:00" d="2021-07-20 09:00:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% Escape From Family Dinner
There's a huge water balloon fight at the creek but Craig is stuck at home for a family dinner, unless he can escape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 09:00:00" d="2021-07-20 09:15:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% Monster in the Garden
Craig is determined to catch the monster that has been wreaking havoc in Granddad's garden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 09:15:00" d="2021-07-20 09:25:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% The Curse
Craig, Kelsey and JP run afoul of some no-good teenage witches and are cursed! Lousy teenagers!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 09:25:00" d="2021-07-20 09:35:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Future Is Cardboard
The kids meet an eccentric Cardboard Creator that invites Craig to help finish his masterpiece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 09:35:00" d="2021-07-20 09:55:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dog Decider
Unable to make tough decisions, Craig decides to put his choices in the hands of a dog named Fred</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 09:55:00" d="2021-07-20 10:05:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Tez Says
Vic &amp; Val are in awe of the new magician in town, but things go awry when they agree to help him out with a new trick, despite Chata's wishes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 10:05:00" d="2021-07-20 10:20:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Forever Ever
When Vic and Val do a sloppy job cleaning up in Maria Theresa's attic, they accidentally set off a time loop, trapping them in an endless</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 10:20:00" d="2021-07-20 10:30:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Tree Buds
Vic and Val build a treehouse and Val dismisses Vic with a frivolous task so he can build the treehouse exactly how he wants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 10:30:00" d="2021-07-20 10:50:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>On Nagual Hill
Vic &amp; Val take over a forest HILL and build an epic WATERSLIDE, disturbing the plants and animals that normally inhabit it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 10:50:00" d="2021-07-20 10:55:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Wild Modeling
Grizzy and the Lemmings discover the ranger's latest acquisition: a 3D printer that will duplicate anything at all in miniature format</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 10:55:00" d="2021-07-20 11:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The Bear Next Door
Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a strange gateway to a parallel world. On the other side, there is the same cabin, only it doesn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 11:00:00" d="2021-07-20 11:10:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Wild Zapping
Grizzy and the Lemmings clumsily destroy the TV remote control while fighting over who gets to watch his favorite program. While looking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 11:10:00" d="2021-07-20 11:20:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Warning: Unlimited Lemmings
The Lemmings discover that by changing the speed limit sign on the side of the road, they can accelerate truck traffic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 11:20:00" d="2021-07-20 11:30:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bouncing Bear
While trying to stop the Lemmings from playing their extreme trampoline game, Grizzy slips on the canvas and unwittingly executes an amazing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 11:30:00" d="2021-07-20 11:35:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Masked Racoon
The Lemmings have hitched up a racoon with a sweet-tooth to their sled and get a ride by throwing cookies in front of the creature with a sling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 11:35:00" d="2021-07-20 11:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Spinning Lemmings
The Lemmings have unearthed a strange little gadget from amongst the Forest Ranger's belongings: a hand spinner. Grizzy thinks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 11:40:00" d="2021-07-20 11:55:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Game Madness
The Lemmings play with poseable figurines of wild Canadian animals. When Grizzy sees that the bear figurine has been put inside a little</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 11:55:00" d="2021-07-20 12:00:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Cabin Fervor
Bugs and Squeaks are going on week three of being snowed in when they discover the last bit of food in the house. Let the battle begin!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 12:00:00" d="2021-07-20 12:05:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% The Grand Barbari-yon
Bugs and Squeaks take a trip to the Grand Canyon only to have their travels sidelined by a run-in with the Barbarian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 12:05:00" d="2021-07-20 12:10:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Giant Rabbit Hunters
The dim hunters believe Bigfoot is a giant rabbit and hunt him. Bugs just wants to be left alone but keeps getting involved</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 12:10:00" d="2021-07-20 12:20:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Amusement Pork
Bugs wants to be the first to ride a new mega roller coaster and finds himself lucky to be front and center with Porky Pig</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 12:20:00" d="2021-07-20 12:25:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Now You See Me Now You Still See Me
Bugs attempts to help Dr. Clovenhoof become the Superhero he's always dreamed of becoming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 12:25:00" d="2021-07-20 12:30:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Tis the Seasoning
Bugs and Yosemite Sam fight over the last hot toy of the holiday season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 12:30:00" d="2021-07-20 12:35:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Winter Blunderland
When Squeaks mistakes the Barbarian for Santa Claus Bugs has to intervene in order to retrieve his Holiday Wish List</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 12:35:00" d="2021-07-20 12:50:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Ear! We! Go!
Bugs' slumber is interrupted when his ears decide it's time to go dancing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 12:50:00" d="2021-07-20 13:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Nest
A breaking news report tells the Wattersons their neighbour is among the several mysterious disappearances happening across Elmore. Their search</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 13:00:00" d="2021-07-20 13:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Points
Gumball and Darwin agree to do all of Tobias’s chores in exchange for good points! Gumball and Darwin discover that Tobias is doing way better</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 13:10:00" d="2021-07-20 13:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Bus
When Rocky suggests that the Elmore Junior High kids skip school, the bus is boarded by criminals who seem to want to teach them the importance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 13:25:00" d="2021-07-20 13:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Night
As night falls in Elmore the Moon takes us on a tour through the various dreams - and nightmares - of the town's slumbering inhabitants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 13:35:00" d="2021-07-20 13:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Misunderstandings
Gumball has misunderstood about his date with Penny: he thought they were meeting for dinner, but they were actually meeting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 13:55:00" d="2021-07-20 14:05:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Legend of the Hidden Skate Park
While searching for a hidden skate park, V and V happen upon a tribe of wild kids, who live in a society without rules or adults</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 14:05:00" d="2021-07-20 14:25:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Cleaning Day
Victor and Valentino gain a newfound respect for cleanliness after Chata's house traps them inside its labyrinth of ancient, magical walls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 14:25:00" d="2021-07-20 14:35:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Babysitter
Vic and Val want to sneak out to a secret fireworks show but are thwarted when their new babysitter, Xochi, outsmarts them at every turn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 14:35:00" d="2021-07-20 14:50:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hurricane Chata
When Vic and Val discover that Chata's emotions control the water in the lake, they use it to their advantage and start their own wave pool business</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 14:50:00" d="2021-07-20 15:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>TV Knight 3
Batman is more interested in watching TV than participating in his birthday party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 15:00:00" d="2021-07-20 15:10:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% Bro-Pocalypse
When the male Titans are injured Raven and Starfire must become bros to stop the Bropocalypse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 15:10:00" d="2021-07-20 15:25:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% Flashback: Part 1
A flashback reveals how Robin formed the Teen Titans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 15:25:00" d="2021-07-20 15:35:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% Flashback: Part 2
A flashback reveals how Robin changed from mild-mannered sidekick to quick-tempered leader</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 15:35:00" d="2021-07-20 15:50:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% The Scoop
The Titans find it odd when Starfire becomes friends with an ice cream scoop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 15:50:00" d="2021-07-20 16:00:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Shortcut
An unusually hot day at the Creek melts all of Kit's ice pops, so Craig helps her find a short cut to her frozen snack supplier before everyone else melts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 16:00:00" d="2021-07-20 16:20:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Deep Creek Salvage
The Trio finds gold in the muddy depths of the Creek so Craig builds a rig to recover it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 16:20:00" d="2021-07-20 16:30:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% Dibs Court
When a kid claims dibs on the Stump, Craig has no choice but to take them to court. Dibs Court</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 16:30:00" d="2021-07-20 16:40:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% The Great Fossil Rush
JP finds a fossil in the Creek which quickly causes the landscape to change</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 16:40:00" d="2021-07-20 17:00:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Alone Quest
Craig has an &quot;emergency&quot; leaving Kelsey alone at the Stump</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 17:00:00" d="2021-07-20 17:25:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Worst in Show
While on a trip to New York Scooby and the gang find themselves taking part in a dog show competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 17:25:00" d="2021-07-20 17:55:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Mysteries on the Disorient Express
Scooby and his friends decide to go on a train trip. But they learn that pets are not allowed in the main carriages</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 17:55:00" d="2021-07-20 18:00:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... II (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Tail of Two Kitties
Ginger accidentally backs her car over Butch's tail. Feeling awful, she brings the alley cat into her home until he's feeling better</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 18:00:00" d="2021-07-20 18:05:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... II (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vanishing Creamed
Hildie is mixing a batch of foot balm that'll soften and beautify her gnarly-looking feet. She has Tom rub it in, nice and good</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 18:05:00" d="2021-07-20 18:20:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... II (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Unhappily Harried After
It's Tom's wedding day! He's getting married to Toodles in a backyard wedding that we're experiencing through the</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 18:20:00" d="2021-07-20 18:25:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... II (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In the Beginning
We open on a SOLD sign in front of what will be Rick and Ginger's house. Inside, the house is empty – no Rick, no Ginger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 18:25:00" d="2021-07-20 18:35:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... II (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Splinter of Discontent
Tom &amp; Jerry help Tyke with a splinter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 18:35:00" d="2021-07-20 18:50:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... II (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Uncle Pecos Rides Again
Tom and Jerry are in the middle of it when Tom hears someone singing the tale of a cat who met his unfortunate, painful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 18:50:00" d="2021-07-20 19:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Stories
Fed up with having to listen to Molly's long tedious anecdotes Gumball and Darwin try to teach her how to make them sound more exciting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 19:00:00" d="2021-07-20 19:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Guy
Gumball and Darwin put Anais' new friend -- Josh -- through a series of tests, to see if he's good enough for their sister</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 19:10:00" d="2021-07-20 19:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Boredom
Gumball and Darwin are convinced it's one of those days when nothing interesting is happening. But as they walk around Elmore in search</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 19:25:00" d="2021-07-20 19:35:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nice to Meet You, Bakugan!
Magnus’ sister Emily is back and this time she has come along with a new pink Bakugan in tow -Webam. Emily and Webam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 19:35:00" d="2021-07-20 19:55:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Magnus
After the Tiko incident, Bakugan brawling with a device has become extremely restricted. But there will always be people using devices to control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 19:55:00" d="2021-07-20 20:05:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% Chicken in the Cradle
Beast Boy neglects his responsibilities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 20:05:00" d="2021-07-20 20:15:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% Kabooms: Part 1
The Titans are excited to see the movie version of their favorite show, &quot;Babies vs. Dogs&quot; until the movie's exposition makes watching it super-boring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 20:15:00" d="2021-07-20 20:30:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% Kabooms: Part 2
Inspired by the &quot;Babies vs Dogs&quot; movie, the Titans decide to make a big Hollywood film of their own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 20:30:00" d="2021-07-20 20:40:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% Tower Renovation
The Titans go house hunting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 20:40:00" d="2021-07-20 21:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Quantum Fun
Robin takes the other Titans on a trip through the dizzying world of quantum physics</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 21:00:00" d="2021-07-20 21:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Move
Gumball confronts Clayton about his fabled Seven Pressure Point Heart Exploding Technique assuming it’s another one of his outlandish claims</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 21:10:00" d="2021-07-20 21:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Law
Gumball jaywalks and is pulled over by Donut Cop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 21:25:00" d="2021-07-20 21:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Allergy
Darwin starts sneezing repeatedly and it seems he can't stop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 21:35:00" d="2021-07-20 21:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Mothers
It's Mother's Day and Gumball and Darwin discover that Tobias and Banana Joe have both made a card for The Best Mum in the World</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 21:55:00" d="2021-07-20 22:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% The Balance Of Nature
Angelo makes Tracy cry and feels terrible about it. He declares a truce. Problem is… their growing friendship throws off the balance of nature!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 22:05:00" d="2021-07-20 22:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Cat Burglar
Joe Mama has been stealing stuff from around town and storing it under Angelo’s bed. Angelo and friends embark on a reverse scavenger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 22:20:00" d="2021-07-20 22:40:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu IX (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% The Weakest Link
Lloyd turns the tables on Harumi to take his father’s power away and the Ninja learn what it takes to be a Dragon Hunter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 22:40:00" d="2021-07-20 22:50:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Madtrap
Madcap and Princess SugarSalt trap Axel and the team inside a Minergy-powered labyrinth that attacks them with their greatest fears, forcing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 22:50:00" d="2021-07-20 23:05:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Four Color Fallout
Axel Galileo and Sarge get Minergy-transported by Madcap into the pages of Axel's favorite comic book the hero of which turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 23:05:00" d="2021-07-20 23:15:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Grin and Bear It
When a toothache sends Axel to the dentist the team must fight off Princess SugarSalt who confuses Axel's new crown for the real thing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 23:15:00" d="2021-07-20 23:25:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Green with Envy
When the local news interviews Uncle Andrew about his toy inventing, an envious Galileo stages a play in the park with</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 23:25:00" d="2021-07-20 23:35:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Return of Thermometron 9000
During a brutal heatwave Axel and his team must track down Thermometron 9000, stolen by Ice Crusher for two purposes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 23:35:00" d="2021-07-21 00:00:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu IX (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% The Weakest Link
Lloyd turns the tables on Harumi to take his father’s power away and the Ninja learn what it takes to be a Dragon Hunter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 00:00:00" d="2021-07-21 00:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Heart
When Mr Robinson accidentally lets slip how little he cares for Gumball and Darwin, they react by giving him the cold shoulder. Surprisingly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 00:10:00" d="2021-07-21 00:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Ghouls
It's Halloween in Elmore. As the kids go trick or treating we see what everyone in town is up to. The ghosts and ghouls are finding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 00:20:00" d="2021-07-21 00:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The BFFS
Gumball's old BFF, Fuzzy, turns up on his doorstep. Darwin struggles to accept that there was someone before him and fails to contain his jealousy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 00:35:00" d="2021-07-21 00:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Agent
Gumball and Darwin's clothes go missing after a swimming lesson, and Gumball is forced to wear a tuxedo from the lost and found office</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 00:45:00" d="2021-07-21 00:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Decisions
When everything goes wrong in Darwin's life, he begins to suspect that Gumball's bad influence might be to blame. Darwin decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 00:55:00" d="2021-07-21 01:05:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Web
Gumball and Darwin realize that the adult residents of Elmore are dangerously naive when it comes to being safe online</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 01:05:00" d="2021-07-21 01:15:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Friend
Anais throws a party but no-one shows up as she has no friends or social skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 01:15:00" d="2021-07-21 01:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Saint
Alan is so good-natured that Gumball feels compelled to make him lose his temper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 01:30:00" d="2021-07-21 01:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Society
Things aren’t going Gumball’s way at school so he assumes there must be a Secret Society</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 01:40:00" d="2021-07-21 01:50:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Spoiler
Gumball and Darwin want to see the scariest film of the year</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 01:50:00" d="2021-07-21 02:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Countdown
Gumball and Darwin hit snooze too many times on their alarm clock and miss the school-bus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 02:00:00" d="2021-07-21 02:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Pow!
Angelo and friends attempt to negotiate a deal for Peter and Cooper’s nonsensical home-made comic book with a famous comic book publisher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 02:10:00" d="2021-07-21 02:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Better Call Angelo
Angelo attempts to rack up the high score on an online business rating service to win free dinner at a fancy Japanese Steak House</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 02:25:00" d="2021-07-21 02:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Electra
When Dad surprises the family with a brand new Electra smart home device everyone loves it at first then Dad gets hooked and Angelo and Elena</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 02:35:00" d="2021-07-21 02:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Best Friends Forever
After failing an online “best friends” quiz Sherwood and Angelo drift apart. Angelo discovers the quiz was fake and tries to repair his relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 02:45:00" d="2021-07-21 03:00:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Cook Off
Angelo enters a pie baking contest with his Dad as his partner until the two have creative differences and go it alone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 03:00:00" d="2021-07-21 03:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Procrastinators
Gumball and Darwin are offended when Mom calls them “procrastinators” once she’s told them what it means</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 03:10:00" d="2021-07-21 03:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Shell
While performing a school play Gumball is so nervous about kissing Penny that he accidentally head-butts her and cracks open her shell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 03:20:00" d="2021-07-21 03:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Mirror
Gumball receives a scare-email from a freaky ghost and decides to ignore it despite Darwin's advice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 03:35:00" d="2021-07-21 03:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Burden
Vice Principal Brown gives Gumball and Darwin the ancient school hamster Chris Morris to look after for the weekend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 03:45:00" d="2021-07-21 04:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Bros
When Darwin and Gumball reveal how they’d spend their perfect day Gumball confesses that he would spend it with Penny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 04:00:00" d="2021-07-21 04:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Uploads
Gumball and Darwin try to tear themselves away from the internet but end up falling down the Elmore Stream-hole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 04:10:00" d="2021-07-21 04:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Wicked
After being framed for feeding coffee to the squirrels in the park, Gumball proclaims that Mrs Robinson is pure evil. Darwin tells</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 04:20:00" d="2021-07-21 04:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Origins
When Mom and Dad struggle to keep hyperactive toddler-aged Gumball from trashing the house and exhausting them they decide to buy him a pet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 04:30:00" d="2021-07-21 04:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Origins Part Two
Via the sewers Darwin finds himself flushed out to sea. He is terrified but determined to make his way back to the Wattersons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 04:40:00" d="2021-07-21 04:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Traitor
When Alan ditches Gumball to do something more fun Gumball is desperate to track him down and make him pay for his betrayal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-21 04:55:00" d="2021-07-21 05:05:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 2016 II (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Chicken Nuggets of Wisdom
When Ben and Max get into an argument, Ben goes Heatblast to blow off steam against Max's wishes, but once Dr. Animo spots</k>  </p>
</a>
