<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="104" t="2020-05-12 04:31:09"><p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 05:00:00" d="2020-05-19 05:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% A group of kids get locked in the school after their parents have a charity gala. They appoint Gumball as leader to get them out but it leads to chaos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 05:10:00" d="2020-05-19 05:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Clayton shapeshifts into people to take their detentions for money. He starts framing people for misdemeanors so GB and DW must track him down to stop him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 05:20:00" d="2020-05-19 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Sarah finds a notebook from an awesome store!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 05:35:00" d="2020-05-19 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Vice Principal Brown gives Gumball and Darwin the ancient school hamster, Chris Morris, to look after for the weekend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 05:45:00" d="2020-05-19 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball decides to put Mr. Small's eco-friendly principles to the test but it doesn't quite go as planned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 06:00:00" d="2020-05-19 06:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Ben and Max get into an argument, Ben goes Heatblast to blow off steam against Max's wishes; but Dr. Animo spots him and subsequently turns Max into a chicken</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 06:10:00" d="2020-05-19 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After Ben stumbles upon a video of Cannonbolt ripping up a computer lab on the internet, Team Tennyson must race to State U where Ben discovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 06:25:00" d="2020-05-19 06:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball accidentally uploads a video of himself and wants it gone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 06:35:00" d="2020-05-19 06:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Watterson kids come up with a fool-proof plan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 06:50:00" d="2020-05-19 07:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball refuses to get out of bed because he is in a lousy mood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 07:00:00" d="2020-05-19 07:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Nicole arranges a playdate for Anais with the son of a classy lady she met at the supermarket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 07:15:00" d="2020-05-19 07:24:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% After not receiving participation medals, the Titans must demonstrate what they learned at camp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 07:24:00" d="2020-05-19 07:40:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When her teammates turns evil it's up to Lady Legasus to stop the League of Legs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 07:40:00" d="2020-05-19 07:51:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Cats' Lair is attacked by gold-loving robot pirates! This is a good thing since it means Lion-O and the ThunderKittens can ditch their chores and fight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 07:51:00" d="2020-05-19 08:05:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Freed from the Astral Plane, the ghost of the ThunderCats mentor is now free to visit the Cats' Lair. Which means he can finally tell them why Thundera exploded. It’s story time!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 08:05:00" d="2020-05-19 08:16:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Axel ventures into his uncle's strictly off-limits basement lab in hopes of fixing a broken toy and ends up unleashing living ones instead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 08:16:00" d="2020-05-19 08:35:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Axel discovers that he can transform into a toy and teams up with his new team of toys to stop Madcap from stealing a Minergy battery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 08:35:00" d="2020-05-19 08:55:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% The Scooby gang need to figure out why the ghost of Elias Kingston, the founder of Kingston University, is haunting the school halls!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 08:55:00" d="2020-05-19 09:20:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Daphne brings the Gang to a Victorian murder mystery party, so they can dress up and solve a fake mystery for once</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 09:20:00" d="2020-05-19 09:30:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Craig Kelsey and JP become smugglers to sneak candy to kids in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 09:30:00" d="2020-05-19 10:10:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>JP decides to follow his heart and tries to join the Horse Girls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 10:10:00" d="2020-05-19 10:21:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are invited to a high school party, and have to bring a date!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 10:21:00" d="2020-05-19 10:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin unsuccessfully attempt to get a refund for their computer game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 10:40:00" d="2020-05-19 10:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are reading Anais’ diary when they discover that her relationship with her new friend seems a bit one-sided</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 10:50:00" d="2020-05-19 11:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Bobert finds he is infected with a virus called love.exe he asks Gumball and Darwin to give him a definition for the word ‘love’</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 11:00:00" d="2020-05-19 11:09:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin insists he's a multiple trick pony</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 11:09:00" d="2020-05-19 11:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% We finally learn the true source of the Titans' goofy humor: pizza</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 11:25:00" d="2020-05-19 11:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Beast Boy writes a song to tell Raven his feelings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 11:34:00" d="2020-05-19 11:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Beast Boy goes on tour with his song</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 11:50:00" d="2020-05-19 12:01:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>What begins as a simple vandalism investigation becomes an all-out turf war when the team encounters a powerful trio of Kryptonians bent on world domination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 12:01:00" d="2020-05-19 12:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>What begins as a simple vandalism investigation becomes an all-out turf war when the team encounters a powerful trio of Kryptonians bent on world domination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 12:15:00" d="2020-05-19 12:25:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Unikitty and the gang have crashed on a fabulous island</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 12:25:00" d="2020-05-19 12:40:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Concerned about Puppycorn's propensity to hurt himself constantly, the gang places him into Richard's old Safety Suit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 12:40:00" d="2020-05-19 12:50:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>For Panda's Birthday the Bears try to help Panda meet his favorite K-Pop band Monsta X</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 12:50:00" d="2020-05-19 13:10:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Each of the Bears get offbeat items at a local yard sale. Their new possessions send them on their own separate adventures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 13:10:00" d="2020-05-19 13:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are devastated to learn that Mr. Robinson -- their favourite person in the world -- is selling his house and leaving town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 13:20:00" d="2020-05-19 13:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Mom and the kids depart for their hard day's work, leaving a seemingly lazy Dad half-asleep on the sofa. Mom has given him one very simple job: buy mayonnaise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 13:30:00" d="2020-05-19 13:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When the Wattersons arrive at the mall for a day of shopping, they struggle to find a space in the parking lot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 13:40:00" d="2020-05-19 13:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin see an advert for the latest, cutting-edge Bobert operating system and excitedly talk Bobert into downloading it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 13:55:00" d="2020-05-19 14:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Everyone assumes Darwin &amp; Carrie's relationship is doomed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 14:05:00" d="2020-05-19 14:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Leslie calls Gumball's bluff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 14:25:00" d="2020-05-19 14:36:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The boys forget to get Chata a gift for Abuela Day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 14:36:00" d="2020-05-19 14:50:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vic gets sick and is stuck in his room</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 14:50:00" d="2020-05-19 14:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% After not receiving participation medals, the Titans must demonstrate what they learned at camp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 14:59:00" d="2020-05-19 15:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When her teammates turns evil it's up to Lady Legasus to stop the League of Legs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 15:10:00" d="2020-05-19 15:19:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin tries to teach the Titans valuable life lessons by reading them fairytales but the others co-opt his stories and spin them into their own twisted yarns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 15:19:00" d="2020-05-19 15:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Brother Blood takes the Titans to trial for their recent destruction of Jump City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 15:35:00" d="2020-05-19 15:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>JP invites his friends over for a sleepover but it happens to be on the night of a huge game of Flashlight Tag in the Creek!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 15:45:00" d="2020-05-19 16:00:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Craig vows to make the game of Four Square fun again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 16:00:00" d="2020-05-19 16:11:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Axel and the team battle Princess SugarSalt for possession of Bearbarian's hammer traded to her by one of their own - Galileo!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 16:11:00" d="2020-05-19 16:25:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Axel and the team compete against themselves in tests of skill strength and stamina but when SloBot gets belittled he splits into three separate robots</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 16:25:00" d="2020-05-19 16:34:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang puts their favorite items in a Time Capsule to send 100 years in the future, but they get stuck inside right before the door seals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 16:34:00" d="2020-05-19 16:50:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Unikitty hosts a live music video countdown show for the kingdom, presenting the ecstatic audience with the top 4 music videos in the Unikingdom, featuring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 16:50:00" d="2020-05-19 16:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Bumbleebee becomes the 6th Titan and moves into the Tower but has a hard time adjusting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 16:59:00" d="2020-05-19 17:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans try to outprank each other on April Fools' Day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 17:15:00" d="2020-05-19 17:26:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Panthro hits it off with a new friend, Barbastella the Queen of the Bats! Now Panthro needs help getting ready for his date with her because it turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 17:26:00" d="2020-05-19 17:40:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After a battle with the Mutants, Jackalman gets confused and accidentally returns to the Cats' Lair with the ThunderCats. He is the dumbest mutant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 17:40:00" d="2020-05-19 18:00:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang force Fred to relax at a beach house. Unfortunately, when a walking shark attacks the beach community, the gang must solve the mystery without</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 18:00:00" d="2020-05-19 18:25:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Feeling unwell, Scooby is brought to a vet clinic. Soon, the gang finds a werewolf is roaming around the place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 18:25:00" d="2020-05-19 18:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is late to meet Penny at the mall, but a series of misunderstandings on the way only delay him further</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 18:35:00" d="2020-05-19 18:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Mom sees Darwin gazing longingly at a fish-tank she thinks their mammalian lifestyle isn’t fulfilling her adopted son and deep down he longs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 18:55:00" d="2020-05-19 19:06:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin help Anais rescue her doll from Tina Rex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 19:06:00" d="2020-05-19 19:17:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are unwitting accomplices in a gas station robbery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 19:17:00" d="2020-05-19 19:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin accidentally destroy Mr Robinson’s new car… or do they?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 19:30:00" d="2020-05-19 19:41:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The boys forget to get Chata a gift for Abuela Day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 19:41:00" d="2020-05-19 19:55:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vic gets sick and is stuck in his room</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 19:55:00" d="2020-05-19 20:00:00"><n>The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While escaping from a grizzly bear, Ivandoe and Bert fall into an underground cave where a large Troll-woman in a party dress keeps them captive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 20:00:00" d="2020-05-19 20:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>During a tour of the Japanese Robotics Museum Ben finds hero-gone-wrong Tim Buktu trying to save Tokyo from a Dragon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 20:10:00" d="2020-05-19 20:20:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>During medieval times Team Tennyson must fight to remember that they're not in the past at all but actually at a Renaissance-esque faire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 20:20:00" d="2020-05-19 20:35:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After an overpass collapses on the highway Team Tennyson is in a traffic jam along with Simon Sez and family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 20:35:00" d="2020-05-19 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% Magnus's new team of Bakugan Brawlers overhear Lightning's warnings of a sick Core Cell./Magnus heads into the Labyrinth to claim the Fortus Core Cell for his own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 21:00:00" d="2020-05-19 21:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lloyd turns the tables on Harumi to take his father’s power away, and the Ninja learn what it takes to be a Dragon Hunter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 21:25:00" d="2020-05-19 21:45:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lloyd and his team plot to take control of the Oni Titan. Meanwhile in the First Realm, the Ninja fall into Iron Baron’s clutches and an old master returns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 21:45:00" d="2020-05-19 22:10:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% When Iron Baron forces Wu to retrieve the Dragon Armor, things don’t go as planned. In Ninjago, Lloyd can only endure so much as he holds onto hope for the Ninjas’ return</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 22:10:00" d="2020-05-19 22:30:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The Ninja finally return home and unite to stop Emperor Garmadon, forcing Lloyd to make a decision that will forever change Ninjago</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 22:30:00" d="2020-05-19 22:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% The line for Adventureparkland’s newest ride is way too long so Angelo and the gang decide to spread rumors of wolves attacking people at the park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 22:40:00" d="2020-05-19 22:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% With Lola and Sherwood away Angelo interviews and auditions potential replacements</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 22:55:00" d="2020-05-19 23:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% After Angelo trashes Burst’s stage set, his punishment is that he must star in Burst’s unusual, arty play. With Sherwood and Lola helping backstage, Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 23:05:00" d="2020-05-19 23:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% After accidentally breaking a window, Angelo and friends complete a series of chores at the rec center as pay back. But it’s all good because Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 23:15:00" d="2020-05-19 23:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% To convince his parents to buy him a phone Angelo must turn his text addicted sister into a smart phone role model</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 23:25:00" d="2020-05-19 23:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% After Mr. Foot confiscates all electronics before class, Angelo and friends have to kick it old school and pass hand written notes to communicate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 23:40:00" d="2020-05-19 23:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Dreams do come true and Angelo and friends turn Angelo’s Dad into a rock star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 23:50:00" d="2020-05-20 00:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo attempts to join the secretive “school council” and learns-- never become a member of a group that will have you has a member</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 00:05:00" d="2020-05-20 00:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Nicole and her parents have it out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 00:15:00" d="2020-05-20 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Nicole decides to pay the cable bill in person at Chanax, she leaves specific instructions for Richard to stay in the car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 00:30:00" d="2020-05-20 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are at the convenience store considering playing truant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 00:40:00" d="2020-05-20 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin argue with the Internet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 00:50:00" d="2020-05-20 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Hector is unhappy with his height</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 01:00:00" d="2020-05-20 01:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Channel 6 Elmore News has all the top local stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 01:15:00" d="2020-05-20 01:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin find themselves in serious trouble when they agree to everything the new kid in school says. The truth is they can't understand a word that he says</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 01:25:00" d="2020-05-20 01:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball decides it’s time to play cupid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 01:35:00" d="2020-05-20 01:46:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball’s magic tinfoil helmet threatens to tear the Watterson family apart!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 01:46:00" d="2020-05-20 01:57:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Anais is convinced that Gumball is being bullied by Tina Rex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 01:57:00" d="2020-05-20 02:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are convinced that the world will end in 24 hours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 02:10:00" d="2020-05-20 02:35:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The Oni in Ninjago City are stronger than anyone could have imagined, and the ninja must risk a daring rescue of Lloyd and Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 02:35:00" d="2020-05-20 03:00:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% In the wake of a vicious attack upon the palace, the Sons of Garmadon steal the second Oni Mask, and the ninja invite the royal princess, Harumi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 03:00:00" d="2020-05-20 03:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% In order to join the Sons of Garmadon, Zane (aka Snake Jaguar) participates in a deadly motorcycle initiation race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 03:25:00" d="2020-05-20 03:50:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Zane’s near demise at the hands of Mr. E forces the ninja to flee aboard the Bounty, where they discover a message Zane intercepted may reveal the hidden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 03:50:00" d="2020-05-20 04:01:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin help Anais rescue her doll from Tina Rex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 04:01:00" d="2020-05-20 04:12:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are unwitting accomplices in a gas station robbery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 04:12:00" d="2020-05-20 04:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin accidentally destroy Mr Robinson’s new car… or do they?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 04:25:00" d="2020-05-20 04:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Nicole and her parents have it out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 04:35:00" d="2020-05-20 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Nicole decides to pay the cable bill in person at Chanax, she leaves specific instructions for Richard to stay in the car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 04:50:00" d="2020-05-20 05:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are at the convenience store considering playing truant</k>  </p>
</a>
