<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="101" t="2020-04-11 04:28:58"><p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 05:00:00" d="2020-04-18 05:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Things keep going missing in the house, so it’s up to Gumball and Darwin to find the culprit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 05:10:00" d="2020-04-18 05:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball refuses to get out of bed because he is in a lousy mood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 05:20:00" d="2020-04-18 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Nicole arranges a playdate for Anais with the son of a classy lady she met at the supermarket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 05:35:00" d="2020-04-18 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Dad is in charge of getting the kids to their first day back at school on time, but he's overslept and now he can't find Gumball, Darwin, or Anais anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 05:45:00" d="2020-04-18 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin discover that Rob, who once swore to wreak vengeance on them, has been trying to destroy them for some time. but his traps never work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 06:00:00" d="2020-04-18 06:11:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While visiting Lake Erie, a relaxing day at the beach gets all washed up when Ben, Gwen and Grandpa Max come face-to-face with Hex and his summer intern, Kevin!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 06:11:00" d="2020-04-18 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ben gets a tough lesson on knowing his limits when he competes in a gruelling obstacle race, made even worse by the Weatherheads!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 06:25:00" d="2020-04-18 06:36:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin’s martial arts costumes make them a laughing stock at school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 06:36:00" d="2020-04-18 06:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball is traumatised when accidentally kissed on the mouth by his Grandma JoJo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 06:50:00" d="2020-04-18 07:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Badgerclops smells, but Mao Mao and Adorabat don't know how to tell him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 07:00:00" d="2020-04-18 07:15:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Rufus and Reg come to swindle the town, Sheriff Mao Mao teaches them a lesson in justice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 07:15:00" d="2020-04-18 07:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When the gang bands together to form a giant robot, Robin is relegated to the left leg - but he makes the left leg count!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 07:25:00" d="2020-04-18 07:40:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When the Titans replace the couch with a treadmill, Cyborg and Beast Boy must get guidance from the couch spirit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 07:40:00" d="2020-04-18 07:49:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% It's Movie Night and the Titans have a hard time deciding who gets to choose which movie they watch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 07:49:00" d="2020-04-18 08:05:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% It's back to school as the Titans teach each other about science and grammar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 08:05:00" d="2020-04-18 08:14:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When Robin needs an archenemy, Starfire generously offers to fill the role and she exceeds expectations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 08:14:00" d="2020-04-18 08:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans trick Starfire into believing in second Christmas with second Santa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 08:35:00" d="2020-04-18 08:45:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Badgerclops smells, but Mao Mao and Adorabat don't know how to tell him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 08:45:00" d="2020-04-18 08:55:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Rufus and Reg come to swindle the town, Sheriff Mao Mao teaches them a lesson in justice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 08:55:00" d="2020-04-18 09:05:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang decide to compete in the annual Thumb War competition, but a surprise forces Mao Mao to deal with the unthinkable. losing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 09:05:00" d="2020-04-18 09:16:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Mao Mao discovers that he is not as popular as Badgerclops and Adorabat, they decide to reinvent him as a kinder, cuddlier hero</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 09:16:00" d="2020-04-18 09:27:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang struggles to get rid of the King when he joins them as their new deputy-for-a-day!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 09:27:00" d="2020-04-18 09:38:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% A group of kids get locked in the school after their parents have a charity gala. They appoint Gumball as leader to get them out but it leads to chaos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 09:38:00" d="2020-04-18 09:49:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Clayton shapeshifts into people to take their detentions for money. He starts framing people for misdemeanors so GB and DW must track him down to stop him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 09:49:00" d="2020-04-18 10:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Sarah finds a notebook from an awesome store!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 10:00:00" d="2020-04-18 10:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Rocky suggests that the Elmore Junior High kids skip school, the bus is boarded by criminals who seem to want to teach them the importance of school attendance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 10:10:00" d="2020-04-18 10:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball decides to put Mr. Small's eco-friendly principles to the test but it doesn't quite go as planned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 10:40:00" d="2020-04-18 11:01:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Master Wu mistakenly tries to single-handedly complete a battle he began decades ago against Acronix, one of the twin Hands of Time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 11:01:00" d="2020-04-18 11:22:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The Ninja learn more about the Krux and Acronix—the two fallen Elemental Masters known as the Hands of Time—and are sure that this threat has finally been eliminated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 11:22:00" d="2020-04-18 11:43:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Kai's investigation of a Vermillion Warrior Helmet leads him to discover that Krux is alive and well in Ninjago, living under an assumed identity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 11:43:00" d="2020-04-18 12:04:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% In the midst of an epidemic of mysterious metal thefts by the Vermillion Warriors, Lloyd realises that stepping up and taking over for the ailing Master</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 12:04:00" d="2020-04-18 12:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% While the Ninja fight to save MegaMonster Amusement Park, Jay struggles to defend his family's home from the Vermillion Warriors</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 12:25:00" d="2020-04-18 12:46:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The Ninja celebrate their escape from the Vermillion Army and their retrieval of the Emerald Time Blade, but Acronix and Krux are determined to get their Blade back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 12:46:00" d="2020-04-18 13:30:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Secrets are revealed as Nya confronts the Samurai X imposter, Kai pursues the truth about his parents and the other Ninja desperately seek to locate and rescue Master Wu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 13:30:00" d="2020-04-18 13:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% A mysterious package shows up at the Watterson’s house and they do their best to avoid opening it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 13:40:00" d="2020-04-18 13:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Darwin likes a girl in his class so Gumball decides it’s time to play cupid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 13:55:00" d="2020-04-18 14:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% A group of kids get locked in the school after their parents have a charity gala. They appoint Gumball as leader to get them out but it leads to chaos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 14:05:00" d="2020-04-18 14:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Clayton shapeshifts into people to take their detentions for money. He starts framing people for misdemeanors so GB and DW must track him down to stop him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 14:25:00" d="2020-04-18 14:35:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After getting rejected by a photography club, Val tries to get a picture of the legendary Chupacabra in order to prove himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 14:35:00" d="2020-04-18 14:50:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After faking an injury to get out of work, Vic gains sympathy from everyone while unknowingly attracting attention from a dangerous mythical creature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 14:50:00" d="2020-04-18 15:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When a computer dating program matches Beast Boy to Raven, he tries wooing her to disastrous effect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 15:00:00" d="2020-04-18 15:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Raven shows the rest of the Titans that books can be fun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 15:10:00" d="2020-04-18 15:19:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When Robin starts doing power moves with Cyborg, Beast Boy gets very jealous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 15:19:00" d="2020-04-18 15:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When he is tasked with looking after the Bat-cave, Robin questions his relationship with Batman while struggling to keep the other Titans in line</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 15:35:00" d="2020-04-18 15:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bernard is left in charge for the evening</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 15:45:00" d="2020-04-18 16:00:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Craig discovers a bunch of bugs under a rock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 16:00:00" d="2020-04-18 16:10:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang decide to compete in the annual Thumb War competition, but a surprise forces Mao Mao to deal with the unthinkable. losing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 16:10:00" d="2020-04-18 16:25:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Mao Mao discovers that he is not as popular as Badgerclops and Adorabat, they decide to reinvent him as a kinder, cuddlier hero</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 16:25:00" d="2020-04-18 16:35:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Unikitty is the reigning champ of Hide N’ Seek Day. But when Unikitty finds everyone in the kingdom except for Richard, she hunts him down at all costs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 16:35:00" d="2020-04-18 16:50:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When a blizzard hits, Master Frown tries to ruin the fun by pretending to be a snowman! But when he gets frozen inside, he's forced to experience</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 16:50:00" d="2020-04-18 16:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Batman is more interested in watching TV than his party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 16:59:00" d="2020-04-18 17:26:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin tries to tell the origin story of the Teen Titans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 17:26:00" d="2020-04-18 17:40:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Batgirl’s worlds collide when her best friend from Gotham City moves to Metropolis. Meanwhile, Catwoman is making some new friends of her own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 17:40:00" d="2020-04-18 18:00:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang visits a farm that’s being haunted by a creepy Scarecrow Ghost</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 18:00:00" d="2020-04-18 18:25:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang is honored to take part in the wedding of two close friends. But can Shaggy and Daphne, save their friend’s perfect day from a tragic Ghost Bride?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 18:25:00" d="2020-04-18 18:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Gumball and Darwin discover his diploma is fake, Principal Brown is determined to keep their discovery a secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 18:35:00" d="2020-04-18 18:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin start noticing small details around Elmore High that don't add up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 18:55:00" d="2020-04-18 19:06:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin barely survive a school picnic in the Forest of Doom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 19:06:00" d="2020-04-18 19:17:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball sets out to win his Dad back by winning a blindfolded “dumb” race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 19:17:00" d="2020-04-18 19:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball almost loses his mind trying to guess Darwin’s secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 19:30:00" d="2020-04-18 19:40:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After getting rejected by a photography club, Val tries to get a picture of the legendary Chupacabra in order to prove himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 19:40:00" d="2020-04-18 19:55:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After faking an injury to get out of work, Vic gains sympathy from everyone while unknowingly attracting attention from a dangerous mythical creature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 19:55:00" d="2020-04-18 20:00:00"><n>The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ivandoe and Bert get captured and tied up by a very intense forest survivalist who happens to be a pink poodle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 20:00:00" d="2020-04-18 20:11:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ben, Gwen and Grandpa Max find themselves killing time at the local town library but soon scramble to out manoeuvre Hex as he searches for a hidden ancient artefact</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 20:11:00" d="2020-04-18 20:22:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Team Tennyson enjoy a convention in town but when a costume store employee finds a familiar-looking helmet and tries it on, Ben is faced with the return of Forever Knight!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 20:22:00" d="2020-04-18 20:35:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Tennysons come across a naturally formed pit with no bottom. Ben fights his better judgment to jump in until Kevin 11 shows up and goads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 20:35:00" d="2020-04-18 20:45:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% Lightning discovers a new Bakugan, Artulean, leading to an unhealthy rivalry with Howlkor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 20:45:00" d="2020-04-18 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% While Lia's newswoman mom does an expose on the AO Strata the Hunter tries to capture Hydorous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 21:00:00" d="2020-04-18 21:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% As Ninjago City rebuilds, Faith arrives with a dire warning: the Oni have returned and are destroying the realms, one by one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 21:25:00" d="2020-04-18 21:45:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Having freed Lord Garmadon from Kryptarium Prison, the ninja are beset by doubts, particularly Lloyd</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 21:45:00" d="2020-04-18 22:10:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The Oni in Ninjago City are stronger than anyone could have imagined, and the ninja must risk a daring rescue of Lloyd and Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 22:10:00" d="2020-04-18 22:30:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The ninja race back to the Monastery of Spinjitzu. This is the last stand. The final battle against the Oni is now</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 22:30:00" d="2020-04-18 22:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% After making a bet that their life is harder, Angelo and Mr. Foot trade places. Angelo becomes the teacher, and Mr. Foot the unruly student</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 22:40:00" d="2020-04-18 22:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% After taking a career test that claims to predict your future and receiving disappointing results, Angelo and friends set out to change their destinies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 22:55:00" d="2020-04-18 23:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% The line for Adventureparkland’s newest ride is way too long so Angelo and the gang decide to spread rumors of wolves attacking people at the park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 23:05:00" d="2020-04-18 23:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% With Lola and Sherwood away Angelo interviews and auditions potential replacements</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 23:15:00" d="2020-04-18 23:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% After Angelo trashes Burst’s stage set, his punishment is that he must star in Burst’s unusual, arty play. With Sherwood and Lola helping backstage, Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 23:25:00" d="2020-04-18 23:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% After accidentally breaking a window, Angelo and friends complete a series of chores at the rec center as pay back. But it’s all good because Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 23:40:00" d="2020-04-18 23:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% To convince his parents to buy him a phone Angelo must turn his text addicted sister into a smart phone role model</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-18 23:50:00" d="2020-04-19 00:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% After Mr. Foot confiscates all electronics before class, Angelo and friends have to kick it old school and pass hand written notes to communicate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 00:05:00" d="2020-04-19 00:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Gumball and Darwin decide it's time they join a crew, they agree that the coolest posse in Elmore is the Senior Citizens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 00:15:00" d="2020-04-19 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Anais reveals that she's in the grade above them at school, Gumball and Darwin's eyes are suddenly opened to a whole new world of other students</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 00:30:00" d="2020-04-19 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Dad discovers that Granny Jojo and Louie plan to get married and move to Florida. To stop this happening he adopts Louie so that he can forbid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 00:40:00" d="2020-04-19 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% After they receive an extravagant invitation to Masami's birthday party, Gumball and Darwin are anxious to find just the right gift for her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 00:50:00" d="2020-04-19 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball decides that the best way to prove to Mr. Fitzgerald that he's good enough for Penny is to become his apprentice for the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 01:00:00" d="2020-04-19 01:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball, Darwin and Anais are delighted when Grandpa Louie gives them a check for $5000. They immediately start fantasizing over what to spend it on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 01:15:00" d="2020-04-19 01:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When they find Anais training herself for a brutal showdown, Gumball and Darwin realise that their sister is being pestered at school by an annoying kid: Billy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 01:25:00" d="2020-04-19 01:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Darwin taunts Gumball about how predictable he is, Gumball tries to prove that he can still surprise his buddy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 01:35:00" d="2020-04-19 01:46:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin barely survive a school picnic in the Forest of Doom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 01:46:00" d="2020-04-19 01:57:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball sets out to win his Dad back by winning a blindfolded “dumb” race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 01:57:00" d="2020-04-19 02:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball almost loses his mind trying to guess Darwin’s secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 02:10:00" d="2020-04-19 02:35:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% When Iron Baron forces Wu to retrieve the Dragon Armor, things don’t go as planned. In Ninjago, Lloyd can only endure so much as he holds onto hope for the Ninjas’ return</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 02:35:00" d="2020-04-19 03:00:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Having freed Lord Garmadon from Kryptarium Prison, the ninja are beset by doubts, particularly Lloyd</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 03:00:00" d="2020-04-19 03:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The ninja race back to the Monastery of Spinjitzu. This is the last stand. The final battle against the Oni is now</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 03:25:00" d="2020-04-19 03:50:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% When an unknown criminal syndicate threatens the Royal Family, the Ninja are called into action. They must protect the princess and an artifact</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 03:50:00" d="2020-04-19 04:01:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin barely survive a school picnic in the Forest of Doom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 04:01:00" d="2020-04-19 04:12:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball sets out to win his Dad back by winning a blindfolded “dumb” race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 04:12:00" d="2020-04-19 04:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball almost loses his mind trying to guess Darwin’s secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 04:25:00" d="2020-04-19 04:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Gumball and Darwin decide it's time they join a crew, they agree that the coolest posse in Elmore is the Senior Citizens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 04:35:00" d="2020-04-19 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Anais reveals that she's in the grade above them at school, Gumball and Darwin's eyes are suddenly opened to a whole new world of other students</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 04:50:00" d="2020-04-19 05:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Dad discovers that Granny Jojo and Louie plan to get married and move to Florida. To stop this happening he adopts Louie so that he can forbid</k>  </p>
</a>
