<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="104" t="2020-05-13 04:31:13"><p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 05:00:00" d="2020-05-20 05:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin argue with the Internet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 05:10:00" d="2020-05-20 05:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Hector is unhappy with his height</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 05:20:00" d="2020-05-20 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Channel 6 Elmore News has all the top local stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 05:35:00" d="2020-05-20 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin find themselves in serious trouble when they agree to everything the new kid in school says. The truth is they can't understand a word that he says</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 05:45:00" d="2020-05-20 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball decides it’s time to play cupid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 06:00:00" d="2020-05-20 06:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When a forest fire interrupts their fun, Team Tennyson must hurry if they are to save the bird population and discover who is behind the growing fire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 06:10:00" d="2020-05-20 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>As Team Tennyson admires the efficiency of a super modern train station Ben is quick to sniff out one of Steam Smythe's robots holding up the line</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 06:25:00" d="2020-05-20 06:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The life of the background objects of Elmore are shown in a series of short skits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 06:35:00" d="2020-05-20 06:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Wattersons are surprised to discover that their past actions have consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 06:50:00" d="2020-05-20 07:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Dad is in charge of getting the kids to their first day back at school on time, but he's overslept and now he can't find Gumball, Darwin, or Anais anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 07:00:00" d="2020-05-20 07:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin discover that Rob, who once swore to wreak vengeance on them, has been trying to destroy them for some time. but his traps never work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 07:15:00" d="2020-05-20 07:24:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Bumbleebee becomes the 6th Titan and moves into the Tower but has a hard time adjusting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 07:24:00" d="2020-05-20 07:40:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans try to outprank each other on April Fools' Day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 07:40:00" d="2020-05-20 07:51:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Panthro hits it off with a new friend, Barbastella the Queen of the Bats! Now Panthro needs help getting ready for his date with her because it turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 07:51:00" d="2020-05-20 08:05:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After a battle with the Mutants, Jackalman gets confused and accidentally returns to the Cats' Lair with the ThunderCats. He is the dumbest mutant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 08:05:00" d="2020-05-20 08:16:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Axel and the team battle Princess SugarSalt for possession of Bearbarian's hammer traded to her by one of their own - Galileo!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 08:16:00" d="2020-05-20 08:35:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Axel and the team compete against themselves in tests of skill strength and stamina but when SloBot gets belittled he splits into three separate robots</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 08:35:00" d="2020-05-20 08:55:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Fred gets a call for help from Chuck, his daredevil of a best friend, leading the gang on a rescue mission deep in the caverns of an ancient civilization</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 08:55:00" d="2020-05-20 09:20:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It's Scooby's dream come true as the gang visits the set of his favourite TV show and he meets the star, his celebrity crush, a dog actress who plays</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 09:20:00" d="2020-05-20 09:30:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>JP invites his friends over for a sleepover but it happens to be on the night of a huge game of Flashlight Tag in the Creek!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 09:30:00" d="2020-05-20 10:10:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Craig vows to make the game of Four Square fun again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 10:10:00" d="2020-05-20 10:21:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball discovers that Bobert is planning to take over his identity and replace him!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 10:21:00" d="2020-05-20 10:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin barely survive a school picnic in the Forest of Doom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 10:40:00" d="2020-05-20 10:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% At Halloween show and tell, the class isn’t buying Gumball’s story about Gargaroth The Devourer until Carrie fakes a terrifying haunting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 10:50:00" d="2020-05-20 11:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is walking in the same direction as Hot Dog Guy, and with each step it becomes increasingly awkward</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 11:00:00" d="2020-05-20 11:09:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Beast Man: Beast Boy discovers he can transform into an adult man</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 11:09:00" d="2020-05-20 11:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin tries to teach The Titans to respect money but he ends up bee-ing the one who learns the lesson./Cyborg wants to have an 80s TV show marathon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 11:25:00" d="2020-05-20 11:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans are determined to find out what happened to the missing 2'oclock hour during Daylight Saving Time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 11:35:00" d="2020-05-20 11:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% It's St. Patrick's Day and after wishing to become a leprechaun Beast Boy becomes obsessed with gold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 11:50:00" d="2020-05-20 12:00:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A fun day for Barbara Gordon and her bestie Harleen Quinzel is turned on its head when out of nowhere the villainous Harley Quinn shows up to wreak havoc!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 12:00:00" d="2020-05-20 12:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Jessica Cruz &amp; Pam Isley bond over protecting an ancient tree - without realizing who the other's alter ego is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 12:15:00" d="2020-05-20 12:25:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang is taking an airplane trip together, and Hawk is at the helm since today he's taking his captain's license test</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 12:25:00" d="2020-05-20 12:40:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When the kingdom runs out of inspiration, Unikitty takes it on herself to re-inspire the citizens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 12:40:00" d="2020-05-20 12:50:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A thunderstorm forces Chloe to spend the night at the Cave with the Bears. When Chloe's parents tell the Bears to protect Chloe, they take the task a bit too seriously</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 12:50:00" d="2020-05-20 13:10:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A doctor tells the Bears to go on a “cleanse” to improve their health. But when Grizz realises he can only eat what grizzly bears eat, he starts to lose his mind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 13:10:00" d="2020-05-20 13:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is the star of his own comic, but struggles to match up to his heroic alter-ego</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 13:20:00" d="2020-05-20 13:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% After Gumball convinces himself that Penny doesn't love him as much as she used to, he decides to put together a romantic quest to remind her of their good times together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 13:30:00" d="2020-05-20 13:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Everyone knows you can never watch just one video on the internet but Gumball and Darwin think they are the exception to the rule</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 13:40:00" d="2020-05-20 13:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% After being framed for feeding coffee to the squirrels in the park, Gumball proclaims that Mrs Robinson is pure evil</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 13:55:00" d="2020-05-20 14:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Anais and psycho Jamie are accused of the same crime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 14:05:00" d="2020-05-20 14:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Dad decides to resolve the Watterson family's differences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 14:25:00" d="2020-05-20 14:36:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vic and Val tag along with Xochi to a punk concert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 14:36:00" d="2020-05-20 14:50:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vic &amp; Val are in awe of the new magician in town, but things go awry when they agree to help him out with a new trick - despite Chata's wishes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 14:50:00" d="2020-05-20 14:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Bumbleebee becomes the 6th Titan and moves into the Tower but has a hard time adjusting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 14:59:00" d="2020-05-20 15:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans try to outprank each other on April Fools' Day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 15:10:00" d="2020-05-20 15:19:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% After the other Titans are injured Beast Boy donates his blood to save them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 15:19:00" d="2020-05-20 15:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans' Halloween party is interupted by the Hive Five robbing a candy factory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 15:35:00" d="2020-05-20 15:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Craig rescues a tadpole and decides to raise him into a level 100 frog!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 15:45:00" d="2020-05-20 16:00:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Craig has an emergency leaving Kelsey alone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 16:00:00" d="2020-05-20 16:11:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Axel finds himself at the center of a disagreement between Sarge and Masko over what's more important in battle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 16:11:00" d="2020-05-20 16:25:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zoe builds her own battle suit in hopes of joining Axel's team. The only problem? She can't shrink!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 16:25:00" d="2020-05-20 16:35:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Puppycorn is sick of Unikitty always helping him out and doesn't want to be the &quot;little&quot; brother anymore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 16:35:00" d="2020-05-20 16:50:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Master Frown starts ruining parties to earn a promotion from his bosses, the Doom Lords, Brock accidentally gets blamed for the calamity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 16:50:00" d="2020-05-20 17:02:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Bumblebee offers to help Robin with his leadership skills by teaching him how to act like a queen bee</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 17:02:00" d="2020-05-20 17:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% In order to save Titans Tower from some wealthy land developers the Titans search for pirate treasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 17:15:00" d="2020-05-20 17:26:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The ThunderCats are exhausted from fighting bad guys all the time so Lion-O suggests they spend a relaxing summer fun day at the beach with no fighting!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 17:26:00" d="2020-05-20 17:40:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While minding her own business, Cheetara is caught in a trap set by Safari Joe, the famously annoying hunter! After escaping she rallies the other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 17:40:00" d="2020-05-20 18:00:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang heads to the Velma’s beloved Renaissance Fair, where they must find a way to infiltrate the royal feast to stop an evil court jester from ending the king’s reign</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 18:00:00" d="2020-05-20 18:25:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Shaggy and Scooby decide to leave the gang! But before that, they insist on training the new recruits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 18:25:00" d="2020-05-20 18:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Parent Teacher Association of Elmore Junior High ban video games, so the kids try and prove that games aren’t a bad influence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 18:35:00" d="2020-05-20 18:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Anais arrives in the bedroom to find a messy crime-scene and her Daisy doll missing. She realises that Gumball and Darwin are the chief suspects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 18:55:00" d="2020-05-20 19:06:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball experiences an impossibly unfortunate chain of events</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 19:06:00" d="2020-05-20 19:17:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin accidentally create a loveable monster that eats their family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 19:17:00" d="2020-05-20 19:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is embarrassed when Mum comes to school to spend some “quality time”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 19:30:00" d="2020-05-20 19:41:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vic and Val tag along with Xochi to a punk concert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 19:41:00" d="2020-05-20 19:55:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vic &amp; Val are in awe of the new magician in town, but things go awry when they agree to help him out with a new trick - despite Chata's wishes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 19:55:00" d="2020-05-20 20:00:00"><n>The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ivandoe dismisses Bert and takes on a duck as his new Squire. The duck proves to be worse than useless when they come face to face with an angry tentacled forest creature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 20:00:00" d="2020-05-20 20:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>At Biggie Box Japan, Ben waits in an epic line for the release of the latest Sumo Slammers video game, Cyber Slammers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 20:10:00" d="2020-05-20 20:20:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Ben and family go to London to visit the legendary Big Ben, the Bugg Brothers are there to greet them with yet another outrageously over the top plan of course</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 20:20:00" d="2020-05-20 20:35:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After traveling to Tampa Beach, Florida, Team Tennyson hope to get some much-needed rest and relaxation but the Weatherheads have other plans that Ben must thwart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 20:35:00" d="2020-05-20 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% Driven by revenge, Magnus decides to claim the Fortus Core Cell energy for himself./Super charged by the Fortus Core Cell, Magnus wages war on the AO</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 21:00:00" d="2020-05-20 21:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% As Ninjago City rebuilds, Faith arrives with a dire warning: the Oni have returned and are destroying the realms, one by one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 21:25:00" d="2020-05-20 21:45:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Having freed Lord Garmadon from Kryptarium Prison, the ninja are beset by doubts, particularly Lloyd</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 21:45:00" d="2020-05-20 22:10:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The Oni in Ninjago City are stronger than anyone could have imagined, and the ninja must risk a daring rescue of Lloyd and Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 22:10:00" d="2020-05-20 22:30:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The ninja race back to the Monastery of Spinjitzu. This is the last stand. The final battle against the Oni is now</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 22:30:00" d="2020-05-20 22:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo gives us his tips and tricks for the most awesome sleepover ever. Until, the “prank call” trick ruins the night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 22:40:00" d="2020-05-20 22:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo stupidly boasts that his Dad used to be a stuntman. And the next day Dad has been invited to speak to Angelo’s class for career day. Gah!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 22:55:00" d="2020-05-20 23:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo makes Tracy cry and feels terrible about it. He declares a truce. Problem is… their growing friendship throws off the balance of nature!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 23:05:00" d="2020-05-20 23:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Joe Mama has been stealing stuff from around town and storing it under Angelo’s bed. Angelo and friends embark on a reverse scavenger hunt to figure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 23:15:00" d="2020-05-20 23:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo and Lola are stuck with Manetti as a science project partner. The only way to complete the project is turn Manetti into the science project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 23:25:00" d="2020-05-20 23:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Tracy claims Angelo broke her arm. Angelo’s punishment—become Tracy’s slave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 23:40:00" d="2020-05-20 23:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo discovers Cathy cat and Joe Mama have been accidentally switched at the Vet. And no one believes Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-20 23:50:00" d="2020-05-21 00:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo creates a fake Guatemalan pen pal so he doesn’t fail Mr. Foot’s class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 00:05:00" d="2020-05-21 00:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Wattersons are forced to rent out their house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 00:15:00" d="2020-05-21 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The kids find out Dad has been dressing as a woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 00:30:00" d="2020-05-21 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Everyone assumes Darwin &amp; Carrie's relationship is doomed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 00:40:00" d="2020-05-21 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Leslie calls Gumball's bluff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 00:50:00" d="2020-05-21 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Anais and psycho Jamie are accused of the same crime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 01:00:00" d="2020-05-21 01:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Dad decides to resolve the Watterson family's differences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 01:15:00" d="2020-05-21 01:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The kids find out Dad has been dressing as a woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 01:25:00" d="2020-05-21 01:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball, Darwin and Banana Joe investigate Banana Barbara's mysterious disappearance and uncover an old rival's shadowy scheme in the process</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 01:35:00" d="2020-05-21 01:46:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is desperate to avoid a late fee on the rented dvd he accidentally destroyed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 01:46:00" d="2020-05-21 01:57:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Tobias compete for Penny's affection by putting on the lamest duel in history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 01:57:00" d="2020-05-21 02:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin learn that it isn't wise to upset Hector, Elmore's resident Giant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 02:10:00" d="2020-05-21 02:35:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% While Princess Harumi adjusts to life with the ninja, Lloyd and Jay search for answers about the Oni Masks, while Cole and Zane attempt to infiltrate the Sons of Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 02:35:00" d="2020-05-21 03:00:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% As Lloyd and Harumi venture deep into Primeval’s Eye in search of the third Oni Mask, the ninja attempt to fix the Bounty and make a startling discovery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 03:00:00" d="2020-05-21 03:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The ninja appeal to the police commissioner of Ninjago in an effort to help save Lloyd and thwart Harumi’s efforts to resurrect the evil Lord Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 03:25:00" d="2020-05-21 03:50:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lord Garmadon returns and frees Harumi, who encourages him to “achieve his true potential” by conquering the one thing that has always stood in his way… his son, Lloyd</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 03:50:00" d="2020-05-21 04:01:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball experiences an impossibly unfortunate chain of events</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 04:01:00" d="2020-05-21 04:12:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin accidentally create a loveable monster that eats their family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 04:12:00" d="2020-05-21 04:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is embarrassed when Mum comes to school to spend some “quality time”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 04:25:00" d="2020-05-21 04:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Wattersons are forced to rent out their house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 04:35:00" d="2020-05-21 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The kids find out Dad has been dressing as a woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 04:50:00" d="2020-05-21 05:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Everyone assumes Darwin &amp; Carrie's relationship is doomed</k>  </p>
</a>
