<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="108" t="2020-05-16 04:45:42"><p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 05:00:00" d="2020-05-23 05:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The students find their world turned upside down</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 05:10:00" d="2020-05-23 05:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Whilst Gumball and Darwin make fun of Mum and Dad for being old, their voices start to break</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 05:20:00" d="2020-05-23 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Sarah, the new kid in school, is Gumball and Darwin's number one, slightly obsessive, fan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 05:35:00" d="2020-05-23 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The new coach at Elmore High stands up to Jamie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 05:45:00" d="2020-05-23 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin help Anais rescue her doll from Tina Rex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 06:00:00" d="2020-05-23 06:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Back stateside Ben can't get into a cat cosplay competition…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 06:10:00" d="2020-05-23 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ben Gwen and Grandpa Max next travel to Castle Bishopbrook to visit a distant relative who's royalty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 06:25:00" d="2020-05-23 06:36:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin babysit Anais “responsibly”, whilst “irresponsibly” flooding the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 06:36:00" d="2020-05-23 06:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball goes to school in a dress and becomes the darling of Elmore High</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 06:50:00" d="2020-05-23 07:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball decides that the best way to prove to Mr. Fitzgerald that he's good enough for Penny is to become his apprentice for the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 07:00:00" d="2020-05-23 07:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball, Darwin and Anais are delighted when Grandpa Louie gives them a check for $5000. They immediately start fantasizing over what to spend it on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 07:15:00" d="2020-05-23 07:24:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin tells the Titans to stop being reckless teens or the Creepy Catcher will get them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 07:24:00" d="2020-05-23 07:40:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans put on a show but Robin warns that the performance must be boring or else they'll wake up the wolves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 07:40:00" d="2020-05-23 07:51:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lion-O and the other ThunderCats are thrilled to meet a new Thunderian! She’s good at fighting robots and most importantly thinks Lion-O and his Sword</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 07:51:00" d="2020-05-23 08:05:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Snarf leaves the Cats' Lair to get a needed vacation by transforming into a normal cat and hanging out with a nice old lady on a farm! But his relaxing day is threatened</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 08:05:00" d="2020-05-23 08:16:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Axel and the team try to figure out what Sarge Charge's secret weapon is they get ejected from the house by his newly upgraded security system</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 08:16:00" d="2020-05-23 08:35:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Axel must team up with Bearbarian to stop Madcap from transforming Luka's stuffed bear collection into an invincible army</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 08:35:00" d="2020-05-23 08:46:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Everything is going well for Kara Danvers both as a teen and a superhero until she starts taking the blame for things she didn't do</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 08:46:00" d="2020-05-23 08:57:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In an attempt to make Karen feel better about a pimple, Zee recounts her embarrassing transition into magichood, and the rift it created between her and her father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 08:57:00" d="2020-05-23 09:08:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After an embarrassing incident ruins Barbara Gordon’s reputation, rather than owning it, she decides it’s easier to harness The Flash’s ability to travel back in time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 09:08:00" d="2020-05-23 09:19:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Supergirl is presumed dead after a battle with Livewire, Kara Danvers decides to reinvent herself with a new look, a new personality, and a new name. Power Girl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 09:19:00" d="2020-05-23 09:29:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Desperate to emerge from her father’s shadow, Zee Zatara performs for her own audience, but loses her cool when her act is dismissed as fakery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 09:29:00" d="2020-05-23 09:39:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin's reputation is challenged and they really couldn't care less</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 09:39:00" d="2020-05-23 09:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball accidentally uploads a video of himself and wants it gone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 09:50:00" d="2020-05-23 10:01:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Watterson kids come up with a fool-proof plan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 10:01:00" d="2020-05-23 10:11:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The life of the background objects of Elmore are shown in a series of short skits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 10:11:00" d="2020-05-23 10:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Wattersons are surprised to discover that their past actions have consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 10:40:00" d="2020-05-23 10:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is late to meet Penny at the mall, but a series of misunderstandings on the way only delay him further</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 10:50:00" d="2020-05-23 11:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Mom sees Darwin gazing longingly at a fish-tank she thinks their mammalian lifestyle isn’t fulfilling her adopted son and deep down he longs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 11:00:00" d="2020-05-23 11:08:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When Beast Boy's head starts to rattle, Robin suggests that he should find a hobby so that his brain will stop shrinking. Beast Boy and his brain agree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 11:08:00" d="2020-05-23 11:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Gizmo convinces the Titans he's kidnapped Cyborg./Raven is cursed to be nice; meanwhile Starfire is about to marry a pot of chili</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 11:25:00" d="2020-05-23 11:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The other Titans are trying to stop a cow-stealing UFO</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 11:34:00" d="2020-05-23 11:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans tell their slightly inaccurate origin stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 11:50:00" d="2020-05-23 12:01:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Jessica Cruz is convinced she can find the purr-fect forever home for Dexter, a cat who has been deemed unadoptable because he’s basically the worst cat in the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 12:01:00" d="2020-05-23 12:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Babs and Kara spar over whose dog is better at the Metropolis Dog Show, Ace the Bat-Hound and Krypto the Superdog must find a way to save the day themselves!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 12:15:00" d="2020-05-23 12:25:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After an excessive spending spree, the Golden Goose tells the gang it won't give them any more golden eggs until they learn the value of money</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 12:25:00" d="2020-05-23 12:40:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The moon is bored of taking the nightshift, since everyone's always asleep. So Unikitty leads the gang in putting on an over-the-top late night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 12:40:00" d="2020-05-23 12:50:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Feeling unappreciated, Ice Bear leaves his brothers to be the chef of a restaurant. Desperate to fill the void, Grizz and Panda look for Ice Bear’s replacement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 12:50:00" d="2020-05-23 13:10:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fed up with sharing, Panda forbids his brothers from using his cellphone. But when the brothers get their own super-advanced smartphones, Panda succumbs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 13:10:00" d="2020-05-23 13:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% At Halloween show and tell, the class isn’t buying Gumball’s story about Gargaroth The Devourer until Carrie fakes a terrifying haunting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 13:20:00" d="2020-05-23 13:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is walking in the same direction as Hot Dog Guy, and with each step it becomes increasingly awkward</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 13:30:00" d="2020-05-23 13:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Elmore residents are going missing, and the cause of these disappearances may be closer to home than Gumball and Darwin think</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 13:40:00" d="2020-05-23 13:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin discover that Tobias is doing way better than them in an online game called Galatrek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 13:55:00" d="2020-05-23 14:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The kids find out Dad has been dressing as a woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 14:05:00" d="2020-05-23 14:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The boys manage to lose Polly in the blink of an eye</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 14:25:00" d="2020-05-23 14:35:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Vic accidently unleashes the lord of mischief from an ancient relic, V and V have to work together to trap it back inside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 14:35:00" d="2020-05-23 14:50:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Vic doesn't pick Val for his soccer team, Val vows to win with his own squad. But when his team doesn't match up, he resorts to supernatural means to win</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 14:50:00" d="2020-05-23 14:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin tells the Titans to stop being reckless teens or the Creepy Catcher will get them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 14:59:00" d="2020-05-23 15:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans put on a show but Robin warns that the performance must be boring or else they'll wake up the wolves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 15:10:00" d="2020-05-23 15:19:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When Robin starts doing power moves with Cyborg, Beast Boy gets very jealous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 15:19:00" d="2020-05-23 15:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When he is tasked with looking after the Bat-cave, Robin questions his relationship with Batman while struggling to keep the other Titans in line</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 15:35:00" d="2020-05-23 15:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>JP invites his friends over for a sleepover but it happens to be on the night of a huge game of Flashlight Tag in the Creek!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 15:45:00" d="2020-05-23 16:00:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Craig rescues a tadpole and decides to raise him into a level 100 frog!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 16:00:00" d="2020-05-23 16:11:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Axel must wrangle Galileo and Bobbie to shut down a rogue thermostat - improperly upgraded by Slobot - as it plunges the house into extreme hot and cold zones</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 16:11:00" d="2020-05-23 16:25:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After a Porcupunk sighting Axel leads a recon mission that slowly but surely proves to be a wild goose chase devised by Sarge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 16:25:00" d="2020-05-23 16:35:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Puppycorn's birthday wish is stolen by Master Frown, the biggest downer in the kingdom!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 16:35:00" d="2020-05-23 16:50:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Unikitty learns that boring old Richard has never produced any happy Sparkle Matter ever!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 16:50:00" d="2020-05-23 16:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin tells the Titans to stop being reckless teens or the Creepy Catcher will get them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 16:59:00" d="2020-05-23 17:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans put on a show but Robin warns that the performance must be boring or else they'll wake up the wolves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 17:15:00" d="2020-05-23 17:26:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fleeing the destruction of their home planet, Thundera, Lion-O and the ThunderCats land on the mysterious, dangerous all-around awesome world of Third Earth!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 17:26:00" d="2020-05-23 17:40:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fleeing the destruction of their home planet, Thundera, Lion-O and the ThunderCats land on the mysterious, dangerous all-around awesome world of Third Earth!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 17:40:00" d="2020-05-23 18:00:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When the ghost of a small town's founder returns to scare off mayoral candidates, the gang decides to run Velma as mayor to bait the ghost</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 18:00:00" d="2020-05-23 18:25:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Scooby Gang enter Dickens' classic &quot;A Christmas Carol&quot; as they try to get to the bottom of the mysterious ghost tormenting Scrooge in 1843 England</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 18:25:00" d="2020-05-23 18:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Sarah, the new kid in school, is Gumball and Darwin's number one, slightly obsessive, fan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 18:35:00" d="2020-05-23 18:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The new coach at Elmore High stands up to Jamie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 18:55:00" d="2020-05-23 19:06:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Nicole seeks to develop a sense of ambition in Gumball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 19:06:00" d="2020-05-23 19:16:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When everyone in the Watterson household wants to watch their favourite show at the same time, a massive fight breaks out over control of the television remote</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 19:16:00" d="2020-05-23 19:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is determined to drive Penny away from Leslie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 19:30:00" d="2020-05-23 19:40:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Vic accidently unleashes the lord of mischief from an ancient relic, V and V have to work together to trap it back inside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 19:40:00" d="2020-05-23 19:55:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Vic doesn't pick Val for his soccer team, Val vows to win with his own squad. But when his team doesn't match up, he resorts to supernatural means to win</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 19:55:00" d="2020-05-23 20:00:00"><n>The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ivandoe and Bert come across a tiny miserable prince in the forest. He needs a kiss to transform him back into the beautiful bullfrog he once was</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 20:00:00" d="2020-05-23 20:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Team Tennyson is saved by a toddler</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 20:10:00" d="2020-05-23 20:20:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Team Tennyson discovers a Hartfield-McJoy reenactment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 20:20:00" d="2020-05-23 20:35:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A mysterious electrical storm downs the Omni-Copter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 20:35:00" d="2020-05-23 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% The AO discover that old enemies Lord Brakken, Magnus, and Nillious are unnaturally happy to see them./Shun convinces Lord Brakken that his usual enemies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 21:00:00" d="2020-05-23 21:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lord Garmadon returns and frees Harumi, who encourages him to “achieve his true potential” by conquering the one thing that has always stood in his way… his son, Lloyd</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 21:25:00" d="2020-05-23 21:45:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The ninja race to save Lloyd, as a more powerful-than-ever Lord Garmadon creates an enormous Colossi to help him rule Ninjago and defeat the ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 21:45:00" d="2020-05-23 22:10:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Emperor Garmadon has taken control of Ninjago City where Lloyd retreats to the shadows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 22:10:00" d="2020-05-23 22:30:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Cole and Young Wu attempt to free their friends, who have been taken captive by a tribe of Dragon Hunters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 22:30:00" d="2020-05-23 22:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo and friends are stuck hanging out with Geezer’s Nephew -- a terrible, horrible, no good delinquent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 22:40:00" d="2020-05-23 22:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo and friends attempt to raise Butterfingers flagging self-esteem by training him in the art of Angelo-fu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 22:55:00" d="2020-05-23 23:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo shares his tips and tricks for trading favors and then cashing them all in to create “a perfect day.”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 23:05:00" d="2020-05-23 23:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% When his family go on vacation Angelo sets all kinds of traps in his house for potential thieves. Problem is when they return home Angelo lost his guide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 23:15:00" d="2020-05-23 23:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo and friends attempt to negotiate a deal for Peter and Cooper’s nonsensical home-made comic book with a famous comic book publisher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 23:25:00" d="2020-05-23 23:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo attempts to rack up the high score on an online business rating service to win free dinner at a fancy Japanese Steak House</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 23:40:00" d="2020-05-23 23:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% When Dad surprises the family with a brand new Electra smart home device everyone loves it at first, then Dad gets hooked and Angelo and Elena</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 23:50:00" d="2020-05-24 00:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% After failing an online “best friends” quiz Sherwood and Angelo drift apart. Angelo discovers the quiz was fake and tries to repair his relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 00:05:00" d="2020-05-24 00:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The secret behind Anton's immortality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 00:15:00" d="2020-05-24 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The kids finally get the puppy they always wanted, except it’s a turtle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 00:30:00" d="2020-05-24 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Mum reveals that Gumball's real name is &quot;Zach&quot;, Gumball adopts a cheesy, annoying persona to match the name</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 00:40:00" d="2020-05-24 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Nothing much is happening for Gumball and Darwin and the background characters in Elmore seize their moment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 00:50:00" d="2020-05-24 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is in such a bad mood that it spreads to Darwin, who joins him in complaining about everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 01:00:00" d="2020-05-24 01:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Wattersons are swapping scary stories on a family vacation, when their car breaks down in the middle of the desert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 01:15:00" d="2020-05-24 01:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Gumball and Darwin discover his diploma is fake, Principal Brown is determined to keep their discovery a secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 01:25:00" d="2020-05-24 01:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin start noticing small details around Elmore High that don't add up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 01:35:00" d="2020-05-24 01:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball, Darwin, and Anais search for the Watterson family treasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 01:45:00" d="2020-05-24 01:56:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Carrie takes Gumball, Darwin and Anais to a real haunted house party on Halloween</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 01:56:00" d="2020-05-24 02:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Darwin is too polite to speak his mind, so Gumball teaches him to be direct</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 02:10:00" d="2020-05-24 02:35:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The headquarters to the resistance is breached and Lloyd scrambles to avoid capture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 02:35:00" d="2020-05-24 03:00:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lloyd and his team plot to take control of the Oni Titan. Meanwhile in the First Realm, the Ninja fall into Iron Baron’s clutches and an old master returns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 03:00:00" d="2020-05-24 03:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The Ninja finally return home and unite to stop Emperor Garmadon, forcing Lloyd to make a decision that will forever change Ninjago</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 03:25:00" d="2020-05-24 03:50:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% As Ninjago City rebuilds, Faith arrives with a dire warning: the Oni have returned and are destroying the realms, one by one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 03:50:00" d="2020-05-24 04:01:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Nicole seeks to develop a sense of ambition in Gumball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 04:01:00" d="2020-05-24 04:11:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When everyone in the Watterson household wants to watch their favourite show at the same time, a massive fight breaks out over control of the television remote</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 04:11:00" d="2020-05-24 04:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is determined to drive Penny away from Leslie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 04:25:00" d="2020-05-24 04:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The secret behind Anton's immortality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 04:35:00" d="2020-05-24 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The kids finally get the puppy they always wanted, except it’s a turtle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 04:50:00" d="2020-05-24 05:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Mum reveals that Gumball's real name is &quot;Zach&quot;, Gumball adopts a cheesy, annoying persona to match the name</k>  </p>
</a>
