<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="108" t="2020-05-10 04:29:29"><p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 05:00:00" d="2020-05-17 05:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Wattersons fear the worst when they are summoned to a Town Hall meeting, but are surprised when they're offered a new house. Until they discover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 05:10:00" d="2020-05-17 05:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Wattersons compete over who has the worst life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 05:20:00" d="2020-05-17 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When the kids find out that Mom's life hasn't panned out as she'd hoped, they start taking on her chores. However, they accidentally grab her bucket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 05:35:00" d="2020-05-17 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Wattersons will do whatever it takes to get into the first screening of the latest Stellar Odyssey sequel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 05:45:00" d="2020-05-17 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Join the citizens of Elmore for a song and dance spectacular that will have you covering your ears with joy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 06:00:00" d="2020-05-17 06:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>As Max attempts to get Ben and Gwen to the Four Corners Monument before sunset, an ominous fog bank engulfs the roadway</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 06:10:00" d="2020-05-17 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After Ben gets too much publicity for his alien antics in Fort Knox a jealous Gwen feels unappreciated but she soon must prove she's a worthy member of Team Tennyson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 06:25:00" d="2020-05-17 06:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin try to understand Juke's urgent beatbox message</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 06:35:00" d="2020-05-17 06:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Richard is left in charge for the day, but his lack of rules attracts unwanted guests to the Watterson house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 06:50:00" d="2020-05-17 07:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Things aren’t going Gumball’s way at school so he assumes there must be a Secret Society</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 07:00:00" d="2020-05-17 07:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin want to see the scariest film of the year</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 07:15:00" d="2020-05-17 07:24:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans are at Super Hero Summer Camp for the week and they may need to add another teammate to win the big canoe race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 07:24:00" d="2020-05-17 07:40:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans give Robin advice to guide him through his camp romance with Wonder Girl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 07:40:00" d="2020-05-17 07:51:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Cheetara is the fastest living person in the universe until Monkian beats her in a race?! Now Cheetara has to find something else to be the best at</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 07:51:00" d="2020-05-17 08:05:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lion-O &quot;accidentally&quot; releases a whole space prison-full of space criminals and winds up on the wrong side of the law. On the right side</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 08:05:00" d="2020-05-17 08:15:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Bears switch bedrooms for the night and get a glimpse of the living space of one of their brothers. But as they go deeper, hidden secrets are revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 08:15:00" d="2020-05-17 08:35:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>To recover a missing package, The Bears get help from Ranger Tabes, an eccentric forest ranger. But her overblown sense of justice might</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 08:35:00" d="2020-05-17 08:45:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When she stumbles across a villainous plot - and all the other heroes are indisposed - Bumblebee must rise to the occasion… despite being the smallest of the bunch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 08:45:00" d="2020-05-17 08:55:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>With her boss at the Burrito Bucket eager to fire her, Babs is torn between her role as a Super Hero and a dutiful employee when a bank robbery breaks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 08:55:00" d="2020-05-17 09:06:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Jessica Cruz is convinced she can find the purr-fect forever home for Dexter, a cat who has been deemed unadoptable because he’s basically the worst cat in the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 09:06:00" d="2020-05-17 09:17:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The girls must track down Katana a mysterious warrior who’s stealing the souls of Metropolis’s villains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 09:17:00" d="2020-05-17 09:28:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The girls must track down Katana a mysterious warrior who's stealing the souls of Metropolis's villains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 09:28:00" d="2020-05-17 09:39:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Darwin has promised to play video games with Gumball, but his promise with Banana Joe interferes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 09:39:00" d="2020-05-17 09:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin must apologise to everyone they know after getting a threatening message on Elmore Plus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 09:50:00" d="2020-05-17 10:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin try to understand Juke's urgent beatbox message</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 10:00:00" d="2020-05-17 10:11:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Richard is left in charge for the day, but his lack of rules attracts unwanted guests to the Watterson house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 10:11:00" d="2020-05-17 10:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin fail to make some instant homemade movie classics</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 10:40:00" d="2020-05-17 10:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Alan ditches Gumball to do something more fun, Gumball is desperate to track him down and make him pay for his betrayal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 10:50:00" d="2020-05-17 11:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% To try and make Mr Small feel like he’s inspired the students, Gumball and Darwin try to follow every piece of advice Mr Small gives them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 11:00:00" d="2020-05-17 11:09:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When Cyborg and Starfire find a baby bird, it awakens their inner child</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 11:09:00" d="2020-05-17 11:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% After Young Justice easily takes out the HIVE while the other Titans make silly jokes Robin decides the team needs to get serious./ The Titans visit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 11:25:00" d="2020-05-17 11:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% It's Crime Season and Robin is determined to continue his streak of stopping 52 crimes every year</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 11:34:00" d="2020-05-17 11:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin's streak of stopping 52 crimes every year is in jeopardy when members of his team are poached by Kid Flash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 11:50:00" d="2020-05-17 12:00:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Having just moved to the boring Metropolis suburbs Batgirl is thrilled when she intercepts a call from Batman asking for help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 12:00:00" d="2020-05-17 12:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Supergirl always relies on her strength, but she'll need more than brawn to stop brainy Catwoman from stealing valuable gems from the local science museum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 12:15:00" d="2020-05-17 12:25:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Unikitty's installed Bad Vibe detectors in the castle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 12:25:00" d="2020-05-17 12:40:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Unikitty and gang have ordered some delicious Thai food for dinner. Unfortunately the wait for the delivery is proving too much, time itself seems to have slowed down</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 12:40:00" d="2020-05-17 12:50:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Bears get a Shmorby home assistant device and become lazy couch potatoes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 12:50:00" d="2020-05-17 13:10:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Bears star in a reality TV show along with Griff Tom and Isaac</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 13:10:00" d="2020-05-17 13:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Gumball and Darwin decide it's time they join a crew, they agree that the coolest posse in Elmore is the Senior Citizens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 13:20:00" d="2020-05-17 13:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Anais reveals that she's in the grade above them at school, Gumball and Darwin's eyes are suddenly opened to a whole new world of other students</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 13:30:00" d="2020-05-17 13:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Dad discovers that Granny Jojo and Louie plan to get married and move to Florida. To stop this happening he adopts Louie so that he can forbid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 13:40:00" d="2020-05-17 13:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% After they receive an extravagant invitation to Masami's birthday party, Gumball and Darwin are anxious to find just the right gift for her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 13:55:00" d="2020-05-17 14:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin find themselves in serious trouble when they agree to everything the new kid in school says. The truth is they can't understand a word that he says</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 14:05:00" d="2020-05-17 14:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball decides it’s time to play cupid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 14:25:00" d="2020-05-17 14:36:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vic and Val go on a hot air balloon trip with Sal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 14:36:00" d="2020-05-17 14:50:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vic and Val head to a haunted island</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 14:50:00" d="2020-05-17 14:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans are at Super Hero Summer Camp for the week and they may need to add another teammate to win the big canoe race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 14:59:00" d="2020-05-17 15:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans give Robin advice to guide him through his camp romance with Wonder Girl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 15:10:00" d="2020-05-17 15:19:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin refuses to give the Titans any more orders so that they'll learn to think for themselves. Instead the Titans start taking their cues from fortune cookies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 15:19:00" d="2020-05-17 15:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin convinces the Titans to go back to school with him so he can finally become the all-American class president-type he's dreamt of being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 15:35:00" d="2020-05-17 15:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Craig and his sister Jessica try their hand at running the daycare at the Creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 15:45:00" d="2020-05-17 16:00:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Craig Kelsey and JP become smugglers to sneak candy to kids in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 16:00:00" d="2020-05-17 16:10:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Badgerclops gets huge to destroy a towering monster but when he refuses to shrink down the kingdom faces a new terror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 16:10:00" d="2020-05-17 16:25:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When a Sweetypie isn't impressed with the sheriff dept's antics, our three heroes try everything to win him over</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 16:25:00" d="2020-05-17 16:35:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After an excessive spending spree, the Golden Goose tells the gang it won't give them any more golden eggs until they learn the value of money</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 16:35:00" d="2020-05-17 16:50:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The moon is bored of taking the nightshift, since everyone's always asleep. So Unikitty leads the gang in putting on an over-the-top late night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 16:50:00" d="2020-05-17 16:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans are at Super Hero Summer Camp for the week and they may need to add another teammate to win the big canoe race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 16:59:00" d="2020-05-17 17:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans give Robin advice to guide him through his camp romance with Wonder Girl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 17:15:00" d="2020-05-17 17:26:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lion-O is tasked with mapping the beaches of Third Earth which leads to him somehow draining the oceans of all water entirely. Woops!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 17:26:00" d="2020-05-17 17:40:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lion-O never pays attention during Tygra’s training sessions so when he’s asked to do a pop quiz on &quot;sword magic&quot; he accidentally opens a portal to the Astral Plane!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 17:40:00" d="2020-05-17 18:00:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang head out to a Day of the Dead festival. There, they learn the spirit of the old, legendary criminal, El Bandito, has returned to terrorise the locals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 18:00:00" d="2020-05-17 18:25:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Daphne agrees to watch her friend’s kid, Wayne, and convinces Fred to take a night off from mysteries to go to the boardwalk amusement park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 18:25:00" d="2020-05-17 18:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Elmore residents are going missing, and the cause of these disappearances may be closer to home than Gumball and Darwin think</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 18:35:00" d="2020-05-17 18:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin discover that Tobias is doing way better than them in an online game called Galatrek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 18:55:00" d="2020-05-17 19:06:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin’s wish comes true when they suddenly turn into men</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 19:06:00" d="2020-05-17 19:17:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball discovers the difference between a “date” and a “pet’s funeral”. he hard way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 19:17:00" d="2020-05-17 19:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Gumball rejects “The Rejects Club”, the rejects wreak their revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 19:30:00" d="2020-05-17 19:41:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vic and Val go on a hot air balloon trip with Sal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 19:41:00" d="2020-05-17 19:55:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vic and Val head to a haunted island</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 19:55:00" d="2020-05-17 20:00:00"><n>The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ivandoe and Bert comes to the rescue when a damsell in distress is being threatened by a big scary wolf. Will the enchanting young lady steal more than Ivandoe’s heart?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 20:00:00" d="2020-05-17 20:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Back stateside Ben can't get into a cat cosplay competition…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 20:10:00" d="2020-05-17 20:20:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ben Gwen and Grandpa Max next travel to Castle Bishopbrook to visit a distant relative who's royalty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 20:20:00" d="2020-05-17 20:35:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While in Paris, Ben catches Zombozo robbing the Louvre. But when Zombozo hypnotizes Ben to remain speechless, Ben must navigate a foreign</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 20:35:00" d="2020-05-17 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% Near giving up, Magnus gains new strength and insight on the AO's mission to find Core Cells./Drago's sickness leads Dan to a revelation that there is an ailing Core Cell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 21:00:00" d="2020-05-17 21:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lord Garmadon returns and frees Harumi, who encourages him to “achieve his true potential” by conquering the one thing that has always stood in his way… his son, Lloyd</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 21:25:00" d="2020-05-17 21:45:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The ninja race to save Lloyd, as a more powerful-than-ever Lord Garmadon creates an enormous Colossi to help him rule Ninjago and defeat the ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 21:45:00" d="2020-05-17 22:10:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Emperor Garmadon has taken control of Ninjago City where Lloyd retreats to the shadows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 22:10:00" d="2020-05-17 22:30:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Cole and Young Wu attempt to free their friends, who have been taken captive by a tribe of Dragon Hunters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 22:30:00" d="2020-05-17 22:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo and friends make a TV show pilot called “Angelo Rules,” with Lola producing, Sherwood directing, Angelo writing, and Butterfingers playing Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 22:40:00" d="2020-05-17 22:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% After Mom cuts off Angelo’s videogame time Angelo attempts to change her mind. He sets out to prove to her that gaming is an important skillset</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 22:55:00" d="2020-05-17 23:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo and friends are stuck hanging out with Geezer’s Nephew -- a terrible, horrible, no good delinquent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 23:05:00" d="2020-05-17 23:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo and friends attempt to raise Butterfingers flagging self-esteem by training him in the art of Angelo-fu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 23:15:00" d="2020-05-17 23:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo shares his tips and tricks for trading favors and then cashing them all in to create “a perfect day.”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 23:25:00" d="2020-05-17 23:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% When his family go on vacation Angelo sets all kinds of traps in his house for potential thieves. Problem is when they return home Angelo lost his guide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 23:40:00" d="2020-05-17 23:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo and friends attempt to negotiate a deal for Peter and Cooper’s nonsensical home-made comic book with a famous comic book publisher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-17 23:50:00" d="2020-05-18 00:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo attempts to rack up the high score on an online business rating service to win free dinner at a fancy Japanese Steak House</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 00:05:00" d="2020-05-18 00:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Darwin is delighted when they discover their old childhood toys, but soon realises that some things are best left in the past</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 00:15:00" d="2020-05-18 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Darwin ends up in detention with the Bomb Kid, who decides to make Darwin his new target. However, it backfires when Darwin ruins his life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 00:30:00" d="2020-05-18 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The kids convince Mr Corneille to become a cage fighter and set up a fight against a fearsome Russian fighter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 00:40:00" d="2020-05-18 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are jealous of a sparking a baby war</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 00:50:00" d="2020-05-18 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Tobias tries to be Gumball's best friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 01:00:00" d="2020-05-18 01:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin just want to veg out all day but end up having to save the rest of the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 01:15:00" d="2020-05-18 01:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The kids try to help Dad bond with Frankie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 01:25:00" d="2020-05-18 01:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Hotdog Kid discover why they're so awkward with each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 01:35:00" d="2020-05-18 01:46:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin help Anais rescue her doll from Tina Rex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 01:46:00" d="2020-05-18 01:57:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are unwitting accomplices in a gas station robbery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 01:57:00" d="2020-05-18 02:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin accidentally destroy Mr Robinson’s new car… or do they?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 02:10:00" d="2020-05-18 02:35:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The headquarters to the resistance is breached and Lloyd scrambles to avoid capture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 02:35:00" d="2020-05-18 03:00:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lloyd and his team plot to take control of the Oni Titan. Meanwhile in the First Realm, the Ninja fall into Iron Baron’s clutches and an old master returns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 03:00:00" d="2020-05-18 03:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The Ninja finally return home and unite to stop Emperor Garmadon, forcing Lloyd to make a decision that will forever change Ninjago</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 03:25:00" d="2020-05-18 03:50:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% As Ninjago City rebuilds, Faith arrives with a dire warning: the Oni have returned and are destroying the realms, one by one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 03:50:00" d="2020-05-18 04:01:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin’s wish comes true when they suddenly turn into men</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 04:01:00" d="2020-05-18 04:12:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball discovers the difference between a “date” and a “pet’s funeral”. he hard way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 04:12:00" d="2020-05-18 04:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Gumball rejects “The Rejects Club”, the rejects wreak their revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 04:25:00" d="2020-05-18 04:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Darwin is delighted when they discover their old childhood toys, but soon realises that some things are best left in the past</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 04:35:00" d="2020-05-18 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Darwin ends up in detention with the Bomb Kid, who decides to make Darwin his new target. However, it backfires when Darwin ruins his life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 04:50:00" d="2020-05-18 05:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The kids convince Mr Corneille to become a cage fighter and set up a fight against a fearsome Russian fighter</k>  </p>
</a>
