<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="104" t="2020-05-11 04:19:42"><p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 05:00:00" d="2020-05-18 05:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are jealous of a sparking a baby war</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 05:10:00" d="2020-05-18 05:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Tobias tries to be Gumball's best friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 05:20:00" d="2020-05-18 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin just want to veg out all day but end up having to save the rest of the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 05:35:00" d="2020-05-18 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The kids try to help Dad bond with Frankie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 05:45:00" d="2020-05-18 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Hotdog Kid discover why they're so awkward with each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 06:00:00" d="2020-05-18 06:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After a lull in alien antics a restless Ben suggests to Max and Gwen that he might be a better hero if he went solo. Ben soon finds out he must rethink his strategy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 06:10:00" d="2020-05-18 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Weatherheads set their sights on Winter Wonderland as their next target and Ben must become one with his emotion if he is to save the town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 06:25:00" d="2020-05-18 06:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin fail to make some instant homemade movie classics</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 06:35:00" d="2020-05-18 06:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin's reputation is challenged and they really couldn't care less</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 06:50:00" d="2020-05-18 07:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin hit snooze too many times on their alarm clock and miss the school-bus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 07:00:00" d="2020-05-18 07:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Things keep going missing in the house, so it’s up to Gumball and Darwin to find the culprit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 07:15:00" d="2020-05-18 07:24:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans put on a show but Robin warns that the performance must be boring or else they'll wake up the wolves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 07:24:00" d="2020-05-18 07:40:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin finally teaches the other Titans a very valuable lesson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 07:40:00" d="2020-05-18 07:51:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lion-O is tasked with mapping the beaches of Third Earth which leads to him somehow draining the oceans of all water entirely. Woops!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 07:51:00" d="2020-05-18 08:05:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lion-O never pays attention during Tygra’s training sessions so when he’s asked to do a pop quiz on &quot;sword magic&quot; he accidentally opens a portal to the Astral Plane!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 08:05:00" d="2020-05-18 08:15:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Feeling unappreciated, Ice Bear leaves his brothers to be the chef of a restaurant. Desperate to fill the void, Grizz and Panda look for Ice Bear’s replacement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 08:15:00" d="2020-05-18 08:35:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fed up with sharing, Panda forbids his brothers from using his cellphone. But when the brothers get their own super-advanced smartphones, Panda succumbs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 08:35:00" d="2020-05-18 08:55:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fred and the gang help with a mystery involving a figure from Fred's past. Fred discovers his old childhood friend has also arrived with her gang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 08:55:00" d="2020-05-18 09:20:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Shaggy drags the gang to a childhood arcade where he's determined to finally collect enough tickets to win the prize he's wanted since he was a boy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 09:20:00" d="2020-05-18 09:30:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Craig and his sister Jessica try their hand at running the daycare at the Creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 09:30:00" d="2020-05-18 10:10:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Kelsey accepts a quest from the Elders of the Creek, but is she ready for her terrifying opponent?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 10:10:00" d="2020-05-18 10:21:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin’s martial arts costumes make them a laughing stock at school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 10:21:00" d="2020-05-18 10:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is traumatised when accidentally kissed on the mouth by his Grandma JoJo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 10:40:00" d="2020-05-18 10:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Darwin asks for his advice on hats, Gumball suddenly can’t speak and offends Darwin. Darwin is convinced Gumball said he had a fat head</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 10:50:00" d="2020-05-18 11:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When she has no one to share her lunch with, Jamie realises she needs a sweetheart. Darwin's the only one who doesn’t flee immediately, so he and Jamie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 11:00:00" d="2020-05-18 11:09:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% After Young Justice easily takes out the HIVE while the other Titans make silly jokes Robin decides the team needs to get serious./ The Titans visit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 11:09:00" d="2020-05-18 11:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Raven and Beast Boy are shocked to discover that their exes, Terra and Aqualad, are now dating each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 11:25:00" d="2020-05-18 11:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% It's Movie Night and the Titans have a hard time deciding who gets to choose which movie they watch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 11:34:00" d="2020-05-18 11:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% It's back to school as the Titans teach each other about science and grammar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 11:50:00" d="2020-05-18 12:00:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Diana Prince is absolutely crushing it in every single aspect of life as a student at Metropolis High… until someone shows up who threatens to throw</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 12:00:00" d="2020-05-18 12:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Desperate to emerge from her father’s shadow, Zee Zatara performs for her own audience, but loses her cool when her act is dismissed as fakery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 12:15:00" d="2020-05-18 12:25:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When the Score creeper traps Unikitty and the gang in his laser tag arena the gang must defeat the house team or be imprisoned forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 12:25:00" d="2020-05-18 12:40:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang are at the local laundromat cleaning their clothes, when Unikitty finds Batman's uniform mixed in with her clothes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 12:40:00" d="2020-05-18 12:50:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A gang of streetwise kids takes Baby Ice Bear under their wing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 12:50:00" d="2020-05-18 13:10:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Bears have trouble assembling some furniture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 13:10:00" d="2020-05-18 13:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball decides that the best way to prove to Mr. Fitzgerald that he's good enough for Penny is to become his apprentice for the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 13:20:00" d="2020-05-18 13:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball, Darwin and Anais are delighted when Grandpa Louie gives them a check for $5000. They immediately start fantasizing over what to spend it on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 13:30:00" d="2020-05-18 13:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When they find Anais training herself for a brutal showdown, Gumball and Darwin realise that their sister is being pestered at school by an annoying kid: Billy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 13:40:00" d="2020-05-18 13:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Darwin taunts Gumball about how predictable he is, Gumball tries to prove that he can still surprise his buddy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 13:55:00" d="2020-05-18 14:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Wattersons are forced to rent out their house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 14:05:00" d="2020-05-18 14:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The kids find out Dad has been dressing as a woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 14:25:00" d="2020-05-18 14:36:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Vic &amp; Val are forced to go to Guillermo’s boring birthday party, they devise a scheme to leave early, but end up discovering that the party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 14:36:00" d="2020-05-18 14:50:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Vic &amp; Val accidently turn themselves and Don into babies, they must escape a daycare center in order to change back to their normal ages</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 14:50:00" d="2020-05-18 14:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans put on a show but Robin warns that the performance must be boring or else they'll wake up the wolves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 14:59:00" d="2020-05-18 15:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin finally teaches the other Titans a very valuable lesson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 15:10:00" d="2020-05-18 15:19:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Control Freak informs the Titans that they are on a TV show he created and demands they earn him an award</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 15:19:00" d="2020-05-18 15:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Cyborg's real strength comes not from his robot parts, but from his favourite song</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 15:35:00" d="2020-05-18 15:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Craig Kelsey and JP become smugglers to sneak candy to kids in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 15:45:00" d="2020-05-18 16:00:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>JP decides to follow his heart and tries to join the Horse Girls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 16:00:00" d="2020-05-18 16:11:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Axel ventures into his uncle's strictly off-limits basement lab in hopes of fixing a broken toy and ends up unleashing living ones instead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 16:11:00" d="2020-05-18 16:25:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Axel discovers that he can transform into a toy and teams up with his new team of toys to stop Madcap from stealing a Minergy battery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 16:25:00" d="2020-05-18 16:35:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After Unikitty finds out that tourism is down in the Unikingdom, she recruits the gang to make a tourism video to inspire people to visit the kingdom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 16:35:00" d="2020-05-18 16:50:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A mysterious relative, Uncle Donklecorn, shows up unexpectedly, claiming to be family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 16:50:00" d="2020-05-18 16:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% After not receiving participation medals, the Titans must demonstrate what they learned at camp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 16:59:00" d="2020-05-18 17:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When her teammates turns evil it's up to Lady Legasus to stop the League of Legs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 17:15:00" d="2020-05-18 17:26:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Cats' Lair is attacked by gold-loving robot pirates! This is a good thing since it means Lion-O and the ThunderKittens can ditch their chores and fight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 17:26:00" d="2020-05-18 17:40:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Freed from the Astral Plane, the ghost of the ThunderCats mentor is now free to visit the Cats' Lair. Which means he can finally tell them why Thundera exploded. It’s story time!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 17:40:00" d="2020-05-18 18:00:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang goes on a camping trip. Fred’s desire for the gang to get in touch with their natural instincts turns into on-the-job training as Viking Ghosts attack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 18:00:00" d="2020-05-18 18:25:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fred is on trial, convicted of being the mastermind behind the mysteries he’s solved. With the help of his attorney, Daphne, we go back over the day’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 18:25:00" d="2020-05-18 18:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Rocky suggests that the Elmore Junior High kids skip school, the bus is boarded by criminals who seem to want to teach them the importance of school attendance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 18:35:00" d="2020-05-18 18:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% As night falls in Elmore, the Moon takes us on a tour through the various dreams -- and nightmares -- of the town’s slumbering inhabitants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 18:55:00" d="2020-05-18 19:06:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin make their Dad believe in magic again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 19:06:00" d="2020-05-18 19:17:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Ms Simian sets out to “befriend” Gumball in order to win a Favourite Teacher Award</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 19:17:00" d="2020-05-18 19:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin give Mr Robinson a home and end up saving his marriage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 19:30:00" d="2020-05-18 19:41:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Vic &amp; Val are forced to go to Guillermo’s boring birthday party, they devise a scheme to leave early, but end up discovering that the party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 19:41:00" d="2020-05-18 19:55:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Vic &amp; Val accidently turn themselves and Don into babies, they must escape a daycare center in order to change back to their normal ages</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 19:55:00" d="2020-05-18 20:00:00"><n>The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ivandoe and Bert get captured and tied up by a very intense forest survivalist who happens to be a pink poodle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 20:00:00" d="2020-05-18 20:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A trip to the South Pole goes upside down when Team Tennyson land on the North Pole instead! Ben quickly discovers the culprits are magnetically-powered scientists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 20:10:00" d="2020-05-18 20:20:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ben Gwen and Grandpa Max arrive at a Native American national park to witness the Ayasha Plinths</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 20:20:00" d="2020-05-18 20:35:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Team Tennyson checks out a Samurai Museum in Tokyo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 20:35:00" d="2020-05-18 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% Strata's return is much more than a simple rematch when he's been infected by a strange ooze./Using Strata's gauntlet, the AO think they've found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 21:00:00" d="2020-05-18 21:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lloyd must find his voice as he leads a small resistance to capture the airwaves in Ninjago City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 21:25:00" d="2020-05-18 21:45:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lloyd and the rebels celebrate their successful strike against Emperor Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 21:45:00" d="2020-05-18 22:10:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The headquarters to the resistance is breached and Lloyd scrambles to avoid capture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 22:10:00" d="2020-05-18 22:30:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% As Lloyd unmasks Mystake for who she truly is, Emperor Garmadon embraces Harumi as his daughter of darkness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 22:30:00" d="2020-05-18 22:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% When Dad surprises the family with a brand new Electra smart home device everyone loves it at first, then Dad gets hooked and Angelo and Elena</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 22:40:00" d="2020-05-18 22:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% After failing an online “best friends” quiz Sherwood and Angelo drift apart. Angelo discovers the quiz was fake and tries to repair his relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 22:55:00" d="2020-05-18 23:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo enters a pie baking contest with his Dad as his partner until the two have creative differences and go it alone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 23:05:00" d="2020-05-18 23:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo and Lola start a campaign to help Sherwood get voted “most likely to succeed” by his classmates instead of Tracy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 23:15:00" d="2020-05-18 23:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Dad takes a parenting class which works! Now he has more control of his kids. Angelo infiltrates the parenting class (posing as an adult) to learn Dad’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 23:25:00" d="2020-05-18 23:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo comes up with unique inventions to win “Snake Pit” a TV show where you pitch your business idea to local “business tycoons” hoping to get them to invest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 23:40:00" d="2020-05-18 23:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% After making a bet that their life is harder, Angelo and Mr. Foot trade places. Angelo becomes the teacher, and Mr. Foot the unruly student</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-18 23:50:00" d="2020-05-19 00:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% After taking a career test that claims to predict your future and receiving disappointing results, Angelo and friends set out to change their destinies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 00:05:00" d="2020-05-19 00:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin try to find out the name of their neighbour, Antlers Guy, but accidentally blow his witness protection cover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 00:15:00" d="2020-05-19 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Pr Brown make a pact to tell each other's girlfriends about problems they have</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 00:30:00" d="2020-05-19 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Alan has lost faith in humanity and turned the world black and white. Gumball has to get over his hatred of Alan to bring the color back by singing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 00:40:00" d="2020-05-19 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% A group of kids get locked in the school after their parents have a charity gala. They appoint Gumball as leader to get them out but it leads to chaos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 00:50:00" d="2020-05-19 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Clayton shapeshifts into people to take their detentions for money. He starts framing people for misdemeanors so GB and DW must track him down to stop him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 01:00:00" d="2020-05-19 01:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Sarah finds a notebook from an awesome store!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 01:15:00" d="2020-05-19 01:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin get caught in the middle of a trash can war between Richard and Mr. Robinson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 01:25:00" d="2020-05-19 01:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball decides to put Mr. Small's eco-friendly principles to the test but it doesn't quite go as planned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 01:35:00" d="2020-05-19 01:46:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball experiences an impossibly unfortunate chain of events</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 01:46:00" d="2020-05-19 01:57:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin accidentally create a loveable monster that eats their family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 01:57:00" d="2020-05-19 02:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is embarrassed when Mum comes to school to spend some “quality time”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 02:10:00" d="2020-05-19 02:35:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% When Iron Baron forces Wu to retrieve the Dragon Armor, things don’t go as planned. In Ninjago, Lloyd can only endure so much as he holds onto hope for the Ninjas’ return</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 02:35:00" d="2020-05-19 03:00:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Having freed Lord Garmadon from Kryptarium Prison, the ninja are beset by doubts, particularly Lloyd</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 03:00:00" d="2020-05-19 03:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The ninja race back to the Monastery of Spinjitzu. This is the last stand. The final battle against the Oni is now</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 03:25:00" d="2020-05-19 03:50:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% When an unknown criminal syndicate threatens the Royal Family, the Ninja are called into action. They must protect the princess and an artifact</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 03:50:00" d="2020-05-19 04:01:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin make their Dad believe in magic again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 04:01:00" d="2020-05-19 04:12:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Ms Simian sets out to “befriend” Gumball in order to win a Favourite Teacher Award</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 04:12:00" d="2020-05-19 04:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin give Mr Robinson a home and end up saving his marriage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 04:25:00" d="2020-05-19 04:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin try to find out the name of their neighbour, Antlers Guy, but accidentally blow his witness protection cover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 04:35:00" d="2020-05-19 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Pr Brown make a pact to tell each other's girlfriends about problems they have</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-19 04:50:00" d="2020-05-19 05:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Alan has lost faith in humanity and turned the world black and white. Gumball has to get over his hatred of Alan to bring the color back by singing</k>  </p>
</a>
