<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="120" t="2021-07-12 04:54:05"><p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 05:05:00" d="2021-07-19 05:15:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 2016 II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bounty Ball
While Gwen listens to a lecture on the Transcontinental Railroad, Ben sneaks away to the gift shop, but once the Bounty Hunters appear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 05:15:00" d="2021-07-19 05:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 2016 II (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fear the Fogg
As Max attempts to get Ben and Gwen to the Four Corners Monument before sunset, an ominous fog bank engulfs the roadway and forces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 05:25:00" d="2021-07-19 05:35:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Trouble Busters!
Now that the Awesome Brawlers are world famous Bakugan experts, they want to help people solve their Bakugan-related problems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 05:35:00" d="2021-07-19 05:50:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>French Fry Wars
The Awesome Brawlers are arguing over who gets to eat the last french-fry. At first, each member makes a case for why they should</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 05:50:00" d="2021-07-19 05:55:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Baby Steps
Magoo is babysitting the Neighbors' toddler. The baby flees and kidnaps Fizz mistaking him for a plush toy. Thinking he’s playing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 05:55:00" d="2021-07-19 06:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Golden Fizz
Fizz plans on replacing the statue from an Oscar-like award's ceremony, with a statue in his effigy. But Magoo grabs it, thinking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 06:05:00" d="2021-07-19 06:10:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Saving the Gnomes of Astroturf
Magoo mistakes some kids at the park for gnomes in a magic forest. Fizz uses a remote to immobilize them to win over their parents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 06:10:00" d="2021-07-19 06:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dusk of the Cucumber
Fizz invents a cucumber that turns whoever is holding it into an object of human worship. When Magoo sees hypnotized passers-by being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 06:25:00" d="2021-07-19 06:30:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Spinning Headlock Elbow Drop
Magoo thinks that he is auditioning for a circus troop but he is actually in a professional wrestling ring in the middle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 06:30:00" d="2021-07-19 06:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mega Magoo vs Dr. Fizz
Fizz controlling a robot distributes free ice cream to everyone in the city. When Magoo mistakes him for a destructive monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 06:35:00" d="2021-07-19 06:45:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ghost Hunt
Fizz has invented a machine which stops toast from landing butter-side down. Magoo paying his neighbor a visit sees some floating toast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 06:45:00" d="2021-07-19 07:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Love Thy Neighbour
Magoo thinks he is housesitting for Weasel while the latter is on vacation. When he sees him returning from the grocery store</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 07:00:00" d="2021-07-19 07:25:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Renn Scare
The gang heads to the Velma’s beloved authentic Renaissance Fair where they must find a way to infiltrate the royal feast in order</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 07:25:00" d="2021-07-19 07:55:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% How to Train Your Coward
Shaggy and Scooby decide to leave the gang! But before that they insist on training the new recruits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 07:55:00" d="2021-07-19 08:05:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek III (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Afterschool Snackdown
Craig enters a food competition in the Creek but worries he may be out of his league</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 08:05:00" d="2021-07-19 08:20:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek III (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Creature Feature
Craig finds himself being chased by a monster in the Creek that's straight out of the movies!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 08:20:00" d="2021-07-19 08:30:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek III (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>King Of Camping
The Williams Family goes camping and Craig helps his dad prove he's the King of Camping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 08:30:00" d="2021-07-19 08:50:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek III (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Rise And Fall Of The Green Poncho
Craig tries to warn his friends about the Other Side of the Creek with a tale from the Creek's defender - the Green Poncho</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 08:50:00" d="2021-07-19 09:00:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek II (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Summer Wish
When Craig decides to keep a lightning bug in a jar, he disrupts the delicate balance of Summer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 09:00:00" d="2021-07-19 09:15:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek III (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Alternate Creekiverse
Craig, Kelsey and JP imagine a disturbing alternate reality where they never became friends!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 09:15:00" d="2021-07-19 09:25:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>You're It
A vicious game of tag wreaks havoc on the Creek, claiming Kelsey as the next &quot;it&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 09:25:00" d="2021-07-19 09:35:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Itch To Explore
Craig's quest to map the entire Creek takes him and his friends into the treacherous Poison Ivy Grove</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 09:35:00" d="2021-07-19 09:55:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% Jessica Goes To The Creek
When Craig and Jessica are locked out of the house, Craig has no choice but to bring his little sister to the Creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 09:55:00" d="2021-07-19 10:05:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Guillermo's Gathering
When Vic &amp; Val are forced to go to Guillermo's boring birthday party, they devise a scheme to leave early, but end up discovering</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 10:05:00" d="2021-07-19 10:20:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Escape From Bebe Bay
When Vic &amp; Val accidentally turn themselves and Don into babies, they must escape a daycare center in order to change back to their normal ages</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 10:20:00" d="2021-07-19 10:30:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Great Bongo Heist
The boys forget to get Chata a gift for Abuela Day and in a panicked move, they pretend that the bongo drums they borrowed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 10:30:00" d="2021-07-19 10:50:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Cat-Pocalyspe
When Vic gets sick and is stuck in his room, he spies on Pineapple and becomes convinced that Pineapple is creating an army of zombie cats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 10:50:00" d="2021-07-19 10:55:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Animal Pics
Grizzy and the Lemmings discover the joys of photography with the ranger's instant print camera. Grizzy would like to make a beautiful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 10:55:00" d="2021-07-19 11:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Diet
The fridge in the cabin has changed: it's been replaced by a brand new state-of-the-art appliance which analyzes the body fat percentage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 11:00:00" d="2021-07-19 11:10:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Balloon Bear
Grizzy watches a demonstration of balloon modelling on TV. He decides to make a balloon poodle to offer the she-bear he's enamored with</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 11:10:00" d="2021-07-19 11:20:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Pillow
Grizzy needs a nice nap. He can't find a pillow comfortable enough to his taste until he tests the pillow that the Lemmings use as a high-jump mat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 11:20:00" d="2021-07-19 11:30:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Hooks and Loops Bear
Grizzy is awakened from his nap by the unpleasant, ongoing sound of Velcro strips being ripped off. The Lemmings have covered their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 11:30:00" d="2021-07-19 11:35:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Fast Workout
The she-bear Grizzy is enamored with has lost her favorite flower in an inaccessible spot under a giant boulder. Grizzy tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 11:35:00" d="2021-07-19 11:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bat-Grizzy
The Lemmings try to catch a bat to play rodeo, disturbing Grizzy as he plays his favorite game on the ranger's mobile. But when the phone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 11:40:00" d="2021-07-19 11:55:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Moveable Apps
The Lemmings have a blast testing every app on the ranger's tablet one by one. Grizzy, who is starving, sees that the cupboards are bare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 11:55:00" d="2021-07-19 12:00:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Rodeo Bugs
Bugs and Yosemite Sam attend a rodeo only to have their sideline shenanigans force them into the ring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 12:00:00" d="2021-07-19 12:05:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Slugsworthy's Mega-Mansion
Slugsworthy builds a new mega-mansion right over Bugs' home so Bugs battles back for the right to his turf</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 12:05:00" d="2021-07-19 12:10:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Wile E.'s Walnuts
Wile has invented a machine that runs purely on walnut oil - Squeaks' main food source!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 12:10:00" d="2021-07-19 12:20:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Just One of Those Days
Bugs pops out of his hole to discover he is surrounded by a handful of adversaries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 12:20:00" d="2021-07-19 12:25:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Mooch Housin' Syndrome
When Wile thinks that he has gravely injured Squeaks Squeaks milks it for all it's worth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 12:25:00" d="2021-07-19 12:30:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Sir Littlechin the Unicorn Hunter
Sir Littlechin is on a quest to capture a unicorn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 12:30:00" d="2021-07-19 12:35:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Erin Go Bugs
Shameless O'Scanty plots to get Bugs to Ireland so he can get his lucky rabbit's foot on his own turf</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 12:35:00" d="2021-07-19 12:50:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Proud to be a Coal Miner's Wabbit
Bugs' peace and tranquility is interrupted when Yosemite Sam mines his home for coal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 12:50:00" d="2021-07-19 13:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Girlfriend
When she has no one to share her lunch with, Jamie realises she needs a sweetheart. Darwin is the only one who doesn't flee immediately</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 13:00:00" d="2021-07-19 13:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Parasite
Anais has made a new friend but Gumball and Darwin aren't sure their relationship is equal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 13:10:00" d="2021-07-19 13:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Love
When Bobert finds he's infected with a virus called love.exe he asks Gumball and Darwin to give him a definition for the word 'love'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 13:25:00" d="2021-07-19 13:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Scam
At Halloween show-and-tell, the class isn't buying Gumball's story about Gargaroth The Devourer until Carrie fakes a terrifying haunting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 13:35:00" d="2021-07-19 13:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Awkwardness
Gumball is too busy singing about ketchup to notice he's about to bump into Hot Dog Guy. They manage to get through an awkward moment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 13:55:00" d="2021-07-19 14:05:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Folk Art Foes
When Vic accidently unleashes the lord of mischief from an ancient relic, V and V have to work together to trap it back inside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 14:05:00" d="2021-07-19 14:25:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dead Ringer
When Vic doesn't pick Val for his soccer team, Val vows to win with his own squad. But when his team doesn't match up, he resorts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 14:25:00" d="2021-07-19 14:35:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Chata's Quinta Quinceanera
Vic and Val want to go to a friend's pool party on the same day as their grandma's quinceanera, so they use a magical flute</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 14:35:00" d="2021-07-19 14:50:00"><n u="Victor and Valentino">Victor and Valentino I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Brotherly Love
After breaking Chata's plant, Vic and Val must accomplish the seemingly easy task of replacing it; this proves difficult when their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 14:50:00" d="2021-07-19 15:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Demon Prom
Trigon makes Raven attend her prom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 15:00:00" d="2021-07-19 15:10:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>BBCYFSHIPBDAY
Beast Boy and Cyborg celebrate the birthday of their friendship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 15:10:00" d="2021-07-19 15:25:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Thanksgetting
The Titans are sick of normal Thanksgiving traditions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 15:25:00" d="2021-07-19 15:35:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mo' Money Mo' Problems
The Titans make Robin give them a tour of Wayne Manor and discover how fun it is to be rich</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 15:35:00" d="2021-07-19 15:50:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Beast Girl
As the Titans deal with Madame Rouge Beast Boy is excited to meet his female counterpart Beast Girl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 15:50:00" d="2021-07-19 16:00:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% Jextra Perrestrial
JP believes he may be from another planet, so Craig tries to help him make contact</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 16:00:00" d="2021-07-19 16:20:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% The Takeout Mission
Kelsey leads her friends on the most important quest ever, picking up takeout for dinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 16:20:00" d="2021-07-19 16:30:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Jessica's Trail
Jessica wanders into an unfamiliar creek, leaving Craig to find her before his Mom notices!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 16:30:00" d="2021-07-19 16:40:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dinner at the Creek
Bernard is left in charge for the evening, so Craig sets out to find his own dinner at the creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 16:40:00" d="2021-07-19 17:00:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% Bug City
Craig discovers a bunch of bugs under a rock and decides to build them a city</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 17:00:00" d="2021-07-19 17:25:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Renn Scare
The gang heads to the Velma’s beloved authentic Renaissance Fair where they must find a way to infiltrate the royal feast in order</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 17:25:00" d="2021-07-19 17:55:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% How to Train Your Coward
Shaggy and Scooby decide to leave the gang! But before that they insist on training the new recruits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 17:55:00" d="2021-07-19 18:00:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... II (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Home Insecurity
After Rick and Ginger install a high-tech, state-of-the-art home security system, Tom and Jerry's shenanigans activate the home's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 18:00:00" d="2021-07-19 18:05:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... II (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Tom-Fu
A little cat and mouse ends with Tom taking a shot to the kisser that knocks the cat out. After a little first aid, Tom wakes up as a kung-fu master</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 18:05:00" d="2021-07-19 18:20:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... II (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Jerry Rigged
After another unsuccessful attempt on Tom's part to catch Jerry, a traveling cat salesman named Carver is happy to sell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 18:20:00" d="2021-07-19 18:25:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... II (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Downton Tabby
In a post-Edwardian era, Tom lives in the basement of an impressive manor belonging to an aristocratic family. When the Butler</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 18:25:00" d="2021-07-19 18:35:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... II (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Art of the Deal
When Spike's poker playing pals go missing, he hires the cat and mouse detective to find out where they've gone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 18:35:00" d="2021-07-19 18:50:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... II (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pillow Case
Unable to sleep because of the incessant barking from a dog somewhere in the city, Tom and Jerry must track down the noisy mutt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 18:50:00" d="2021-07-19 19:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Compilation
A compilation of some of the funniest, most bizarre clips uploaded onto the internet by the people of Elmore. Clips include Banana Joe's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 19:00:00" d="2021-07-19 19:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Disaster
Rob purchases a universal remote from the Awesome Store, and discovers he can control the entire universe with it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 19:10:00" d="2021-07-19 19:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball V (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Rerun - Part 2
When we last saw Gumball, he was hitting rewind on Rob's Universal Remote, just in time to save himself from being trapped in The Void</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 19:25:00" d="2021-07-19 19:35:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Lady and the Queen
China Riot finds a new Bakugan: Barbetra. But this buzzy new Bakugan is a bit timid on the battleground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 19:35:00" d="2021-07-19 19:55:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The AB's Silver Screen Debut
Lord Brakken and Duran have teamed up and are now the Bakugan film business. They look to the Awesome Brawlers for their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 19:55:00" d="2021-07-19 20:05:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>TV Knight 3
Batman is more interested in watching TV than participating in his birthday party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 20:05:00" d="2021-07-19 20:15:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% Bro-Pocalypse
When the male Titans are injured Raven and Starfire must become bros to stop the Bropocalypse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 20:15:00" d="2021-07-19 20:30:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% Flashback: Part 1
A flashback reveals how Robin formed the Teen Titans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 20:30:00" d="2021-07-19 20:40:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% Flashback: Part 2
A flashback reveals how Robin changed from mild-mannered sidekick to quick-tempered leader</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 20:40:00" d="2021-07-19 21:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! V (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% The Scoop
The Titans find it odd when Starfire becomes friends with an ice cream scoop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 21:00:00" d="2021-07-19 21:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Vacation
The Wattersons are swapping scary stories on a family vacation when their car breaks down in the middle of the desert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 21:10:00" d="2021-07-19 21:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Fraud
When Gumball and Darwin discover his diploma is fake Principal Brown is determined to keep their discovery a secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 21:25:00" d="2021-07-19 21:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Void
Gumball and Darwin start noticing small details around Elmore High that don't add up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 21:35:00" d="2021-07-19 21:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Boss
Gumball and Darwin help Rocky land an office job so that his dad Mr Robinson will be proud of him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 21:55:00" d="2021-07-19 22:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Sleepover
Angelo gives us his tips and tricks for the most awesome sleepover ever. Until the “prank call” trick ruins the night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 22:05:00" d="2021-07-19 22:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Fake Stuntman
Angelo stupidly boasts that his Dad used to be a stuntman. And the next day Dad has been invited to speak to Angelo’s class for career day. Gah!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 22:20:00" d="2021-07-19 22:40:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu IX (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Two Lies, One Truth
As Lloyd unmasks Mystake for who she truly is Emperor Garmadon embraces Harumi as his daughter of darkness. Meanwhile Wu holds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 22:40:00" d="2021-07-19 22:50:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Thirst for Power
Axel and his toys deploy the Joyride in a ship to ship battle against Dr. Nautilus who has punctured a water main to flood the sewers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 22:50:00" d="2021-07-19 23:05:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>All Trick No Treat
On Halloween Axel gets too caught up in the scares and loses track of the fun - just in time for an infiltration by the worst trick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 23:05:00" d="2021-07-19 23:15:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Just Like Robots
Axel and the team find themselves bested by Madcap when the baddie uses their digital devices to track their every move in combat forcing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 23:15:00" d="2021-07-19 23:25:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Opposites Attract
Claiming he's good at heart, Dynamo convinces Axel and the team to help him find a battery that can power his centrifuge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 23:25:00" d="2021-07-19 23:35:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Thing in the Wall
When Axel and the team accuse Galileo of stealing their possessions the lizard must hunt down the true culprit - a mysterious</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 23:35:00" d="2021-07-20 00:00:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu IX (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Two Lies, One Truth
As Lloyd unmasks Mystake for who she truly is Emperor Garmadon embraces Harumi as his daughter of darkness. Meanwhile Wu holds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 00:00:00" d="2021-07-20 00:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Future
Gumball Darwin and Banana Joe investigate Banana Barbara's mysterious disappearance and uncover an old rival's shadowy scheme in the process</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 00:10:00" d="2021-07-20 00:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Wish
Darwin asks Gumball to teach him how to skate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 00:20:00" d="2021-07-20 00:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Factory
Gumball and Darwin follow Nicole to the Rainbow Factory for Bring your Kids to Work Day. They are expecting a magical place full of dreams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 00:35:00" d="2021-07-20 00:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Revolt
Darwin tries to highlight the plight of all the household objects he feels are being oppressed and maltreated by the uncaring residents of Elmore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 00:45:00" d="2021-07-20 00:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Mess
The boys stay up all night, even though the next day they're supposed to be babysitting Polly - Penny's little sister. They're so tired</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 00:55:00" d="2021-07-20 01:05:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Possession
Nicole has decided it's time to throw out the family's refrigerator. This doesn't go down too well with Richard, as it's his favourite possession</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 01:05:00" d="2021-07-20 01:15:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Lie
The citizens of Elmore are feeling down because it’s January so Gumball and Anais invent a new holiday called Sluzzle Tag</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 01:15:00" d="2021-07-20 01:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Butterfly
In Biology class Gumball and Darwin are waiting for a butterfly to emerge from its chrysalis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 01:30:00" d="2021-07-20 01:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Question
After Gumball and Darwin have too much sugary cereal they begin thinking about the mysteries of the universe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 01:40:00" d="2021-07-20 01:50:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Oracle
Gumball Darwin and Anais discover that Banana Joe’s mom paints pictures which predict the future</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 01:50:00" d="2021-07-20 02:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Safety
When Mr Small shows a health and safety video in class Darwin becomes obsessed with the idea of keeping the Wattersons safe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 02:00:00" d="2021-07-20 02:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In The Game
After Mom cuts off Angelo’s videogame time Angelo attempts to change her mind. He sets out to prove to her that gaming is an important</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 02:10:00" d="2021-07-20 02:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Geezer's Nephew
Angelo and friends are stuck hanging out with Geezer’s Nephew -- a terrible horrible no good delinquent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 02:25:00" d="2021-07-20 02:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Enter The Karate Kid
Angelo and friends attempt to raise Butterfingers flagging self-esteem by training him in the art of Angelo-fu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 02:35:00" d="2021-07-20 02:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% A Perfect Day
Angelo shares his tips and tricks for trading favors and then cashing them all in to create “a perfect day.”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 02:45:00" d="2021-07-20 03:00:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Home Security
When his family go on vacation Angelo sets all kinds of traps in his house for potential thieves. Problem is when they return home Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 03:00:00" d="2021-07-20 03:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Move
Gumball confronts Clayton about his fabled Seven Pressure Point Heart Exploding Technique assuming it’s another one of his outlandish claims</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 03:10:00" d="2021-07-20 03:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Law
Gumball jaywalks and is pulled over by Donut Cop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 03:20:00" d="2021-07-20 03:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Allergy
Darwin starts sneezing repeatedly and it seems he can't stop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 03:35:00" d="2021-07-20 03:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Mothers
It's Mother's Day and Gumball and Darwin discover that Tobias and Banana Joe have both made a card for The Best Mum in the World</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 03:45:00" d="2021-07-20 04:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Password
Mum has forced Dad to install a password on the computer…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 04:00:00" d="2021-07-20 04:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Routine
Mum and the kids depart for their hard day's work, leaving a seemingly lazy Dad half-asleep on the sofa. Mum has given him one very simple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 04:10:00" d="2021-07-20 04:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Parking
When the Wattersons arrive at the mall for a day of shopping, they struggle to find a space in the parking lot. They search for a space</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 04:20:00" d="2021-07-20 04:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Upgrade
Gumball and Darwin see an advert for the latest cutting-edge Bobert operating system and excitedly talk Bobert into downloading it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 04:30:00" d="2021-07-20 04:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Comic
Gumball is the star of his own comic but struggles to match up to his heroic alter-ego</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 04:40:00" d="2021-07-20 04:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Romantic
After Gumball convinces himself that Penny doesn't love him as much as she used to, he decides to put together a romantic quest to remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-20 04:55:00" d="2021-07-20 05:05:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 2016 II (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Charm Offensive
After Ben gets too much publicity for his alien-antics in Fort Knox, a jealous Gwen feels unappreciated and looks</k>  </p>
</a>
