<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="103" t="2020-05-14 04:47:15"><p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 05:00:00" d="2020-05-21 05:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Leslie calls Gumball's bluff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 05:10:00" d="2020-05-21 05:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Anais and psycho Jamie are accused of the same crime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 05:20:00" d="2020-05-21 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Dad decides to resolve the Watterson family's differences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 05:35:00" d="2020-05-21 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The kids find out Dad has been dressing as a woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 05:45:00" d="2020-05-21 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball, Darwin and Banana Joe investigate Banana Barbara's mysterious disappearance and uncover an old rival's shadowy scheme in the process</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 06:00:00" d="2020-05-21 06:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After Billy Billions' efforts to carve his face onto Mount Rushmore with a laser are thwarted by Ben the billionaire brat turns his focus on removing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 06:10:00" d="2020-05-21 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ben accidentally creates a giant sink hole and frees King Koil and his Kimodo Dragon from below</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 06:25:00" d="2020-05-21 06:36:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin spice up their friendship by introducing a third best friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 06:36:00" d="2020-05-21 06:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball has to save Mr Robinson’s life during Elmore’s Senior Talent Show!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 06:50:00" d="2020-05-21 07:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Gumball and Darwin decide it's time they join a crew, they agree that the coolest posse in Elmore is the Senior Citizens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 07:00:00" d="2020-05-21 07:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Anais reveals that she's in the grade above them at school, Gumball and Darwin's eyes are suddenly opened to a whole new world of other students</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 07:15:00" d="2020-05-21 07:27:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Bumblebee offers to help Robin with his leadership skills by teaching him how to act like a queen bee</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 07:27:00" d="2020-05-21 07:40:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% In order to save Titans Tower from some wealthy land developers the Titans search for pirate treasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 07:40:00" d="2020-05-21 07:51:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The ThunderCats are exhausted from fighting bad guys all the time so Lion-O suggests they spend a relaxing summer fun day at the beach with no fighting!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 07:51:00" d="2020-05-21 08:05:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While minding her own business, Cheetara is caught in a trap set by Safari Joe, the famously annoying hunter! After escaping she rallies the other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 08:05:00" d="2020-05-21 08:16:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Axel finds himself at the center of a disagreement between Sarge and Masko over what's more important in battle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 08:16:00" d="2020-05-21 08:35:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zoe builds her own battle suit in hopes of joining Axel's team. The only problem? She can't shrink!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 08:35:00" d="2020-05-21 08:55:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Gang venture in an intricate labyrinth of crystal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 08:55:00" d="2020-05-21 09:20:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A terrifying sea monster attacks the gang whilst at sea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 09:20:00" d="2020-05-21 09:30:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Craig rescues a tadpole and decides to raise him into a level 100 frog!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 09:30:00" d="2020-05-21 10:10:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A vicious game of tag wreaks havoc on the Creek claiming Kelsey as the next it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 10:10:00" d="2020-05-21 10:21:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball sets out to win his Dad back by winning a blindfolded “dumb” race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 10:21:00" d="2020-05-21 10:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball almost loses his mind trying to guess Darwin’s secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 10:40:00" d="2020-05-21 10:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Elmore residents are going missing, and the cause of these disappearances may be closer to home than Gumball and Darwin think</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 10:50:00" d="2020-05-21 11:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin discover that Tobias is doing way better than them in an online game called Galatrek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 11:00:00" d="2020-05-21 11:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin tries to teach The Titans to respect money but he ends up bee-ing the one who learns the lesson./Cyborg wants to have an 80s TV show marathon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 11:10:00" d="2020-05-21 11:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans immerse themselves in different video game worlds./ Rose Wilson escapes from prison defeating the Titans with cool one liners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 11:25:00" d="2020-05-21 11:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin uses his skills as a master detective</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 11:34:00" d="2020-05-21 11:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% It's Easter and the Tooth Fairy is trying to take over the holiday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 11:50:00" d="2020-05-21 12:00:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Batgirl’s worlds collide when her best friend from Gotham City moves to Metropolis. Meanwhile, Catwoman is making some new friends of her own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 12:00:00" d="2020-05-21 12:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Batgirl’s worlds collide when her best friend from Gotham City moves to Metropolis. Meanwhile, Catwoman is making some new friends of her own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 12:15:00" d="2020-05-21 12:25:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It's time for the gang's yearly vacation, but Hawk refuses to go, claiming the gang's vacations are never fun for him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 12:25:00" d="2020-05-21 12:40:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>An asteroid is headed right for the kingdom, so Dr Fox leads the gang on a mission to save the kingdom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 12:40:00" d="2020-05-21 12:50:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nom Nom recruits the Bears to act as his entourage of friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 12:50:00" d="2020-05-21 13:10:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After Panda gets injured on the basketball court, the Bears invite Charlie to be on their basketball team</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 13:10:00" d="2020-05-21 13:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Mom and Dad struggle to keep hyperactive, toddler-aged Gumball from trashing the house and exhausting them, they decide to buy him a pet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 13:20:00" d="2020-05-21 13:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Via the sewers, Darwin finds himself flushed out to sea. He is terrified, but determined to make his way back to the Wattersons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 13:30:00" d="2020-05-21 13:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Alan ditches Gumball to do something more fun, Gumball is desperate to track him down and make him pay for his betrayal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 13:40:00" d="2020-05-21 13:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% To try and make Mr Small feel like he’s inspired the students, Gumball and Darwin try to follow every piece of advice Mr Small gives them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 13:55:00" d="2020-05-21 14:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The kids find out Dad has been dressing as a woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 14:05:00" d="2020-05-21 14:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball, Darwin and Banana Joe investigate Banana Barbara's mysterious disappearance and uncover an old rival's shadowy scheme in the process</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 14:25:00" d="2020-05-21 14:36:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vic and Val accidentally set off a time loop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 14:36:00" d="2020-05-21 14:50:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vic and Val build a treehouse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 14:50:00" d="2020-05-21 15:02:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Bumblebee offers to help Robin with his leadership skills by teaching him how to act like a queen bee</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 15:02:00" d="2020-05-21 15:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% In order to save Titans Tower from some wealthy land developers the Titans search for pirate treasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 15:10:00" d="2020-05-21 15:19:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% It's Beast Boy's birthday! But will the other Titans remember?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 15:19:00" d="2020-05-21 15:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Starfire is visited by three ghosts and shown the true meaning of Black Friday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 15:35:00" d="2020-05-21 16:00:00"><n>Craig of the Creek: The Other Side</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Craig, Kelsey and JP must journey past the Overpass into uncharted territory - the Other Side of the Creek. / Craig, Kelsey and JP must journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 16:00:00" d="2020-05-21 16:11:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Axel must help Sarge and Bobbie learn to walk in each other's shoes - literally - after Luka unwittingly switches the toys' heads!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 16:11:00" d="2020-05-21 16:25:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Axel and his toys deploy the Joyride in a ship to ship battle against Dr. Nautilus who has punctured a water main to flood the sewers and established</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 16:25:00" d="2020-05-21 16:35:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Puppycorn is determined to become the Hot Dog King and joins an underground hot dog eating contest called Weiner Club</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 16:35:00" d="2020-05-21 16:50:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>During a fun fireworks show, Unikitty and Master Frown become trapped in the horn of the Unikitty Castle when she catches Master Frown messing with her fireworks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 16:50:00" d="2020-05-21 16:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Needing a hero with shrinking powers but forgetting about Bumblebee Robin invites The Atom to join their fight against the Brain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 16:59:00" d="2020-05-21 17:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When yet another crime alert interrupts their relaxation the Titans decide to become villains and do whatever they want</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 17:15:00" d="2020-05-21 17:26:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The ThunderCats have gotten so good at defeating the Mutants of Plun-Darr that it’s basically become routine. That all changes with the arrival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 17:26:00" d="2020-05-21 17:40:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lion-O is playing with Snarf and doesn’t have a care in the world. Unfortunately he’s accidentally stomping on the miniature village of the Micrits!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 17:40:00" d="2020-05-21 18:00:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While on a trip to New York, Scooby and the gang find themselves taking part in a dog show competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 18:00:00" d="2020-05-21 18:25:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Scooby and his friends decide to go on a train trip. But they learn that pets are not allowed in the main carriages</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 18:25:00" d="2020-05-21 18:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% A mysterious figure from Nicole’s past shows up and challenges her to a fight, but the kids are surprised when she refuses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 18:35:00" d="2020-05-21 18:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% A compilation of some of the funniest, most bizarre clips uploaded onto the internet by the people of Elmore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 18:55:00" d="2020-05-21 19:06:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball’s magic tinfoil helmet threatens to tear the Watterson family apart!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 19:06:00" d="2020-05-21 19:17:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Anais is convinced that Gumball is being bullied by Tina Rex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 19:17:00" d="2020-05-21 19:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are convinced that the world will end in 24 hours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 19:30:00" d="2020-05-21 19:41:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vic and Val accidentally set off a time loop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 19:41:00" d="2020-05-21 19:55:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vic and Val build a treehouse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 19:55:00" d="2020-05-21 20:00:00"><n>The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ivandoe and Bert come across a Talking Tree who promises to tell their fortune in exchange for gold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 20:00:00" d="2020-05-21 20:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While visiting China Ben Gwen and Grandpa Max take a trek to the Great Wall</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 20:10:00" d="2020-05-21 20:20:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>During a family cookout, Charmcaster uses her magic to switch places with Gwen. But when Ben catches &quot;Charmcaster&quot; sneaking about, he attacks, unaware</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 20:20:00" d="2020-05-21 20:35:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In Aspen Colorado Ben Gwen and Grandpa Max are on a hike to find the Forgeti</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 20:35:00" d="2020-05-21 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% The AO discover the only way to stop Magnus involves shutting down the infected Fortus Core Cell./The AO must decide whether or not to help Benton Dusk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 21:00:00" d="2020-05-21 21:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% When an unknown criminal syndicate threatens the Royal Family, the Ninja are called into action. They must protect the princess and an artifact</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 21:25:00" d="2020-05-21 21:45:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% In the wake of a vicious attack upon the palace, the Sons of Garmadon steal the second Oni Mask, and the ninja invite the royal princess, Harumi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 21:45:00" d="2020-05-21 22:10:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% While Princess Harumi adjusts to life with the ninja, Lloyd and Jay search for answers about the Oni Masks, while Cole and Zane attempt to infiltrate the Sons of Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 22:10:00" d="2020-05-21 22:30:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% In order to join the Sons of Garmadon, Zane (aka Snake Jaguar) participates in a deadly motorcycle initiation race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 22:30:00" d="2020-05-21 22:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo becomes an intern at Adventureparkland. But, his dream job isn’t all it’s cracked up to be because he has to actually… work!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 22:40:00" d="2020-05-21 22:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Miss Perla turns detention time into art therapy where Angelo makes cool bobble-head sculptures which become all the rage in school. Result:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 22:55:00" d="2020-05-21 23:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% When Cathy hikes the price of her famous cupcake the “Brooklyn Blackout,” Lola goes undercover in search of the secret recipe. Angelo and the gang discover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 23:05:00" d="2020-05-21 23:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo shares his tips and tricks for delaying a test</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 23:15:00" d="2020-05-21 23:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Because of his cunning and tenacity Angelo always gets what he wants. Is this the way life is always going to be? Angelo has an existential crisis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 23:25:00" d="2020-05-21 23:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Elena and Angelo are grounded for fighting with each other. They have to put aside their differences and work together to escape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 23:40:00" d="2020-05-21 23:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Lola has a pigeon phobia. Paging Dr. Angelo and Dr. Sherwood to cure her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-21 23:50:00" d="2020-05-22 00:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% A new hipster cupcake shop opens across the street from Cathy’s siphoning off all the customers. Angelo and friends come up with strategies to help Cathy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 00:05:00" d="2020-05-22 00:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Darwin asks Gumball to teach him how to skate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 00:15:00" d="2020-05-22 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin follow Nicole to the Rainbow Factory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 00:30:00" d="2020-05-22 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The kids find out Dad has been dressing as a woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 00:40:00" d="2020-05-22 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The boys manage to lose Polly in the blink of an eye</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 00:50:00" d="2020-05-22 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Nicole has decided it's time to throw out the family's refrigerator</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 01:00:00" d="2020-05-22 01:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Mr. Robinson accidentally lets his feelings slip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 01:15:00" d="2020-05-22 01:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% It's Halloween in Elmore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 01:25:00" d="2020-05-22 01:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball's old BFF Fuzzy, turns up on his doorstep</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 01:35:00" d="2020-05-22 01:46:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Nicole seeks to develop a sense of ambition in Gumball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 01:46:00" d="2020-05-22 01:56:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When everyone in the Watterson household wants to watch their favourite show at the same time, a massive fight breaks out over control of the television remote</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 01:56:00" d="2020-05-22 02:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is determined to drive Penny away from Leslie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 02:10:00" d="2020-05-22 02:35:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% As Lloyd and Harumi search the Oni Temple for the last mask, the ninja are taken hostage and discover Princess Harumi’s true intentions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 02:35:00" d="2020-05-22 03:00:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The ninja race to save Lloyd, as a more powerful-than-ever Lord Garmadon creates an enormous Colossi to help him rule Ninjago and defeat the ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 03:00:00" d="2020-05-22 03:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Cole and Young Wu attempt to free their friends, who have been taken captive by a tribe of Dragon Hunters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 03:25:00" d="2020-05-22 03:50:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lloyd must find his voice as he leads a small resistance to capture the airwaves in Ninjago City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 03:50:00" d="2020-05-22 04:01:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball’s magic tinfoil helmet threatens to tear the Watterson family apart!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 04:01:00" d="2020-05-22 04:12:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Anais is convinced that Gumball is being bullied by Tina Rex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 04:12:00" d="2020-05-22 04:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are convinced that the world will end in 24 hours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 04:25:00" d="2020-05-22 04:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Darwin asks Gumball to teach him how to skate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 04:35:00" d="2020-05-22 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin follow Nicole to the Rainbow Factory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 04:50:00" d="2020-05-22 05:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The kids find out Dad has been dressing as a woman</k>  </p>
</a>
