<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="107" t="2020-05-17 04:30:45"><p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 05:00:00" d="2020-05-24 05:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Nothing much is happening for Gumball and Darwin and the background characters in Elmore seize their moment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 05:10:00" d="2020-05-24 05:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is in such a bad mood that it spreads to Darwin, who joins him in complaining about everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 05:20:00" d="2020-05-24 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Wattersons are swapping scary stories on a family vacation, when their car breaks down in the middle of the desert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 05:35:00" d="2020-05-24 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Gumball and Darwin discover his diploma is fake, Principal Brown is determined to keep their discovery a secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 05:45:00" d="2020-05-24 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin start noticing small details around Elmore High that don't add up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 06:00:00" d="2020-05-24 06:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While in Paris, Ben catches Zombozo robbing the Louvre. But when Zombozo hypnotizes Ben to remain speechless, Ben must navigate a foreign</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 06:10:00" d="2020-05-24 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A trip to the South Pole goes upside down when Team Tennyson land on the North Pole instead! Ben quickly discovers the culprits are magnetically-powered scientists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 06:25:00" d="2020-05-24 06:36:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin challenge Dad to a “lazy-off”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 06:36:00" d="2020-05-24 06:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball must learn to say “no” when Carrie the Ghost uses his body against his will</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 06:50:00" d="2020-05-24 07:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When they find Anais training herself for a brutal showdown, Gumball and Darwin realise that their sister is being pestered at school by an annoying kid: Billy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 07:00:00" d="2020-05-24 07:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Darwin taunts Gumball about how predictable he is, Gumball tries to prove that he can still surprise his buddy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 07:15:00" d="2020-05-24 07:24:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% After not receiving participation medals, the Titans must demonstrate what they learned at camp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 07:24:00" d="2020-05-24 07:40:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Bumbleebee becomes the 6th Titan and moves into the Tower but has a hard time adjusting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 07:40:00" d="2020-05-24 07:51:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fleeing the destruction of their home planet, Thundera, Lion-O and the ThunderCats land on the mysterious, dangerous all-around awesome world of Third Earth!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 07:51:00" d="2020-05-24 08:05:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fleeing the destruction of their home planet, Thundera, Lion-O and the ThunderCats land on the mysterious, dangerous all-around awesome world of Third Earth!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 08:05:00" d="2020-05-24 08:16:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Axel must wrangle Galileo and Bobbie to shut down a rogue thermostat - improperly upgraded by Slobot - as it plunges the house into extreme hot and cold zones</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 08:16:00" d="2020-05-24 08:35:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After a Porcupunk sighting Axel leads a recon mission that slowly but surely proves to be a wild goose chase devised by Sarge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 08:35:00" d="2020-05-24 08:45:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Babs and Kara spar over whose dog is better at the Metropolis Dog Show, Ace the Bat-Hound and Krypto the Superdog must find a way to save the day themselves!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 08:45:00" d="2020-05-24 08:55:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When the local mall is attached by the monstrous supervillain Giganta, Karen Beecher discovers that tiny Bumblebee might be the only one small enough to save the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 08:55:00" d="2020-05-24 09:05:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Barbara Minerva is super-jealous of little Miss Perfect Diana Prince</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 09:05:00" d="2020-05-24 09:16:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Zee (Zatanna) asks Kara to look after her two magical bunnies, they quickly start to multiply, wreaking havoc all across Metropolis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 09:16:00" d="2020-05-24 09:26:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hal’s ex-girlfriend shows up at the Metropolis High homecoming game and goes love-ballistic as the villain Star Sapphire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 09:26:00" d="2020-05-24 09:37:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Whilst Gumball and Darwin make fun of Mum and Dad for being old, their voices start to break</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 09:37:00" d="2020-05-24 09:48:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Sarah, the new kid in school, is Gumball and Darwin's number one, slightly obsessive, fan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 09:48:00" d="2020-05-24 09:58:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The new coach at Elmore High stands up to Jamie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 09:58:00" d="2020-05-24 10:09:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin receive an heirloom from Richard but lose it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 10:09:00" d="2020-05-24 10:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Bobert loses a bet to Gumball so has to obey him for 24 hours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 10:40:00" d="2020-05-24 10:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Parent Teacher Association of Elmore Junior High ban video games, so the kids try and prove that games aren’t a bad influence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 10:50:00" d="2020-05-24 11:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Anais arrives in the bedroom to find a messy crime-scene and her Daisy doll missing. She realises that Gumball and Darwin are the chief suspects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 11:00:00" d="2020-05-24 11:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Gizmo convinces the Titans he's kidnapped Cyborg./Raven is cursed to be nice; meanwhile Starfire is about to marry a pot of chili</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 11:10:00" d="2020-05-24 11:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans are having a terrible time on their camping trip./ The Hive agrees to take a day off</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 11:25:00" d="2020-05-24 11:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin ignores the rules for a game of jinx</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 11:34:00" d="2020-05-24 11:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When drinking tea turns the other Titans English it's up to Robin to save America from another British invasion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 11:50:00" d="2020-05-24 12:01:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The girls must track down Katana a mysterious warrior who’s stealing the souls of Metropolis’s villains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 12:01:00" d="2020-05-24 12:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The girls must track down Katana a mysterious warrior who's stealing the souls of Metropolis's villains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 12:15:00" d="2020-05-24 12:25:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After Unikitty finds out that tourism is down in the Unikingdom, she recruits the gang to make a tourism video to inspire people to visit the kingdom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 12:25:00" d="2020-05-24 12:40:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A mysterious relative, Uncle Donklecorn, shows up unexpectedly, claiming to be family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 12:40:00" d="2020-05-24 12:50:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In order to abide by the clothing-policy of their favorite Boba shop, the Bears get some new outfits. But with new looks come new lives!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 12:50:00" d="2020-05-24 13:10:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While trying to sail to Japan, the Baby Bears get stranded on an island. Luckily, they meet Dave and Karla, who help with survival on the island, while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 13:10:00" d="2020-05-24 13:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Rocky suggests that the Elmore Junior High kids skip school, the bus is boarded by criminals who seem to want to teach them the importance of school attendance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 13:20:00" d="2020-05-24 13:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% As night falls in Elmore, the Moon takes us on a tour through the various dreams -- and nightmares -- of the town’s slumbering inhabitants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 13:30:00" d="2020-05-24 13:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is late to meet Penny at the mall, but a series of misunderstandings on the way only delay him further</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 13:40:00" d="2020-05-24 13:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Mom sees Darwin gazing longingly at a fish-tank she thinks their mammalian lifestyle isn’t fulfilling her adopted son and deep down he longs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 13:55:00" d="2020-05-24 14:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Nicole has decided it's time to throw out the family's refrigerator</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 14:05:00" d="2020-05-24 14:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Mr. Robinson accidentally lets his feelings slip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 14:25:00" d="2020-05-24 14:35:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vic and Val use a magical flute to teleport</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 14:35:00" d="2020-05-24 14:50:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After breaking Chata's plant, Vic and Val must accomplish the seemingly easy task of replacing it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 14:50:00" d="2020-05-24 14:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% After not receiving participation medals, the Titans must demonstrate what they learned at camp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 14:59:00" d="2020-05-24 15:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Bumbleebee becomes the 6th Titan and moves into the Tower but has a hard time adjusting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 15:10:00" d="2020-05-24 15:18:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans visit the Hall of Justice to use the pool but then decide to check out the inside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 15:18:00" d="2020-05-24 15:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans must save the members of the Justice League from the clutches of the supervillain Darkseid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 15:35:00" d="2020-05-24 16:00:00"><n>Craig of the Creek: The Other Side</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Craig, Kelsey and JP must journey past the Overpass into uncharted territory - the Other Side of the Creek. / Craig, Kelsey and JP must journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 16:00:00" d="2020-05-24 16:11:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Axel and the team juggle not waking Uncle Andrew from his nap and stopping Orangutank from stealing Andrew's latest invention: the Knockout Box!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 16:11:00" d="2020-05-24 16:25:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>At a rummage sale with Uncle Andrew Axel and Zoe must stop Madcap from turning her long-lost tank toy Joyride into an agent of mayhem!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 16:25:00" d="2020-05-24 16:35:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Unikitty discovers Puppycorn's only other friend is a boring old rock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 16:35:00" d="2020-05-24 16:50:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Hawkodile develops a secret crush on Dr. Fox, he finds himself crushing down in size! Being too embarrassed to tell her about it, Unikitty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 16:50:00" d="2020-05-24 16:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% After not receiving participation medals, the Titans must demonstrate what they learned at camp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 16:59:00" d="2020-05-24 17:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Bumbleebee becomes the 6th Titan and moves into the Tower but has a hard time adjusting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 17:15:00" d="2020-05-24 17:26:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Panthro is getting a little fed up with having to fix things around the Cats' Lair constantly which is unfortunate because the ThunderCats are about to be attacked</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 17:26:00" d="2020-05-24 17:40:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lion-O is reminded that he needs to plug the Sword of Omens into the Cats' Lair each night or else the base will run out of power. That's fine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 17:40:00" d="2020-05-24 18:00:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A very bad parking choice on Fred’s part leads the gang to an asteroid mining base in outer space where an alien virus appears to be turning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 18:00:00" d="2020-05-24 18:25:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>To escape a snowstorm, the gang checks into a creepy, massive hotel run by a man very strict about the hotel rules established by his deceased mother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 18:25:00" d="2020-05-24 18:36:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Darwin is sent away to a government institute for geniuses. Yes. Really</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 18:36:00" d="2020-05-24 18:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The secret behind Anton's immortality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 18:55:00" d="2020-05-24 19:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball seeks justice when Banana Joe chews Darwin's pen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 19:05:00" d="2020-05-24 19:16:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Darwin develops a texting addiction when he and Gumball get their first cell phone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 19:16:00" d="2020-05-24 19:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Richard gets a job as a pizza delivery man, which worries Nicole when, at the same time, strange things begin to occur around the neighbourhood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 19:30:00" d="2020-05-24 19:40:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vic and Val use a magical flute to teleport</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 19:40:00" d="2020-05-24 19:55:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After breaking Chata's plant, Vic and Val must accomplish the seemingly easy task of replacing it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 19:55:00" d="2020-05-24 20:00:00"><n>The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ivandoe and Bert comes to the rescue when a damsell in distress is being threatened by a big scary wolf. Will the enchanting young lady steal more than Ivandoe’s heart?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 20:00:00" d="2020-05-24 20:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Phil and Grandpa Max tune-up the Omni-Copter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 20:10:00" d="2020-05-24 20:20:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A small village's goats are being terrorized</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 20:20:00" d="2020-05-24 20:35:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Our hero must stop at nothing to get back what's his!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 20:35:00" d="2020-05-24 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% The AO's plane falls under attack by Pyravian who strangely believes the team to be Bakuzon./The AO find themselves in a battle against the Bakuzon forces of Tiko</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 21:00:00" d="2020-05-24 21:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Lloyd must find his voice as he leads a small resistance to capture the airwaves in Ninjago City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 21:25:00" d="2020-05-24 21:45:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Lloyd and the rebels celebrate their successful strike against Emperor Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 21:45:00" d="2020-05-24 22:10:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The headquarters to the resistance is breached and Lloyd scrambles to avoid capture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 22:10:00" d="2020-05-24 22:30:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% As Lloyd unmasks Mystake for who she truly is, Emperor Garmadon embraces Harumi as his daughter of darkness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 22:30:00" d="2020-05-24 22:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo enters a pie baking contest with his Dad as his partner until the two have creative differences and go it alone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 22:40:00" d="2020-05-24 22:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo and Lola start a campaign to help Sherwood get voted “most likely to succeed” by his classmates instead of Tracy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 22:55:00" d="2020-05-24 23:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Dad takes a parenting class which works! Now he has more control of his kids. Angelo infiltrates the parenting class (posing as an adult) to learn Dad’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 23:05:00" d="2020-05-24 23:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo comes up with unique inventions to win “Snake Pit” a TV show where you pitch your business idea to local “business tycoons” hoping to get them to invest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 23:15:00" d="2020-05-24 23:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% After making a bet that their life is harder, Angelo and Mr. Foot trade places. Angelo becomes the teacher, and Mr. Foot the unruly student</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 23:25:00" d="2020-05-24 23:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% After taking a career test that claims to predict your future and receiving disappointing results, Angelo and friends set out to change their destinies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 23:40:00" d="2020-05-24 23:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% The line for Adventureparkland’s newest ride is way too long so Angelo and the gang decide to spread rumors of wolves attacking people at the park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-24 23:50:00" d="2020-05-25 00:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% With Lola and Sherwood away Angelo interviews and auditions potential replacements</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-25 00:05:00" d="2020-05-25 00:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin help Rocky land an office job so that his dad, Mr Robinson, will be proud of him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-25 00:15:00" d="2020-05-25 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball confronts Clayton about his fabled Seven Pressure Point Heart Exploding Technique, assuming it’s another one of his outlandish claims</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-25 00:30:00" d="2020-05-25 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball jaywalks and is pulled over by Donut Cop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-25 00:40:00" d="2020-05-25 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Darwin starts sneezing repeatedly and it seems he can't stop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-25 00:50:00" d="2020-05-25 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% It's Mother's Day, and Gumball and Darwin discover that Tobias and Banana Joe have both made a card for &quot;The Best Mum in the World&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-25 01:00:00" d="2020-05-25 01:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Mum has forced Dad to install a password on the computer…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-25 01:15:00" d="2020-05-25 01:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are offended when Mom calls them “procrastinators”, once she’s told them what it means</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-25 01:25:00" d="2020-05-25 01:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% While performing a school play, Gumball is so nervous about kissing Penny that he accidentally head-butts her and cracks open her shell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-25 01:35:00" d="2020-05-25 01:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% For once in his life Gumball is the one who's owed an apology</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-25 01:45:00" d="2020-05-25 01:56:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin befriend Clayton, who is a compulsive liar and begins contaminating them with lies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-25 01:56:00" d="2020-05-25 02:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Wattersons run over Santa Claus and must save Christmas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-25 02:10:00" d="2020-05-25 02:35:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% When Iron Baron forces Wu to retrieve the Dragon Armor, things don’t go as planned. In Ninjago, Lloyd can only endure so much as he holds onto hope for the Ninjas’ return</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-25 02:35:00" d="2020-05-25 03:00:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Having freed Lord Garmadon from Kryptarium Prison, the ninja are beset by doubts, particularly Lloyd</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-25 03:00:00" d="2020-05-25 03:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% The ninja race back to the Monastery of Spinjitzu. This is the last stand. The final battle against the Oni is now</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-25 03:25:00" d="2020-05-25 03:50:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% When an unknown criminal syndicate threatens the Royal Family, the Ninja are called into action. They must protect the princess and an artifact</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-25 03:50:00" d="2020-05-25 04:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball seeks justice when Banana Joe chews Darwin's pen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-25 04:00:00" d="2020-05-25 04:11:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Darwin develops a texting addiction when he and Gumball get their first cell phone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-25 04:11:00" d="2020-05-25 04:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Richard gets a job as a pizza delivery man, which worries Nicole when, at the same time, strange things begin to occur around the neighbourhood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-25 04:25:00" d="2020-05-25 04:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin help Rocky land an office job so that his dad, Mr Robinson, will be proud of him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-25 04:35:00" d="2020-05-25 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball confronts Clayton about his fabled Seven Pressure Point Heart Exploding Technique, assuming it’s another one of his outlandish claims</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-25 04:50:00" d="2020-05-25 05:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball jaywalks and is pulled over by Donut Cop</k>  </p>
</a>
