<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="107" t="2020-04-13 04:27:01"><p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 05:00:00" d="2020-04-20 05:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin see an advert for the latest, cutting-edge Bobert operating system and excitedly talk Bobert into downloading it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 05:10:00" d="2020-04-20 05:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball is the star of his own comic, but struggles to match up to his heroic alter-ego</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 05:20:00" d="2020-04-20 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% After Gumball convinces himself that Penny doesn't love him as much as she used to, he decides to put together a romantic quest to remind her of their good times together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 05:35:00" d="2020-04-20 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Everyone knows you can never watch just one video on the internet but Gumball and Darwin think they are the exception to the rule</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 05:45:00" d="2020-04-20 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% After being framed for feeding coffee to the squirrels in the park, Gumball proclaims that Mrs Robinson is pure evil</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 06:00:00" d="2020-04-20 06:11:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While visiting Lake Erie, a relaxing day at the beach gets all washed up when Ben, Gwen and Grandpa Max come face-to-face with Hex and his summer intern, Kevin!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 06:11:00" d="2020-04-20 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ben gets a tough lesson on knowing his limits when he competes in a gruelling obstacle race, made even worse by the Weatherheads!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 06:25:00" d="2020-04-20 06:36:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball discovers that Bobert is planning to take over his identity and replace him!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 06:36:00" d="2020-04-20 06:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin barely survive a school picnic in the Forest of Doom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 06:50:00" d="2020-04-20 07:01:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang struggles to get rid of the King when he joins them as their new deputy-for-a-day!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 07:01:00" d="2020-04-20 07:15:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Worried that his sword is a glorified consolation prize, Mao Mao sets out to prove the worth of his weapon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 07:15:00" d="2020-04-20 07:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% After Robin swipes her cloak, Raven's figure is revealed and she transforms into Lady Legasus; meanwhile Cyborg gets stuck in the cloak, revealing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 07:25:00" d="2020-04-20 07:40:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Starfire convinces the reluctant Titans to try defeating their enemies with compassion rather than violence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 07:40:00" d="2020-04-20 07:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans are determined to find out what happened to the missing 2'oclock hour during Daylight Saving Time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 07:50:00" d="2020-04-20 08:05:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% It's St. Patrick's Day and after wishing to become a leprechaun Beast Boy becomes obsessed with gold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 08:05:00" d="2020-04-20 08:14:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Cyborg and Beast Boy annoy the other Titans by refusing to say anything but &quot;Waffles.&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 08:14:00" d="2020-04-20 08:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Cyborg has a star-crossed crush on Jinx, the cutest member of The Hive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 08:35:00" d="2020-04-20 08:55:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Daphne always dreamed of meeting extra terrestrial life but that dream becomes a nightmare when the gang gets caught up in the mystery of a scary Alien Monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 08:55:00" d="2020-04-20 09:20:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Shaggy takes the Gang to the Minor League Baseball stadium of his youth only to learn that it's about to be shut down because a Ghostly Baseball Player</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 09:20:00" d="2020-04-20 09:30:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After getting rejected by a photography club, Val tries to get a picture of the legendary Chupacabra in order to prove himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 09:30:00" d="2020-04-20 09:45:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After faking an injury to get out of work, Vic gains sympathy from everyone while unknowingly attracting attention from a dangerous mythical creature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 09:45:00" d="2020-04-20 09:55:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% Lightning discovers a new Bakugan, Artulean, leading to an unhealthy rivalry with Howlkor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 09:55:00" d="2020-04-20 10:10:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% While Lia's newswoman mom does an expose on the AO Strata the Hunter tries to capture Hydorous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 10:10:00" d="2020-04-20 10:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Nicole is angry at Richard for forgetting her special day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 10:20:00" d="2020-04-20 10:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Channel 6 Elmore News has all the top hard-hitting local stories. Newscaster Kip Schlezinger is the man to bring you the latest news, even when there is nothing to report</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 10:40:00" d="2020-04-20 10:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Gumball and Darwin discover his diploma is fake, Principal Brown is determined to keep their discovery a secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 10:50:00" d="2020-04-20 11:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin start noticing small details around Elmore High that don't add up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 11:00:00" d="2020-04-20 11:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When the gang bands together to form a giant robot, Robin is relegated to the left leg - but he makes the left leg count!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 11:10:00" d="2020-04-20 11:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When the Titans replace the couch with a treadmill, Cyborg and Beast Boy must get guidance from the couch spirit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 11:25:00" d="2020-04-20 11:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The other Titans are trying to stop a cow-stealing UFO</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 11:34:00" d="2020-04-20 11:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans tell their slightly inaccurate origin stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 11:50:00" d="2020-04-20 12:01:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The girls must track down Katana a mysterious warrior who's stealing the souls of Metropolis's villains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 12:01:00" d="2020-04-20 12:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Overwhelmed by Superman coverage in Metropolis, Supergirl decides to really show the city what she can do. But is she helping people or her ego?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 12:15:00" d="2020-04-20 12:25:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hawkodile is the toughest action hero in the land, until his old rival shows up to take vengeance on him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 12:25:00" d="2020-04-20 12:40:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Master Frown’s head gets stuck on Unikitty’s butt, she vows to help him get his own body back, but sharing a body with Master Frown can get pretty complicated!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 12:40:00" d="2020-04-20 12:50:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Baby Bears enter a Mexican wrestling tournament</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 12:50:00" d="2020-04-20 13:10:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Charlie meets a creature just like him named Ralph</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 13:10:00" d="2020-04-20 13:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball discovers that Rob, his old nemesis, is &quot;neme-seeing&quot; someone else. Devastated that Rob has fallen out of hate with him, Gumball refuses to accept</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 13:20:00" d="2020-04-20 13:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When they see the school bullies making fun of Sussie, Gumball and Darwin decide to try and help her act less weird</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 13:30:00" d="2020-04-20 13:39:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% The prize jewel on the Secret Joyful Burger menu is a mysterious burger, but to order it you need to know its name. And Larry refuses to tell the guys what it's called</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 13:39:00" d="2020-04-20 13:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Gumball finds out that their 8-bit friend Ocho has an Italian plumber called Mario for an uncle, he assumes it’s ‘that’ Mario and says he’ll do anything to meet him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 13:55:00" d="2020-04-20 14:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball decides to put Mr. Small's eco-friendly principles to the test but it doesn't quite go as planned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 14:05:00" d="2020-04-20 14:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Nicole and her parents have it out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 14:25:00" d="2020-04-20 14:35:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After being told by Chata that they can't get a pet, Vic &amp; Val adopt a wild lizard, unaware of its magical properties, and decide to keep it secret from Chata</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 14:35:00" d="2020-04-20 14:50:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Chata lets Vic be the boss of the taco stand for the day Vic decides to fire Val, which has disastrous consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 14:50:00" d="2020-04-20 15:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin makes the other Titans sell their treasured mementos from past episodes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 15:00:00" d="2020-04-20 15:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When Cyborg starts to rage out Starfire takes him to her secret garden in the backyard to relax</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 15:10:00" d="2020-04-20 15:20:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans go to an amusement park to see LeBron James but instead help solve a mystery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 15:20:00" d="2020-04-20 15:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% It's Valentine's Day and Cyborg goes to great lengths to make it special for his girlfriend Jinx</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 15:35:00" d="2020-04-20 15:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A kid claims dibs on the Stump</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 15:45:00" d="2020-04-20 16:00:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>JP finds a fossil in the Creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 16:00:00" d="2020-04-20 16:10:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After struggling to keep up, Adorabat gets a cybernetic &quot;Mega-Mech.&quot; But can fancy new powers make up for experience?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 16:10:00" d="2020-04-20 16:25:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Feeling left out Adorabat wishes Mao Mao and Badgerclops would spend less time with each other and more time with her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 16:25:00" d="2020-04-20 16:35:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hawkodile's caught by the Action Police for bodyguarding without an Action License</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 16:35:00" d="2020-04-20 16:50:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Unikitty comes to the conclusion that everyone would be a lot happier if they would just think the way she does, and with Dr. Fox's help, maybe they can!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 16:50:00" d="2020-04-20 16:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Raven just wants some peace and quiet and makes a magical deal that eliminates all sounds. /Robin uses a prism to split each Titan into the five facets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 16:59:00" d="2020-04-20 17:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin throws his own party with a special guest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 17:15:00" d="2020-04-20 17:26:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In an attempt to make Karen feel better about a pimple, Zee recounts her embarrassing transition into magichood, and the rift it created between her and her father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 17:26:00" d="2020-04-20 17:40:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hal’s ex-girlfriend shows up at the Metropolis High homecoming game and goes love-ballistic as the villain Star Sapphire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 17:40:00" d="2020-04-20 18:00:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang goes on a camping trip. Fred’s desire for the gang to get in touch with their natural instincts turns into on-the-job training as Viking Ghosts attack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 18:00:00" d="2020-04-20 18:25:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fred is on trial, convicted of being the mastermind behind the mysteries he’s solved. With the help of his attorney, Daphne, we go back over the day’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 18:25:00" d="2020-04-20 18:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball jaywalks and is pulled over by Donut Cop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 18:35:00" d="2020-04-20 18:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Darwin starts sneezing repeatedly and it seems he can't stop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 18:55:00" d="2020-04-20 19:06:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball discovers the difference between a “date” and a “pet’s funeral”. he hard way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 19:06:00" d="2020-04-20 19:17:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Gumball rejects “The Rejects Club”, the rejects wreak their revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 19:17:00" d="2020-04-20 19:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin make their Dad believe in magic again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 19:30:00" d="2020-04-20 19:40:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After being told by Chata that they can't get a pet, Vic &amp; Val adopt a wild lizard, unaware of its magical properties, and decide to keep it secret from Chata</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 19:40:00" d="2020-04-20 19:55:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Chata lets Vic be the boss of the taco stand for the day Vic decides to fire Val, which has disastrous consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 19:55:00" d="2020-04-20 20:00:00"><n>The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ivandoe dismisses Bert and takes on a duck as his new Squire. The duck proves to be worse than useless when they come face to face with an angry tentacled forest creature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 20:00:00" d="2020-04-20 20:11:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ben learns about the possible existence of a mythical creature, the Quetzalcoatl, and takes it upon himself to find the feathered serpent on his own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 20:11:00" d="2020-04-20 20:21:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Team Tennyson help transport a caged Quetzalcoatl through the Yucatan jungle only to encounter a saboteur, LaGrange, who hijacks the precious cargo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 20:21:00" d="2020-04-20 20:35:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>During a trip to the Lake of the Ozarks, Max gets word of a suspicious rockslide nearby. Ben and Gwen must stop their quarrel if they are to rescue the trapped miners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 20:35:00" d="2020-04-20 20:45:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% Wynton finds a new Bakugan who proves difficult to control but things get more complicated when Col. Tripp seizes control of Trox</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 20:45:00" d="2020-04-20 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% With &quot;Dan&quot; behaving strangely toward the AO Lightning sniffs out the truth- an impostor!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 21:00:00" d="2020-04-20 21:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Zane’s near demise at the hands of Mr. E forces the ninja to flee aboard the Bounty, where they discover a message Zane intercepted may reveal the hidden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 21:25:00" d="2020-04-20 21:45:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% As Lloyd and Harumi venture deep into Primeval’s Eye in search of the third Oni Mask, the ninja attempt to fix the Bounty and make a startling discovery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 21:45:00" d="2020-04-20 22:10:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% As Lloyd and Harumi search the Oni Temple for the last mask, the ninja are taken hostage and discover Princess Harumi’s true intentions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 22:10:00" d="2020-04-20 22:30:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The ninja appeal to the police commissioner of Ninjago in an effort to help save Lloyd and thwart Harumi’s efforts to resurrect the evil Lord Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 22:30:00" d="2020-04-20 22:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo discovers Cathy cat and Joe Mama have been accidentally switched at the Vet. And no one believes Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 22:40:00" d="2020-04-20 22:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo creates a fake Guatemalan pen pal so he doesn’t fail Mr. Foot’s class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 22:55:00" d="2020-04-20 23:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo becomes an intern at Adventureparkland. But, his dream job isn’t all it’s cracked up to be because he has to actually… work!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 23:05:00" d="2020-04-20 23:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Miss Perla turns detention time into art therapy where Angelo makes cool bobble-head sculptures which become all the rage in school. Result:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 23:15:00" d="2020-04-20 23:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% When Cathy hikes the price of her famous cupcake the “Brooklyn Blackout,” Lola goes undercover in search of the secret recipe. Angelo and the gang discover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 23:25:00" d="2020-04-20 23:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo shares his tips and tricks for delaying a test</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 23:40:00" d="2020-04-20 23:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Because of his cunning and tenacity Angelo always gets what he wants. Is this the way life is always going to be? Angelo has an existential crisis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 23:50:00" d="2020-04-21 00:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Elena and Angelo are grounded for fighting with each other. They have to put aside their differences and work together to escape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 00:05:00" d="2020-04-21 00:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Alan ditches Gumball to do something more fun, Gumball is desperate to track him down and make him pay for his betrayal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 00:15:00" d="2020-04-21 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% To try and make Mr Small feel like he’s inspired the students, Gumball and Darwin try to follow every piece of advice Mr Small gives them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 00:30:00" d="2020-04-21 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Darwin asks for his advice on hats, Gumball suddenly can’t speak and offends Darwin. Darwin is convinced Gumball said he had a fat head</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 00:40:00" d="2020-04-21 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When she has no one to share her lunch with, Jamie realises she needs a sweetheart. Darwin's the only one who doesn’t flee immediately, so he and Jamie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 00:50:00" d="2020-04-21 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin are reading Anais’ diary when they discover that her relationship with her new friend seems a bit one-sided</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 01:00:00" d="2020-04-21 01:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Bobert finds he is infected with a virus called love.exe he asks Gumball and Darwin to give him a definition for the word ‘love’</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 01:15:00" d="2020-04-21 01:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% At Halloween show and tell, the class isn’t buying Gumball’s story about Gargaroth The Devourer until Carrie fakes a terrifying haunting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 01:25:00" d="2020-04-21 01:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball is walking in the same direction as Hot Dog Guy, and with each step it becomes increasingly awkward</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 01:35:00" d="2020-04-21 01:46:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball discovers the difference between a “date” and a “pet’s funeral”. he hard way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 01:46:00" d="2020-04-21 01:57:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Gumball rejects “The Rejects Club”, the rejects wreak their revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 01:57:00" d="2020-04-21 02:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin make their Dad believe in magic again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 02:10:00" d="2020-04-21 02:35:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% While Princess Harumi adjusts to life with the ninja, Lloyd and Jay search for answers about the Oni Masks, while Cole and Zane attempt to infiltrate the Sons of Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 02:35:00" d="2020-04-21 03:00:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% As Lloyd and Harumi venture deep into Primeval’s Eye in search of the third Oni Mask, the ninja attempt to fix the Bounty and make a startling discovery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 03:00:00" d="2020-04-21 03:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The ninja appeal to the police commissioner of Ninjago in an effort to help save Lloyd and thwart Harumi’s efforts to resurrect the evil Lord Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 03:25:00" d="2020-04-21 03:50:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lord Garmadon returns and frees Harumi, who encourages him to “achieve his true potential” by conquering the one thing that has always stood in his way… his son, Lloyd</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 03:50:00" d="2020-04-21 04:01:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball discovers the difference between a “date” and a “pet’s funeral”. he hard way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 04:01:00" d="2020-04-21 04:12:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Gumball rejects “The Rejects Club”, the rejects wreak their revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 04:12:00" d="2020-04-21 04:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin make their Dad believe in magic again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 04:25:00" d="2020-04-21 04:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Alan ditches Gumball to do something more fun, Gumball is desperate to track him down and make him pay for his betrayal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 04:35:00" d="2020-04-21 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% To try and make Mr Small feel like he’s inspired the students, Gumball and Darwin try to follow every piece of advice Mr Small gives them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 04:50:00" d="2020-04-21 05:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Darwin asks for his advice on hats, Gumball suddenly can’t speak and offends Darwin. Darwin is convinced Gumball said he had a fat head</k>  </p>
</a>
