<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="107" t="2020-04-09 04:29:19"><p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 05:00:00" d="2020-04-16 05:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% While performing a school play, Gumball is so nervous about kissing Penny that he accidentally head-butts her and cracks open her shell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 05:10:00" d="2020-04-16 05:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball receives a scare-email from a freaky ghost and decides to ignore it, despite Darwin's advice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 05:20:00" d="2020-04-16 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Vice Principal Brown gives Gumball and Darwin the ancient school hamster, Chris Morris, to look after for the weekend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 05:35:00" d="2020-04-16 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Darwin and Gumball reveal how they’d spend their perfect day, Gumball confesses that he would spend it with Penny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 05:45:00" d="2020-04-16 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Granny Jojo has brought a boyfriend to her birthday meal and Dad isn’t happy about it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 06:00:00" d="2020-04-16 06:11:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While in Tokyo, Team Tennyson learn that Japan's hottest new restaurant is being run by the Bugg Brothers as a nefarious scheme to make loads of money</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 06:11:00" d="2020-04-16 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Team Tennyson watched a sumo wrestling match when the Twain Twins crash the event. Ben must think things through if he is to stop the polarizing family!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 06:25:00" d="2020-04-16 06:36:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin challenge Dad to a “lazy-off”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 06:36:00" d="2020-04-16 06:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball must learn to say “no” when Carrie the Ghost uses his body against his will</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 06:50:00" d="2020-04-16 07:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Badgerclops adopts an abandoned monster, but some things are better left in the wild</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 07:00:00" d="2020-04-16 07:15:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Feeling left out Adorabat wishes Mao Mao and Badgerclops would spend less time with each other and more time with her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 07:15:00" d="2020-04-16 07:24:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Starfire's new pet is a horribly dangerous parasite, but Robin is the only one who is suspicious of the beast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 07:24:00" d="2020-04-16 07:40:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Beast Boy teaches Starfire how to lie and it backfires as her lies get more and more outrageous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 07:40:00" d="2020-04-16 07:49:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Santa calls it quits so the Titans must pitch in to save the holiday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 07:49:00" d="2020-04-16 08:05:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans play Spin The Bottle as Starfire tries to improve her vocabulary through kissing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 08:05:00" d="2020-04-16 08:14:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Raven eats a bad meatball that causes tentacles to spring from her teeth and devour the other Titans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 08:14:00" d="2020-04-16 08:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When the gang breaks Robin's beloved staff, Robin is forced to find a replacement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 08:35:00" d="2020-04-16 08:55:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>To solve the mystery of a ghostly performer haunting her former venue, the Gang has to pretend to be a rock band themselves!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 08:55:00" d="2020-04-16 09:20:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fred is excited to visit The Vault - a high security prison that no convict has ever escaped from</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 09:20:00" d="2020-04-16 09:30:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vic &amp; Val want to sneak out to a secret fireworks show but are thwarted when their new babysitter, Xochi, outsmarts them at every turn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 09:30:00" d="2020-04-16 09:45:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When V &amp; V discover that Chata's emotions control the water in the lake, they use it to their advantage and start their own wave pool business</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 09:45:00" d="2020-04-16 09:55:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% After the AO cause accidental destruction Dan's parents question whether the kids should be allowed to keep their Bakugan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 09:55:00" d="2020-04-16 10:10:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% Lia disagrees with her new Bakugan Pegatrix on battle techniques but during a fierce fight Lia must rely on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 10:10:00" d="2020-04-16 10:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball learns that the Wattersons have been stealing Mr Robinson’s wi-fi for years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 10:20:00" d="2020-04-16 10:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is livid when an online test keeps telling him that his character-type is &quot;The Loser&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 10:40:00" d="2020-04-16 10:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Mum reveals that Gumball's real name is &quot;Zach&quot;, Gumball adopts a cheesy, annoying persona to match the name</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 10:50:00" d="2020-04-16 11:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Nothing much is happening for Gumball and Darwin and the background characters in Elmore seize their moment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 11:00:00" d="2020-04-16 11:09:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Beast Boy falls for Terra despite clear signs that she is more interested in destroying the Titans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 11:09:00" d="2020-04-16 11:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans revert to creative game-playing in order to have a chance at beating the undefeated supervillain dodgeball team</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 11:25:00" d="2020-04-16 11:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin uses his skills as a master detective</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 11:34:00" d="2020-04-16 11:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% It's Easter and the Tooth Fairy is trying to take over the holiday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 11:50:00" d="2020-04-16 12:01:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>What begins as a simple vandalism investigation becomes an all-out turf war when the team encounters a powerful trio of Kryptonians bent on world domination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 12:01:00" d="2020-04-16 12:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Zee (Zatanna) asks Kara to look after her two magical bunnies, they quickly start to multiply, wreaking havoc all across Metropolis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 12:15:00" d="2020-04-16 12:25:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>During the gang's Halloween party, Unikitty discovers Brick isn't scared of anything!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 12:25:00" d="2020-04-16 12:40:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang’s board game night gets too competitive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 12:40:00" d="2020-04-16 12:50:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Bears have trouble assembling some furniture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 12:50:00" d="2020-04-16 13:10:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Baby Bears get jobs as paper boys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 13:10:00" d="2020-04-16 13:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Nicole encourages Gumball to do what comes naturally. reak stuff!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 13:20:00" d="2020-04-16 13:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball kind of teaches Darwin how to be a skater…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 13:30:00" d="2020-04-16 13:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Darwin finds it harder than expected to give up his favourite foodstuff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 13:40:00" d="2020-04-16 13:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% While performing a school play, Gumball is so nervous about kissing Penny that he accidentally head-butts her and cracks open her shell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 13:55:00" d="2020-04-16 14:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Hotdog Kid discover why they're so awkward with each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 14:05:00" d="2020-04-16 14:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin try to find out the name of their neighbour, Antlers Guy, but accidentally blow his witness protection cover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 14:25:00" d="2020-04-16 14:35:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vic &amp; Val want to sneak out to a secret fireworks show but are thwarted when their new babysitter, Xochi, outsmarts them at every turn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 14:35:00" d="2020-04-16 14:50:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When V &amp; V discover that Chata's emotions control the water in the lake, they use it to their advantage and start their own wave pool business</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 14:50:00" d="2020-04-16 14:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Control Freak informs the Titans that they are on a TV show he created and demands they earn him an award</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 14:59:00" d="2020-04-16 15:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Cyborg's real strength comes not from his robot parts, but from his favourite song</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 15:10:00" d="2020-04-16 15:19:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin tries to teach the Titans valuable life lessons by reading them fairytales but the others co-opt his stories and spin them into their own twisted yarns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 15:19:00" d="2020-04-16 15:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Brother Blood takes the Titans to trial for their recent destruction of Jump City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 15:35:00" d="2020-04-16 15:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Kelsey starts a super secret book club</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 15:45:00" d="2020-04-16 16:00:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>JP believes he may be from another planet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 16:00:00" d="2020-04-16 16:10:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Badgerclops gets huge to destroy a towering monster but when he refuses to shrink down the kingdom faces a new terror</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 16:10:00" d="2020-04-16 16:25:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When a Sweetypie isn't impressed with the sheriff dept's antics, our three heroes try everything to win him over</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 16:25:00" d="2020-04-16 16:35:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hawkodile is the toughest action hero in the land, until his old rival shows up to take vengeance on him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 16:35:00" d="2020-04-16 16:50:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Master Frown’s head gets stuck on Unikitty’s butt, she vows to help him get his own body back, but sharing a body with Master Frown can get pretty complicated!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 16:50:00" d="2020-04-16 17:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Batman and Commissioner Gordon have a slumber party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 17:00:00" d="2020-04-16 17:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin creates the Teen Titan Awards in an effort to get his teammates to clean up the Tower</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 17:15:00" d="2020-04-16 17:26:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The girls must track down Katana a mysterious warrior who’s stealing the souls of Metropolis’s villains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 17:26:00" d="2020-04-16 17:40:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When she stumbles across a villainous plot - and all the other heroes are indisposed - Bumblebee must rise to the occasion… despite being the smallest of the bunch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 17:40:00" d="2020-04-16 18:00:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang’s trip to be bayou is ruined by a shambling Swamp Beast that’s scaring away anyone who dares to enter its soggy domain!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 18:00:00" d="2020-04-16 18:25:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang hits the ski slopes, but the fun is soon interrupted by the appearance of an evil Snowman Monster eager to scare all trespassers off his mountain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 18:25:00" d="2020-04-16 18:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Mum reveals that Gumball's real name is &quot;Zach&quot;, Gumball adopts a cheesy, annoying persona to match the name</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 18:35:00" d="2020-04-16 18:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Nothing much is happening for Gumball and Darwin and the background characters in Elmore seize their moment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 18:55:00" d="2020-04-16 19:06:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin’s harmless pranks on Dad spiral hopelessly out of control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 19:06:00" d="2020-04-16 19:17:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin’s martial arts costumes make them a laughing stock at school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 19:17:00" d="2020-04-16 19:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is traumatised when accidentally kissed on the mouth by his Grandma JoJo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 19:30:00" d="2020-04-16 19:40:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vic &amp; Val want to sneak out to a secret fireworks show but are thwarted when their new babysitter, Xochi, outsmarts them at every turn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 19:40:00" d="2020-04-16 19:55:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When V &amp; V discover that Chata's emotions control the water in the lake, they use it to their advantage and start their own wave pool business</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 19:55:00" d="2020-04-16 20:00:00"><n>The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ivandoe and Bert come across a tiny miserable prince in the forest. He needs a kiss to transform him back into the beautiful bullfrog he once was</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 20:00:00" d="2020-04-16 20:11:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ben, Gwen and Grandpa Max arrive in Bismarck for its annual celebration of bee pollination, bringing them face-to-face with Queen Bee and a bold new scheme</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 20:11:00" d="2020-04-16 20:21:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Team Tennyson look to take in the sights of the Shoshone Falls but when they find Steam Smythe siphoning off the water, it is up to Ben, Grandpa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 20:21:00" d="2020-04-16 20:35:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>With the Rust Bucket stopped on the Midwest roadside Ben locks himself inside with his tablet as Max and Gwen enjoy the great outdoors</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 20:35:00" d="2020-04-16 20:45:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% After the AO cause accidental destruction Dan's parents question whether the kids should be allowed to keep their Bakugan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 20:45:00" d="2020-04-16 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% Lia disagrees with her new Bakugan Pegatrix on battle techniques but during a fierce fight Lia must rely on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 21:00:00" d="2020-04-16 21:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lloyd must find his voice as he leads a small resistance to capture the airwaves in Ninjago City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 21:25:00" d="2020-04-16 21:45:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lloyd and the rebels celebrate their successful strike against Emperor Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 21:45:00" d="2020-04-16 22:10:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The headquarters to the resistance is breached and Lloyd scrambles to avoid capture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 22:10:00" d="2020-04-16 22:30:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% As Lloyd unmasks Mystake for who she truly is, Emperor Garmadon embraces Harumi as his daughter of darkness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 22:30:00" d="2020-04-16 22:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Everyone’s favorite skater, Ollie Van Dunk, crashes out in a big contest, loses his mojo, and quits skating. Angelo and friends try to raise his spirits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 22:40:00" d="2020-04-16 22:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% When Angelo gets stuck with the chore of painting Geezer’s old broken down fence, he channels his inner Tom Sawyer and manages to convince everyone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 22:55:00" d="2020-04-16 23:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo and friends make a TV show pilot called “Angelo Rules,” with Lola producing, Sherwood directing, Angelo writing, and Butterfingers playing Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 23:05:00" d="2020-04-16 23:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% After Mom cuts off Angelo’s videogame time Angelo attempts to change her mind. He sets out to prove to her that gaming is an important skillset</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 23:15:00" d="2020-04-16 23:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo and friends are stuck hanging out with Geezer’s Nephew -- a terrible, horrible, no good delinquent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 23:25:00" d="2020-04-16 23:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo and friends attempt to raise Butterfingers flagging self-esteem by training him in the art of Angelo-fu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 23:40:00" d="2020-04-16 23:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo shares his tips and tricks for trading favors and then cashing them all in to create “a perfect day.”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-16 23:50:00" d="2020-04-17 00:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% When his family go on vacation Angelo sets all kinds of traps in his house for potential thieves. Problem is when they return home Angelo lost his guide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-17 00:05:00" d="2020-04-17 00:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Wattersons complain about their day and order a pizza from Larry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-17 00:15:00" d="2020-04-17 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The citizens of Elmore are feeling down because it’s January, so Gumball and Anais invent a new holiday called Sluzzle Tag</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-17 00:30:00" d="2020-04-17 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% In Biology class, Gumball and Darwin are waiting for a butterfly to emerge from its chrysalis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-17 00:40:00" d="2020-04-17 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% After Gumball and Darwin have too much sugary cereal they begin thinking about the mysteries of the universe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-17 00:50:00" d="2020-04-17 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball, Darwin and Anais discover that Banana Joe’s mom paints pictures which predict the future</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-17 01:00:00" d="2020-04-17 01:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Mr Small shows a health and safety video in class, Darwin becomes obsessed with the idea of keeping the Wattersons safe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-17 01:15:00" d="2020-04-17 01:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Anais throws a party but no-one shows up as she has no friends or social skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-17 01:25:00" d="2020-04-17 01:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Alan is so good-natured that Gumball feels compelled to make him lose his temper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-17 01:35:00" d="2020-04-17 01:46:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin’s harmless pranks on Dad spiral hopelessly out of control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-17 01:46:00" d="2020-04-17 01:57:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin’s martial arts costumes make them a laughing stock at school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-17 01:57:00" d="2020-04-17 02:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is traumatised when accidentally kissed on the mouth by his Grandma JoJo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-17 02:10:00" d="2020-04-17 02:35:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Emperor Garmadon has taken control of Ninjago City where Lloyd retreats to the shadows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-17 02:35:00" d="2020-04-17 03:00:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lloyd and the rebels celebrate their successful strike against Emperor Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-17 03:00:00" d="2020-04-17 03:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% As Lloyd unmasks Mystake for who she truly is, Emperor Garmadon embraces Harumi as his daughter of darkness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-17 03:25:00" d="2020-04-17 03:50:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lloyd turns the tables on Harumi to take his father’s power away, and the Ninja learn what it takes to be a Dragon Hunter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-17 03:50:00" d="2020-04-17 04:01:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin’s harmless pranks on Dad spiral hopelessly out of control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-17 04:01:00" d="2020-04-17 04:12:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin’s martial arts costumes make them a laughing stock at school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-17 04:12:00" d="2020-04-17 04:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is traumatised when accidentally kissed on the mouth by his Grandma JoJo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-17 04:25:00" d="2020-04-17 04:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Wattersons complain about their day and order a pizza from Larry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-17 04:35:00" d="2020-04-17 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The citizens of Elmore are feeling down because it’s January, so Gumball and Anais invent a new holiday called Sluzzle Tag</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-17 04:50:00" d="2020-04-17 05:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% In Biology class, Gumball and Darwin are waiting for a butterfly to emerge from its chrysalis</k>  </p>
</a>
