<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="107" t="2020-04-15 04:29:12"><p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 05:00:00" d="2020-04-22 05:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% As night falls in Elmore, the Moon takes us on a tour through the various dreams -- and nightmares -- of the town’s slumbering inhabitants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 05:10:00" d="2020-04-22 05:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball is late to meet Penny at the mall, but a series of misunderstandings on the way only delay him further</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 05:20:00" d="2020-04-22 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Mom sees Darwin gazing longingly at a fish-tank she thinks their mammalian lifestyle isn’t fulfilling her adopted son and deep down he longs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 05:35:00" d="2020-04-22 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% The Parent Teacher Association of Elmore Junior High ban video games, so the kids try and prove that games aren’t a bad influence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 05:45:00" d="2020-04-22 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Anais arrives in the bedroom to find a messy crime-scene and her Daisy doll missing. She realises that Gumball and Darwin are the chief suspects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 06:00:00" d="2020-04-22 06:11:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ben, Gwen and Grandpa Max find themselves killing time at the local town library but soon scramble to out manoeuvre Hex as he searches for a hidden ancient artefact</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 06:11:00" d="2020-04-22 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Team Tennyson enjoy a convention in town but when a costume store employee finds a familiar-looking helmet and tries it on, Ben is faced with the return of Forever Knight!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 06:25:00" d="2020-04-22 06:36:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin are taught confusing lessons about honesty by the school councillor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 06:36:00" d="2020-04-22 06:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Darwin is sent away to a government institute for geniuses. Yes. Really</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 06:50:00" d="2020-04-22 07:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When the Sweetypies think the mythical Torbaclaun has come to Pure Heart Valley, Mao Mao tries to prove to them that it isn't real</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 07:00:00" d="2020-04-22 07:15:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mao Mao's legendary, gigantic and critical father visits his son at his new job as sheriff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 07:15:00" d="2020-04-22 07:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Cyborg wants Pain Bot to be his “little buddy” but is the destructive robot too dangerous to be a sidekick?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 07:25:00" d="2020-04-22 07:40:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Killer Moth offers a reward for Silkie's return, but will Silkier be happier away from the Titans?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 07:40:00" d="2020-04-22 07:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin learns that avocados are a super food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 07:50:00" d="2020-04-22 08:05:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin vows to never wash his hand again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 08:05:00" d="2020-04-22 08:14:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% BB and Cyborg invite Starfire to join in their fun as long as she avoids dreaded uncle jokes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 08:14:00" d="2020-04-22 08:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin tries to teach his superhero ways to Spanish speaking brothers Mas y Menos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 08:35:00" d="2020-04-22 08:55:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It's a classic haunted house caper when a rich man, whose life Scooby once saved, writes Scooby into his will!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 08:55:00" d="2020-04-22 09:20:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Shaggy and Scooby discover their new favourite food as the gang investigates the mystery of a frightening Sorcerer that’s haunting a snack factory!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 09:20:00" d="2020-04-22 09:30:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After being told by Chata that they can't get a pet, Vic &amp; Val adopt a wild lizard, unaware of its magical properties, and decide to keep it secret from Chata</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 09:30:00" d="2020-04-22 09:45:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Chata lets Vic be the boss of the taco stand for the day Vic decides to fire Val, which has disastrous consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 09:45:00" d="2020-04-22 09:55:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% Wynton finds a new Bakugan who proves difficult to control but things get more complicated when Col. Tripp seizes control of Trox</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 09:55:00" d="2020-04-22 10:10:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% With &quot;Dan&quot; behaving strangely toward the AO Lightning sniffs out the truth- an impostor!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 10:10:00" d="2020-04-22 10:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Darwin finds it harder than expected to give up his favourite foodstuff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 10:20:00" d="2020-04-22 10:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% It's Halloween in Elmore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 10:40:00" d="2020-04-22 10:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball jaywalks and is pulled over by Donut Cop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 10:50:00" d="2020-04-22 11:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Darwin starts sneezing repeatedly and it seems he can't stop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 11:00:00" d="2020-04-22 11:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Cyborg and Beast Boy have a staring contest for 30 years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 11:10:00" d="2020-04-22 11:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin challenges the gang not to use their powers - and they're more successful than he suspects!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 11:25:00" d="2020-04-22 11:33:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Beast Boy starts using more than 10% of his brain in an effort to find the hidden images in a puzzle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 11:33:00" d="2020-04-22 11:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans become hackers to stop a gang of computer pirates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 11:50:00" d="2020-04-22 12:01:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Jessica Cruz is convinced she can find the purr-fect forever home for Dexter, a cat who has been deemed unadoptable because he’s basically the worst cat in the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 12:01:00" d="2020-04-22 12:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When mean-girl Leslie Willis becomes a social media sensation by posting mean videos, Wonder Woman questions the moral integrity of the World of Man</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 12:15:00" d="2020-04-22 12:25:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Unikitty is the reigning champ of Hide N’ Seek Day. But when Unikitty finds everyone in the kingdom except for Richard, she hunts him down at all costs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 12:25:00" d="2020-04-22 12:40:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When a blizzard hits, Master Frown tries to ruin the fun by pretending to be a snowman! But when he gets frozen inside, he's forced to experience</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 12:40:00" d="2020-04-22 12:50:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Baby Bears get adopted by an eccentric millionaire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 12:50:00" d="2020-04-22 13:10:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Bears go to the gym and get quite the work out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 13:10:00" d="2020-04-22 13:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When the kids find out that Mom's life hasn't panned out as she'd hoped, they start taking on her chores. However, they accidentally grab her bucket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 13:20:00" d="2020-04-22 13:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% The Wattersons will do whatever it takes to get into the first screening of the latest Stellar Odyssey sequel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 13:30:00" d="2020-04-22 13:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Join the citizens of Elmore for a song and dance spectacular that will have you covering your ears with joy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 13:40:00" d="2020-04-22 13:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Darwin is delighted when they discover their old childhood toys, but soon realises that some things are best left in the past</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 13:55:00" d="2020-04-22 14:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin argue with the Internet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 14:05:00" d="2020-04-22 14:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Hector is unhappy with his height</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 14:25:00" d="2020-04-22 14:35:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>As everyone celebrates Valentino for growing his first facial hair, a jealous Vic resorts to magical methods to grow a mustache and compete for attention</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 14:35:00" d="2020-04-22 14:50:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Vic &amp; Val discover that Don isn't really himself, it's up to them to use his kooky codex of conspiracies to save him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 14:50:00" d="2020-04-22 15:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans start speaking Pig Latin to prevent Robin from eavesdropping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 15:00:00" d="2020-04-22 15:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans try to outprank each other on April Fools' Day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 15:10:00" d="2020-04-22 15:19:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans discover the magic of fan strength thanks to their #1 fan Wally T!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 15:19:00" d="2020-04-22 15:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Easter Bunny is missing and it's up to the Titans to find him before Easter is ruined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 15:35:00" d="2020-04-22 15:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A terrible haircut forces Craig to go undercover at the Creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 15:45:00" d="2020-04-22 16:00:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When the Time Keeper goes missing Craig and his friends take up the task of helping kids get home in time for dinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 16:00:00" d="2020-04-22 16:10:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>An explosive loner and his slacker best friend are waylaid from their journey into legend, only to find that their story is just beginning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 16:10:00" d="2020-04-22 16:25:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Mao Mao underestimates enemy and friend alike, it almost costs him the entire kingdom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 16:25:00" d="2020-04-22 16:34:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dr. Fox's robot helpers go on strike, so Unikitty and Puppycorn volunteer to be her lab rats, er, research assistants in a bold new experiment rocketing them into space!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 16:34:00" d="2020-04-22 16:50:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Richard's prepared one of the tastiest desserts ever, but he's locked it up tight until the friends have their boring dinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 16:50:00" d="2020-04-22 16:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% After the other Titans are turned into collectibles and disappear Robin must search yard sales and stores to find them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 16:59:00" d="2020-04-22 17:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin is inadvertently the getaway driver for a bank robbery in the midst of his driver's ed exam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 17:15:00" d="2020-04-22 17:26:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Everything is going well for Kara Danvers both as a teen and a superhero until she starts taking the blame for things she didn't do</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 17:26:00" d="2020-04-22 17:40:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When the local mall is attached by the monstrous supervillain Giganta, Karen Beecher discovers that tiny Bumblebee might be the only one small enough to save the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 17:40:00" d="2020-04-22 18:00:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang heads to the Velma’s beloved Renaissance Fair, where they must find a way to infiltrate the royal feast to stop an evil court jester from ending the king’s reign</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 18:00:00" d="2020-04-22 18:25:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Shaggy and Scooby decide to leave the gang! But before that, they insist on training the new recruits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 18:25:00" d="2020-04-22 18:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin are offended when Mom calls them “procrastinators”, once she’s told them what it means</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 18:35:00" d="2020-04-22 18:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% While performing a school play, Gumball is so nervous about kissing Penny that he accidentally head-butts her and cracks open her shell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 18:55:00" d="2020-04-22 19:06:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin are unwitting accomplices in a gas station robbery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 19:06:00" d="2020-04-22 19:17:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin accidentally destroy Mr Robinson’s new car… or do they?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 19:17:00" d="2020-04-22 19:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball experiences an impossibly unfortunate chain of events</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 19:30:00" d="2020-04-22 19:40:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>As everyone celebrates Valentino for growing his first facial hair, a jealous Vic resorts to magical methods to grow a mustache and compete for attention</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 19:40:00" d="2020-04-22 19:55:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Vic &amp; Val discover that Don isn't really himself, it's up to them to use his kooky codex of conspiracies to save him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 19:55:00" d="2020-04-22 20:00:00"><n>The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ivandoe comes face to face with a cocky young swan prince. To settle their differences they engage in a good old-fashioned Prince-Off</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 20:00:00" d="2020-04-22 20:11:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Tennysons come across a naturally formed pit with no bottom. Ben fights his better judgment to jump in until Kevin 11 shows up and goads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 20:11:00" d="2020-04-22 20:21:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Team Tennyson trade campfire stories in an anthology-style series that pits Ben against his arch-rival, Kevin 11, and teaches him the power of imagination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 20:21:00" d="2020-04-22 20:35:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While Gwen listens to a lecture on the Transcontinental Railroad, Ben sneaks away to the gift shop. But the Bounty Hunters appear and corner him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 20:35:00" d="2020-04-22 20:45:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% Philomena Dusk from AAAnimus Corp. hires Magnus and gives him a control implant to bolster the power of his Bakugan to defeat Dan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 20:45:00" d="2020-04-22 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% A cryptic call leads the AO in search of a missing Bakugan but they soon realize the call was</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 21:00:00" d="2020-04-22 21:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lloyd must find his voice as he leads a small resistance to capture the airwaves in Ninjago City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 21:25:00" d="2020-04-22 21:45:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lloyd and the rebels celebrate their successful strike against Emperor Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 21:45:00" d="2020-04-22 22:10:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The headquarters to the resistance is breached and Lloyd scrambles to avoid capture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 22:10:00" d="2020-04-22 22:30:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% As Lloyd unmasks Mystake for who she truly is, Emperor Garmadon embraces Harumi as his daughter of darkness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 22:30:00" d="2020-04-22 22:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo and friends make a TV show pilot called “Angelo Rules,” with Lola producing, Sherwood directing, Angelo writing, and Butterfingers playing Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 22:40:00" d="2020-04-22 22:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% After Mom cuts off Angelo’s videogame time Angelo attempts to change her mind. He sets out to prove to her that gaming is an important skillset</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 22:55:00" d="2020-04-22 23:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo and friends are stuck hanging out with Geezer’s Nephew -- a terrible, horrible, no good delinquent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 23:05:00" d="2020-04-22 23:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo and friends attempt to raise Butterfingers flagging self-esteem by training him in the art of Angelo-fu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 23:15:00" d="2020-04-22 23:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo shares his tips and tricks for trading favors and then cashing them all in to create “a perfect day.”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 23:25:00" d="2020-04-22 23:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% When his family go on vacation Angelo sets all kinds of traps in his house for potential thieves. Problem is when they return home Angelo lost his guide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 23:40:00" d="2020-04-22 23:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo and friends attempt to negotiate a deal for Peter and Cooper’s nonsensical home-made comic book with a famous comic book publisher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 23:50:00" d="2020-04-23 00:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo attempts to rack up the high score on an online business rating service to win free dinner at a fancy Japanese Steak House</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 00:05:00" d="2020-04-23 00:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% A mysterious figure from Nicole’s past shows up and challenges her to a fight, but the kids are surprised when she refuses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 00:15:00" d="2020-04-23 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% A compilation of some of the funniest, most bizarre clips uploaded onto the internet by the people of Elmore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 00:30:00" d="2020-04-23 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Rob purchases a universal remote from the Awesome Store, he discovers he can control the universe. He rewinds into the past and remembers Gumball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 00:40:00" d="2020-04-23 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball saved himself from being trapped in The Void, just in time. The remote has now taken Gumball back to the beginning of that disastrous day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 00:50:00" d="2020-04-23 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Fed up with having to listen to Molly's long, tedious anecdotes, Gumball and Darwin try to teach her how to make them sound more exciting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 01:00:00" d="2020-04-23 01:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin put Anais' new friend, Josh, through a series of tests, to see if he's good enough for their sister</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 01:15:00" d="2020-04-23 01:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin are convinced it's a day when nothing interesting is happening. But as they walk around Elmore, it is apparent exciting things</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 01:25:00" d="2020-04-23 01:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Gumball and Darwin accidentally find a sinister secret manifesto on Alan's memory stick, they decide they have to foil his plan for total world domination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 01:35:00" d="2020-04-23 01:46:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin are unwitting accomplices in a gas station robbery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 01:46:00" d="2020-04-23 01:57:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin accidentally destroy Mr Robinson’s new car… or do they?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 01:57:00" d="2020-04-23 02:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball experiences an impossibly unfortunate chain of events</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 02:10:00" d="2020-04-23 02:35:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Emperor Garmadon has taken control of Ninjago City where Lloyd retreats to the shadows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 02:35:00" d="2020-04-23 03:00:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lloyd and the rebels celebrate their successful strike against Emperor Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 03:00:00" d="2020-04-23 03:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% As Lloyd unmasks Mystake for who she truly is, Emperor Garmadon embraces Harumi as his daughter of darkness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 03:25:00" d="2020-04-23 03:50:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lloyd turns the tables on Harumi to take his father’s power away, and the Ninja learn what it takes to be a Dragon Hunter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 03:50:00" d="2020-04-23 04:01:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin are unwitting accomplices in a gas station robbery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 04:01:00" d="2020-04-23 04:12:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin accidentally destroy Mr Robinson’s new car… or do they?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 04:12:00" d="2020-04-23 04:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball experiences an impossibly unfortunate chain of events</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 04:25:00" d="2020-04-23 04:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% A mysterious figure from Nicole’s past shows up and challenges her to a fight, but the kids are surprised when she refuses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 04:35:00" d="2020-04-23 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% A compilation of some of the funniest, most bizarre clips uploaded onto the internet by the people of Elmore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 04:50:00" d="2020-04-23 05:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Rob purchases a universal remote from the Awesome Store, he discovers he can control the universe. He rewinds into the past and remembers Gumball</k>  </p>
</a>
