<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="102" t="2020-04-12 04:27:41"><p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 05:00:00" d="2020-04-19 05:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% After they receive an extravagant invitation to Masami's birthday party, Gumball and Darwin are anxious to find just the right gift for her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 05:10:00" d="2020-04-19 05:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball decides that the best way to prove to Mr. Fitzgerald that he's good enough for Penny is to become his apprentice for the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 05:20:00" d="2020-04-19 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball, Darwin and Anais are delighted when Grandpa Louie gives them a check for $5000. They immediately start fantasizing over what to spend it on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 05:35:00" d="2020-04-19 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When they find Anais training herself for a brutal showdown, Gumball and Darwin realise that their sister is being pestered at school by an annoying kid: Billy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 05:45:00" d="2020-04-19 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Darwin taunts Gumball about how predictable he is, Gumball tries to prove that he can still surprise his buddy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 06:00:00" d="2020-04-19 06:11:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ben learns about the possible existence of a mythical creature, the Quetzalcoatl, and takes it upon himself to find the feathered serpent on his own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 06:11:00" d="2020-04-19 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Team Tennyson help transport a caged Quetzalcoatl through the Yucatan jungle only to encounter a saboteur, LaGrange, who hijacks the precious cargo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 06:25:00" d="2020-04-19 06:36:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin are invited to a high school party, and have to bring a date!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 06:36:00" d="2020-04-19 06:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin unsuccessfully attempt to get a refund for their computer game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 06:50:00" d="2020-04-19 07:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang decide to compete in the annual Thumb War competition, but a surprise forces Mao Mao to deal with the unthinkable. losing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 07:00:00" d="2020-04-19 07:15:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Mao Mao discovers that he is not as popular as Badgerclops and Adorabat, they decide to reinvent him as a kinder, cuddlier hero</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 07:15:00" d="2020-04-19 07:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Cyborg and Beast Boy have a staring contest for 30 years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 07:25:00" d="2020-04-19 07:40:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin challenges the gang not to use their powers - and they're more successful than he suspects!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 07:40:00" d="2020-04-19 07:49:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Beast Boy writes a song to tell Raven his feelings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 07:49:00" d="2020-04-19 08:05:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Beast Boy goes on tour with his song</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 08:05:00" d="2020-04-19 08:14:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When Robin, Cyborg, and Beast Boy get trapped in an elevator the limits of their friendship are tested, while Starfire and Raven bond with a supervillain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 08:14:00" d="2020-04-19 08:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans overuse Raven's dark magic, causing unintended consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 08:35:00" d="2020-04-19 08:45:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Worried that his sword is a glorified consolation prize, Mao Mao sets out to prove the worth of his weapon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 08:45:00" d="2020-04-19 08:55:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After struggling to keep up, Adorabat gets a cybernetic &quot;Mega-Mech.&quot; But can fancy new powers make up for experience?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 08:55:00" d="2020-04-19 09:06:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When the Sweetypies think the mythical Torbaclaun has come to Pure Heart Valley, Mao Mao tries to prove to them that it isn't real</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 09:06:00" d="2020-04-19 09:17:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mao Mao's legendary, gigantic and critical father visits his son at his new job as sheriff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 09:17:00" d="2020-04-19 09:27:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>An explosive loner and his slacker best friend are waylaid from their journey into legend, only to find that their story is just beginning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 09:27:00" d="2020-04-19 09:37:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Nicole and her parents have it out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 09:37:00" d="2020-04-19 09:48:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Nicole decides to pay the cable bill in person at Chanax, she leaves specific instructions for Richard to stay in the car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 09:48:00" d="2020-04-19 09:59:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin are at the convenience store considering playing truant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 09:59:00" d="2020-04-19 10:09:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin argue with the Internet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 10:09:00" d="2020-04-19 10:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Hector is unhappy with his height</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 10:40:00" d="2020-04-19 11:01:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Kai confronts his dad for aiding the Hands of Time, only to discover that his parents are actually Acronix and Krux's captives. Meanwhile, as the Ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 11:01:00" d="2020-04-19 11:22:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The Hands of Time blackmail Kai and Nya into using their combined Elemental powers to retrieve the fourth and final Time Blade from the Boiling Sea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 11:22:00" d="2020-04-19 11:43:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% To save Master Wu, Kai and Nya stow away aboard Krux and Acronix's time travelling mech. Once in the past, they must prevent the Hands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 11:43:00" d="2020-04-19 12:03:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% As Ninjago City rebuilds, Faith arrives with a dire warning: the Oni have returned and are destroying the realms, one by one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 12:03:00" d="2020-04-19 12:24:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Having freed Lord Garmadon from Kryptarium Prison, the ninja are beset by doubts, particularly Lloyd</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 12:24:00" d="2020-04-19 12:44:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The Oni in Ninjago City are stronger than anyone could have imagined, and the ninja must risk a daring rescue of Lloyd and Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 12:44:00" d="2020-04-19 13:30:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The ninja race back to the Monastery of Spinjitzu. This is the last stand. The final battle against the Oni is now</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 13:30:00" d="2020-04-19 13:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Miss Simian discovers a failed test from Gumball's past that brings down his grade point average. This means he has to retake kindergarten all over again!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 13:40:00" d="2020-04-19 13:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin discover the reason Dad's diet wasn't working was that he was actually on ten diets and eating a meal for each of them!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 13:55:00" d="2020-04-19 14:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Sarah finds a notebook from an awesome store!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 14:05:00" d="2020-04-19 14:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% The kids finally get the puppy they always wanted, except it’s a turtle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 14:25:00" d="2020-04-19 14:35:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Vic accidentally loses one of Val's prized coins Val makes a deal with a mysterious antiques collector to replace it, but the deal has terrible consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 14:35:00" d="2020-04-19 14:50:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Val holds a grudge against Vic, unwittingly attracting an evil cadejo, a mythological wolf-like beast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 14:50:00" d="2020-04-19 14:58:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans visit the Hall of Justice to use the pool but then decide to check out the inside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 14:58:00" d="2020-04-19 15:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans must save the members of the Justice League from the clutches of the supervillain Darkseid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 15:10:00" d="2020-04-19 15:18:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans learn about cartoon-style violence in order to get revenge on a snack-stealing squirrel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 15:18:00" d="2020-04-19 15:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans head to the north pole to take themselves off the Naughty List</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 15:35:00" d="2020-04-19 15:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>An unusually hot day at the Creek melts Kit's ice pops</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 15:45:00" d="2020-04-19 16:00:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Trio finds gold in the muddy depths of the Creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 16:00:00" d="2020-04-19 16:11:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang struggles to get rid of the King when he joins them as their new deputy-for-a-day!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 16:11:00" d="2020-04-19 16:25:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Worried that his sword is a glorified consolation prize, Mao Mao sets out to prove the worth of his weapon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 16:25:00" d="2020-04-19 16:35:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang bring home a tiny creature named Pet Pet, but Richard wants proof that they are responsible owners. When Pet Pet runs away, Unikitty pretends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 16:35:00" d="2020-04-19 16:50:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Unikitty and Puppycorn are invited to Master Frown and Brock's apartment for a dinner party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 16:50:00" d="2020-04-19 16:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% A flashback reveals how Robin formed the Teen Titans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 16:59:00" d="2020-04-19 17:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% A flashback reveals how Robin changed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 17:15:00" d="2020-04-19 17:26:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>What begins as a simple vandalism investigation becomes an all-out turf war when the team encounters a powerful trio of Kryptonians bent on world domination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 17:26:00" d="2020-04-19 17:40:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>What begins as a simple vandalism investigation becomes an all-out turf war when the team encounters a powerful trio of Kryptonians bent on world domination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 17:40:00" d="2020-04-19 18:00:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang head out to a Day of the Dead festival. There, they learn the spirit of the old, legendary criminal, El Bandito, has returned to terrorise the locals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 18:00:00" d="2020-04-19 18:25:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Daphne agrees to watch her friend’s kid, Wayne, and convinces Fred to take a night off from mysteries to go to the boardwalk amusement park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 18:25:00" d="2020-04-19 18:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin help Rocky land an office job so that his dad, Mr Robinson, will be proud of him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 18:35:00" d="2020-04-19 18:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball confronts Clayton about his fabled Seven Pressure Point Heart Exploding Technique, assuming it’s another one of his outlandish claims</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 18:55:00" d="2020-04-19 19:06:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin are taught confusing lessons about honesty by the school councillor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 19:06:00" d="2020-04-19 19:17:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Darwin is sent away to a government institute for geniuses. Yes. Really</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 19:17:00" d="2020-04-19 19:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin’s wish comes true when they suddenly turn into men</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 19:30:00" d="2020-04-19 19:40:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Vic accidentally loses one of Val's prized coins Val makes a deal with a mysterious antiques collector to replace it, but the deal has terrible consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 19:40:00" d="2020-04-19 19:55:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Val holds a grudge against Vic, unwittingly attracting an evil cadejo, a mythological wolf-like beast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 19:55:00" d="2020-04-19 20:00:00"><n>The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While escaping from a grizzly bear, Ivandoe and Bert fall into an underground cave where a large Troll-woman in a party dress keeps them captive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 20:00:00" d="2020-04-19 20:11:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Team Tennyson trade campfire stories in an anthology-style series that pits Ben against his arch-rival, Kevin 11, and teaches him the power of imagination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 20:11:00" d="2020-04-19 20:22:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Team Tennyson's quest for the best pizza in Rome leads them to the Bugg Brothers and their latest culinary caper, complete with stolen recipes and kidnapped chefs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 20:22:00" d="2020-04-19 20:35:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In Rome, Gwen takes Team Tennyson on a self-guided tour of the many ancient sites when a distracted Ben accidentally stumbles upon Queen Bee’s monumental heist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 20:35:00" d="2020-04-19 20:45:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% The AO compete with a rival Brawling team for ViewTube hits leading to a &quot;winner take all&quot; brawl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 20:45:00" d="2020-04-19 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% Everett Ray, a promotor, tries to get the AO to join an official league for Bakugan Battling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 21:00:00" d="2020-04-19 21:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% When an unknown criminal syndicate threatens the Royal Family, the Ninja are called into action. They must protect the princess and an artifact</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 21:25:00" d="2020-04-19 21:45:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% In the wake of a vicious attack upon the palace, the Sons of Garmadon steal the second Oni Mask, and the ninja invite the royal princess, Harumi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 21:45:00" d="2020-04-19 22:10:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% While Princess Harumi adjusts to life with the ninja, Lloyd and Jay search for answers about the Oni Masks, while Cole and Zane attempt to infiltrate the Sons of Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 22:10:00" d="2020-04-19 22:30:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% In order to join the Sons of Garmadon, Zane (aka Snake Jaguar) participates in a deadly motorcycle initiation race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 22:30:00" d="2020-04-19 22:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Dreams do come true and Angelo and friends turn Angelo’s Dad into a rock star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 22:40:00" d="2020-04-19 22:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo attempts to join the secretive “school council” and learns-- never become a member of a group that will have you has a member</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 22:55:00" d="2020-04-19 23:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo gives us his tips and tricks for the most awesome sleepover ever. Until, the “prank call” trick ruins the night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 23:05:00" d="2020-04-19 23:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo stupidly boasts that his Dad used to be a stuntman. And the next day Dad has been invited to speak to Angelo’s class for career day. Gah!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 23:15:00" d="2020-04-19 23:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo makes Tracy cry and feels terrible about it. He declares a truce. Problem is… their growing friendship throws off the balance of nature!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 23:25:00" d="2020-04-19 23:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Joe Mama has been stealing stuff from around town and storing it under Angelo’s bed. Angelo and friends embark on a reverse scavenger hunt to figure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 23:40:00" d="2020-04-19 23:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo and Lola are stuck with Manetti as a science project partner. The only way to complete the project is turn Manetti into the science project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-19 23:50:00" d="2020-04-20 00:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Tracy claims Angelo broke her arm. Angelo’s punishment—become Tracy’s slave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 00:05:00" d="2020-04-20 00:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin are devastated to learn that Mr. Robinson -- their favourite person in the world -- is selling his house and leaving town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 00:15:00" d="2020-04-20 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Mom and the kids depart for their hard day's work, leaving a seemingly lazy Dad half-asleep on the sofa. Mom has given him one very simple job: buy mayonnaise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 00:30:00" d="2020-04-20 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When the Wattersons arrive at the mall for a day of shopping, they struggle to find a space in the parking lot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 00:40:00" d="2020-04-20 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin see an advert for the latest, cutting-edge Bobert operating system and excitedly talk Bobert into downloading it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 00:50:00" d="2020-04-20 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball is the star of his own comic, but struggles to match up to his heroic alter-ego</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 01:00:00" d="2020-04-20 01:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% After Gumball convinces himself that Penny doesn't love him as much as she used to, he decides to put together a romantic quest to remind her of their good times together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 01:15:00" d="2020-04-20 01:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Everyone knows you can never watch just one video on the internet but Gumball and Darwin think they are the exception to the rule</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 01:25:00" d="2020-04-20 01:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% After being framed for feeding coffee to the squirrels in the park, Gumball proclaims that Mrs Robinson is pure evil</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 01:35:00" d="2020-04-20 01:46:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin are taught confusing lessons about honesty by the school councillor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 01:46:00" d="2020-04-20 01:57:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Darwin is sent away to a government institute for geniuses. Yes. Really</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 01:57:00" d="2020-04-20 02:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin’s wish comes true when they suddenly turn into men</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 02:10:00" d="2020-04-20 02:35:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The Oni in Ninjago City are stronger than anyone could have imagined, and the ninja must risk a daring rescue of Lloyd and Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 02:35:00" d="2020-04-20 03:00:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% In the wake of a vicious attack upon the palace, the Sons of Garmadon steal the second Oni Mask, and the ninja invite the royal princess, Harumi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 03:00:00" d="2020-04-20 03:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% In order to join the Sons of Garmadon, Zane (aka Snake Jaguar) participates in a deadly motorcycle initiation race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 03:25:00" d="2020-04-20 03:50:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Zane’s near demise at the hands of Mr. E forces the ninja to flee aboard the Bounty, where they discover a message Zane intercepted may reveal the hidden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 03:50:00" d="2020-04-20 04:01:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin are taught confusing lessons about honesty by the school councillor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 04:01:00" d="2020-04-20 04:12:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Darwin is sent away to a government institute for geniuses. Yes. Really</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 04:12:00" d="2020-04-20 04:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin’s wish comes true when they suddenly turn into men</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 04:25:00" d="2020-04-20 04:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin are devastated to learn that Mr. Robinson -- their favourite person in the world -- is selling his house and leaving town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 04:35:00" d="2020-04-20 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Mom and the kids depart for their hard day's work, leaving a seemingly lazy Dad half-asleep on the sofa. Mom has given him one very simple job: buy mayonnaise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-20 04:50:00" d="2020-04-20 05:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When the Wattersons arrive at the mall for a day of shopping, they struggle to find a space in the parking lot</k>  </p>
</a>
