<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="120" t="2021-07-11 04:54:52"><p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 05:05:00" d="2021-07-18 05:15:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 2016 II (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>That's the Stuff
While touring a space museum, Ben's excitement multiplies when he learns that recently discovered &quot;space stuff&quot; is being examined inside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 05:15:00" d="2021-07-18 05:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 2016 II (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Half-Sies
During a trip to the Lake of the Ozarks, Ben and Gwen squabble over Ben's unnecessary &quot;half-birthday&quot; celebration, but when Max</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 05:25:00" d="2021-07-18 05:35:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Brawler Headhunting
As acting president of Kazami International, Shun is called upon to entertain another new young CEO Noah Schmidt, who’s interested</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 05:35:00" d="2021-07-18 05:50:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lightning's Entrance Exam
The Awesome Brawlers may be world famous heroes, but that doesn’t mean they get out of going to school. They are still regular</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 05:50:00" d="2021-07-18 05:55:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Magoo in Shining Armor
Magoo on a construction site thinks he’s been hired for a medieval theater show. Fizz and Weasel bump into Magoo at</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 05:55:00" d="2021-07-18 06:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Space Hamster
In order to make himself an object of worship Fizz makes people believe he’s an alien coming to share his wisdom. Magoo mistakes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 06:05:00" d="2021-07-18 06:10:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Doctor Magoo
Magoo thinks he’s helping out at an understaffed veterinary clinic. In fact he’s at the supermarket where Fizz is trying to gain popularity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 06:10:00" d="2021-07-18 06:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Toes in the Sand
Magoo thinks he is on a beach and that sailors are emptying their oil tanker right into the ocean. Wanting to put a stop to the pollution</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 06:25:00" d="2021-07-18 06:30:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dinosaur Island
Fizz has reduced the size of the moon in order to model it in his own image. But Magoo thinks it’s a dinosaur egg ready to hatch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 06:30:00" d="2021-07-18 06:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Santa's Little Helper
Magoo a Christmas volunteer in a supermarket thinks a burglar is entering overnight and decides to stop him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 06:35:00" d="2021-07-18 06:45:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>At the Heart of the Crater
Magoo thinks that he is at the foot of a volcano but in fact he’s next to a huge soup vat. And he sets it all awry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 06:45:00" d="2021-07-18 07:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lost in the Subway
Magoo thinks he is in the subway but actually he’s in a cave. Running into Weasel he thinks he’s lost and decides to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 07:00:00" d="2021-07-18 07:25:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Some Fred Time
The gang force the over-worked Fred to relax and take time off from mysteries at Daphne’s family’s beach house. Unfortunately</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 07:25:00" d="2021-07-18 07:55:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% There Wolf
Feeling unwell Scooby is brought to a vet clinic. Soon the gang finds a werewolf is roaming around the place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 07:55:00" d="2021-07-18 08:05:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek III (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Ground Is Lava!
When an intense game of &quot;The Ground is Lava&quot; breaks out, Craig must carefully traverse the Creek to save his sister</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 08:05:00" d="2021-07-18 08:20:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek III (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Council Of The Creek: Operation Hive-Mind
Hive Mind - When bees take over the Trading Tree, Craig must assemble the Council of the Creek to avert disaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 08:20:00" d="2021-07-18 08:30:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek III (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Bike Thief
Craig investigates the theft of the 10 Speed's bikes in hopes of finding the culprit!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 08:30:00" d="2021-07-18 08:50:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek III (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Craig Of The Beach
Craig gets to hit the beach with his friends and family, but starts to get worried his Dad is more fun than him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 08:50:00" d="2021-07-18 09:00:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek III (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Plush Kingdom
Craig, Kelsey, JP and Jessica discover a group of plushie obsessed kids, deep within the creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 09:00:00" d="2021-07-18 09:15:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek III (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% The Ice Pop Trio: Creek Street
Craig sets out in search of Ice Pops on a hot day with the help of an unlikely duo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 09:15:00" d="2021-07-18 09:25:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pencil Break Mania
When Pencil Break Mania hits the Creek, JP finds himself as an unlikely champion and is forced to defend his title against the very best!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 09:25:00" d="2021-07-18 09:35:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Last Game Of Summer
It's the last day of summer, and the last chance for Craig to uncover an ancient treasure beneath the Creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 09:35:00" d="2021-07-18 09:55:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fall Anthology
In an attempt to finish a school project, Craig remembers some of his favorite Fall moments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 09:55:00" d="2021-07-18 10:05:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Grody to the Maximum
Cody gets a super cool, new t-shirt. It's SO cool that the kids don't even recognize him, so Cody jumps on the chance to leave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 10:05:00" d="2021-07-18 10:20:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Wiggin' Out
Bridgette donates her hair to a charity that makes wigs for hairless cats and now some classmates want to do the same. But their quest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 10:20:00" d="2021-07-18 10:30:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Upside of Hunger
Owen has a mishap while baking an upside-down cake and is transported to an upside-down world where he is forced tooutwit himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 10:30:00" d="2021-07-18 10:50:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fire in the Hole
Duncan cooks up a nuclear hot sauce to mess with Chef, but accidentally summons Terry Spice, King of the Underworld!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 10:50:00" d="2021-07-18 10:55:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Timeless Bear
When Grizzy and the Lemmings accidentally activate a magic disk representing the earth they are sent back in time to the prehistoric era</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 10:55:00" d="2021-07-18 11:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Weightless Bear
While fighting over a jar of chocolate spread, Grizzy and the Lemmings set off a chain reaction which sends the jar flying into space</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 11:00:00" d="2021-07-18 11:10:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Call of the Bear
Grizzy discovers the ranger's collection of bird calls by chance. With a simple blow of the whistle, he can attract a flock of partridges</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 11:10:00" d="2021-07-18 11:20:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Yummy Fly
The Lemmings notice that Grizzy moves away from the jar of chocolate spread whenever he chases the fly buzzing around him. But the insect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 11:20:00" d="2021-07-18 11:30:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Good Bear Bad Bear
A magic tomahawk divides Grizzy into two identical bears with diametrically opposite personalities: one short-tempered, the other super-sweet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 11:30:00" d="2021-07-18 11:35:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Hat Tricks
Grizzy finds a magician's hat that tosses out objects stored inside beforehand with the tap of a magic wand. He decides to impress his beloved</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 11:35:00" d="2021-07-18 11:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lemming Beach
A newly unpacked UV tanning booth holds the place of honor in the middle of the cabin. Grizzy gets it into his head that a classy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 11:40:00" d="2021-07-18 11:55:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% No See No Do
Grizzy wants to try out the brand new packaging format of chocolate spread that he discovers in the ranger's cupboard: a yummy-looking XXL jar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 11:55:00" d="2021-07-18 12:00:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Squeaks Upon a Star
Squeaks wishes Bugs was small so he would learn what it's like to be short. The wish comes true</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 12:00:00" d="2021-07-18 12:05:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Mile Hi Grub
King Thes keeps trying to eat Squeaks while they are all flying on a plane</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 12:05:00" d="2021-07-18 12:10:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Pole Position
Bugs and Squeaks have to compete in a series of challenges so the Beaver will put them on a totem pole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 12:10:00" d="2021-07-18 12:20:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Thirst Things First
Bugs awakens with a terrible case of cotton mouth. Will he be able to quench his thirst?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 12:20:00" d="2021-07-18 12:25:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Bugs of Chance
Shifty tries to con Bugs and Squeaks at carnival games. Bugs wins in the end</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 12:25:00" d="2021-07-18 12:30:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Bugs for Mayor
Squint Eatswood tries to bully his way into being Mayor of the Forest so Bugs has no choice but to run against him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 12:30:00" d="2021-07-18 12:35:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% The Lepra-Con
Shameless O'Scanty wants Bugs' lucky rabbit foot but Bugs is too attached to it to give it up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 12:35:00" d="2021-07-18 12:50:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Squeak Show
Bigfoot mistakes Squeaks as Bugs' new cat and goes to every effort to return him to his rightful place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 12:50:00" d="2021-07-18 13:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Origins
When Mom and Dad struggle to keep hyperactive toddler-aged Gumball from trashing the house and exhausting them they decide to buy him a pet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 13:00:00" d="2021-07-18 13:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Origins Part Two
Via the sewers Darwin finds himself flushed out to sea. He is terrified but determined to make his way back to the Wattersons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 13:10:00" d="2021-07-18 13:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Traitor
When Alan ditches Gumball to do something more fun Gumball is desperate to track him down and make him pay for his betrayal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 13:25:00" d="2021-07-18 13:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Advice
To make Mr Small feel like he's inspired the students, Gumball and Darwin try to follow every piece of advice Mr Small gives them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 13:35:00" d="2021-07-18 13:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Signal
When Darwin asks for his advice on hats, Gumball suddenly can't speak and offends Darwin. Darwin is convinced Gumball said he had a fat head</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 13:55:00" d="2021-07-18 14:05:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>45% Supply Mom
When Chef's mom becomes the supply teacher for a day Duncan replaces Chef's to-do list with one of his own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 14:05:00" d="2021-07-18 14:20:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>45% Mooshy Mon Mons
After eating Chef's extremely rare and expensive chocolates Courtney drags Owen, Izzy and Beth all the way to theNorberian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 14:20:00" d="2021-07-18 14:30:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>45% Student Becomes the Teacher
Chef is knocked unconscious right before a School Board Evaluator shows up for a big review. Now Owen has to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 14:30:00" d="2021-07-18 14:50:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>45% Beth and the Beanstalk
After having a chocolate bar confiscated by Chef, Beth finds herself in a parallel giant world and aims to get back her now giant chocolate bar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 14:50:00" d="2021-07-18 15:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% The Academy
Robin creates the Teen Titan Awards in an effort to get his teammates to clean up the Tower</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 15:00:00" d="2021-07-18 15:10:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Throne of Bones
When the other Titans start listening to heavy metal music Robin warns them of the dangers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 15:10:00" d="2021-07-18 15:25:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Costume Contest
Sick of losing the costume contest to the Hive Five every year the Titans hatch a scheme to win</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 15:25:00" d="2021-07-18 15:35:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% The Self-Indulgent 200th Episode Spectacular!: Part 1
The Titans must confront their creators</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 15:35:00" d="2021-07-18 15:50:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% The Self-Indulgent 200th Episode Spectacular!: Part 2
The Titans discover how hard cartoons are to produce</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 15:50:00" d="2021-07-18 16:00:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% Big Pinchy
JP leads his friends on a voyage to find the biggest crayfish in the creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 16:00:00" d="2021-07-18 16:20:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% The Kid From 3030
The kids meet a mysterious kid from the future and try to help him complete his mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 16:20:00" d="2021-07-18 16:30:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% Power Punchers
Fed up with losing in video games to his Dad, Craig seeks training in the Creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 16:30:00" d="2021-07-18 16:40:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% Creek Cart Racers
A high-speed race with a high-stakes prize may be too much for Craig and his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 16:40:00" d="2021-07-18 17:00:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% Secret Book Club
Kelsey starts a super secret book club to introduce Craig and JP to the joys of reading</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 17:00:00" d="2021-07-18 17:25:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Some Fred Time
The gang force the over-worked Fred to relax and take time off from mysteries at Daphne’s family’s beach house. Unfortunately</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 17:25:00" d="2021-07-18 17:55:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% There Wolf
Feeling unwell Scooby is brought to a vet clinic. Soon the gang finds a werewolf is roaming around the place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 17:55:00" d="2021-07-18 18:00:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... II (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Life's A Beach
Tom is stranded on a deserted island. The only other living inhabitant is Jerry. Let the survival of the fittest begin!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 18:00:00" d="2021-07-18 18:05:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... II (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hiccup and Away
When Tom gets the hiccups, the witches decide that the only way to cure him is to scare him, so they banish him to the Wicked Forest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 18:05:00" d="2021-07-18 18:20:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... II (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>I Quit
After a particularly rough cat-and-mouse chase, Jerry quits! Tom is stunned as he watches his little friend storm off to his hole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 18:20:00" d="2021-07-18 18:25:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... II (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>You Can't Handle the Tooth
When Hildie and Beatie bring home a magic ogre's tooth, they warn Tom and Jerry not to touch it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 18:25:00" d="2021-07-18 18:35:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... II (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pain for Sale
When Rick plans a big yard sale for the next morning, Spike recruits Tom and Jerry to find Tyke's first puppy collar in the gear before it's sold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 18:35:00" d="2021-07-18 18:50:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... II (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Return to Sender
When Hildie receives another dozen black roses from a secret admirer, her curiosity is piqued. Sending Tom and Jerry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 18:50:00" d="2021-07-18 19:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Blame
Gumball gives Billy his first taste of video-games but the sheer excitement causes him to pass out. His mother Felicity summons the Parent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 19:00:00" d="2021-07-18 19:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Detective
Anais arrives in the bedroom to find a messy crime-scene and her Daisy doll missing. She realises that Gumball and Darwin are the chief suspects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 19:10:00" d="2021-07-18 19:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Fury
When an unknown figure shows up and insults their Mom the kids are expecting a massive showdown but are surprised when Mom chooses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 19:25:00" d="2021-07-18 19:35:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Phantom Thief Comes to Call
An archeological discovery is made in Los Volmos. Exploration at the site is cut short, when a master thief</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 19:35:00" d="2021-07-18 19:55:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Phantom Thief Ajit
An Ancient Bakugon artifact from an archeological discovery is placed in the Los Volmos Museum. The Awesome Brawlers are charged</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 19:55:00" d="2021-07-18 20:05:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Demon Prom
Trigon makes Raven attend her prom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 20:05:00" d="2021-07-18 20:15:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>BBCYFSHIPBDAY
Beast Boy and Cyborg celebrate the birthday of their friendship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 20:15:00" d="2021-07-18 20:30:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Thanksgetting
The Titans are sick of normal Thanksgiving traditions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 20:30:00" d="2021-07-18 20:40:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mo' Money Mo' Problems
The Titans make Robin give them a tour of Wayne Manor and discover how fun it is to be rich</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 20:40:00" d="2021-07-18 21:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Beast Girl
As the Titans deal with Madame Rouge Beast Boy is excited to meet his female counterpart Beast Girl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 21:00:00" d="2021-07-18 21:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Puppy
The kids finally get the puppy they always wanted except it’s a turtle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 21:10:00" d="2021-07-18 21:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Name
When Mum reveals that Gumball's real name is Zach Gumball adopts a cheesy annoying persona to match the name</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 21:25:00" d="2021-07-18 21:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Extras
Nothing much is happening for Gumball and Darwin and the background characters in Elmore seize their moment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 21:35:00" d="2021-07-18 21:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Gripes
Gumball is in such a bad mood that it spreads to Darwin who joins him in complaining about everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 21:55:00" d="2021-07-18 22:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Rock Star Dad
Dreams do come true and Angelo and friends turn Angelo’s Dad into a rock star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 22:05:00" d="2021-07-18 22:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% School Council
Angelo attempts to join the secretive “school council” and learns-- never become a member of a group that will have you has a member</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 22:20:00" d="2021-07-18 22:40:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu IX (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% The Gilded Path
The headquarters to the resistance is breached and Lloyd scrambles to avoid capture. Meanwhile the Ninja are caught by Heavy Metal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 22:40:00" d="2021-07-18 22:50:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Friend Wars
Princess SugarSalt dupes Axel into hanging out with Cleo LeBall and usurps his role as team leader forcing Zoe to step in and keep the toys together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 22:50:00" d="2021-07-18 23:05:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Scratch Pack
Axel and the team must run damage control after a loose spark of Minergy accidentally turns Zoe's old toys - a set of cute squishy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 23:05:00" d="2021-07-18 23:15:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Countdown
Axel has to clean up the living room in time for his uncle's dinner party but trying to do too much at once leaves him stuck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 23:15:00" d="2021-07-18 23:25:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Freeze!
Axel and his team find themselves in a tough position after Ice Crusher makes it too cold for them to fight back at full speed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 23:25:00" d="2021-07-18 23:35:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stuck on You
Tired of Axel and the team taking him for granted Masko tries to get kidnapped and ends up stuck to Dynamo who's less than enthused</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 23:35:00" d="2021-07-19 00:00:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu IX (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% The Gilded Path
The headquarters to the resistance is breached and Lloyd scrambles to avoid capture. Meanwhile the Ninja are caught by Heavy Metal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 00:00:00" d="2021-07-19 00:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Understanding
Gumball and Darwin find themselves in serious trouble when they agree to everything the new kid in school says. The truth is they can't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 00:10:00" d="2021-07-19 00:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Ad
To make ends meet, the Wattersons are forced to rent out their house. However with nowhere else to stay they decide to secretly remain at the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 00:20:00" d="2021-07-19 00:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Slip
Richard doesn't answer the door in time and the jobsworth delivery guy will not let him have his package. His options are to pick his package</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 00:35:00" d="2021-07-19 00:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Drama
Everyone assumes Darwin and Carrie's relationship is doomed as they're so different. That is everyone except Darwin and Carrie. When Carrie's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 00:45:00" d="2021-07-19 00:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Master
Dad decides to resolve the Watterson family's differences through the power and magic of his favourite roleplaying game. As they embark</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 00:55:00" d="2021-07-19 01:05:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Silence
When Gumball and Darwin's conversation dries up they worry that their friendship is coming to an end. They try to find</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 01:05:00" d="2021-07-19 01:15:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Mirror
Gumball receives a scare-email from a freaky ghost and decides to ignore it despite Darwin's advice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 01:15:00" d="2021-07-19 01:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Burden
Vice Principal Brown gives Gumball and Darwin the ancient school hamster Chris Morris to look after for the weekend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 01:30:00" d="2021-07-19 01:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Bros
When Darwin and Gumball reveal how they’d spend their perfect day Gumball confesses that he would spend it with Penny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 01:40:00" d="2021-07-19 01:50:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Man
Granny Jojo has brought a boyfriend to her birthday meal and Dad isn’t happy about it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 01:50:00" d="2021-07-19 02:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Pizza
The Wattersons complain about their day and order a pizza from Larry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 02:00:00" d="2021-07-19 02:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Photobomb
Angelo’s photo bombs make him a big hit on the internet and he is loving his newfound popularity. Until Butterfingers starts getting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 02:10:00" d="2021-07-19 02:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Not Gym Class
The equipment in Coach Zonka’s gym class is deemed a safety hazard so gym class is canceled permanently. Angelo attempts to rally the school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 02:25:00" d="2021-07-19 02:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Van Dunk's Mojo
Everyone’s favorite skater Ollie Van Dunk crashes out in a big contest loses his mojo and quits skating. Angelo and friends try to raise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 02:35:00" d="2021-07-19 02:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Das Fence
When Angelo gets stuck with the chore of painting Geezer’s old broken down fence he channels his inner Tom Sawyer and manages to convince</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 02:45:00" d="2021-07-19 03:00:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% The World According To Angelo
Angelo and friends make a TV show pilot called “Angelo Rules” with Lola producing Sherwood directing Angelo writing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 03:00:00" d="2021-07-19 03:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Gripes
Gumball is in such a bad mood that it spreads to Darwin who joins him in complaining about everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 03:10:00" d="2021-07-19 03:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Vacation
The Wattersons are swapping scary stories on a family vacation when their car breaks down in the middle of the desert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 03:20:00" d="2021-07-19 03:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Fraud
When Gumball and Darwin discover his diploma is fake Principal Brown is determined to keep their discovery a secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 03:35:00" d="2021-07-19 03:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Void
Gumball and Darwin start noticing small details around Elmore High that don't add up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 03:45:00" d="2021-07-19 04:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Boss
Gumball and Darwin help Rocky land an office job so that his dad Mr Robinson will be proud of him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 04:00:00" d="2021-07-19 04:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Apprentice
Gumball decides that the best way to show Mr Fitzgerald that he's good enough for Penny, is to become his apprentice for the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 04:10:00" d="2021-07-19 04:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Check
Gumball, Darwin and Anais are delighted when Grandpa Louie gives them a check for $5,000. They immediately start fantasising over what to spend it on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 04:20:00" d="2021-07-19 04:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Pest
When they find Anais training herself for a brutal showdown Gumball and Darwin realise that their sister is being pestered at school by an annoying kid: Billy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 04:30:00" d="2021-07-19 04:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Hug
When Darwin taunts Gumball about how predictable he is Gumball tries to prove that he can still surprise his buddy. He thinks that greeting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 04:40:00" d="2021-07-19 04:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Sale
Gumball and Darwin are devastated to learn that Mr Robinson - their favourite person in the world - is selling his house and leaving town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-19 04:55:00" d="2021-07-19 05:05:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 2016 II (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Xingo's Back
Left to entertain himself as Max takes a must deserved nap, Ben stumbles upon a Xingo arcade game and goes OE-Shock Rock to power</k>  </p>
</a>
