<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="107" t="2020-04-14 04:27:33"><p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 05:00:00" d="2020-04-21 05:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When she has no one to share her lunch with, Jamie realises she needs a sweetheart. Darwin's the only one who doesn’t flee immediately, so he and Jamie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 05:10:00" d="2020-04-21 05:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin are reading Anais’ diary when they discover that her relationship with her new friend seems a bit one-sided</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 05:20:00" d="2020-04-21 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Bobert finds he is infected with a virus called love.exe he asks Gumball and Darwin to give him a definition for the word ‘love’</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 05:35:00" d="2020-04-21 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% At Halloween show and tell, the class isn’t buying Gumball’s story about Gargaroth The Devourer until Carrie fakes a terrifying haunting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 05:45:00" d="2020-04-21 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball is walking in the same direction as Hot Dog Guy, and with each step it becomes increasingly awkward</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 06:00:00" d="2020-04-21 06:11:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ben learns about the possible existence of a mythical creature, the Quetzalcoatl, and takes it upon himself to find the feathered serpent on his own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 06:11:00" d="2020-04-21 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Team Tennyson help transport a caged Quetzalcoatl through the Yucatan jungle only to encounter a saboteur, LaGrange, who hijacks the precious cargo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 06:25:00" d="2020-04-21 06:36:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball sets out to win his Dad back by winning a blindfolded “dumb” race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 06:36:00" d="2020-04-21 06:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball almost loses his mind trying to guess Darwin’s secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 06:50:00" d="2020-04-21 07:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After struggling to keep up, Adorabat gets a cybernetic &quot;Mega-Mech.&quot; But can fancy new powers make up for experience?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 07:00:00" d="2020-04-21 07:15:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Feeling left out Adorabat wishes Mao Mao and Badgerclops would spend less time with each other and more time with her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 07:15:00" d="2020-04-21 07:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin tries to destroy some pesky mocking birds but they come back bigger, stronger, and ready to mock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 07:25:00" d="2020-04-21 07:40:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Beast Boy invites Tara to the Titan's Valentine's Day dance and she accepts in order to destroy all of the Titans and exact revenge on Beast Boy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 07:40:00" d="2020-04-21 07:49:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin uses his skills as a master detective</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 07:49:00" d="2020-04-21 08:05:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% It's Easter and the Tooth Fairy is trying to take over the holiday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 08:05:00" d="2020-04-21 08:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% BB avoids being &quot;the dumb one&quot; by making the rest of the Titans dumber, which leaves only Silkie to save the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 08:15:00" d="2020-04-21 08:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin goes undercover to destroy the Hive. ight after he enjoys some of their perks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 08:35:00" d="2020-04-21 08:55:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When an Artificial Intelligence takes over the building of a trendy tech company, the Gang has to solve the computerised mystery and learn a lesson about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 08:55:00" d="2020-04-21 09:20:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Gang has seats on the largest airplane ever to fly the open airways! Unfortunately the plane is also beset by a Gremlin bent on sabotaging the flight!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 09:20:00" d="2020-04-21 09:30:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Vic accidentally loses one of Val's prized coins Val makes a deal with a mysterious antiques collector to replace it, but the deal has terrible consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 09:30:00" d="2020-04-21 09:45:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Val holds a grudge against Vic, unwittingly attracting an evil cadejo, a mythological wolf-like beast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 09:45:00" d="2020-04-21 09:55:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% The AO compete with a rival Brawling team for ViewTube hits leading to a &quot;winner take all&quot; brawl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 09:55:00" d="2020-04-21 10:10:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% Everett Ray, a promotor, tries to get the AO to join an official league for Bakugan Battling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 10:10:00" d="2020-04-21 10:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Nicole encourages Gumball to do what comes naturally. reak stuff!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 10:20:00" d="2020-04-21 10:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball kind of teaches Darwin how to be a skater…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 10:40:00" d="2020-04-21 10:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin help Rocky land an office job so that his dad, Mr Robinson, will be proud of him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 10:50:00" d="2020-04-21 11:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball confronts Clayton about his fabled Seven Pressure Point Heart Exploding Technique, assuming it’s another one of his outlandish claims</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 11:00:00" d="2020-04-21 11:09:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When Robin needs an archenemy, Starfire generously offers to fill the role and she exceeds expectations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 11:09:00" d="2020-04-21 11:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans trick Starfire into believing in second Christmas with second Santa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 11:25:00" d="2020-04-21 11:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin ignores the rules for a game of jinx</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 11:34:00" d="2020-04-21 11:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When drinking tea turns the other Titans English it's up to Robin to save America from another British invasion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 11:50:00" d="2020-04-21 12:01:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In an attempt to make Karen feel better about a pimple, Zee recounts her embarrassing transition into magichood, and the rift it created between her and her father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 12:01:00" d="2020-04-21 12:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hal’s ex-girlfriend shows up at the Metropolis High homecoming game and goes love-ballistic as the villain Star Sapphire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 12:15:00" d="2020-04-21 12:25:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When a giant monster attacks, the gang fights back with Dr. Fox’s new secret weapon: a mega robot! But after the threat is contained, Unikitty doesn’t</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 12:25:00" d="2020-04-21 12:40:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Master Frown causes Unikitty to have an angry outburst that gets a little too destructive…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 12:40:00" d="2020-04-21 12:50:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Tabes and Charlie team up to find Tabes’ missing dog, Kirk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 12:50:00" d="2020-04-21 13:10:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>On Christmas Eve the Baby Bears defend a video store from getting robbed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 13:10:00" d="2020-04-21 13:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Richard discovers that going into a bank whilst wearing a motorcycle helmet can land you in a lot of trouble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 13:20:00" d="2020-04-21 13:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Leslie's petals begin falling off he feels like his good looks are fading, Gumball and Darwin use everything they know about style and beauty to try and help him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 13:30:00" d="2020-04-21 13:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% The Wattersons fear the worst when they are summoned to a Town Hall meeting, but are surprised when they're offered a new house. Until they discover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 13:40:00" d="2020-04-21 13:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% The Wattersons compete over who has the worst life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 13:55:00" d="2020-04-21 14:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Nicole decides to pay the cable bill in person at Chanax, she leaves specific instructions for Richard to stay in the car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 14:05:00" d="2020-04-21 14:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin are at the convenience store considering playing truant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 14:25:00" d="2020-04-21 14:35:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After Vic loses a wrestling match, V&amp;V journey to the underworld to seek advice from their uncle, a famous wrestler named El Toro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 14:35:00" d="2020-04-21 14:50:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After Vic loses a wrestling match, V&amp;V journey to the underworld to seek advice from their uncle, a famous wrestler named El Toro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 14:50:00" d="2020-04-21 14:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When the Titans get trapped in a giant bottle in their living room they pass the time by reminiscing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 14:59:00" d="2020-04-21 15:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Beast Boy starts making tons of cash thanks to a pyramid scheme and convinces the other Titans to join in</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 15:10:00" d="2020-04-21 15:20:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin finally teaches the other Titans a very valuable lesson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 15:20:00" d="2020-04-21 15:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When her teammates turns evil it's up to Lady Legasus to stop the League of Legs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 15:35:00" d="2020-04-21 15:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Craig has an emergency leaving Kelsey alone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 15:45:00" d="2020-04-21 16:00:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A pillar of the Creek community leaves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 16:00:00" d="2020-04-21 16:10:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When the Sweetypies think the mythical Torbaclaun has come to Pure Heart Valley, Mao Mao tries to prove to them that it isn't real</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 16:10:00" d="2020-04-21 16:25:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mao Mao's legendary, gigantic and critical father visits his son at his new job as sheriff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 16:25:00" d="2020-04-21 16:35:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It's opening night at the Unikingdom Film Festival!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 16:35:00" d="2020-04-21 16:50:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It's Lazy Sunday, and Unikitty and Puppycorn are having such an amazing time hanging out on the couch, they never want to move!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 16:50:00" d="2020-04-21 17:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Justice League holds another talent competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 17:00:00" d="2020-04-21 17:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans must find a way to beat the Hive Five</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 17:15:00" d="2020-04-21 17:26:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Jessica Cruz is convinced she can find the purr-fect forever home for Dexter, a cat who has been deemed unadoptable because he’s basically the worst cat in the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 17:26:00" d="2020-04-21 17:40:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When mean-girl Leslie Willis becomes a social media sensation by posting mean videos, Wonder Woman questions the moral integrity of the World of Man</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 17:40:00" d="2020-04-21 18:00:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang force Fred to relax at a beach house. Unfortunately, when a walking shark attacks the beach community, the gang must solve the mystery without</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 18:00:00" d="2020-04-21 18:25:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Feeling unwell, Scooby is brought to a vet clinic. Soon, the gang finds a werewolf is roaming around the place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 18:25:00" d="2020-04-21 18:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% It's Mother's Day, and Gumball and Darwin discover that Tobias and Banana Joe have both made a card for &quot;The Best Mum in the World&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 18:35:00" d="2020-04-21 18:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Mum has forced Dad to install a password on the computer…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 18:55:00" d="2020-04-21 19:06:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Ms Simian sets out to “befriend” Gumball in order to win a Favourite Teacher Award</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 19:06:00" d="2020-04-21 19:17:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin give Mr Robinson a home and end up saving his marriage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 19:17:00" d="2020-04-21 19:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin help Anais rescue her doll from Tina Rex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 19:30:00" d="2020-04-21 19:40:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After Vic loses a wrestling match, V&amp;V journey to the underworld to seek advice from their uncle, a famous wrestler named El Toro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 19:40:00" d="2020-04-21 19:55:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After Vic loses a wrestling match, V&amp;V journey to the underworld to seek advice from their uncle, a famous wrestler named El Toro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 19:55:00" d="2020-04-21 20:00:00"><n>The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ivandoe and Bert come across a Talking Tree who promises to tell their fortune in exchange for gold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 20:00:00" d="2020-04-21 20:11:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ben, Gwen and Grandpa Max find themselves killing time at the local town library but soon scramble to out manoeuvre Hex as he searches for a hidden ancient artefact</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 20:11:00" d="2020-04-21 20:21:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Team Tennyson enjoy a convention in town but when a costume store employee finds a familiar-looking helmet and tries it on, Ben is faced with the return of Forever Knight!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 20:21:00" d="2020-04-21 20:35:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ben stumbles upon a Xingo arcade game and goes OE-Shock Rock to power it up but when it receives too much juice Xingo leaps out into the real world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 20:35:00" d="2020-04-21 20:45:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% Dan and Wynton meet a strange boy who leads them into an underground maze whe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 20:45:00" d="2020-04-21 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% After a Bakugan field errupts the town kids stampede to get their own Bakugan but when the field is contaminated Lia must save the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 21:00:00" d="2020-04-21 21:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lord Garmadon returns and frees Harumi, who encourages him to “achieve his true potential” by conquering the one thing that has always stood in his way… his son, Lloyd</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 21:25:00" d="2020-04-21 21:45:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The ninja race to save Lloyd, as a more powerful-than-ever Lord Garmadon creates an enormous Colossi to help him rule Ninjago and defeat the ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 21:45:00" d="2020-04-21 22:10:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Emperor Garmadon has taken control of Ninjago City where Lloyd retreats to the shadows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 22:10:00" d="2020-04-21 22:30:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Cole and Young Wu attempt to free their friends, who have been taken captive by a tribe of Dragon Hunters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 22:30:00" d="2020-04-21 22:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Lola has a pigeon phobia. Paging Dr. Angelo and Dr. Sherwood to cure her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 22:40:00" d="2020-04-21 22:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% A new hipster cupcake shop opens across the street from Cathy’s siphoning off all the customers. Angelo and friends come up with strategies to help Cathy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 22:55:00" d="2020-04-21 23:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% In honor of older sisters, Slobber offers free tickets to whomever can make the best short film about their older sister. Angelo is all set</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 23:05:00" d="2020-04-21 23:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo searches for the ultimate object to bring to show and tell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 23:15:00" d="2020-04-21 23:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo’s photo bombs make him a big hit on the internet and he is loving his newfound popularity. Until, Butterfingers starts getting more “likes”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 23:25:00" d="2020-04-21 23:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% The equipment in Coach Zonka’s gym class is deemed a safety hazard so gym class is canceled permanently. Angelo attempts to rally the school to bring back gym class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 23:40:00" d="2020-04-21 23:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Everyone’s favorite skater, Ollie Van Dunk, crashes out in a big contest, loses his mojo, and quits skating. Angelo and friends try to raise his spirits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-21 23:50:00" d="2020-04-22 00:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% When Angelo gets stuck with the chore of painting Geezer’s old broken down fence, he channels his inner Tom Sawyer and manages to convince everyone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 00:05:00" d="2020-04-22 00:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Elmore residents are going missing, and the cause of these disappearances may be closer to home than Gumball and Darwin think</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 00:15:00" d="2020-04-22 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin discover that Tobias is doing way better than them in an online game called Galatrek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 00:30:00" d="2020-04-22 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Rocky suggests that the Elmore Junior High kids skip school, the bus is boarded by criminals who seem to want to teach them the importance of school attendance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 00:40:00" d="2020-04-22 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% As night falls in Elmore, the Moon takes us on a tour through the various dreams -- and nightmares -- of the town’s slumbering inhabitants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 00:50:00" d="2020-04-22 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball is late to meet Penny at the mall, but a series of misunderstandings on the way only delay him further</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 01:00:00" d="2020-04-22 01:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Mom sees Darwin gazing longingly at a fish-tank she thinks their mammalian lifestyle isn’t fulfilling her adopted son and deep down he longs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 01:15:00" d="2020-04-22 01:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% The Parent Teacher Association of Elmore Junior High ban video games, so the kids try and prove that games aren’t a bad influence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 01:25:00" d="2020-04-22 01:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Anais arrives in the bedroom to find a messy crime-scene and her Daisy doll missing. She realises that Gumball and Darwin are the chief suspects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 01:35:00" d="2020-04-22 01:46:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Ms Simian sets out to “befriend” Gumball in order to win a Favourite Teacher Award</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 01:46:00" d="2020-04-22 01:57:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin give Mr Robinson a home and end up saving his marriage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 01:57:00" d="2020-04-22 02:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin help Anais rescue her doll from Tina Rex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 02:10:00" d="2020-04-22 02:35:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% As Lloyd and Harumi search the Oni Temple for the last mask, the ninja are taken hostage and discover Princess Harumi’s true intentions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 02:35:00" d="2020-04-22 03:00:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The ninja race to save Lloyd, as a more powerful-than-ever Lord Garmadon creates an enormous Colossi to help him rule Ninjago and defeat the ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 03:00:00" d="2020-04-22 03:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Cole and Young Wu attempt to free their friends, who have been taken captive by a tribe of Dragon Hunters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 03:25:00" d="2020-04-22 03:50:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lloyd must find his voice as he leads a small resistance to capture the airwaves in Ninjago City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 03:50:00" d="2020-04-22 04:01:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Ms Simian sets out to “befriend” Gumball in order to win a Favourite Teacher Award</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 04:01:00" d="2020-04-22 04:12:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin give Mr Robinson a home and end up saving his marriage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 04:12:00" d="2020-04-22 04:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin help Anais rescue her doll from Tina Rex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 04:25:00" d="2020-04-22 04:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Elmore residents are going missing, and the cause of these disappearances may be closer to home than Gumball and Darwin think</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 04:35:00" d="2020-04-22 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% Gumball and Darwin discover that Tobias is doing way better than them in an online game called Galatrek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-22 04:50:00" d="2020-04-22 05:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% When Rocky suggests that the Elmore Junior High kids skip school, the bus is boarded by criminals who seem to want to teach them the importance of school attendance</k>  </p>
</a>
