<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="107" t="2020-04-16 04:29:32"><p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 05:00:00" d="2020-04-23 05:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball saved himself from being trapped in The Void, just in time. The remote has now taken Gumball back to the beginning of that disastrous day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 05:10:00" d="2020-04-23 05:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Fed up with having to listen to Molly's long, tedious anecdotes, Gumball and Darwin try to teach her how to make them sound more exciting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 05:20:00" d="2020-04-23 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin put Anais' new friend, Josh, through a series of tests, to see if he's good enough for their sister</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 05:35:00" d="2020-04-23 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are convinced it's a day when nothing interesting is happening. But as they walk around Elmore, it is apparent exciting things</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 05:45:00" d="2020-04-23 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Gumball and Darwin accidentally find a sinister secret manifesto on Alan's memory stick, they decide they have to foil his plan for total world domination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 06:00:00" d="2020-04-23 06:11:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Tennysons come across a naturally formed pit with no bottom. Ben fights his better judgment to jump in until Kevin 11 shows up and goads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 06:11:00" d="2020-04-23 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Team Tennyson trade campfire stories in an anthology-style series that pits Ben against his arch-rival, Kevin 11, and teaches him the power of imagination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 06:25:00" d="2020-04-23 06:36:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin’s wish comes true when they suddenly turn into men</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 06:36:00" d="2020-04-23 06:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball discovers the difference between a “date” and a “pet’s funeral”. he hard way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 06:50:00" d="2020-04-23 07:00:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>An explosive loner and his slacker best friend are waylaid from their journey into legend, only to find that their story is just beginning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 07:00:00" d="2020-04-23 07:15:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Mao Mao underestimates enemy and friend alike, it almost costs him the entire kingdom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 07:15:00" d="2020-04-23 07:24:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% A glimpse inside each Titan's dream world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 07:24:00" d="2020-04-23 07:40:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Using a grandma voice, Cyborg makes the others dress warmly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 07:40:00" d="2020-04-23 07:49:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The other Titans are trying to stop a cow-stealing UFO</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 07:49:00" d="2020-04-23 08:05:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans tell their slightly inaccurate origin stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 08:05:00" d="2020-04-23 08:14:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin dabbles with magic, ignoring Raven's warning that he will anger the magic god</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 08:14:00" d="2020-04-23 08:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When Robin gets frustrated with the Titans' disobedience he turns to. uppets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 08:35:00" d="2020-04-23 08:55:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang’s trip to be bayou is ruined by a shambling Swamp Beast that’s scaring away anyone who dares to enter its soggy domain!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 08:55:00" d="2020-04-23 09:20:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang hits the ski slopes, but the fun is soon interrupted by the appearance of an evil Snowman Monster eager to scare all trespassers off his mountain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 09:20:00" d="2020-04-23 09:30:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After Vic loses a wrestling match, V&amp;V journey to the underworld to seek advice from their uncle, a famous wrestler named El Toro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 09:30:00" d="2020-04-23 09:45:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After Vic loses a wrestling match, V&amp;V journey to the underworld to seek advice from their uncle, a famous wrestler named El Toro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 09:45:00" d="2020-04-23 09:55:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% Dan and Wynton meet a strange boy who leads them into an underground maze whe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 09:55:00" d="2020-04-23 10:10:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% After a Bakugan field errupts the town kids stampede to get their own Bakugan but when the field is contaminated Lia must save the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 10:10:00" d="2020-04-23 10:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball, Darwin and Anais find themselves plunged into an RPG version of Elmore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 10:20:00" d="2020-04-23 10:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Wattersons transform their house into The Big House</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 10:40:00" d="2020-04-23 10:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% It's Mother's Day, and Gumball and Darwin discover that Tobias and Banana Joe have both made a card for &quot;The Best Mum in the World&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 10:50:00" d="2020-04-23 11:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Mum has forced Dad to install a password on the computer…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 11:00:00" d="2020-04-23 11:09:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When Robin, Cyborg, and Beast Boy get trapped in an elevator the limits of their friendship are tested, while Starfire and Raven bond with a supervillain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 11:09:00" d="2020-04-23 11:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans overuse Raven's dark magic, causing unintended consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 11:25:00" d="2020-04-23 11:34:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin introduces the other Titans to a money maker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 11:34:00" d="2020-04-23 11:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% To prove his point about classic superhero cartoons Control Freak sends the Titans to a former version of Teen Titans Go!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 11:50:00" d="2020-04-23 12:01:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Everything is going well for Kara Danvers both as a teen and a superhero until she starts taking the blame for things she didn't do</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 12:01:00" d="2020-04-23 12:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When the local mall is attached by the monstrous supervillain Giganta, Karen Beecher discovers that tiny Bumblebee might be the only one small enough to save the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 12:15:00" d="2020-04-23 12:25:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang bring home a tiny creature named Pet Pet, but Richard wants proof that they are responsible owners. When Pet Pet runs away, Unikitty pretends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 12:25:00" d="2020-04-23 12:40:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Unikitty and Puppycorn are invited to Master Frown and Brock's apartment for a dinner party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 12:40:00" d="2020-04-23 12:50:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Bears get pizza at Papa Bear's Pizza Cave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 12:50:00" d="2020-04-23 13:10:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In order to get some sleep, the Bears help an annoying bird find a new mate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 13:10:00" d="2020-04-23 13:21:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Tobias compete for Penny's affection by putting on the lamest duel in history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 13:21:00" d="2020-04-23 13:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin learn that it isn't wise to upset Hector, Elmore's resident Giant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 13:30:00" d="2020-04-23 13:41:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Nicole seeks to develop a sense of ambition in Gumball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 13:41:00" d="2020-04-23 13:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When everyone in the Watterson household wants to watch their favourite show at the same time, a massive fight breaks out over control of the television remote</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 13:55:00" d="2020-04-23 14:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Channel 6 Elmore News has all the top local stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 14:05:00" d="2020-04-23 14:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin find themselves in serious trouble when they agree to everything the new kid in school says. The truth is they can't understand a word that he says</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 14:25:00" d="2020-04-23 14:36:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Vic &amp; Val start making good money from selling churros at the taco stand, their lust for stuff makes them do dirty tricks to take out their competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 14:36:00" d="2020-04-23 14:50:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Vic accidently unleashes evil bats from a cave, it's up to the boys and Don to protect the town, but Vic's know-it-all attitude keeps getting in the way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 14:50:00" d="2020-04-23 15:00:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% After seeing a pair of cool dudes on rollerblades Robin tries to be just like them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 15:00:00" d="2020-04-23 15:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin tries to teach the Titans valuable history lessons but the others co-opt his stories and spin them into their own twisted yarns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 15:10:00" d="2020-04-23 15:19:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The other Titans train Beast Boy in the ways of the ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 15:19:00" d="2020-04-23 15:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans are reckless with their money and health much to the detriment of their future selves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 15:35:00" d="2020-04-23 15:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Craig discovers that the Honeysuckle Rangers have snuck into his side of the Creek to steal his most prized possession</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 15:45:00" d="2020-04-23 16:00:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Craig can't go to the Creek he and his mom decide to build the biggest blanket fort in the world!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 16:00:00" d="2020-04-23 16:10:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Mao Mao gets hungry for the perfect adventure Adorabat tells a white lie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 16:10:00" d="2020-04-23 16:25:00"><n>Mao Mao: Heroes of Pure Heart</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mao Mao's desire to be a legend drives him to keep topping himself. But how much is enough?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 16:25:00" d="2020-04-23 16:35:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>You're watching the Unikingdom News Show Super Good Morning Time Program Action Information Show, a variety news program put on (badly) by Unikitty and the gang!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 16:35:00" d="2020-04-23 16:50:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Unikitty and the gang discover a gross bug in the castle, they desperately want it gone for good, but Unikitty refuses to allow them to squish it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 16:50:00" d="2020-04-23 16:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The gang agrees to babysit Silkie, but then loses him; meanwhile, Silkie has a telenovela adventure south of the border</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 16:59:00" d="2020-04-23 17:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Beast Boy takes over as Alpha male of the Titans when he is in Gorilla-mode and Robin has to figure out how to get back on top</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 17:15:00" d="2020-04-23 17:26:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After an embarrassing incident ruins Barbara Gordon’s reputation, rather than owning it, she decides it’s easier to harness The Flash’s ability to travel back in time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 17:26:00" d="2020-04-23 17:40:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Supergirl always relies on her strength, but she'll need more than brawn to stop brainy Catwoman from stealing valuable gems from the local science museum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 17:40:00" d="2020-04-23 18:00:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While on a trip to New York, Scooby and the gang find themselves taking part in a dog show competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 18:00:00" d="2020-04-23 18:25:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Scooby and his friends decide to go on a train trip. But they learn that pets are not allowed in the main carriages</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 18:25:00" d="2020-04-23 18:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball receives a scare-email from a freaky ghost and decides to ignore it, despite Darwin's advice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 18:35:00" d="2020-04-23 18:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Vice Principal Brown gives Gumball and Darwin the ancient school hamster, Chris Morris, to look after for the weekend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 18:55:00" d="2020-04-23 19:06:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin accidentally create a loveable monster that eats their family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 19:06:00" d="2020-04-23 19:17:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is embarrassed when Mum comes to school to spend some “quality time”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 19:17:00" d="2020-04-23 19:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball’s magic tinfoil helmet threatens to tear the Watterson family apart!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 19:30:00" d="2020-04-23 19:41:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Vic &amp; Val start making good money from selling churros at the taco stand, their lust for stuff makes them do dirty tricks to take out their competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 19:41:00" d="2020-04-23 19:55:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Vic accidently unleashes evil bats from a cave, it's up to the boys and Don to protect the town, but Vic's know-it-all attitude keeps getting in the way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 19:55:00" d="2020-04-23 20:00:00"><n>The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ivandoe and Bert come across a tiny miserable prince in the forest. He needs a kiss to transform him back into the beautiful bullfrog he once was</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 20:00:00" d="2020-04-23 20:11:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Team Tennyson's quest for the best pizza in Rome leads them to the Bugg Brothers and their latest culinary caper, complete with stolen recipes and kidnapped chefs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 20:11:00" d="2020-04-23 20:21:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In Rome, Gwen takes Team Tennyson on a self-guided tour of the many ancient sites when a distracted Ben accidentally stumbles upon Queen Bee’s monumental heist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 20:21:00" d="2020-04-23 20:35:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>As Max attempts to get Ben and Gwen to the Four Corners Monument before sunset, an ominous fog bank engulfs the roadway</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 20:35:00" d="2020-04-23 20:45:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% We are introduced to Shun's mysterious backstory, his relationship with his industrialist father and desire for a closer knit family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 20:45:00" d="2020-04-23 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% Dan and Shun butt heads on how best to make the AO a real team amidst growing threats includin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 21:00:00" d="2020-04-23 21:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lloyd turns the tables on Harumi to take his father’s power away, and the Ninja learn what it takes to be a Dragon Hunter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 21:25:00" d="2020-04-23 21:45:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lloyd and his team plot to take control of the Oni Titan. Meanwhile in the First Realm, the Ninja fall into Iron Baron’s clutches and an old master returns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 21:45:00" d="2020-04-23 22:10:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% When Iron Baron forces Wu to retrieve the Dragon Armor, things don’t go as planned. In Ninjago, Lloyd can only endure so much as he holds onto hope for the Ninjas’ return</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 22:10:00" d="2020-04-23 22:30:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The Ninja finally return home and unite to stop Emperor Garmadon, forcing Lloyd to make a decision that will forever change Ninjago</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 22:30:00" d="2020-04-23 22:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% When Dad surprises the family with a brand new Electra smart home device everyone loves it at first, then Dad gets hooked and Angelo and Elena</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 22:40:00" d="2020-04-23 22:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% After failing an online “best friends” quiz Sherwood and Angelo drift apart. Angelo discovers the quiz was fake and tries to repair his relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 22:55:00" d="2020-04-23 23:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo enters a pie baking contest with his Dad as his partner until the two have creative differences and go it alone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 23:05:00" d="2020-04-23 23:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo and Lola start a campaign to help Sherwood get voted “most likely to succeed” by his classmates instead of Tracy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 23:15:00" d="2020-04-23 23:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Dad takes a parenting class which works! Now he has more control of his kids. Angelo infiltrates the parenting class (posing as an adult) to learn Dad’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 23:25:00" d="2020-04-23 23:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo comes up with unique inventions to win “Snake Pit” a TV show where you pitch your business idea to local “business tycoons” hoping to get them to invest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 23:40:00" d="2020-04-23 23:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% After making a bet that their life is harder, Angelo and Mr. Foot trade places. Angelo becomes the teacher, and Mr. Foot the unruly student</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-23 23:50:00" d="2020-04-24 00:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% After taking a career test that claims to predict your future and receiving disappointing results, Angelo and friends set out to change their destinies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-24 00:05:00" d="2020-04-24 00:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Nicole remembers the day she first met Richard, and the different choices she could have made</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-24 00:15:00" d="2020-04-24 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball learns that the Wattersons have been stealing Mr Robinson’s wi-fi for years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-24 00:30:00" d="2020-04-24 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is livid when an online test keeps telling him that his character-type is &quot;The Loser&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-24 00:40:00" d="2020-04-24 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Rocky is trying to find love with the help of the latest dating app…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-24 00:50:00" d="2020-04-24 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin give Bobert specific instructions to ensure he acts in a safe and responsible manner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-24 01:00:00" d="2020-04-24 01:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Nicole is angry at Richard for forgetting her special day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-24 01:15:00" d="2020-04-24 01:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Channel 6 Elmore News has all the top hard-hitting local stories. Newscaster Kip Schlezinger is the man to bring you the latest news, even when there is nothing to report</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-24 01:25:00" d="2020-04-24 01:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Nicole encourages Gumball to do what comes naturally. reak stuff!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-24 01:35:00" d="2020-04-24 01:46:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin accidentally create a loveable monster that eats their family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-24 01:46:00" d="2020-04-24 01:57:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is embarrassed when Mum comes to school to spend some “quality time”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-24 01:57:00" d="2020-04-24 02:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball’s magic tinfoil helmet threatens to tear the Watterson family apart!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-24 02:10:00" d="2020-04-24 02:35:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The headquarters to the resistance is breached and Lloyd scrambles to avoid capture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-24 02:35:00" d="2020-04-24 03:00:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lloyd and his team plot to take control of the Oni Titan. Meanwhile in the First Realm, the Ninja fall into Iron Baron’s clutches and an old master returns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-24 03:00:00" d="2020-04-24 03:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The Ninja finally return home and unite to stop Emperor Garmadon, forcing Lloyd to make a decision that will forever change Ninjago</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-24 03:25:00" d="2020-04-24 03:50:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% As Ninjago City rebuilds, Faith arrives with a dire warning: the Oni have returned and are destroying the realms, one by one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-24 03:50:00" d="2020-04-24 04:01:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin accidentally create a loveable monster that eats their family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-24 04:01:00" d="2020-04-24 04:12:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is embarrassed when Mum comes to school to spend some “quality time”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-24 04:12:00" d="2020-04-24 04:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball’s magic tinfoil helmet threatens to tear the Watterson family apart!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-24 04:25:00" d="2020-04-24 04:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Nicole remembers the day she first met Richard, and the different choices she could have made</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-24 04:35:00" d="2020-04-24 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball learns that the Wattersons have been stealing Mr Robinson’s wi-fi for years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-04-24 04:50:00" d="2020-04-24 05:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is livid when an online test keeps telling him that his character-type is &quot;The Loser&quot;</k>  </p>
</a>
