<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="103" t="2020-05-15 04:46:52"><p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 05:00:00" d="2020-05-22 05:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The boys manage to lose Polly in the blink of an eye</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 05:10:00" d="2020-05-22 05:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Nicole has decided it's time to throw out the family's refrigerator</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 05:20:00" d="2020-05-22 05:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Mr. Robinson accidentally lets his feelings slip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 05:35:00" d="2020-05-22 05:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% It's Halloween in Elmore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 05:45:00" d="2020-05-22 06:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball's old BFF Fuzzy, turns up on his doorstep</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 06:00:00" d="2020-05-22 06:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After a series of reoccurring nightmares affect his sleep, Ben refuses to open up to Max and Gwen about what's bothering him. But they realize Zombozo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 06:10:00" d="2020-05-22 06:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Team Tennyson go international in the Omni-Copter. The first stop is for a hike in the Scottish Highlands but the weather is foggy and that means</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 06:25:00" d="2020-05-22 06:36:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball tries to save Darwin from being kissed by a girl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 06:36:00" d="2020-05-22 06:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Principal Brown tries to “fix” Gumball’s dysfunctional family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 06:50:00" d="2020-05-22 07:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Dad discovers that Granny Jojo and Louie plan to get married and move to Florida. To stop this happening he adopts Louie so that he can forbid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 07:00:00" d="2020-05-22 07:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% After they receive an extravagant invitation to Masami's birthday party, Gumball and Darwin are anxious to find just the right gift for her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 07:15:00" d="2020-05-22 07:24:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Needing a hero with shrinking powers but forgetting about Bumblebee Robin invites The Atom to join their fight against the Brain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 07:24:00" d="2020-05-22 07:40:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When yet another crime alert interrupts their relaxation the Titans decide to become villains and do whatever they want</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 07:40:00" d="2020-05-22 07:51:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The ThunderCats have gotten so good at defeating the Mutants of Plun-Darr that it’s basically become routine. That all changes with the arrival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 07:51:00" d="2020-05-22 08:05:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lion-O is playing with Snarf and doesn’t have a care in the world. Unfortunately he’s accidentally stomping on the miniature village of the Micrits!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 08:05:00" d="2020-05-22 08:16:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Axel must help Sarge and Bobbie learn to walk in each other's shoes - literally - after Luka unwittingly switches the toys' heads!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 08:16:00" d="2020-05-22 08:35:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Axel and his toys deploy the Joyride in a ship to ship battle against Dr. Nautilus who has punctured a water main to flood the sewers and established</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 08:35:00" d="2020-05-22 08:55:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>To solve the mystery of a ghostly performer haunting her former venue, the Gang has to pretend to be a rock band themselves!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 08:55:00" d="2020-05-22 09:20:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fred is excited to visit The Vault - a high security prison that no convict has ever escaped from</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 09:20:00" d="2020-05-22 10:10:00"><n>Craig of the Creek: The Other Side</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Craig, Kelsey and JP must journey past the Overpass into uncharted territory - the Other Side of the Creek. / Craig, Kelsey and JP must journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 10:10:00" d="2020-05-22 10:21:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are taught confusing lessons about honesty by the school councillor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 10:21:00" d="2020-05-22 10:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Darwin is sent away to a government institute for geniuses. Yes. Really</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 10:40:00" d="2020-05-22 10:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Rocky suggests that the Elmore Junior High kids skip school, the bus is boarded by criminals who seem to want to teach them the importance of school attendance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 10:50:00" d="2020-05-22 11:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% As night falls in Elmore, the Moon takes us on a tour through the various dreams -- and nightmares -- of the town’s slumbering inhabitants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 11:00:00" d="2020-05-22 11:09:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans immerse themselves in different video game worlds./ Rose Wilson escapes from prison defeating the Titans with cool one liners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 11:09:00" d="2020-05-22 11:25:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans learn about the magic of soccer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 11:25:00" d="2020-05-22 11:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin learns that avocados are a super food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 11:35:00" d="2020-05-22 11:50:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Robin vows to never wash his hand again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 11:50:00" d="2020-05-22 12:00:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When she stumbles across a villainous plot - and all the other heroes are indisposed - Bumblebee must rise to the occasion… despite being the smallest of the bunch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 12:00:00" d="2020-05-22 12:15:00"><n>DC Super Hero Girls</n><t>Q</t>    <k>With her boss at the Burrito Bucket eager to fire her, Babs is torn between her role as a Super Hero and a dutiful employee when a bank robbery breaks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 12:15:00" d="2020-05-22 12:25:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A super-grumpy volcano appears in the kingdom, so Unikitty takes the gang on an epic quest to cheer it up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 12:25:00" d="2020-05-22 12:40:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Brock drags Master Frown along to join him in following his dream, to become the Flyer on a cheerleading team</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 12:40:00" d="2020-05-22 12:50:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Bears switch bedrooms for the night and get a glimpse of the living space of one of their brothers. But as they go deeper, hidden secrets are revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 12:50:00" d="2020-05-22 13:10:00"><n>We Bare Bears</n><t>Q</t>    <k>To recover a missing package, The Bears get help from Ranger Tabes, an eccentric forest ranger. But her overblown sense of justice might</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 13:10:00" d="2020-05-22 13:20:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Darwin asks for his advice on hats, Gumball suddenly can’t speak and offends Darwin. Darwin is convinced Gumball said he had a fat head</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 13:20:00" d="2020-05-22 13:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When she has no one to share her lunch with, Jamie realises she needs a sweetheart. Darwin's the only one who doesn’t flee immediately, so he and Jamie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 13:30:00" d="2020-05-22 13:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin are reading Anais’ diary when they discover that her relationship with her new friend seems a bit one-sided</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 13:40:00" d="2020-05-22 13:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Bobert finds he is infected with a virus called love.exe he asks Gumball and Darwin to give him a definition for the word ‘love’</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 13:55:00" d="2020-05-22 14:05:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Darwin asks Gumball to teach him how to skate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 14:05:00" d="2020-05-22 14:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin follow Nicole to the Rainbow Factory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 14:25:00" d="2020-05-22 14:36:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A Nagual transforms Vic and Val into animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 14:36:00" d="2020-05-22 14:50:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vic wants to win the cash prize for a dance contest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 14:50:00" d="2020-05-22 14:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Needing a hero with shrinking powers but forgetting about Bumblebee Robin invites The Atom to join their fight against the Brain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 14:59:00" d="2020-05-22 15:10:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When yet another crime alert interrupts their relaxation the Titans decide to become villains and do whatever they want</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 15:10:00" d="2020-05-22 15:20:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% When a computer dating program matches Beast Boy to Raven, he tries wooing her to disastrous effect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 15:20:00" d="2020-05-22 15:35:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% Raven shows the rest of the Titans that books can be fun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 15:35:00" d="2020-05-22 15:45:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Craig dines at the restaurant where his older brother works and orders up a plate of REVENGE. and lots of breadsticks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 15:45:00" d="2020-05-22 16:00:00"><n>Craig of the Creek</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Craig's determined to get his grandad a cicada shell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 16:00:00" d="2020-05-22 16:11:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Axel and the team try to figure out what Sarge Charge's secret weapon is they get ejected from the house by his newly upgraded security system</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 16:11:00" d="2020-05-22 16:25:00"><n>Power Players</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Axel must team up with Bearbarian to stop Madcap from transforming Luka's stuffed bear collection into an invincible army</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 16:25:00" d="2020-05-22 16:34:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After being rudely interrupted by Bim Bom during her daily morning song, an angry Unikitty takes the advice of her friends and writes down her feelings into a letter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 16:34:00" d="2020-05-22 16:50:00"><n>Unikitty</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It's Halloween again and the gang is desperately trying to tell the scariest story to a couple of trick or treaters. Each of the characters takes turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 16:50:00" d="2020-05-22 16:59:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% So she isn't left out of inside jokes the Titans time travel to past adventures and insert Bumblebee into their memories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 16:59:00" d="2020-05-22 17:15:00"><n>Teen Titans Go! - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>52% The Titans try to remember how to be superheroes in order to stop The Brain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 17:15:00" d="2020-05-22 17:26:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lion-O and the other ThunderCats are thrilled to meet a new Thunderian! She’s good at fighting robots and most importantly thinks Lion-O and his Sword</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 17:26:00" d="2020-05-22 17:40:00"><n>ThunderCats Roar!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Snarf leaves the Cats' Lair to get a needed vacation by transforming into a normal cat and hanging out with a nice old lady on a farm! But his relaxing day is threatened</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 17:40:00" d="2020-05-22 18:00:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Just like every year for Halloween, Fred refuses to leave the house. He believes that no mysteries will be solved on that day and that nothing will go as planned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 18:00:00" d="2020-05-22 18:25:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Scooby and the gang are in Japan where they find out that Velma is a real star. Everyone dresses up like her! But soon, Daphne steals the limelight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 18:25:00" d="2020-05-22 18:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When Rob purchases a universal remote from the Awesome Store, he discovers he can control the universe. He rewinds into the past and remembers Gumball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 18:35:00" d="2020-05-22 18:55:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Whilst Gumball and Darwin make fun of Mum and Dad for being old, their voices start to break</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 18:55:00" d="2020-05-22 19:06:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is desperate to avoid a late fee on the rented dvd he accidentally destroyed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 19:06:00" d="2020-05-22 19:17:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Tobias compete for Penny's affection by putting on the lamest duel in history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 19:17:00" d="2020-05-22 19:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin learn that it isn't wise to upset Hector, Elmore's resident Giant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 19:30:00" d="2020-05-22 19:41:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A Nagual transforms Vic and Val into animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 19:41:00" d="2020-05-22 19:55:00"><n>Victor and Valentino</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vic wants to win the cash prize for a dance contest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 19:55:00" d="2020-05-22 20:00:00"><n>The Heroic Quest of the Valiant Prince Ivandoe</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ivandoe comes face to face with a cocky young swan prince. To settle their differences they engage in a good old-fashioned Prince-Off</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 20:00:00" d="2020-05-22 20:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ben hops into the Rustbuggy for a driving lesson along the sand dunes of Cape Cod but he takes a freaky switchback turn when the Rustbuggy is mutated into a motor-monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 20:10:00" d="2020-05-22 20:20:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Team Tennyson travel to the Chrysalen Institute for some hot yoga and good vibes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 20:20:00" d="2020-05-22 20:35:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ben turns his attention to one upping Gwen at Space Camp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 20:35:00" d="2020-05-22 21:00:00"><n>Bakugan: Battle Planet</n><t>Q</t>    <k>48% The Hide Matrix goes crazy and a simple AO training mission turns into a complicated rampage./After the loss of their HQ, the AO are a little off</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 21:00:00" d="2020-05-22 21:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Zane’s near demise at the hands of Mr. E forces the ninja to flee aboard the Bounty, where they discover a message Zane intercepted may reveal the hidden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 21:25:00" d="2020-05-22 21:45:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% As Lloyd and Harumi venture deep into Primeval’s Eye in search of the third Oni Mask, the ninja attempt to fix the Bounty and make a startling discovery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 21:45:00" d="2020-05-22 22:10:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% As Lloyd and Harumi search the Oni Temple for the last mask, the ninja are taken hostage and discover Princess Harumi’s true intentions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 22:10:00" d="2020-05-22 22:30:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The ninja appeal to the police commissioner of Ninjago in an effort to help save Lloyd and thwart Harumi’s efforts to resurrect the evil Lord Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 22:30:00" d="2020-05-22 22:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% In honor of older sisters, Slobber offers free tickets to whomever can make the best short film about their older sister. Angelo is all set</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 22:40:00" d="2020-05-22 22:55:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo searches for the ultimate object to bring to show and tell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 22:55:00" d="2020-05-22 23:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo’s photo bombs make him a big hit on the internet and he is loving his newfound popularity. Until, Butterfingers starts getting more “likes”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 23:05:00" d="2020-05-22 23:15:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% The equipment in Coach Zonka’s gym class is deemed a safety hazard so gym class is canceled permanently. Angelo attempts to rally the school to bring back gym class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 23:15:00" d="2020-05-22 23:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Everyone’s favorite skater, Ollie Van Dunk, crashes out in a big contest, loses his mojo, and quits skating. Angelo and friends try to raise his spirits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 23:25:00" d="2020-05-22 23:40:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% When Angelo gets stuck with the chore of painting Geezer’s old broken down fence, he channels his inner Tom Sawyer and manages to convince everyone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 23:40:00" d="2020-05-22 23:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Angelo and friends make a TV show pilot called “Angelo Rules,” with Lola producing, Sherwood directing, Angelo writing, and Butterfingers playing Angelo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-22 23:50:00" d="2020-05-23 00:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 4</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% After Mom cuts off Angelo’s videogame time Angelo attempts to change her mind. He sets out to prove to her that gaming is an important skillset</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 00:05:00" d="2020-05-23 00:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin's clothes go missing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 00:15:00" d="2020-05-23 00:30:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When everything goes wrong in Darwin's life, he begins to suspect that Gumball's bad influence might be to blame</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 00:30:00" d="2020-05-23 00:40:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Darwin asks Gumball to teach him how to skate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 00:40:00" d="2020-05-23 00:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The students find their world turned upside down</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 00:50:00" d="2020-05-23 01:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Whilst Gumball and Darwin make fun of Mum and Dad for being old, their voices start to break</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 01:00:00" d="2020-05-23 01:15:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Sarah, the new kid in school, is Gumball and Darwin's number one, slightly obsessive, fan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 01:15:00" d="2020-05-23 01:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The new coach at Elmore High stands up to Jamie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 01:25:00" d="2020-05-23 01:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin make their Dad believe in magic again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 01:35:00" d="2020-05-23 01:45:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball seeks justice when Banana Joe chews Darwin's pen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 01:45:00" d="2020-05-23 01:56:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Darwin develops a texting addiction when he and Gumball get their first cell phone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 01:56:00" d="2020-05-23 02:10:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Richard gets a job as a pizza delivery man, which worries Nicole when, at the same time, strange things begin to occur around the neighbourhood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 02:10:00" d="2020-05-23 02:35:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Emperor Garmadon has taken control of Ninjago City where Lloyd retreats to the shadows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 02:35:00" d="2020-05-23 03:00:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lloyd and the rebels celebrate their successful strike against Emperor Garmadon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 03:00:00" d="2020-05-23 03:25:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% As Lloyd unmasks Mystake for who she truly is, Emperor Garmadon embraces Harumi as his daughter of darkness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 03:25:00" d="2020-05-23 03:50:00"><n>NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lloyd turns the tables on Harumi to take his father’s power away, and the Ninja learn what it takes to be a Dragon Hunter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 03:50:00" d="2020-05-23 04:01:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball is desperate to avoid a late fee on the rented dvd he accidentally destroyed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 04:01:00" d="2020-05-23 04:12:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Tobias compete for Penny's affection by putting on the lamest duel in history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 04:12:00" d="2020-05-23 04:25:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin learn that it isn't wise to upset Hector, Elmore's resident Giant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 04:25:00" d="2020-05-23 04:35:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gumball and Darwin's clothes go missing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 04:35:00" d="2020-05-23 04:50:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% When everything goes wrong in Darwin's life, he begins to suspect that Gumball's bad influence might be to blame</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2020-05-23 04:50:00" d="2020-05-23 05:00:00"><n>The Amazing World of Gumball - Elements</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Darwin asks Gumball to teach him how to skate</k>  </p>
</a>
