<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="117" t="2021-07-10 04:56:27"><p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 05:05:00" d="2021-07-17 05:15:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 2016 II (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Sound and the Furry
As Team Tennyson leaves the Frozen Man Festival, Lord Decibel takes center stage to threaten the festival-goers, creating</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 05:15:00" d="2021-07-17 05:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 2016 II (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>King Koil
Ben and Gwen spend the day volunteering at Repto Ranch and come face to face with King Koil, but need to quickly overcome their fear of snakes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 05:25:00" d="2021-07-17 05:35:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Baku-Gear
The Awesome Brawlers are excited over their discovery of Baku-Gear, and want to get some footage of it in action. While they’re filming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 05:35:00" d="2021-07-17 05:50:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bakugan Rock!
Baku-gear has shown up twice for Dan and Drago and it’s starting to eat away at the other awesome brawlers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 05:50:00" d="2021-07-17 05:55:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Home Havoc
Magoo can't find the book that Linda lent him and he's ready to turn the house upside down to find it. The problem is that he</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 05:55:00" d="2021-07-17 06:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pinkbeard's Treasure
Magoo hunting for Pinkbeard’s treasure mistakes the park for an island. Fizz and Weasel are there selling ice cream that never falls on the ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 06:05:00" d="2021-07-17 06:10:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mistaken Identity
At the supermarket, Magoo mixes his shopping cart up with a baby stroller. Fizz decides to save the toddler and become a media star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 06:10:00" d="2021-07-17 06:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hamster Fishing
Fizz is at the municipal pool, he wants to revolution the world of sub-marine hairdressing!But Magoo, thinking that he is actually fishing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 06:25:00" d="2021-07-17 06:30:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Whiter Than White
Magoo thinking he’s at the laundromat wanders into a candy factory where Fizz and Weasel are creating a bubblegum that makes Fizz-shaped bubbles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 06:30:00" d="2021-07-17 06:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Poolwatch!
Magoo thinks that the whole neighborhood has been flooded when in fact he is just at the local swimming pool. He starts trying to rescue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 06:40:00" d="2021-07-17 06:45:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hibernafizz
Magoo comes across Fizz encased in ice and thinks he has found a prehistoric man. He thaws him out and acts like a Cro-Magnon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 06:45:00" d="2021-07-17 07:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fizz Tower
Thinking he’s hunting down a rat in his attic Magoo finds himself on the theme park devoted to…the glory of Fizz. He decides to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 07:00:00" d="2021-07-17 07:25:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% The Norse Case. 
The gang goes on a camping trip, although they can't really agree on why. Fred's desire for the gang to get in touch with their natural</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 07:25:00" d="2021-07-17 07:55:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% The People vs. Fred Jones
Fred is on trial, convicted of being the real mastermind behind all the mysteries he's solved. With the help of his defence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 07:55:00" d="2021-07-17 08:05:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek II (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% The Children Of…
Craig has tried to convince his family to get a dog for years but has never been successful, but he may have a chance if he follows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 08:05:00" d="2021-07-17 08:20:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek II (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ferret Quest
The kids are on the search for an elusive ferret in the Creek. Kelsey unites her friends Stacks and Wildernessa to find it, but worries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 08:20:00" d="2021-07-17 08:30:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek II (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Into The Overpast
Craig and The Green Poncho travel to the Other Side of the Creek where Craig learns Green Poncho's shocking origin story</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 08:30:00" d="2021-07-17 08:50:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek II (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Time Capsule
Worried he'll one day forget all his favorite memories, Craig creates a time capsule to remember them all</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 08:50:00" d="2021-07-17 09:00:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek II (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Beyond The Rapids
Resident creek scientist Wren enlists Craig to voyage through dangerous waters in search of a path to the Ocean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 09:00:00" d="2021-07-17 09:15:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek II (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Jinxening
Craig, Kelsey and JP help a kid who's been jinxed and can't talk, but they soon come to regret it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 09:15:00" d="2021-07-17 09:25:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek II (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% Voyage of the…
When a rainy day keeps Craig inside, he uses his toys and imagination to create his own Creek adventure in Craig of the Creek's first musical episode!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 09:25:00" d="2021-07-17 09:55:00"><n>The Other Side: The Tournament</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Tournament - Hoping to win a special prize for his Dad's birthday, Craig and his friends compete in a tournament on the Other Side of the Creek!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 09:55:00" d="2021-07-17 10:05:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>For a Few Duncans More
While trying to photocopy his butt on Chef?s fancy new copier Duncan accidentally makes an entire other Duncan. Great! This other Duncan can do all the school stuff while the real Duncan chills. But things go badly when the other Duncan decides to copy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 10:05:00" d="2021-07-17 10:20:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>He Who Wears the Clown
After trying on the nose of a clown Owen learns that this is how clowns are made and he is stuck as a clown until he can trick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 10:20:00" d="2021-07-17 10:30:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Us 'R' Toys
When Chef brings in some old toys from his childhood he, Duncan and Gwen, each get magically sucked into one of the toys and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 10:30:00" d="2021-07-17 10:50:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dream Worriers
Izzy forgets the ending to her most amazing dream of all time, so the kids travel into her mind to find out what happened</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 10:50:00" d="2021-07-17 10:55:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lemmings Board
A strange object is delivered to the Ranger's cabin: an over-board! It's a latest generation skateboard which levitates above the ground without wheels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 10:55:00" d="2021-07-17 11:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ice and Bears
The Lemmings encounter a white bear which has drifted all the way to them on a chunk of ice which is slowly melting. The bear makes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 11:00:00" d="2021-07-17 11:10:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% High-Risk Driving
After studying a magazine advertisement with a couple standing in front of an SUV, Grizzy imagines that if only he had</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 11:10:00" d="2021-07-17 11:20:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Fountain of Bear Youth
The Lemmings discover a strange pond in a Native American grotto that has the power to rejuvenate anyone who dips in it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 11:20:00" d="2021-07-17 11:30:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Predictions
While chasing the Lemmings, who stole his jar of chocolate spread, Grizzy crashes into an arcade cabinet near the supermarket which</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 11:30:00" d="2021-07-17 11:35:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Of Fur and Swords
The Lemmings have turned the entire cabin topsy-turvy to organize medieval jousts with the ranger's fencing gear. Grizzy, who wishes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 11:35:00" d="2021-07-17 11:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Irresistible Bear
Grizzy finds a phial containing a love potion: anyone who drinks it immediately falls in love with the first creature he sees</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 11:40:00" d="2021-07-17 11:55:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lemmings Kit
Before taking a nap, Grizzy locks the food cupboard to prevent the Lemmings from getting into it. And to be sure they cannot force the lock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 11:55:00" d="2021-07-17 12:00:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Bug Scouts
Bugs takes on a scoutmaster who is bullying his scout troop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 12:00:00" d="2021-07-17 12:05:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% For Whom the Bugs Trolls
Two trolls try to capture Bugs to serve their boss for dinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 12:05:00" d="2021-07-17 12:10:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% To Beach His Own
Slugsworthy again tries to bully everyone at the beach by being first. Squeaks and Bugs put him in his place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 12:10:00" d="2021-07-17 12:22:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Five Star Bugs
Bugs gets the best of Leslie and his million dollar fountain when Leslie tries to make points with his boss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 12:22:00" d="2021-07-17 12:25:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Yoga to Be Kidding Me
Bugs is conned into yoga classes. He runs amok in class and gets the best of the teacher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 12:25:00" d="2021-07-17 12:30:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Rabbits of the Lost Ark
Sam and Bugs go on an Indiana Jones-type adventure in some ancient ruins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 12:30:00" d="2021-07-17 12:35:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Appropriate Technology
Wile has created a fully automated house. When the power goes out Wile is helpless and Bugs lends a hand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 12:35:00" d="2021-07-17 12:50:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Pork in the Road
Porky is a Guber Driver trying to get Bugs to his party on time. Nothing goes well during the trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 12:50:00" d="2021-07-17 13:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Upgrade
Gumball and Darwin see an advert for the latest cutting-edge Bobert operating system and excitedly talk Bobert into downloading it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 13:00:00" d="2021-07-17 13:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Comic
Gumball is the star of his own comic but struggles to match up to his heroic alter-ego</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 13:10:00" d="2021-07-17 13:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Romantic
After Gumball convinces himself that Penny doesn't love him as much as she used to, he decides to put together a romantic quest to remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 13:25:00" d="2021-07-17 13:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Uploads
Gumball and Darwin try to tear themselves away from the internet but end up falling down the Elmore Stream-hole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 13:35:00" d="2021-07-17 13:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Wicked
After being framed for feeding coffee to the squirrels in the park, Gumball proclaims that Mrs Robinson is pure evil. Darwin tells</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 13:55:00" d="2021-07-17 14:05:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>45% Lie-Ranosaurus Wrecked
Owen pretends to be Izzy's pet dinosaur after leading her to believe she dug him up in the school playground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 14:05:00" d="2021-07-17 14:20:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>45% An Egg-stremely Bad Idea
Hoping to 'brighten her day', Izzy and Owen pimp out Gwen's egg chair. But when it ends up in a museum run by angry chickens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 14:20:00" d="2021-07-17 14:30:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>45% Exercising the Demons
When a severe screen addiction turns the kids into lazy deadbeats, Chef brings in a professional to whip them into shape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 14:30:00" d="2021-07-17 14:50:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>45% Pudding the Planet First
After Chef says opposing viewpoints make the world more interesting and fun Izzy applies it in the worst way possible</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 14:50:00" d="2021-07-17 15:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Classic Titans
To prove his point about classic superhero cartoons Control Freak sends the Titans to a former version of Teen Titans Go!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 15:00:00" d="2021-07-17 15:10:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Labor Day
It's Labor Day and Robin teaches the other Titans about the importance of labor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 15:10:00" d="2021-07-17 15:25:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% Ones and Zeros
The Titans build an AI robot so it will create a pizza that's never been made before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 15:25:00" d="2021-07-17 15:35:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Career Day
Robin forces the other Titans to forget their dreams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 15:35:00" d="2021-07-17 15:50:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>TV Knight 2
Batman and Commissioner Gordon have a slumber party and watch their favorite TV shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 15:50:00" d="2021-07-17 16:00:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% Kelsey Quest
Kelsey accepts a quest from the Elders of the Creek, but is she ready for her terrifying opponent?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 16:00:00" d="2021-07-17 16:20:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% JPony
JP decides to follow his heart and tries to join the Horse Girls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 16:20:00" d="2021-07-17 16:30:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% Ace Of Squares
Craig vows to make the game of Four Square fun again by challenging its most dominant player!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 16:30:00" d="2021-07-17 16:40:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Doorway to Helen
Craig makes a long distance connection with a kid that loves the creek as much as he does</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 16:40:00" d="2021-07-17 17:00:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% The Climb
Craig's phone gets stuck in Mt. Sycamore, the tallest tree in the creek!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 17:00:00" d="2021-07-17 17:25:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% The Norse Case. 
The gang goes on a camping trip, although they can't really agree on why. Fred's desire for the gang to get in touch with their natural</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 17:25:00" d="2021-07-17 17:55:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% The People vs. Fred Jones
Fred is on trial, convicted of being the real mastermind behind all the mysteries he's solved. With the help of his defence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 17:55:00" d="2021-07-17 18:05:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ghost Party
When the Witches leave on vacation Tom's dreams of rest and relaxation are ruined when their ghost nephew Grayson comes over and throws</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 18:05:00" d="2021-07-17 18:20:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Cat-Astrophe
Bigby invents the Asteroid Buster Elite which Jerry uses for fun to destroy asteroids. Tom accidentally gives himself electrical superpowers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 18:20:00" d="2021-07-17 18:30:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Curse Case Scenario
Tom and Jerry are hired by Dutch to find his missing cursed ruby that causes him to have bad luck when it's missing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 18:30:00" d="2021-07-17 18:50:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Say Cheese
Tom eats some canned cheese that has gone bad and hallucinates. He then gets all sorts of visitors from the Tom and Jerry worlds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 18:50:00" d="2021-07-17 19:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Night
As night falls in Elmore the Moon takes us on a tour through the various dreams - and nightmares - of the town's slumbering inhabitants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 19:00:00" d="2021-07-17 19:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Misunderstandings
Gumball has misunderstood about his date with Penny: he thought they were meeting for dinner, but they were actually meeting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 19:10:00" d="2021-07-17 19:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Roots
When Mum sees Darwin gazing longingly at a fish-tank she thinks their mammalian lifestyle isn't fulfilling her adopted son and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 19:25:00" d="2021-07-17 19:35:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Trouble Busters!
Now that the Awesome Brawlers are world famous Bakugan experts, they want to help people solve their Bakugan-related problems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 19:35:00" d="2021-07-17 19:55:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>French Fry Wars
The Awesome Brawlers are arguing over who gets to eat the last french-fry. At first, each member makes a case for why they should</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 19:55:00" d="2021-07-17 20:05:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% The Academy
Robin creates the Teen Titan Awards in an effort to get his teammates to clean up the Tower</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 20:05:00" d="2021-07-17 20:15:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Throne of Bones
When the other Titans start listening to heavy metal music Robin warns them of the dangers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 20:15:00" d="2021-07-17 20:30:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Costume Contest
Sick of losing the costume contest to the Hive Five every year the Titans hatch a scheme to win</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 20:30:00" d="2021-07-17 20:40:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% The Self-Indulgent 200th Episode Spectacular!: Part 1
The Titans must confront their creators</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 20:40:00" d="2021-07-17 21:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% The Self-Indulgent 200th Episode Spectacular!: Part 2
The Titans discover how hard cartoons are to produce</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 21:00:00" d="2021-07-17 21:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Kids
Whilst Gumball and Darwin make fun of Mum and Dad for being old their voices start to break</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 21:10:00" d="2021-07-17 21:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Fan
Sarah the new kid in school is Gumball and Darwin's number one slightly obsessive fan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 21:25:00" d="2021-07-17 21:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Coach
Miss Simian has to save herself from a contagious Joy virus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 21:35:00" d="2021-07-17 21:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Recipe
The secret behind Anton's immortality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 21:55:00" d="2021-07-17 22:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Dumb Phone
To convince his parents to buy him a phone Angelo must turn his text addicted sister into a smart phone role model</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 22:05:00" d="2021-07-17 22:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% The Note King
After Mr. Foot confiscates all electronics before class Angelo and friends have to kick it old school and pass hand written notes to communicate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 22:20:00" d="2021-07-17 22:40:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu IX (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% How to Build a Dragon
While Lloyd and the rebels celebrate their successful strike against Emperor Garmadon in the Realm of Oni and Dragon the Ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 22:40:00" d="2021-07-17 22:50:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Gathering Dark
Axel must help Bearbarian overcome his secret fear of the dark to stop Dynamo from stealing his ride</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 22:50:00" d="2021-07-17 23:05:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>From Below
Axel juggles looking after Luka and defending the house from Dr. Nautilus's latest abomination a tentacle monster that attacks from every drain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 23:05:00" d="2021-07-17 23:15:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Party On
As Zoe preps Cleo LeBall's birthday party, Axel and the team run damage control against a jealous crasher - Princess SugarSalt, who has turned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 23:15:00" d="2021-07-17 23:25:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Prepare for the Worst
Axel and Bobbie Blobby skip out on Sarge's disaster-prep drills leaving enough of a gap in the team's defenses for a crow to swoop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 23:25:00" d="2021-07-17 23:35:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>On Your Toes
After a Porcupunk sighting Axel leads a recon mission that slowly but surely proves to be a wild goose chase devised by Sarge who's secretly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 23:35:00" d="2021-07-18 00:00:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu IX (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% How to Build a Dragon
While Lloyd and the rebels celebrate their successful strike against Emperor Garmadon in the Realm of Oni and Dragon the Ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 00:00:00" d="2021-07-18 00:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Founder
When Nicole decides to pay the cable bill in person at Chanax , she leaves specific instructions for Richard to stay in the car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 00:10:00" d="2021-07-18 00:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Schooling
Gumball and Darwin are at the convenience store considering playing truant. Larry warns them that if they don't take their education</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 00:20:00" d="2021-07-18 00:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Intelligence
Gumball and Darwin argue with the Internet and make him mad. So mad in fact that he seeks to wipe out humanity and, whilst doing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 00:35:00" d="2021-07-18 00:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Potion
Gumball and Darwin learn that Hector is not so happy being giant-sized. So they decide to help him by creating a potion that will shrink</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 00:45:00" d="2021-07-18 00:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Spinoffs
Wishing to get rid of Gumball once and for all his nemesis Rob offers up a variety of reality action and comedy shows featuring characters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 00:55:00" d="2021-07-18 01:05:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Transformation
Penny's family are unhappy that she's decided to come out of her shell… literally. And Penny wants her family to come out of their shell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 01:05:00" d="2021-07-18 01:15:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Allergy
Darwin starts sneezing repeatedly and it seems he can't stop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 01:15:00" d="2021-07-18 01:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Mothers
It's Mother's Day and Gumball and Darwin discover that Tobias and Banana Joe have both made a card for The Best Mum in the World</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 01:30:00" d="2021-07-18 01:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Password
Mum has forced Dad to install a password on the computer…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 01:40:00" d="2021-07-18 01:50:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Procrastinators
Gumball and Darwin are offended when Mom calls them “procrastinators” once she’s told them what it means</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 01:50:00" d="2021-07-18 02:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Shell
While performing a school play Gumball is so nervous about kissing Penny that he accidentally head-butts her and cracks open her shell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 02:00:00" d="2021-07-18 02:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Grounded
Elena and Angelo are grounded for fighting with each other. They have to put aside their differences and work together to escape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 02:10:00" d="2021-07-18 02:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% The Pigeons
Lola has a pigeon phobia. Paging Dr. Angelo and Dr. Sherwood to cure her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 02:25:00" d="2021-07-18 02:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Cupcake War
A new hipster cupcake shop opens across the street from Cathy’s siphoning off all the customers. Angelo and friends come up with strategies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 02:35:00" d="2021-07-18 02:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Best Sister Ever
In honor of older sisters Slobber offers free tickets to whomever can make the best short film about their older sister</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 02:45:00" d="2021-07-18 03:00:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Snow And Tell
Angelo searches for the ultimate object to bring to show and tell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 03:00:00" d="2021-07-18 03:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Coach
Miss Simian has to save herself from a contagious Joy virus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 03:10:00" d="2021-07-18 03:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Recipe
The secret behind Anton's immortality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 03:20:00" d="2021-07-18 03:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Puppy
The kids finally get the puppy they always wanted except it’s a turtle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 03:35:00" d="2021-07-18 03:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Name
When Mum reveals that Gumball's real name is Zach Gumball adopts a cheesy annoying persona to match the name</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 03:45:00" d="2021-07-18 04:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Extras
Nothing much is happening for Gumball and Darwin and the background characters in Elmore seize their moment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 04:00:00" d="2021-07-18 04:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Nemesis
Gumball and Darwin discover that Rob, who once swore to wreak vengeance on them, has been trying to destroy them for some time. But his traps never work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 04:10:00" d="2021-07-18 04:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Crew
When Gumball and Darwin decide it's time they join a crew, they agree that the coolest posse in Elmore is the senior citizens. They do everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 04:20:00" d="2021-07-18 04:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Others
When Anais reveals she's in the grade above them at school, Gumball's and Darwin's eyes are suddenly opened to a whole new world of other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 04:30:00" d="2021-07-18 04:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Signature
Dad discovers that Granny Jojo and Louie are planning to get married and move to Florida. To stop this happening he adopts Louie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 04:40:00" d="2021-07-18 04:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Gift
After they receive an extravagant invitation to Masami's birthday party, Gumball and Darwin are anxious to find just the right gift for her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-18 04:55:00" d="2021-07-18 05:05:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 2016 II (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Reststop Roustabout
With the Rustbucket stopped on the Midwest roadside, Ben locks himself inside with his tablet as Max and Gwen enjoy the great</k>  </p>
</a>
