<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="118" t="2021-07-09 06:42:23"><p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 05:05:00" d="2021-07-16 05:15:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 2016 II (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Nature of Things
While sightseeing at the Geyser Gulch National Park, the Tennyson trio uncover Steam Smythe's steam-powered generator</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 05:15:00" d="2021-07-16 05:25:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 2016 II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Assault on Pancake Palace
When Gwen enters a pancake-eating contest at the world famous Pancake Palace, Ben finds the Bugg Bros. and must stop them before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 05:25:00" d="2021-07-16 05:35:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Mysterious Boy
After stopping Tiko’s rampage, the Awesome Brawlers have become world-famous heroes and Bakugan-mania sweeps the globe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 05:35:00" d="2021-07-16 05:50:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A New Power
A Rogue brawler, Ajit and his golden Bakugan have crashed the Awesome Brawlers party. Who is this brawler? How can he control a Golden Bakugan? Only one way to find out – Bakugan Brawl! Dan and Drago go head to head with the outsides to get to the botto</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 05:50:00" d="2021-07-16 05:55:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lend Me Your Earpiece
Magoo finds himself shrunk and then dragged inside the President’s head along with Fizz. He thinks the hamster is a little</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 05:55:00" d="2021-07-16 06:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Wallpapering Magoo
Magoo thinks that he is peeling off old wallpaper on Linda’s walls but he is actually destroying Fizz’ hypnotic posters In order</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 06:05:00" d="2021-07-16 06:10:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A Mountaineer Like No Other
Magoo has decided to go mountain climbing but in reality, he is climbing up a skyscraper! He mixes Fizz up with a wounded</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 06:10:00" d="2021-07-16 06:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Legs of Steel
Thinking he is in the middle of a work-out at his local gym Magoo inadvertently climbs onto a delivery boy’s bicycle. It just so happens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 06:25:00" d="2021-07-16 06:30:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A Recipe for Success
Magoo thinks Weasel has opened a restaurant and wants to help him improve it. He mistakes the FizzLab for a kitchen and prevents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 06:30:00" d="2021-07-16 06:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Honey Bear
Magoo thinks that he is on a camping trip but he is actually just in the city park. When he sees Weasel wearing a suit that allows him to stock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 06:40:00" d="2021-07-16 06:45:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Halloween Hold-up
Magoo is thinks is out trick-or-treating for Halloween. But he unwittingly robs a bank instead of Weasel. Fizz, whose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 06:45:00" d="2021-07-16 07:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Last Groundhog
Magoo mistakes Weasel (in an animal costume) for a groundhog being hunted and confiscates the hunter’s gun. In reality he steals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 07:00:00" d="2021-07-16 07:25:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% El Bandito
The gang heads out to a Day of the Dead festival. There, they learn that the spirit of the old, legendary criminal, El Bandito, has returned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 07:25:00" d="2021-07-16 07:55:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Into the Mouth of Madcap
Daphne agrees to watch her friend’s kid Wayne and convinces Fred to take a night off from mysteries to go to the boardwalk amusement park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 07:55:00" d="2021-07-16 08:05:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Tea Timer's Ball
The Tea Timers throw a dance and invite everyone in the Creek. Craig believes it's solely to prank him, while Kelsey deals with an unwanted admirer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 08:05:00" d="2021-07-16 08:20:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek II (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% The Cardboard…
Craig and his friends stumble upon a mysterious bunker made of cardboard beneath the Creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 08:20:00" d="2021-07-16 08:30:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek II (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% Ancients Of The…
Craig, Kelsey and JP discover an ancient fort that belonged to the first kids in the Creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 08:30:00" d="2021-07-16 08:50:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek II (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% Mortimor To The…
When Craig, Kelsey and JP get stranded in murky water, it's up to Mortimor to save the day!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 08:50:00" d="2021-07-16 09:00:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek II (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Secret in a Bottle
Craig needs to get a secret off his chest, so he pays a visit to the Keeper of Secrets in the Creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 09:00:00" d="2021-07-16 09:15:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek II (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Trading Day
After Craig accidentally destroys a shipment of rare Chocorolls at the Trading Tree, Kit makes him work off his debt by running her trades</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 09:15:00" d="2021-07-16 09:25:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek II (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% Crisis At Elder…
Tragedy strikes the Creek when the Elders get trapped under Elder Rock, and it's up to Craig, Kelsey and JP to rescue them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 09:25:00" d="2021-07-16 09:35:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek II (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Kelsey The Worthy
When Kelsey demolishes a wall at Craig's house, her father takes away her sword. So she enlists Craig and JP to help prove to her father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 09:35:00" d="2021-07-16 09:55:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek II (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The End Was Here
Craig tries to figure out how an ancient war that decimated the Creek began in hopes of stopping history from repeating itself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 09:55:00" d="2021-07-16 10:05:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A Dame-gerous Game
After Leshawna, Bridgette, Owen and Cody win a Hide &amp; Seek competition, they're trapped on a private island by a jealous former</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 10:05:00" d="2021-07-16 10:20:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Royal Flush
When the other kids fear Harold has accidentally flushed himself down Chef's fancy new toilet, they travel into the sewer on a rescue mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 10:20:00" d="2021-07-16 10:30:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>45% Dissing Cousins Pt.1
It's International Cousins Day and Owen and Gwen are dreading the fact that their cousins Max and Ella are spending</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 10:30:00" d="2021-07-16 10:50:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>45% Dissing Cousins Pt.2
It's International Cousins Day and Owen and Gwen are dreading the fact that their cousins Max and Ella are spending</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 10:50:00" d="2021-07-16 10:55:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (73)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Halloween Bear
Grizzy discovers the leftovers of a Halloween party in the ranger's cabin, which was entirely redecorated for the occasion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 10:55:00" d="2021-07-16 11:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (74)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Clean Bear
Grizzy wants to give the she-bear he's in love with a plastic ring which he finds really swell. But since the object was found in the trash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 11:00:00" d="2021-07-16 11:10:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (75)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Wandering Spirits
Grizzy finds a strange American Indian figurine with the power to switch the spirits of two living beings and finds himself imprisoned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 11:10:00" d="2021-07-16 11:20:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (76)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Mirror, Mirror On The Wall
While salmon fishing on the riverbank, Grizzy hauls in an unusual catch: an old hand mirror straight out of a fairytale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 11:20:00" d="2021-07-16 11:30:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (77)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Grizzy the Wizard
In a casing that fell from a circus caravan, the Lemmings find a magic stick that can enchant objects and make them come alive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 11:30:00" d="2021-07-16 11:35:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (76)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Moonwalk Bear
Whilst trying to stop the Lemmings from playing with a crate of firework rockets, Grizzy is literally carried away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 11:35:00" d="2021-07-16 11:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Camping in the Wild
With their endless battles over the ranger's cabin which they do not want to share, Grizzy and the Lemmings end up blowing the cabin up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 11:40:00" d="2021-07-16 11:55:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Carried Away Bear
Grizzy gets rid of the Lemmings by crushing them with one of the ranger's heavy trunks which he immediately clears out of the cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 11:55:00" d="2021-07-16 12:00:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% The IMPoster
Its halloween and Impkin the pumpkin king shows up to cause mischief</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 12:00:00" d="2021-07-16 12:05:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Bugs Over Par
Leslie invites bugs to join their golf game in hope of an easy win and a silver jacket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 12:05:00" d="2021-07-16 12:10:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Fast Feud
Bugs is roped into working at a fast food place. Bugs gets the best of the abusive owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 12:10:00" d="2021-07-16 12:20:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Sir Little Chin Griffin Hunter
Sir Littlechin is on a quest to capture a griffin but not if Bugs has anything to do with it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 12:20:00" d="2021-07-16 12:27:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Bugs in Time
Clovenhoof takes Bugs jumping through time. Bugs just wants to get home. They pick up a T-Rex on the way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 12:27:00" d="2021-07-16 12:32:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Airpork Security
Bugs is late for his flight and he encounters Porky at every step along the airport check-in process</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 12:32:00" d="2021-07-16 12:35:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Home a Clone
Dr. Clovenhoof creates a cloning device and various odd clones of Bugs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 12:35:00" d="2021-07-16 12:50:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Bugs on Ice
Bugs and Squeaks are bullied by a professional ice skater while trying to skate for fun on the lake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 12:50:00" d="2021-07-16 13:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Check
Gumball, Darwin and Anais are delighted when Grandpa Louie gives them a check for $5,000. They immediately start fantasising over what to spend it on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 13:00:00" d="2021-07-16 13:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Pest
When they find Anais training herself for a brutal showdown Gumball and Darwin realise that their sister is being pestered at school by an annoying kid: Billy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 13:10:00" d="2021-07-16 13:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Hug
When Darwin taunts Gumball about how predictable he is Gumball tries to prove that he can still surprise his buddy. He thinks that greeting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 13:25:00" d="2021-07-16 13:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Routine
Mum and the kids depart for their hard day's work, leaving a seemingly lazy Dad half-asleep on the sofa. Mum has given him one very simple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 13:35:00" d="2021-07-16 13:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Parking
When the Wattersons arrive at the mall for a day of shopping, they struggle to find a space in the parking lot. They search for a space</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 13:55:00" d="2021-07-16 14:05:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama I (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>45% Stink. Stank. Stunk
When a skunk comes seeking its annual revenge on Chef, Duncan sees it as an opportunity to get a vacation from daycare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 14:05:00" d="2021-07-16 14:20:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Robo Teacher
When a substitute teacher fills in for Chef, Duncan thinks it's going to be the best day ever. He's wrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 14:20:00" d="2021-07-16 14:30:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Glove Glove Me Do
Owen's newly found gloves make him great at everything. But this greatness comes at a high price</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 14:30:00" d="2021-07-16 14:50:00"><n u="Total DramaRama">Total DramaRama II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>45% The Tooth About Zombies
When Gwen's favorite event, the Zombie March, falls on the same day as Beth's nightmare event, dental hygienist check upday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 14:50:00" d="2021-07-16 15:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Brain Percentages
Beast Boy starts using more than 10% of his brain in an effort to find the hidden images in a puzzle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 15:00:00" d="2021-07-16 15:10:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>BL4Z3
The Titans become hackers to stop a gang of computer pirates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 15:10:00" d="2021-07-16 15:25:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% Lication
Robin introduces the other Titans to a money maker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 15:25:00" d="2021-07-16 15:35:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% Justice League's Next Top Talent Idol Star: Part 1
The Justice League holds a talent competition to find a superhero worthy of joining the team</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 15:35:00" d="2021-07-16 15:50:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% Justice League's Next Top Talent Idol Star: Part 2
The competition heats up as Robin tries everything to win</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 15:50:00" d="2021-07-16 16:00:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% Lost in the Sewer
Craig agrees to help The Sewer Queen map the sewers, but he quickly finds himself in over his head</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 16:00:00" d="2021-07-16 16:20:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% The Brood
Craig's determination to get his granddad a cicada shell causes him, Kelsey and JP to become trapped in their stump!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 16:20:00" d="2021-07-16 16:30:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% Under the Overpass
Craig and his friends travel to find honeysuckle in the creek but discover a whole new part of the creek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 16:30:00" d="2021-07-16 16:40:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% The Invitation
Craig and his friends are invited to an exclusive tea party with delicious desserts, if they can last to the end of the party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 16:40:00" d="2021-07-16 17:00:00"><n u="Craig Of The Creek">Craig Of The Creek I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>72% Vulture's Next
Craig and his friends start a band, but Craig is haunted by a frightening nightmare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 17:00:00" d="2021-07-16 17:25:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% El Bandito
The gang heads out to a Day of the Dead festival. There, they learn that the spirit of the old, legendary criminal, El Bandito, has returned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 17:25:00" d="2021-07-16 17:55:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Into the Mouth of Madcap
Daphne agrees to watch her friend’s kid Wayne and convinces Fred to take a night off from mysteries to go to the boardwalk amusement park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 17:55:00" d="2021-07-16 18:05:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Cat Napped
Tom breaks his leg during a chase. While in his wheelchair he witnesses what seems like the kidnapping of Misty the cute cat in building across the street</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 18:05:00" d="2021-07-16 18:20:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Black Cat
Hildie and Beatie are fed up with Tom and threaten to get a real witches' cat: a black cat. Tom desperately takes a magic potion that makes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 18:20:00" d="2021-07-16 18:30:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hunger Strikes
When the pets believe that they are going to run out of food during a snowstorm they start hoarding food. Things get out of control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 18:30:00" d="2021-07-16 18:50:00"><n u="The Tom and...">The Tom and... I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Gravi-Tom
Jerry and Napoleon play around with a Bigby's brand new anti-gravity machine until Tom breaks into the lab and a zero-g chase begins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 18:50:00" d="2021-07-16 19:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Nest
A breaking news report tells the Wattersons their neighbour is among the several mysterious disappearances happening across Elmore. Their search</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 19:00:00" d="2021-07-16 19:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Points
Gumball and Darwin agree to do all of Tobias’s chores in exchange for good points! Gumball and Darwin discover that Tobias is doing way better</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 19:10:00" d="2021-07-16 19:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Bus
When Rocky suggests that the Elmore Junior High kids skip school, the bus is boarded by criminals who seem to want to teach them the importance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 19:25:00" d="2021-07-16 19:35:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Brawler Headhunting
As acting president of Kazami International, Shun is called upon to entertain another new young CEO Noah Schmidt, who’s interested</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 19:35:00" d="2021-07-16 19:55:00"><n u="Bakugan">Bakugan II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lightning's Entrance Exam
The Awesome Brawlers may be world famous heroes, but that doesn’t mean they get out of going to school. They are still regular</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 19:55:00" d="2021-07-16 20:05:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Classic Titans
To prove his point about classic superhero cartoons Control Freak sends the Titans to a former version of Teen Titans Go!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 20:05:00" d="2021-07-16 20:15:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Labor Day
It's Labor Day and Robin teaches the other Titans about the importance of labor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 20:15:00" d="2021-07-16 20:30:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>54% Ones and Zeros
The Titans build an AI robot so it will create a pizza that's never been made before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 20:30:00" d="2021-07-16 20:40:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Career Day
Robin forces the other Titans to forget their dreams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 20:40:00" d="2021-07-16 21:00:00"><n u="Teen Titans Go!">Teen Titans Go! IV (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>TV Knight 2
Batman and Commissioner Gordon have a slumber party and watch their favorite TV shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 21:00:00" d="2021-07-16 21:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Internet
Gumball accidentally uploads a video of himself and wants it gone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 21:10:00" d="2021-07-16 21:25:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Plan
The Watterson kids come up with a fool-proof plan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 21:25:00" d="2021-07-16 21:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The World
The life of the background objects of Elmore are shown in a series of short skits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 21:35:00" d="2021-07-16 21:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Finale
The Wattersons are surprised to discover that their past actions have consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 21:55:00" d="2021-07-16 22:05:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Monster at the Door
After Angelo trashes Burst’s stage set his punishment is that he must star in Burst’s unusual arty play. With Sherwood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 22:05:00" d="2021-07-16 22:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Videogame Style
After accidentally breaking a window Angelo and friends complete a series of chores at the rec center as pay back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 22:20:00" d="2021-07-16 22:40:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu IX (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Radio Free Ninjago
NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu centers on the adventures of five ninjas. The show is set in the fictional world of Ninjago a place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 22:40:00" d="2021-07-16 22:50:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stretched Too Thin
After a new combo-move leaves Masko permanently limp Axel and the team must help the fallen luchador get his stretch back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 22:50:00" d="2021-07-16 23:05:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Trojan Bear
When Axel opens a subscription gift-box he didn't even order the team finds their ranks divided by a robotic bear - or Princess SugarSalt in disguise!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 23:05:00" d="2021-07-16 23:15:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Porcupunk Rock
Madcap turns to Axel and his team for help after a sonic upgrade to Porcupunk threatens to bring down the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 23:15:00" d="2021-07-16 23:25:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Saving Private Masko
Masko takes Axel's call for more discipline too seriously and loses sight of his own identity in the process, becoming a no-nonsense</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 23:25:00" d="2021-07-16 23:35:00"><n u="Power Players">Power Players I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Out of My Head
Axel must help Sarge and Bobbie learn to walk in each other's shoes - literally - after Luka unwittingly switches the toys' heads!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-16 23:35:00" d="2021-07-17 00:00:00"><n u="NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu">NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu IX (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Radio Free Ninjago
NinjaGo: Masters of Spinjitzu centers on the adventures of five ninjas. The show is set in the fictional world of Ninjago a place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 00:00:00" d="2021-07-17 00:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Candidate
When their parents all go to a charity gala at the school, the kids are locked in a classroom with a VHS tape. However, when the room starts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 00:10:00" d="2021-07-17 00:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Anybody
Gumball wants Clayton to sit his detention for him, so convinces him it's way more exciting to be take the shapes of other people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 00:20:00" d="2021-07-17 00:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Shippening
When people that barely know each other start falling in love, Gumball thinks he knows who's behind it. He rushes to Sarah's house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 00:35:00" d="2021-07-17 00:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Stink
Gumball decides to put Mr.Small's eco-friendly principles to the test but it doesn't quite go as planned. Mr.Small disappears after deciding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 00:45:00" d="2021-07-17 00:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Awareness
Gumball tries to convince Leslie he's an expert on all things plant-related. However, when Leslie realises Gumball hasn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 00:55:00" d="2021-07-17 01:05:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Parents
After accidentally bumping into each other in the grocery aisle, Nicole and her parents have it out. The Wattersons discover why Nicole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 01:05:00" d="2021-07-17 01:15:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Fraud
When Gumball and Darwin discover his diploma is fake Principal Brown is determined to keep their discovery a secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 01:15:00" d="2021-07-17 01:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Void
Gumball and Darwin start noticing small details around Elmore High that don't add up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 01:30:00" d="2021-07-17 01:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Boss
Gumball and Darwin help Rocky land an office job so that his dad Mr Robinson will be proud of him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 01:40:00" d="2021-07-17 01:50:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Move
Gumball confronts Clayton about his fabled Seven Pressure Point Heart Exploding Technique assuming it’s another one of his outlandish claims</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 01:50:00" d="2021-07-17 02:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Law
Gumball jaywalks and is pulled over by Donut Cop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 02:00:00" d="2021-07-17 02:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Employee Of The Month
Angelo becomes an intern at Adventureparkland. But his dream job isn’t all it’s cracked up to be because he has to actually… work!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 02:10:00" d="2021-07-17 02:25:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Bobbleheads Are Gonna Roll
Miss Perla turns detention time into art therapy where Angelo makes cool bobble-head sculptures which become</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 02:25:00" d="2021-07-17 02:35:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Secret Recipe
When Cathy hikes the price of her famous cupcake the “Brooklyn Blackout” Lola goes undercover in search of the secret recipe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 02:35:00" d="2021-07-17 02:45:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Angelo vs. The Test
Angelo shares his tips and tricks for delaying a test</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 02:45:00" d="2021-07-17 03:00:00"><n u="Angelo Rules">Angelo Rules IV (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% What Now?
Because of his cunning and tenacity Angelo always gets what he wants. Is this the way life is always going to be? Angelo has an existential crisis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 03:00:00" d="2021-07-17 03:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Plan
The Watterson kids come up with a fool-proof plan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 03:10:00" d="2021-07-17 03:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The World
The life of the background objects of Elmore are shown in a series of short skits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 03:20:00" d="2021-07-17 03:35:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Finale
The Wattersons are surprised to discover that their past actions have consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 03:35:00" d="2021-07-17 03:45:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Kids
Whilst Gumball and Darwin make fun of Mum and Dad for being old their voices start to break</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 03:45:00" d="2021-07-17 04:00:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball III (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Fan
Sarah the new kid in school is Gumball and Darwin's number one slightly obsessive fan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 04:00:00" d="2021-07-17 04:10:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The BFFS
Gumball's old BFF, Fuzzy, turns up on his doorstep. Darwin struggles to accept that there was someone before him and fails to contain his jealousy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 04:10:00" d="2021-07-17 04:20:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Agent
Gumball and Darwin's clothes go missing after a swimming lesson, and Gumball is forced to wear a tuxedo from the lost and found office</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 04:20:00" d="2021-07-17 04:30:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Decisions
When everything goes wrong in Darwin's life, he begins to suspect that Gumball's bad influence might be to blame. Darwin decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 04:30:00" d="2021-07-17 04:40:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball VI (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Web
Gumball and Darwin realize that the adult residents of Elmore are dangerously naive when it comes to being safe online</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 04:40:00" d="2021-07-17 04:55:00"><n u="The Amazing World of Gumball">The Amazing World of Gumball IV (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Return
Dad has to make the kids on time for their first day back at school. But he's overslept and now he can't find Gumball, Darwin or Anais anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="45" o="2021-07-17 04:55:00" d="2021-07-17 05:05:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10 2016 II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bomzobo Lives
During a routine trip to the DMV, Max takes a driving test to renew his license, but when a disguised Zombozo hijacks</k>  </p>
</a>
