<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2021-07-09 07:15:09"><p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-16 05:15:00" d="2021-07-16 05:30:00"><n>T20 Blast 2006 Final Highlights</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at a classic clash from the T20 Blast. Here, the dramatic 2006 final between the Nottinghamshire Outlaws and the Leicestershire Foxes at Trent Bridge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-16 05:30:00" d="2021-07-16 06:00:00"><n>T20 Blast 2016 Final Highlights</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at a classic clash from the T20 Blast. Here, the dramatic 2016 final between the Northants Steelbacks and Durham Jets at Edgbaston</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-16 06:00:00" d="2021-07-16 06:30:00"><n>Best of The Women's World T20</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the best matches from the ICC Women's T20 World Cup. Here, hosts England meet rivals Australia in the semi-finals of the competition's inaugural event in 2009</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-16 06:30:00" d="2021-07-16 07:00:00"><n>Best of The Women's World T20</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the best matches from the ICC Women's T20 World Cup. Here, the final of the inaugural 2009 event between hosts England and New Zealand at Lord's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-16 07:00:00" d="2021-07-16 08:00:00"><n>England v Pakistan 1st ODI Hlts</n><t>O</t>    <k>England and Pakistan begin their white ball tour with the first of three ODI matches in Cardiff. England come here after defeating Sri Lanka in their ODI series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-16 08:00:00" d="2021-07-16 09:00:00"><n>England v Pakistan 2nd ODI Hlts</n><t>O</t>    <k>England and Pakistan continue their white ball tour with the second of three ODI matches in Cardiff. These sides will also go on to play three T20s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-16 09:00:00" d="2021-07-16 10:00:00"><n>England v Pakistan 3rd ODI Hlts</n><t>O</t>    <k>England and Pakistan continue their white ball tour with the third of three ODI matches in Cardiff. These sides will go on to play three T20s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-16 10:00:00" d="2021-07-16 14:00:00"><n>England v India Women 3rd T20</n><t>O</t>    <k>England and India meet in the third and final T20 match of their series in Chelmsford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-16 14:00:00" d="2021-07-16 15:00:00"><n>ICC WTC Final - The Film</n><t>O</t>    <k>The film looking back at a marquee moment in Test cricket, as India and New Zealand went head to head in the final of the first-ever ICC World Test Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-16 15:00:00" d="2021-07-16 15:30:00"><n>Talking Cricket: Wasim &amp; Waqar</n><t>O</t>    <k>One of cricket's most feared bowling attacks, Wasim Akram and Waqar Younis were game-changers for Pakistan during their careers. Sky Sports Cricket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-16 15:30:00" d="2021-07-16 15:45:00"><n>Best of England v Pakistan</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at some of the finest moments from matches between England and Pakistan. Here, rewind to 2003, and a Cricket World Cup encounter between the sides in Cape Town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-16 15:45:00" d="2021-07-16 16:00:00"><n>Best of T20 Blast Finals Day</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some of the best ever T20 Blast finals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-16 16:00:00" d="2021-07-16 17:00:00"><n>England v Pakistan 1st ODI Hlts</n><t>O</t>    <k>England and Pakistan begin their white ball tour with the first of three ODI matches in Cardiff. England come here after defeating Sri Lanka in their ODI series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-16 17:00:00" d="2021-07-16 18:00:00"><n>England v Pakistan 2nd ODI Hlts</n><t>O</t>    <k>England and Pakistan continue their white ball tour with the second of three ODI matches in Cardiff. These sides will also go on to play three T20s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-16 18:00:00" d="2021-07-16 19:00:00"><n>England v Pakistan 3rd ODI Hlts</n><t>O</t>    <k>England and Pakistan continue their white ball tour with the third of three ODI matches in Cardiff. These sides will go on to play three T20s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-16 19:00:00" d="2021-07-16 23:30:00"><n>Live 1st T20: England v Pakistan</n><t>O</t>    <k>England host Pakistan at Trent Bridge in the first T20 in their series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-16 23:30:00" d="2021-07-17 00:00:00"><n>Cricket's Climate Crisis</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at the challenges that cricket faces due to climate change, and the impact on the future of the sport throughout the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-17 00:00:00" d="2021-07-17 01:15:00"><n>Spinwash 93'</n><t>O</t>    <k>It was a tour like no other - explore England's controversial and chaotic trip to India in 1993, beset by poor performance on the field and bizarre events away from it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-17 01:15:00" d="2021-07-17 04:15:00"><n>England v Pakistan 1st T20</n><t>O</t>    <k>England host Pakistan at Trent Bridge in the first T20 in their series</k>  </p>
</a>
