<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2021-07-08 05:05:55"><p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-13 05:15:00" d="2021-07-13 05:30:00"><n>Best of England v Pakistan</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at some of the finest moments from matches between England and Pakistan. Here, rewind to 2005 and a tight Test between the sides at the Multan Cricket Stadium</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-13 05:30:00" d="2021-07-13 05:45:00"><n>Best of England v Pakistan</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at some of the finest moments from matches between England and Pakistan. Here, rewind to 2012 and the second Test in the series between the sides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-13 05:45:00" d="2021-07-13 06:00:00"><n>Best of England v Pakistan</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at some of the finest moments from matches between England and Pakistan. Here, rewind to 2003, and a Cricket World Cup encounter between the sides in Cape Town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-13 06:00:00" d="2021-07-13 06:30:00"><n>Best of The Women's World T20</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the best matches from the ICC Women's T20 World Cup. Here, hosts England meet rivals Australia in the semi-finals of the competition's inaugural event in 2009</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-13 06:30:00" d="2021-07-13 07:00:00"><n>Best of The Women's World T20</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the best matches from the ICC Women's T20 World Cup. Here, the final of the inaugural 2009 event between hosts England and New Zealand at Lord's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-13 07:00:00" d="2021-07-13 07:20:00"><n>Best of England v Pakistan</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at some of the finest moments from matches between England and Pakistan. Here, rewind to 2000, and a memorable final day in Karachi that went down to the wire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-13 07:20:00" d="2021-07-13 07:45:00"><n>Best of England v Pakistan</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at some of the finest moments from matches between England and Pakistan. Here, rewind to 2001 and the first Test in the series between the sides at Lord's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-13 07:45:00" d="2021-07-13 08:00:00"><n>Best of England v Pakistan</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at some of the finest moments from matches between England and Pakistan. Here, rewind to 2001 and the second Test in the series between the sides at Old Trafford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-13 08:00:00" d="2021-07-13 08:30:00"><n>Best of The Women's World T20</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the best matches from the ICC Women's T20 World Cup. Here, the final of the inaugural 2009 event between hosts England and New Zealand at Lord's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-13 08:30:00" d="2021-07-13 09:00:00"><n>ICC Women's WC 2017 Final Hlts</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember one of English cricket's finest hours as England met India in the 2017 ICC Women's World Cup final in front of a capacity crowd at Lord's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-13 09:00:00" d="2021-07-13 09:30:00"><n>Talking Cricket: Wasim &amp; Waqar</n><t>O</t>    <k>One of cricket's most feared bowling attacks, Wasim Akram and Waqar Younis were game-changers for Pakistan during their careers. Sky Sports Cricket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-13 09:30:00" d="2021-07-13 10:30:00"><n>England v Pakistan 1st ODI Hlts</n><t>O</t>    <k>England and Pakistan begin their white ball tour with the first of three ODI matches in Cardiff. England come here after defeating Sri Lanka in their ODI series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-13 10:30:00" d="2021-07-13 11:30:00"><n>England v Pakistan 2nd ODI Hlts</n><t>O</t>    <k>England and Pakistan continue their white ball tour with the second of three ODI matches in Cardiff. These sides will also go on to play three T20s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-13 11:30:00" d="2021-07-13 12:30:00"><n>England v Pakistan 1st ODI Hlts</n><t>O</t>    <k>England and Pakistan begin their white ball tour with the first of three ODI matches in Cardiff. England come here after defeating Sri Lanka in their ODI series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-13 12:30:00" d="2021-07-13 13:30:00"><n>England v Pakistan 2nd ODI Hlts</n><t>O</t>    <k>England and Pakistan continue their white ball tour with the second of three ODI matches in Cardiff. These sides will also go on to play three T20s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-13 13:30:00" d="2021-07-13 22:00:00"><n>Live England v Pakistan 3rd ODI</n><t>O</t>    <k>The third ODI between England and Pakistan takes place at Edgbaston</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-13 22:00:00" d="2021-07-13 23:00:00"><n>Ashes Memories: Botham &amp; Willis</n><t>O</t>    <k>Sir Ian Botham and Bob Willis discuss their memories of facing Australia in The Ashes. Both men played huge roles for England in their victory in The 1981 Ashes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-13 23:00:00" d="2021-07-13 23:20:00"><n>Botham&amp;Wilis Meet Anderson&amp;Broad</n><t>O</t>    <k>Following the sad news of the death of England cricket legend Bob Willis, look back at when he and Ian Botham met the England fast bowling pair of Jimmy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-13 23:20:00" d="2021-07-13 23:40:00"><n>25 Years of Women's Cricket on Sky</n><t>O</t>    <k>Twenty five years after showing women's cricket for the first time in 1996, Sky Sports looks back at some of the sport's most memorable moments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-13 23:40:00" d="2021-07-14 00:00:00"><n>Brunt &amp; Schiver Interview</n><t>O</t>    <k>Hannah Wilkes chats to England cricketers Katherine Brunt and Nat Sciver ahead of the inaugural 'The Hundred' competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-14 00:00:00" d="2021-07-14 01:00:00"><n>England v Pakistan 3rd ODI Hlts</n><t>O</t>    <k>England and Pakistan continue their white ball tour with the third of three ODI matches in Cardiff. These sides will go on to play three T20s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-14 01:00:00" d="2021-07-14 04:00:00"><n u="S Africa v Pakistan 3rd T20">S Africa v Pakistan 3rd T20 2021</n><t>O</t>    <k>South Africa meet Pakistan in the third out of four T20 matches in Pretoria. The sides come here tied at 1-1 after South Africa comfortably won the second match</k>  </p>
</a>
