<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2019-07-11 00:17:15"><p id_tv="503" o="2019-07-16 05:00:00" d="2019-07-16 06:00:00"><n>Cricket World Cup Classic</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic matches from the ICC Cricket World Cup. Here is Australia against Sri Lanka in the final of the 2007 tournament in Bridgetown, Barbados</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2019-07-16 06:00:00" d="2019-07-16 07:00:00"><n>Capturing The ICC World Cup: 2015</n><t>O</t>    <k>Former Australian captain Michael Clarke shares his memories of winning the 2015 Cricket World Cup in his home country. The Australians defeated New Zealand in the final</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2019-07-16 07:00:00" d="2019-07-16 10:00:00"><n>How The 2003 World Cup Was Won</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to remember the 2003 ICC Cricket World Cup from South Africa, Zimbabwe and Kenya. Australia were the defending champions from the 1999 edition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2019-07-16 10:00:00" d="2019-07-16 13:00:00"><n>How The 2007 ICC World Cup Was Won</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at how the 2007 ICC Cricket World Cup was won. The tournament was held in the West Indies, while Australia came into the event as reigning champions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2019-07-16 13:00:00" d="2019-07-16 14:00:00"><n>The Road To The World Cup</n><t>O</t>    <k>The 2019 ICC Cricket World Cup begins as hosts England take on South Africa at The Oval in the opening match. Both sides are looking to win their very first World Cup</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2019-07-16 14:00:00" d="2019-07-16 15:00:00"><n>The Road To The World Cup</n><t>O</t>    <k>New Zealand take on Sri Lanka at the Cardiff Wales Stadium in a group stage match from the 2019 ICC Cricket World Cup</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2019-07-16 15:00:00" d="2019-07-16 16:00:00"><n>The Road To The World Cup</n><t>O</t>    <k>South Africa take on India at the Hampshire Bowl in Southampton in the group stage of the 2019 ICC Cricket World Cup. South Africa come into this having</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2019-07-16 16:00:00" d="2019-07-16 17:00:00"><n>The Road To The World Cup</n><t>O</t>    <k>England take on Bangladesh at the Cardiff Wales Stadium in the group stage of the 2019 ICC Cricket World Cup. England want to hit back here after losing to Pakistan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2019-07-16 17:00:00" d="2019-07-16 18:00:00"><n>The Road To The World Cup</n><t>O</t>    <k>India take on Australia at the Oval in the group stage of the 2019 ICC Cricket World Cup. India won their opener against South Africa while Australia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2019-07-16 18:00:00" d="2019-07-16 19:00:00"><n>The Road To The World Cup</n><t>O</t>    <k>England meet West Indies in Southampton in the 2019 ICC Cricket World Cup. England come here after getting their World Cup back on track with a 106-run</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2019-07-16 19:00:00" d="2019-07-16 20:00:00"><n>The Road To The World Cup</n><t>O</t>    <k>New Zealand take on South Africa at Edgbaston in the 2019 ICC Cricket World Cup. New Zealand come into this unbeaten in this World Cup, South Africa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2019-07-16 20:00:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00"><n>The Road To The World Cup</n><t>O</t>    <k>A huge match from the 2019 ICC Cricket World Cup as England host old rivals Australia at Lord's. Australia have won five of six games, while England have won four of six</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 22:00:00"><n>The Road To The World Cup</n><t>O</t>    <k>Hosts England take on India at Edgbaston in the 2019 ICC Cricket World Cup. England need a win here as they look to remain in the driving seat to finish in the top four</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2019-07-16 22:00:00" d="2019-07-16 23:00:00"><n>The Road To The World Cup</n><t>O</t>    <k>England take on New Zealand in Durham in the 2019 ICC Cricket World Cup. England know that a win here will secure their passage to the semi-finals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2019-07-16 23:00:00" d="2019-07-17 00:00:00"><n>The Road To The World Cup</n><t>O</t>    <k>The final of the 2019 ICC Cricket World Cup from the iconic Lord's in London</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2019-07-17 00:00:00" d="2019-07-17 02:00:00"><n>How The 2011 ICC World Cup Was Won</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at how the 2011 ICC Cricket World Cup was won. The tournament was jointly held in India, Sri Lanka and Bangladesh. Australia went into the event</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2019-07-17 02:00:00" d="2019-07-17 04:00:00"><n>How The 2015 ICC World Cup Was Won</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at the 2015 ICC Cricket World Cup finals from Australia and New Zealand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2019-07-17 04:00:00" d="2019-07-17 07:00:00"><n>Cricket World Cup Classic</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some classic matches from the ICC Cricket World Cup. Here is England against South Africa from the group stage of the 2011 tournament</k>  </p>
</a>
