<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="17" t="2021-07-09 07:14:49"><p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-14 05:00:00" d="2021-07-14 05:30:00"><n>Best of The Women's World T20</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the best matches from the ICC Women's T20 World Cup. Here, hosts England meet rivals Australia in the semi-finals of the competition's inaugural event in 2009</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-14 05:30:00" d="2021-07-14 06:00:00"><n>Best of The Women's World T20</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the best matches from the ICC Women's T20 World Cup. Here, the final of the inaugural 2009 event between hosts England and New Zealand at Lord's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-14 06:00:00" d="2021-07-14 06:30:00"><n>ICC Women's WC 2017 SF Hlts</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the semi-final of the 2017 Women's Cricket World Cup, as hosts England faced South Africa in Bristol in a tense encounter that went to the final over</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-14 06:30:00" d="2021-07-14 07:00:00"><n>ICC Women's WC 2017 Final Hlts</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember one of English cricket's finest hours as England met India in the 2017 ICC Women's World Cup final in front of a capacity crowd at Lord's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-14 07:00:00" d="2021-07-14 08:00:00"><n>England v India Women 1st ODI Hlts</n><t>O</t>    <k>England Women and India Women begin their ODI series with the opening match in Bristol. This is the first of three games in the series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-14 08:00:00" d="2021-07-14 09:00:00"><n>England v India Women 2nd ODI Hlts</n><t>O</t>    <k>England Women and India Women meet in Taunton in the second ODI of three. England cruised to victory in the opener as they won by eight wickets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-14 09:00:00" d="2021-07-14 10:00:00"><n>England v India Women 3rd ODI Hlts</n><t>O</t>    <k>The third and final ODI of the series between England Women and India Women, held in Worcester. England won by five wickets in the second match</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-14 10:00:00" d="2021-07-14 14:00:00"><n>England v India Women 1st T20</n><t>O</t>    <k>England Women host India Women in the opening T20 match of three, held in Northampton. This comes after the ODI series, which England won 2-1</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-14 14:00:00" d="2021-07-14 18:00:00"><n>England v India Women 2nd T20</n><t>O</t>    <k>England Women host India Women in the second T20 match of three, held in Hove</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-14 18:00:00" d="2021-07-14 18:30:00"><n>Best of The Women's World T20</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the best matches from the ICC Women's T20 World Cup. Here, the final of the inaugural 2009 event between hosts England and New Zealand at Lord's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-14 18:30:00" d="2021-07-14 19:00:00"><n>ICC Women's WC 2017 Final Hlts</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember one of English cricket's finest hours as England met India in the 2017 ICC Women's World Cup final in front of a capacity crowd at Lord's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-14 19:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:00:00"><n>Live England v India Women 3rd T20</n><t>O</t>    <k>England and India meet in the third and final T20 match of their series in Chelmsford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-14 23:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:55:00"><n>England v Pakistan 3rd ODI Hlts</n><t>O</t>    <k>England and Pakistan continue their white ball tour with the third of three ODI matches in Cardiff. These sides will go on to play three T20s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-14 23:55:00" d="2021-07-15 00:15:00"><n>25 Years of Women's Cricket on Sky</n><t>O</t>    <k>Twenty five years after showing women's cricket for the first time in 1996, Sky Sports looks back at some of the sport's most memorable moments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-15 00:15:00" d="2021-07-15 00:45:00"><n>Talking Cricket: Wasim &amp; Waqar</n><t>O</t>    <k>One of cricket's most feared bowling attacks, Wasim Akram and Waqar Younis were game-changers for Pakistan during their careers. Sky Sports Cricket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-15 00:45:00" d="2021-07-15 01:00:00"><n>Best of T20 Blast Finals Day</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some of the best ever T20 Blast finals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="503" o="2021-07-15 01:00:00" d="2021-07-15 05:00:00"><n>England v India Women 3rd T20</n><t>O</t>    <k>England and India meet in the third and final T20 match of their series in Chelmsford</k>  </p>
</a>
