<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="44" t="2019-08-15 22:53:17"><p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 05:00:00" d="2019-08-21 05:30:00"><n>Sporting Records</n><t>O</t>    <k>An in-depth look at some of the greatest milestones ever recorded in sport. Here, the records of runner Jim Hines, gymnast Nadia Comaneci, and cricketer Chris Gayle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 05:30:00" d="2019-08-21 06:00:00"><n>Sporting Records</n><t>O</t>    <k>An in-depth look at some of the greatest milestones ever recorded in sport. Here, the focus is on time, and the feats of Jesse Owens, Greg Lemond</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 06:00:00" d="2019-08-21 06:30:00"><n>Sporting Greats: Jesse Owens</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the career of Jesse Owens, the pioneering track and field athlete who overcame racial discrimination to claim four gold medals at the 1936 Olympics in Berlin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 06:30:00" d="2019-08-21 07:00:00"><n>Sporting Greats: Greg Lemond</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at the career of legendary American road cyclist Greg LeMond, who was a two-time winner of the World Cycling Championship, and three-time winner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 07:00:00" d="2019-08-21 07:30:00"><n>Boxing Gold: Haye v Gurov/Bonin</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic boxing action. Here, look back on David Haye's bouts with Vincenzo Rossitto, Alexander Gurov, and Tomasz Bonin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 07:30:00" d="2019-08-21 08:00:00"><n>Boxing Gold: Bellew v Flores</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic boxing action. Here, Tony Bellew defends his WBC cruiserweight title against American BJ Flores at the Echo Arena</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 08:00:00" d="2019-08-21 08:30:00"><n>Hooked On Africa 2018-19</n><t>O</t>    <k>Alphonse Island is a nature haven in the Indian Ocean, as the waters are home to many aquatic species and the island is the base of the Alphonse fishing company</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 08:30:00" d="2019-08-21 08:45:00"><n>The Bolero</n><t>O</t>    <k>On Valentine's Day 1984, ice-dancing pair Jayne Torvill and Christopher Dean skated their way into sporting lore with their 'Bolero' - achieving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 08:45:00" d="2019-08-21 09:00:00"><n>Record Breaker</n><t>O</t>    <k>In 1994, West Indies batsman Brian Lara smashed his way into the record books as he scored the most runs in one Test innings - making 375 against England</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 09:00:00" d="2019-08-21 09:30:00"><n>Darts Gold: WDC Finals 10/11</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic darts matches. Here are the 2011 World Darts Championship finals at Alexandra Palace</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 09:30:00" d="2019-08-21 10:00:00"><n>Boxing Gold: Bellew v Flores</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic boxing action. Here, Tony Bellew defends his WBC cruiserweight title against American BJ Flores at the Echo Arena</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 10:00:00" d="2019-08-21 11:00:00"><n u="America's Game: Rams">America's Game: Rams 1999</n><t>O</t>    <k>Highly acclaimed documentary in which the stories behind each Super Bowl winning team are told by the people involved. This programme follows the 1999 St Louis Rams side</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 11:00:00" d="2019-08-21 11:30:00"><n>Sporting Records</n><t>O</t>    <k>An in-depth look at some of the greatest milestones ever recorded in sports. Here, a look at speed, focusing on sprinter Usain Bolt, cricketer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 11:30:00" d="2019-08-21 12:00:00"><n>Hooked On Africa 2018-19</n><t>O</t>    <k>Alphonse Island is a nature haven in the Indian Ocean, as the waters are home to many aquatic species and the island is the base of the Alphonse fishing company</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 12:00:00" d="2019-08-21 13:00:00"><n>America's Game: Giants 2011</n><t>O</t>    <k>Highly acclaimed documentary in which the stories behind each Super Bowl-winning team are told by the people involved. Here is the story of the 2011 New York Giants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 13:00:00" d="2019-08-21 14:00:00"><n>A Football Life: Warren Sapp</n><t>O</t>    <k>Series profiling some of the most significant and spectacular players in the history of American football. Here the focus is on former Tampa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 14:00:00" d="2019-08-21 14:30:00"><n>Sporting Records</n><t>O</t>    <k>An in-depth look at some of the greatest milestones ever recorded in sports. Here, a look at speed, focusing on sprinter Usain Bolt, cricketer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 14:30:00" d="2019-08-21 15:00:00"><n>Sporting Records</n><t>O</t>    <k>An in-depth look at some of the greatest records across a variety of sports. Here, a look at medals - athlete Mo Farah, footballer Clarence Seedorf</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 15:00:00" d="2019-08-21 15:30:00"><n>Hooked On Africa 2018-19</n><t>O</t>    <k>Alphonse Island is a nature haven in the Indian Ocean, as the waters are home to many aquatic species and the island is the base of the Alphonse fishing company</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 15:30:00" d="2019-08-21 15:45:00"><n>Darts Gold: Grand Prix Final 2012</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive classic darts matches. Here is Michael van Gerwen against Mervyn King in the final of the 2012 World Grand Prix at Dublin's Citywest Hotel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 15:45:00" d="2019-08-21 16:00:00"><n>Darts Gold: Taylor v Jenkins 2013</n><t>O</t>    <k>Phil Taylor v Terry Jenkins in the second round of the 2013 World Matchplay Darts. Jenkins was the last person to beat Taylor in this event in 2007</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 16:00:00" d="2019-08-21 16:30:00"><n>Boxing Gold: Bellew v Flores</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic boxing action. Here, Tony Bellew defends his WBC cruiserweight title against American BJ Flores at the Echo Arena</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 16:30:00" d="2019-08-21 17:00:00"><n>Darts Gold</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic darts matches. Here are the 1995 World Darts Championship finals at Circus Tavern</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 17:00:00" d="2019-08-21 17:15:00"><n>Darts Gold: Taylor v Mardle</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic darts matches. Here Phil Taylor takes on Wayne Mardle in the semi-finals of the 2006 World Darts Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 17:15:00" d="2019-08-21 17:30:00"><n>Darts Gold: Anderson v Baxter</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic darts action. Here, Bob Anderson takes on Ronnie Baxter in the round of 16 stage at the 2005 PDC World Darts Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 17:30:00" d="2019-08-21 18:00:00"><n>Sporting Records</n><t>O</t>    <k>An in-depth look at some of the greatest milestones ever recorded in sport. Here, in distance, cyclist Bradley Wiggins, marathon runner Dennis Kimetto</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 18:00:00" d="2019-08-21 18:30:00"><n>Salomon Golden Trail Race 4 #11</n><t>O</t>    <k>The fourth race of the Salomon Golden Trail takes competitors to the Sierre-Zinal in Switzerland. This is the fastest race of the series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 18:30:00" d="2019-08-21 19:00:00"><n>Fast Zone 2019</n><t>O</t>    <k>Catch up on the all-action world of motorsport with this special programme. From karting to F1 and everything in between, enjoy the fastest cars in thrilling races</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 19:00:00" d="2019-08-21 20:00:00"><n>Sports Unlimited</n><t>O</t>    <k>The show that combines alternative, extreme and unusual sporting activities in dynamic style. A comprehensive round-up of local and international sports</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 20:00:00" d="2019-08-21 20:30:00"><n>Salomon Golden Trail Race 4 #11</n><t>O</t>    <k>The fourth race of the Salomon Golden Trail takes competitors to the Sierre-Zinal in Switzerland. This is the fastest race of the series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 20:30:00" d="2019-08-21 20:40:00"><n>My Icon: Linford Christie</n><t>O</t>    <k>In the next episode of this special series, former sprint superstar and Olympic gold medalist Linford Christie discusses the individuals that have inspired</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 20:40:00" d="2019-08-21 22:45:00"><n>Live EFL: Charlton v N. Forest</n><t>O</t>    <k>No programme information available</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 22:45:00" d="2019-08-21 23:15:00"><n>Motorsport Mundial 2019</n><t>O</t>    <k>The latest motorsport news and action from around the globe. From Superbikes to Formula 1, Motorsport Mundial has the latest action and talking points from the sport</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-21 23:15:00" d="2019-08-22 00:15:00"><n>Watersports World</n><t>O</t>    <k>The world's ultimate watersports show, with comprehensive coverage of the recent power, sail and surf competitions from around the globe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-22 00:15:00" d="2019-08-22 00:45:00"><n>Motorsport Mundial 2019</n><t>O</t>    <k>The latest motorsport news and action from around the globe. From Superbikes to Formula 1, Motorsport Mundial has the latest action and talking points from the sport</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-22 00:45:00" d="2019-08-22 01:00:00"><n>Darts Gold</n><t>O</t>    <k>Phil Taylor takes on Gary Anderson in the quarter-finals of the 2013 World Grand Prix in Dublin. Taylor saw off Paul Nicholson in the previous round, while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-22 01:00:00" d="2019-08-22 02:00:00"><n u="America's Game: Cowboys">America's Game: Cowboys 1993</n><t>O</t>    <k>Documentary series in which the stories behind each Super Bowl-winning team are told by those involved. Here, a look at the 1993 Dallas Cowboys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-22 02:00:00" d="2019-08-22 02:15:00"><n>Grand Final Gold 2011</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive the 2011 Super League Grand Final between Leeds Rhinos and St Helens at Old Trafford in Manchester</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-22 02:15:00" d="2019-08-22 02:30:00"><n>Grand Final Gold 2012</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive the 2012 Super League Grand Final between Leeds Rhinos and Warrington Wolves. The Rhinos were gunning for their fifth title in six seasons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-22 02:30:00" d="2019-08-22 02:45:00"><n>Grand Final Gold 2013</n><t>O</t>    <k>The 2013 Super League Grand Final between Warrington Wolves and Wigan Warriors. Warrington beat Huddersfield Giants in the semi-finals, while Wigan saw off Leeds Rhinos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-22 02:45:00" d="2019-08-22 03:00:00"><n>Super League Grand Final Gold</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive the 2014 Super League Grand Final between St Helens and Wigan Warriors. The game is remembered for Ben Flower's third-minute red card</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-22 03:00:00" d="2019-08-22 04:30:00"><n>NFLGreat Games: '74 Miami/Oakland</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some of the greatest games in the history of the NFL. Oakland Raiders and the Miami Dolphins meet at the Oakland Coliseum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-22 04:30:00" d="2019-08-22 04:45:00"><n>Legends of Darts: John Lowe</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest darts players of all time. Here the focus is on three-time world champion John Lowe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-22 04:45:00" d="2019-08-22 07:45:00"><n>Legends of Darts: Keith Deller</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest darts players of all time. Here the focus is on 1983 BDO World Champion Keith Deller</k>  </p>
</a>
