<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="37" t="2019-08-13 02:28:36"><p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 05:30:00" d="2019-08-18 06:00:00"><n>Sporting Records</n><t>O</t>    <k>An in-depth look at some of the greatest records across a variety of sports. Here, a look at medals - athlete Mo Farah, footballer Clarence Seedorf</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 06:00:00" d="2019-08-18 06:30:00"><n>Sporting Greats: Paula Radcliffe</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at the career of one of the sporting world's greats. Here, English distance runner Paula Radcliffe - a world record holder in the Marathon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 06:30:00" d="2019-08-18 07:00:00"><n>Sporting Greats: Dan Carter</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at the career of one of the sporting world's greats. Here, New Zealand rugby star Dan Carter, the all-time highest scorer in Test rugby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 07:00:00" d="2019-08-18 08:00:00"><n>Haye v Bellew: The Best Bits</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at the best moments as David Haye fought Tony Bellew in their first dramatic bout at London's O2 Arena in March 2017</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 08:00:00" d="2019-08-18 08:15:00"><n>Rumble In The Jungle</n><t>O</t>    <k>The Rumble in the Jungle, Kinshasa, 1974 - a night remembered as one of the most remarkable ever. Muhammad Ali and George Foreman squared up in a world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 08:15:00" d="2019-08-18 08:30:00"><n>Miracle On Ice</n><t>O</t>    <k>Heading into the 1980 Olympics, the Soviet Union was expected to win a fifth straight gold. The USA team, inexperienced college students, were outsiders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 08:30:00" d="2019-08-18 08:45:00"><n u="7 From">7 From 7</n><t>O</t>    <k>Mark Spitz - considered one of the greatest swimmers ever. The American made history at the 1972 Olympic Games: after years of uninspired performances</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 08:45:00" d="2019-08-18 09:00:00"><n>The Ball Of The Century</n><t>O</t>    <k>The ball of the century: Shane Warne's leg-break to Mike Gatting at Old Trafford in The Ashes in 1993, a memorable moment that introduced the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 09:00:00" d="2019-08-18 10:00:00"><n>Haye v Bellew: The Best Bits</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at the best moments as David Haye fought Tony Bellew in their first dramatic bout at London's O2 Arena in March 2017</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 10:00:00" d="2019-08-18 11:00:00"><n u="America's Game: Broncos">America's Game: Broncos 1997</n><t>O</t>    <k>Highly acclaimed documentary in which the stories behind each Super Bowl winning team are told by the people involved. This week follows the 1997 Denver Broncos side</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 11:00:00" d="2019-08-18 11:30:00"><n>Sporting Records</n><t>O</t>    <k>An in-depth look at some of the greatest records ever achieved in sport. Here, a look at teams, with a focus on the 1992 USA basketball team, Spain's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 11:30:00" d="2019-08-18 12:00:00"><n>Sporting Records</n><t>O</t>    <k>An in-depth look at some of the greatest milestones ever recorded in sport. Here, in distance, cyclist Bradley Wiggins, marathon runner Dennis Kimetto</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 12:00:00" d="2019-08-18 13:00:00"><n>America's Game: Ravens 2012</n><t>O</t>    <k>Highly acclaimed documentary series in which the stories behind each Super Bowl-winning team are told by the people involved</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 13:00:00" d="2019-08-18 13:15:00"><n>Legends of Darts: Phil Taylor</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest darts players of all time. Here the focus is on 16-time world champion Phil Taylor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 13:15:00" d="2019-08-18 13:30:00"><n>Legends of Darts: John Part</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest darts players of all time. Here the focus is on Canada's three-time world champion John Part</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 13:30:00" d="2019-08-18 13:45:00"><n>Legends of Darts: Adrian Lewis</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest darts players of all time. Here the focus is on two-time world champion Adrian Lewis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 13:45:00" d="2019-08-18 13:55:00"><n>Rugby Gold Shorts 2016</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive a classic rugby match. Here, rewind to November 2017 and the autumn international clash between England and Australia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 13:55:00" d="2019-08-18 16:00:00"><n>Live Currie Cup: Lions v Sharks</n><t>O</t>    <k>Lions take on Sharks at the Emirates Airline Park in Johannesburg in the sixth round of fixtures in the Currie Cup</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 16:00:00" d="2019-08-18 16:15:00"><n>Legends of Darts: Phil Taylor</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest darts players of all time. Here the focus is on 16-time world champion Phil Taylor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 16:15:00" d="2019-08-18 16:30:00"><n>Legends of Darts: John Part</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest darts players of all time. Here the focus is on Canada's three-time world champion John Part</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 16:30:00" d="2019-08-18 17:00:00"><n>Darts Gold: WDC Finals 10/11</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic darts matches. Here are the 2011 World Darts Championship finals at Alexandra Palace</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 17:00:00" d="2019-08-18 17:15:00"><n>Legends of Darts: Adrian Lewis</n><t>O</t>    <k>A celebration of some of the finest darts players of all time. Here the focus is on two-time world champion Adrian Lewis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 17:15:00" d="2019-08-18 17:30:00"><n>Darts Gold: Lewis v Van Barneveld</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic darts matches. Here Adrian Lewis takes on Raymond van Barneveld in the last 16 of the 2015 World Darts Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 17:30:00" d="2019-08-18 18:00:00"><n>Sporting Records</n><t>O</t>    <k>An in-depth look at some of the greatest records across a variety of sports. Here, the greatest in their fields - boxer Muhammad Ali, cyclist Eddy Merckx</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 18:00:00" d="2019-08-18 18:30:00"><n>Sporting Records</n><t>O</t>    <k>An in-depth look at some of the greatest milestones ever recorded in sports. Here, a look at speed, focusing on sprinter Usain Bolt, cricketer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 18:30:00" d="2019-08-18 19:00:00"><n>Darts Gold</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic darts matches. Here are the 2003 World Darts Championship finals at Circus Tavern</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 19:00:00" d="2019-08-18 20:00:00"><n u="America's Game: Redskins">America's Game: Redskins 1982</n><t>O</t>    <k>Highly acclaimed documentary in which the stories behind each Super Bowl winning team are told by the people involved. Here, the focus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 20:00:00" d="2019-08-18 21:00:00"><n>A Football Life: Terrell Davis</n><t>O</t>    <k>A series profiling some of the most significant and spectacular players in NFL history. This episode focuses on former Denver Broncos running-back Terrell Davis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 21:00:00" d="2019-08-18 22:00:00"><n>Haye v Bellew: The Best Bits</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at the best moments as David Haye fought Tony Bellew in their first dramatic bout at London's O2 Arena in March 2017</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 22:00:00" d="2019-08-18 22:30:00"><n>Sporting Records</n><t>O</t>    <k>An in-depth look at some of the greatest records across a variety of sports. Here, a look at medals - athlete Mo Farah, footballer Clarence Seedorf</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 22:30:00" d="2019-08-18 23:00:00"><n>Sporting Records</n><t>O</t>    <k>An in-depth look at some of the greatest sporting milestones ever recorded. Here, a focus on age, featuring football icon Pele, boxer Bernard Hopkins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 23:00:00" d="2019-08-18 23:30:00"><n>Darts Gold: WDC Finals 06/07</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive some classic darts matches. Here are the 2006 and 2007 PDC World Darts Championship finals at Circus Tavern</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 23:30:00" d="2019-08-18 23:45:00"><n>Darts Gold: Taylor v Jenkins 2013</n><t>O</t>    <k>Phil Taylor v Terry Jenkins in the second round of the 2013 World Matchplay Darts. Jenkins was the last person to beat Taylor in this event in 2007</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-18 23:45:00" d="2019-08-19 00:00:00"><n>Darts Gold: Lewis v MVG 2013</n><t>O</t>    <k>Adrian Lewis meets Michael Van Gerwen in the semi-finals of the 2013 World Matchplay. Lewis beat Andy Hamilton in the previous round, while Van Gerwen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-19 00:00:00" d="2019-08-19 01:00:00"><n>AJ: The Untold Truth</n><t>O</t>    <k>Anthony Joshua joins Anna Woolhouse to discuss what went wrong against Andy Ruiz Jr, and what he believes will happen in the rematch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-19 01:00:00" d="2019-08-19 02:00:00"><n u="America's Game: Giants">America's Game: Giants 1990</n><t>O</t>    <k>Highly acclaimed documentary in which the stories behind each Super Bowl-winning team are told by the people involved. Here is a look at the New York Giants of 1990</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="504" o="2019-08-19 02:00:00" d="2019-08-19 05:00:00"><n>Live NFL: Seattle @ Minnesota</n><t>O</t>    <k>No programme information available</k>  </p>
</a>
