<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2021-07-08 05:06:06"><p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-13 05:00:00" d="2021-07-13 06:00:00"><n u="The Open Films: Faldo">The Open Films: Faldo 1990</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some of the best contests at The Open in years gone by. Here, The 1990 Open at the Old Course, St Andrews, where Nick Faldo was going</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-13 06:00:00" d="2021-07-13 07:00:00"><n u="The Open Films: Faldo">The Open Films: Faldo 1992</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some of the best contests at The Open in years gone by. Here, The 1992 Open at Muirfield, where Nick Faldo was going for his third Open title</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-13 07:00:00" d="2021-07-13 08:00:00"><n>Best of The Openzone</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at the best moments from The Open Zone at Royal Troon in 2016, with masterclasses and demonstrations from some of golf's finest players</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-13 08:00:00" d="2021-07-13 09:00:00"><n>Best of The Openzone</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look at the best moments from The Open Zone at Royal Birkdale in 2017, with masterclasses and demonstrations from some of golf's finest players</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-13 09:00:00" d="2021-07-13 11:00:00"><n>From The Open Championship</n><t>O</t>    <k>Live coverage ahead of the start of The Open, which is held this year at Royal St George's Golf Club. Ireland's Shane Lowry won the tournament</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-13 11:00:00" d="2021-07-13 12:00:00"><n u="The Open Films: Nicklaus">The Open Films: Nicklaus 1970</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some of the best contests at The Open Championship in years gone by. Here, a look at 1970, held on the Old Course at St Andrews, which ended</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-13 12:00:00" d="2021-07-13 14:00:00"><n>From The Open Championship</n><t>O</t>    <k>Live coverage ahead of the start of The Open, which is held this year at Royal St George's Golf Club. Ireland's Shane Lowry won the tournament</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-13 14:00:00" d="2021-07-13 15:00:00"><n u="The Open Films: Ballesteros">The Open Films: Ballesteros 1979</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some of the best contests at The Open in years gone by. Here, 1979, where a memorable week was in store for Seve Ballesteros at Royal Lytham</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-13 15:00:00" d="2021-07-13 16:00:00"><n u="The Open Films: Ballesteros">The Open Films: Ballesteros 1984</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some of the best contests at The Open in years gone by. Here, The 1984 Open at the Old Course at St Andrews, where Tom Watson was aiming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-13 16:00:00" d="2021-07-13 17:00:00"><n u="The Open Films: Ballesteros">The Open Films: Ballesteros 1988</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some of the best contests at The Open in years gone by. Here, The 1988 Open at Royal Lytham &amp; St Annes Golf Club, as heavy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-13 17:00:00" d="2021-07-13 19:00:00"><n>Live From The Open Championship</n><t>O</t>    <k>All the build up ahead of the year's final Major, as The 149th Open Championship gears up at Royal St George's Golf Club, England</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-13 19:00:00" d="2021-07-13 19:30:00"><n>Nick Dougherty's Tee Time Tips</n><t>O</t>    <k>Sky Sports Golf pundit and former European Tour star Nick Dougherty provides a special set of Tee Time Tips from The 149th Open Championship at Royal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-13 19:30:00" d="2021-07-13 20:00:00"><n>Live: The Open Countdown</n><t>O</t>    <k>The countdown to The 2021 Open Championship kicks off with analysis and discussion of all of the big talking points</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-13 20:00:00" d="2021-07-13 21:00:00"><n>The Open Films: Clarke 2011</n><t>O</t>    <k>A look back at some of the best contests at The Open. Here, a look at The 2011 Open at Royal St George's Golf Club, as a Northern Irish golfer enjoyed a memorable week</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-13 21:00:00" d="2021-07-13 23:00:00"><n>From The Open Championship</n><t>O</t>    <k>All the build up ahead of the year's final Major, as The 149th Open Championship gears up at Royal St George's Golf Club, England</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-13 23:00:00" d="2021-07-14 00:00:00"><n>The Golf Podcast</n><t>O</t>    <k>The Sky Sports Golf Vodcast series, diving deeper behind the scenes into the stories behind the latest events in golf, and all the major talking points</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-14 00:00:00" d="2021-07-14 01:00:00"><n>1999 The Toughest Open</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive the 1999 Open Championship, held at Carnoustie. This tournament - which would go down as one of the toughest in Open history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-14 01:00:00" d="2021-07-14 03:00:00"><n>How The 2016 Open Was Won</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive the dramatic 2016 Open Championship from Royal Troon Golf Club in Scotland. At the end of four hotly contested days, it would</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-14 03:00:00" d="2021-07-14 05:00:00"><n>How The 2017 Open Was Won</n><t>O</t>    <k>As The 2017 Open Championship at Royal Birkdale draws to its conclusion, take a look back and see how the Claret Jug was won</k>  </p>
</a>
