<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2021-07-09 07:14:49"><p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-14 05:00:00" d="2021-07-14 05:30:00"><n>Chronicles Of A Champion Golfer Greg Norman</n><t>O</t>    <k>Born down under, Greg Norman was twice Open Champion and dominated golf for a decade. Always charismatic, at times controversial, he won 91 titles worldwide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-14 05:30:00" d="2021-07-14 06:00:00"><n>Chronicles Of A Champion Golfer Tom Watson</n><t>O</t>    <k>A product of the US, Watson crossed the Atlantic to win British hearts. A fascinating look at the epic battles and agonising disappointment for The Open's greatest champion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-14 06:00:00" d="2021-07-14 07:00:00"><n>The Open Films: Harrington 2007</n><t>O</t>    <k>Sky Sports looks back at some of the best contests at The Open in years gone by. Here, the focus is on The 2007 Open at Carnoustie, which</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-14 07:00:00" d="2021-07-14 08:00:00"><n>Best of The Openzone</n><t>O</t>    <k>Remember the best moments from the 2018 Sky Sports Open Zone, with interviews and golf tips from around the golfing world at The Open at Carnoustie Golf Links</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-14 08:00:00" d="2021-07-14 09:00:00"><n>The Open Films: Harrington 2008</n><t>O</t>    <k>Sky Sports looks back at some of the best contests at The Open. Here, the focus is on The 2008 Open at Royal Birkdale - Padraig Harrington returned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-14 09:00:00" d="2021-07-14 11:00:00"><n>From The Open Championship</n><t>O</t>    <k>All the build up ahead of the year's final Major, as The 149th Open Championship gears up at Royal St George's Golf Club, England</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-14 11:00:00" d="2021-07-14 12:00:00"><n>The Golf Podcast</n><t>O</t>    <k>The Sky Sports Golf Vodcast series, diving deeper behind the scenes into the stories behind the latest events in golf, and all the major talking points</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-14 12:00:00" d="2021-07-14 14:00:00"><n>From The Open Championship</n><t>O</t>    <k>All the build up ahead of the year's final Major, as The 149th Open Championship gears up at Royal St George's Golf Club, England</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-14 14:00:00" d="2021-07-14 14:30:00"><n>The Clara Jug</n><t>O</t>    <k>A special documentary celebrating Shane Lowry - who hails from Clara in the Republic of Ireland - and his remarkable victory in The 2019 Open Championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-14 14:30:00" d="2021-07-14 15:00:00"><n>Nick Dougherty's Tee Time Tips</n><t>O</t>    <k>Sky Sports Golf pundit and former European Tour star Nick Dougherty provides a special set of Tee Time Tips from The 149th Open Championship at Royal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-14 15:00:00" d="2021-07-14 18:00:00"><n>Live The Open Practice Round</n><t>O</t>    <k>Live coverage of a practice round of The Open Championship, held this year at The Royal St George's Golf Club</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-14 18:00:00" d="2021-07-14 18:30:00"><n>Nick Dougherty's Tee Time Tips</n><t>O</t>    <k>Sky Sports Golf pundit and former European Tour star Nick Dougherty provides a special set of Tee Time Tips from The 149th Open Championship at Royal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-14 18:30:00" d="2021-07-14 19:30:00"><n>The Golf Podcast</n><t>O</t>    <k>The Sky Sports Golf Vodcast series, diving deeper behind the scenes into the stories behind the latest events in golf, and all the major talking points</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-14 19:30:00" d="2021-07-14 20:00:00"><n>Live: The Open Countdown</n><t>O</t>    <k>The countdown to The 2021 Open Championship kicks off with analysis and discussion of all of the big talking points</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-14 20:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:00:00"><n>The Open Practice Round</n><t>O</t>    <k>Live coverage of a practice round of The Open Championship, held this year at The Royal St George's Golf Club</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-14 23:00:00" d="2021-07-15 00:00:00"><n>1999 The Toughest Open</n><t>O</t>    <k>A chance to relive the 1999 Open Championship, held at Carnoustie. This tournament - which would go down as one of the toughest in Open history</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-15 00:00:00" d="2021-07-15 01:00:00"><n>The Golf Podcast</n><t>O</t>    <k>The Sky Sports Golf Vodcast series, diving deeper behind the scenes into the stories behind the latest events in golf, and all the major talking points</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-15 01:00:00" d="2021-07-15 03:00:00"><n>How The 2018 Open Was Won</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive all the drama from The 2018 Open Championship at Carnoustie. Take a look at all the key shots and moments on the journey to winning the Claret Jug</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="505" o="2021-07-15 03:00:00" d="2021-07-15 05:00:00"><n>How The 2019 Open Was Won</n><t>O</t>    <k>Relive all the drama from The 2019 Open Championship at Royal Portrush. Take a look at all the key shots and moments on the journey to winning the Claret Jug</k>  </p>
</a>
