<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a><n>Slovenski magazin</n><s o="2019-07-23 14:45:00" d="2019-07-23 15:25:00" n="Slovenija 2" id_tv="510"></s><p><k>Mozaično izobraževalna oddaja</k><d>Mokrišča so med najbolj ogroženimi ekosistemi na našem planetu. 
Grad Snežnik velja za enega najlepših v naši državi, danes ga upravlja Narodni muzej Slovenije.
V podzemlju Celja je na ogled edinstveno arheološko najdišče v naši državi, izhaja iz časov rimske Celeie.
Tomaž Perko je eden redkih slikarskih mojstov, ki še obvlada stare slikarske tehnike neštetih lazur in modeliranja z barvo.
Zakojška grapa v Cerkljanskem hribovju skriva divjo, neokrnjeno naravo.



WETLANDS Wetlands are one of the most endangered ecosystems of our planet. Those that are recognized as internationally important are protected by the Ramsar Convention. Three Slovenian wetlands have in fact made it to the Ramsar List – Lake Cerknica, the Sečovlje Saltpans and the Škocjan Caves.
SNEŽNIK CASTLE
Snežnik Castle, situated in the south of the country, on the edge of extensive forests, is regarded as one of the most beautiful in Slovenia, and one of the few that has managed to preserve its original fittings from the second half of the 19th century. It was first mentioned in written records in 1269 in connection with the Lords of Snežnik of the time. After the Second World War, the castle went into the hands of the state and is now managed by the National Museum of Slovenia.
THE ROMAN CELEIA In the underground of today's Celje, the third largest city in Slovenia, there is a unique archaeological site on display to its visitors. The remains of the Roman Celeia can be found there, a rich and highly populated city also referred to as the second Troy. A walk through the ancient labyrinths reveals the beauty of Celeia, which was completely destroyed by the Huns in 475. 
PAINTER TOMAŽ PERKO 
Tomaž Perko is one of the few master painters who is still adept at the old painting techniques of applying countless glazes and modelling in colour. He is an excellent portrait painter, a sensitive observer of nature and a leading representative of sacral painting in Slovenia.
THE ZAKOJCA RAVINE 
The Cerkno hills in the west of Slovenia are crisscrossed with numerous ravines and gorges, hiding wild, unspoiled nature. Most of the ravines are difficult to hike or are inaccessible for ordinary hiking. The Zakojška grapa or the Zakojca Ravine doesn’t have a marked pathway either, so visiting it is a true adrenaline experience.

Mokrišča so med najbolj ogroženimi ekosistemi na našem planetu. 
Grad Snežnik velja za enega najlepših v naši državi, danes ga upravlja Narodni muzej Slovenije.
V podzemlju Celja je na ogled edinstveno arheološko najdišče v naši državi, izhaja iz časov rimske Celeie.
Tomaž Perko je eden redkih slikarskih mojstov, ki še obvlada stare slikarske tehnike neštetih lazur in modeliranja z barvo.
Zakojška grapa v Cerkljanskem hribovju skriva divjo, neokrnjeno naravo.



WETLANDS Wetlands are one of the most endangered ecosystems of our planet. Those that are recognized as internationally important are protected by the Ramsar Convention. Three Slovenian wetlands have in fact made it to the Ramsar List – Lake Cerknica, the Sečovlje Saltpans and the Škocjan Caves.
SNEŽNIK CASTLE
Snežnik Castle, situated in the south of the country, on the edge of extensive forests, is regarded as one of the most beautiful in Slovenia, and one of the few that has managed to preserve its original fittings from the second half of the 19th century. It was first mentioned in written records in 1269 in connection with the Lords of Snežnik of the time. After the Second World War, the castle went into the hands of the state and is now managed by the National Museum of Slovenia.
THE ROMAN CELEIA In the underground of today's Celje, the third largest city in Slovenia, there is a unique archaeological site on display to its visitors. The remains of the Roman Celeia can be found there, a rich and highly populated city also referred to as the second Troy. A walk through the ancient labyrinths reveals the beauty of Celeia, which was completely destroyed by the Huns in 475. 
PAINTER TOMAŽ PERKO 
Tomaž Perko is one of the few master painters who is still adept at the old painting techniques of applying countless glazes and modelling in colour. He is an excellent portrait painter, a sensitive observer of nature and a leading representative of sacral painting in Slovenia.
THE ZAKOJCA RAVINE 
The Cerkno hills in the west of Slovenia are crisscrossed with numerous ravines and gorges, hiding wild, unspoiled nature. Most of the ravines are difficult to hike or are inaccessible for ordinary hiking. The Zakojška grapa or the Zakojca Ravine doesn’t have a marked pathway either, so visiting it is a true adrenaline experience.</d></p><i><w>http://tv.sms.cz/televize/slovenija-2/20190723/1301045580-Slovenski-magazin</w></i><x></x></a>
