<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a><n>Songbook - Half Moon Run</n><s o="2020-06-08 11:12:00" d="2020-06-08 12:00:00" n="iConcerts" id_tv="543"></s><p><d>“I never heard anyone say that, and yeah, I know exactly what it means. It has to go in there, this has to be a song.” Every song has its own story, and we all think it’s a story we’ve heard before, but we haven’t. Songbook finds and captures these intriguing stories by pulling you into the process of writing and composing. Known for its pristine sound, cinematic 4k video and eye for detail, Songbook live-captured episodes emphasize the paramount importance of quality. It addresses the on-the-spot elements of blending song and location at the right moment. Both the magical location and remarkable music interaction will get the attention they deserve. Simply because Songbook isn’t just a live music session, it lives. This episode of Songbook showcases Half Moon Run, a Montréal-based band of four musicians that communicate through the language of music - be it dreamy alt-pop, bucolic alt-folk, or psychedelic indie rock. Since 2009, Conner Molander (vocals, guitar, keys, piano, harmonica), Dylan Phillips (vocals, drums, piano, keys), Devon Portielje (lead vocals, piano, guitar) and Isaac Symonds (vocals, drums, mandolin, synth, bass) have been stars on the rise in the music scene of their home country Canada, next conquering crowds internationally. The band's three albums - diverse in sound and overall feel - have earned Half Moon Run sold-out shows and praised festival gigs all over the world. On their latest release, 2019's &quot;A Blemish In The Great Light&quot;, the four multi-instrumentalists have elevated their sound, perfecting their individual skills and touching upon lighter notes than on previous records, all the while maintaining the complexity that sets them apart from fellow indie acts. Watch Half Moon Run perform &quot;Sun Leads Me On&quot; and &quot;Favorite Boy&quot; in the unique setting of the Dutch tram museum of Amsterdam.</d></p><i><w>http://tv.sms.cz/televize/iconcerts/20200608/1410081809-Songbook-half-moon-run</w></i><x></x></a>
