<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-05-17 04:38:01"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-24 06:00:00" d="2020-05-24 07:27:00"><n u="Handel - Messiah, HWV">Handel - Messiah, HWV 56</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Messiah (HWV 56) by Georg Frederich Handel, tells the life and suffering of Christ: a story of passion, fire, and sacrifice. This performance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-24 07:27:00" d="2020-05-24 08:27:00"><n>Couperin's Premier Livre, Masterly Mix</n><t>M</t>    <k>We have François Couperin to thank for some of the most stunning pages found in 18th-century harpsichord literature. Today, Aurélien Delage tackles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-24 08:27:00" d="2020-05-24 09:00:00"><n>CMIM - Finals - Julien van Mellaerts</n><t>M</t>    <k>Joao Araújo accompanies baritone Julien van Mellaerts (New-Zealand/UK, 1988) during the finals of the Art Song competition of the Concours musical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-24 09:00:00" d="2020-05-24 10:00:00"><n u="Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 11, Op.">Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 11, Op. 22</n><t>M</t>    <k>Italian pianist Riccardo Schwartz was born in Milan in 1986. One of his best known successes thus far, is the acclaimed concert cycle of Beethoven's 32 Sonatas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-24 10:00:00" d="2020-05-24 10:52:00"><n>Couperin - Leçons de ténebres</n><t>M</t>    <k>The French soprano Hanna Bayodi and the Portuguese Ana Quintans join the Ricercar Consort. The music is by maestro Couperin &quot;le Grand,&quot; who just prior</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-24 10:52:00" d="2020-05-24 11:56:00"><n u="Bruckner - Symphony No.">Bruckner - Symphony No. 7</n><t>Z</t>    <k>In a 2019 performance from the Muziekgebouw in Eindhoven, Hartmut Haenchen conducts the philharmonie zuidnederland for this performance of Anton Bruckner's Symphony No</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-24 11:56:00" d="2020-05-24 13:19:00"><n u="Brahms - The 3 Violin Sonatas, Op. 78, 100 &amp;">Brahms - The 3 Violin Sonatas, Op. 78, 100 &amp; 108</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this splendid 2013 concert from the Church of Verbier, Switzerland, Greek violinist Leonidas Kavakos and Chinese pianist Yuja Wang join forces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-24 13:19:00" d="2020-05-24 14:02:00"><n u="Discovering Masterpieces – Beethoven No.">Discovering Masterpieces – Beethoven No. 5</n><t>S</t>    <k>In this documentary, Ludwig van Beethoven's 'Symphony No. 5' is discussed. The piece has the character of an appeal from the very start, when the four-note</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-24 14:02:00" d="2020-05-24 15:11:00"><n u="Cursive">Cursive II</n><t>M</t>    <k>Cursive II is a sequel to the magnificent Cursive of 2001, both works of the celebrated Taiwanese dancer and choreographer Lin Hwai-min. Lin has surprised</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-24 15:11:00" d="2020-05-24 15:46:00"><n>Valls - Missa Scala Aretina</n><t>M</t>    <k>Patrick Debrabandere conducts the Vox Mago choir and orchestra in a performance of the Missa scala aretina by the Spanish composer Francisco Valls (1672-1747)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-24 15:46:00" d="2020-05-24 16:31:00"><n>Johan de Meij - Echoes of San Marco &amp; Fellini</n><t>M</t>    <k>Johan de Meij conducts two of his own works: &quot;Echoes of San Marco,&quot; a tribute to Giovanni Gabrielli and &quot;Fellini,&quot; a tribute to film composer Federico Fellini</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-24 16:31:00" d="2020-05-24 18:21:00"><n>Waldbühne 2003 - A Gershwin Night</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Waldbühne in Berlin, one of the most appealing outdoor amphitheatres on the European continent, is the home of the Berliner Philharmoniker's summer concerts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-24 18:21:00" d="2020-05-24 18:47:00"><n>Solo Finals - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Dina Ivanova (1994, Russia) performs Liszt'sTotentanz (S525), Schubert/Liszt - Auf dem wasser zu singen (S558/2) and Erlkönig (S558/4) during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-24 18:47:00" d="2020-05-24 20:05:00"><n>Rostropovich - The Indomitable Bow</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Indomitable Bow is a marvelous documentary film, offering a unique portrait of cellist Mstislav Rostropovich. The film was produced</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-24 20:05:00" d="2020-05-24 20:31:00"><n>Shostakovich - Chamber Symphony Op. 110a</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Casco Phil, The Chamber Music Orchestra of Belgium, conducted by Benjamin Haemhouts, performs Shostakovich's Chamber Symphony, Op</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-24 20:31:00" d="2020-05-24 21:00:00"><n>Christmas Concert</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Valerius Ensemble, consisting of Robert Windak (violin), Annemarie van Vliegen (violin), Eva Šušliková (viola) and Réne Geesing (cello) plays</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-24 21:00:00" d="2020-05-24 23:18:00"><n>Verdi - Rigoletto</n><t>M</t>    <k>Under the musical direction of Renato Palumbo, the Orchestre et Choeurs de l'Opéra Royal de Wallonie present the opera &quot;Rigoletto&quot;. Inspired by Victor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-24 23:18:00" d="2020-05-25 00:00:00"><n u="Mozart - Piano Concerto No. 8, K">Mozart - Piano Concerto No. 8, K 246</n><t>M</t>    <k>Soloist Christian Zacharias performs Mozart's Piano Concerto No. 8, K 246, accompanied by the Radio-Sinfonieorchester Stuttgart and conducted by Gianluigi Gelmetti</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-25 00:00:00" d="2020-05-25 02:32:00"><n>Dvořák - Rusalka</n><t>M</t>    <k>Ádám Fischer conducts the orchestra and choir of La Monnaie in a performance of Dvořák's opera Rusalka. The work remains one of the cornerstones of Czech opera houses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-25 02:32:00" d="2020-05-25 03:57:00"><n u="Trios: Tchaikovsky, Op. 50 &amp; Shostakovich, Op.">Trios: Tchaikovsky, Op. 50 &amp; Shostakovich, Op. 67</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Zadig Trio consists of the two French childhood friends Boris Borgolotto (violin), Marc Girard Garcia (cello) and the American pianist Ian Barber</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-25 03:57:00" d="2020-05-25 04:20:00"><n>Sons of Vienna: Part 2 - A Lion's Roar</n><t>S</t>    <k>The six-part series Sons of Vienna portrays extraordinary composers who were active in the cultural city of Vienna and deserve the label of genius</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-25 04:20:00" d="2020-05-25 06:00:00"><n u="Brahms - Violin Sonata No. 3, op.">Brahms - Violin Sonata No. 3, op. 108</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this splendid 2013 concert from the Church of Verbier, Switzerland, Greek violinist Leonidas Kavakos and Chinese pianist Yuja Wang join forces</k>  </p>
</a>
