<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-05-11 04:36:57"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-18 05:13:00" d="2020-05-18 06:00:00"><n>Semi Final II - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sergey Belyavskiy (1993, Russia) performs La notte (S377a) and Hungarian Rhapsody No. 12, (S379a) during semi-final II (chamber music)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-18 06:00:00" d="2020-05-18 07:23:00"><n>Jaroussky sings Bach &amp; Telemann</n><t>M</t>    <k>The film Jaroussky sings Bach &amp; Telemann is a portrait of a very special vocalist - and of two exceptional composers: Telemann and Bach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-18 07:23:00" d="2020-05-18 08:18:00"><n>Ravel &amp; Couperin - Debussy &amp; Rameau</n><t>M</t>    <k>With the Early Music Festival favourite Olga Pashchenko at the fortepiano and the harpsichord, this concert juxtaposes Baroque and neo-Baroque</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-18 08:18:00" d="2020-05-18 08:57:00"><n>Semi Final I - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Yonghwan Jeong (1991, South Korea) performs Harmonies poétiques et réligieuses, No. 7 Funérailles, S173/7 and Grandes Études de Paganini, S141 during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-18 08:57:00" d="2020-05-18 10:01:00"><n u="Prokofiev - Excerpts from Romeo &amp; Julia, Op.">Prokofiev - Excerpts from Romeo &amp; Julia, Op. 64</n><t>M</t>    <k>The beautiful Mariinsky Theatre in St. Petersburg formed the background for the 1996 edition of the annual Europe Concert of the Berliner Philharmoniker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-18 10:01:00" d="2020-05-18 10:32:00"><n>The Boy with the Wig: Kids on Mozart</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this 30-minute film, children have their say; boys and girls aged between eight and eleven recount Mozart's life in their own words. Discover Wolfgang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-18 10:32:00" d="2020-05-18 11:54:00"><n u="Brahms - The 3 Violin Sonatas, Op. 78, 100 &amp;">Brahms - The 3 Violin Sonatas, Op. 78, 100 &amp; 108</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this splendid 2013 concert from the Church of Verbier, Switzerland, Greek violinist Leonidas Kavakos and Chinese pianist Yuja Wang join forces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-18 11:54:00" d="2020-05-18 12:45:00"><n>Rachmaninov &amp; Gershwin: Rhapsodies</n><t>M</t>    <k>The National Philharmonic Orchestra of Russia and acclaimed Russian pianist Boris Berezovsky are conducted by Konstantin Khvatynets in an interpretation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-18 12:45:00" d="2020-05-18 14:01:00"><n u="Chopin - Preludes, Op.">Chopin - Preludes, Op. 28</n><t>M</t>    <k>Alessandra Amara performs Chopin's complete Preludes, Op. 28. Chopin wrote the 24 preludes between 1835 and 1839, partly at Valldemossa, Mallorca, where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-18 14:01:00" d="2020-05-18 16:15:00"><n>Bachfest 2010</n><t>M</t>    <k>András Schiff has, for the entirety of his career, performed Bach's music. In the current recital, filmed as part of the Bachfest 2010, Schiff performs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-18 16:15:00" d="2020-05-18 16:49:00"><n>Stravinsky - Le Sacre du printemps</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Berliner Philharmoniker plays Tchaikovsky's Fantasy Overture from &quot;Roméo et Juliette&quot;, Mozart is his famous Violin Concerto No. 3 in G major</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-18 16:49:00" d="2020-05-18 17:18:00"><n>CMIM - Semi Finals - John Brancy</n><t>M</t>    <k>Peter Dugan accompanies baritone John Brancy (USA, 1988) during the semi-finals of the Art Song competition of the Concours musical international</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-18 17:18:00" d="2020-05-18 18:12:00"><n>Celebrate Saint-Patrick 2019</n><t>M</t>    <k>This program brings the viewers to places most associated with Saint-Patrick and brings highlights of the annual concert, held in the cathedral that bears his name</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-18 18:12:00" d="2020-05-18 18:36:00"><n>Semi Final II - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Michelle Candotti (1996, Italy) performs Die drei Zigeuner (S383), Die Zelle in Nonnenwerth (S382bis) and La lugubre gondola (S134bis) during semi-final</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-18 18:36:00" d="2020-05-18 19:40:00"><n>Beauty is a Crime: Mendelssohn &amp; Brahms</n><t>L</t>    <k>Conductor Teodor Currentzis leads his ensemble MusicAeterna alongside violinist Patricia Kopatchinskaja in a performance of works by Brahms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-18 19:40:00" d="2020-05-18 21:00:00"><n>Mozart on Tour - Episode 4: Mannheim</n><t>S</t>    <k>The 13-part Mozart on Tour series chronicles the journeys of Mozart across Europe. Soloist Christian Zacharias performs Mozart's Piano Concerto No</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-18 21:00:00" d="2020-05-18 23:15:00"><n>Puccini - Turandot</n><t>M</t>    <k>Unfinished and rarely staged, Turandot is Giacomo Puccini's latest opera. This spectacular version of Turandot is presented in a most striking setting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-18 23:15:00" d="2020-05-19 00:00:00"><n u="Brahms - Violin Sonata No. 3, op.">Brahms - Violin Sonata No. 3, op. 108</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this splendid 2013 concert from the Church of Verbier, Switzerland, Greek violinist Leonidas Kavakos and Chinese pianist Yuja Wang join forces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-19 00:00:00" d="2020-05-19 02:38:00"><n>Prokofiev - Betrothal in a Monastery</n><t>M</t>    <k>This outstanding new staging of Betrothal in a Monastery was recorded at the Mariinsky Theatre in St. Petersburg, brilliantly performed by the Kirov Opera</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-19 02:38:00" d="2020-05-19 03:44:00"><n>Veerhavenconcert 2016</n><t>L</t>    <k>On Saturday, August 27, 2016, OVG and Sinfonia Rotterdam presented a new Veerhavenconcert under the direction of Conrad van Alphen. This fantastic concert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-19 03:44:00" d="2020-05-19 04:37:00"><n>Israel Philharmonic Orchestra: Coming Home</n><t>M</t>    <k>On the occasion of its 75th anniversary on the 24th of December, 2011, the Israel Philharmonic Orchestra celebrates with a beautiful documentary about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-19 04:37:00" d="2020-05-19 06:00:00"><n>CMIM - Semi Finals - Axelle Fanyo</n><t>M</t>    <k>Julien LeBlanc accompanies soprano Axelle Fanyo (France, 1989) during the semi-finals of the Art Song competition of the Concours musical international</k>  </p>
</a>
