<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2020-05-31 04:38:09"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 05:04:00" d="2020-06-07 06:00:00"><n>Ennio Morricone - Filmsuite in Duo</n><t>S</t>    <k>Pietro Tagliaferri (clarinet) and Francesco Attesti (piano) play a suite with film music (C'era una volta il West - Mission - Nuovo Cinema Paradiso)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 06:00:00" d="2020-06-07 07:00:00"><n>Couperin's Premier Livre, Masterly Mix</n><t>M</t>    <k>We have François Couperin to thank for some of the most stunning pages found in 18th-century harpsichord literature. Today, Aurélien Delage tackles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 07:00:00" d="2020-06-07 08:16:00"><n>Andrea Marcon conducts La Cetra Barockorchester</n><t>M</t>    <k>Andrea Marcon conducts the La Cetra Barockorchester of Basel, accompanied by mezzo-soprano Magdalena Kožená at the 25th anniversary edition of the Swiss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 08:16:00" d="2020-06-07 08:54:00"><n u="Shostakovich - Piano Trio No.2, Op.">Shostakovich - Piano Trio No.2, Op. 67</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Zadig Trio consists of the two French childhood friends Boris Borgolotto (violin), Marc Girard Garcia (cello) and the American pianist Ian Barber</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 08:54:00" d="2020-06-07 10:00:00"><n u="Bruch - Violin Concerto No. 1, Op.">Bruch - Violin Concerto No. 1, Op. 26</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sir Simon Rattle conducts the Berliner Philharmonic and Vadim Repin during the Europakonzert of 2008 from the Tchaikovsky Conservatory. On the program</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 10:00:00" d="2020-06-07 10:49:00"><n>Josquin - Missa Gaudeamus</n><t>L</t>    <k>Energetic, intellectual, eloquent and confident: in the Missa Gaudeamus we encounter a grown-up Josquin Desprez, who shows off with bravura</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 10:49:00" d="2020-06-07 11:43:00"><n u="Sibelius – Symphony No.">Sibelius – Symphony No. 7</n><t>M</t>    <k>Hannu Lintu, Finnish Radio Symphony Orchestra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 11:43:00" d="2020-06-07 12:48:00"><n>Beauty is a Crime: Mendelssohn &amp; Brahms</n><t>L</t>    <k>Conductor Teodor Currentzis leads his ensemble MusicAeterna alongside violinist Patricia Kopatchinskaja in a performance of works by Brahms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 12:48:00" d="2020-06-07 14:03:00"><n>Mozart on Tour - Episode 3: Milan and Bologna</n><t>S</t>    <k>The 13-part Mozart on Tour series chronicles the journey of Mozart across Europe. Soloist Malcolm Frager performs Mozart's Piano Concerto No</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 14:03:00" d="2020-06-07 14:16:00"><n u="Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 24, Op.">Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 24, Op. 78</n><t>M</t>    <k>Italian pianist Riccardo Schwartz was born in Milan in 1986, and completed his studies at Conservatorio of Milan as a student of acclaimed musicians</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 14:16:00" d="2020-06-07 14:28:00"><n u="Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 25, Op.">Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 25, Op. 79</n><t>M</t>    <k>Italian pianist Riccardo Schwartz was born in Milan in 1986, and completed his studies at Conservatorio of Milan as a student of acclaimed musicians</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 14:28:00" d="2020-06-07 15:58:00"><n>Prague Ballet Gala</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Prague Ballet Gala is an exclusive dance event with some of the leading ballet stars of our time, recorded at the Prague State Opera. Outstanding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 15:58:00" d="2020-06-07 16:52:00"><n>Beethoven - Symphony No. 3 'Eroica'</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Performing Ludwig van Beethoven's nine symphonies is the highlight of Claudio Abbado's 12-year tenure as chief conductor of the Berliner Philharmoniker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 16:52:00" d="2020-06-07 17:32:00"><n u="Beethoven - Symphony No. 7, Op.">Beethoven - Symphony No. 7, Op. 92</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sir Simon Rattle conducts the Berliner Philharmonic and Vadim Repin during the Europakonzert of 2008 from the Tchaikovsky Conservatory. On the program</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 17:32:00" d="2020-06-07 19:04:00"><n>Britten - War Requiem</n><t>M</t>    <k>Paul McCreesh conducts the Orquesta Gulbenkian and Coro Infantil da Academia de Música de Sana Cecília in a performance of Benjamin Britten's War Requiem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 19:04:00" d="2020-06-07 19:28:00"><n>CMIM - Semi Finals - Tomi Punkeri</n><t>M</t>    <k>Olivier Godin accompanies baritone Tomi Punkeri (Finland, 1991) during the semi-finals of the Art Song competition of the Concours musical international</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 19:28:00" d="2020-06-07 20:35:00"><n>Hearing the Silence</n><t>M</t>    <k>Claudio Abbado was one of the world's finest and most-respected conductors. Discover never-before-seen interviews combined with images of the conductor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 20:35:00" d="2020-06-07 21:00:00"><n u="Brahms - Violin Sonata No. 2, Op.">Brahms - Violin Sonata No. 2, Op. 100</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this splendid 2013 concert from the Church of Verbier, Switzerland, Greek violinist Leonidas Kavakos and Chinese pianist Yuja Wang join forces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 21:00:00" d="2020-06-07 23:20:00"><n>Shchedrin - Dead Souls</n><t>M</t>    <k>More than 30 years after the opera Dead Souls' first run, a brand new, bright and expressive staged version sees its premiere at Saint Petersburg's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 23:20:00" d="2020-06-08 00:00:00"><n>Ravel - Mother Goose Suite</n><t>M</t>    <k>Marin Alsop conducts the Britten-Pears Orchestra in a performance of Maurice Ravel's 'Ma mere l'Oye' (Mother Goose). This performance took place at Snape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-08 00:00:00" d="2020-06-08 02:32:00"><n>Dvořák - Rusalka</n><t>M</t>    <k>Ádám Fischer conducts the orchestra and choir of La Monnaie in a performance of Dvořák's opera Rusalka. The work remains one of the cornerstones of Czech opera houses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-08 02:32:00" d="2020-06-08 03:39:00"><n>Mozart Gala in Prague</n><t>M</t>    <k>This gala concert at Prague's beautiful Estates Theatre is one of the highlights of Mozart Year 2006. Conducted by Manfred Honeck, the Czech Philharmonic performs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-08 03:39:00" d="2020-06-08 04:36:00"><n>Mozart on Tour - Episode 11: Frankfurt</n><t>S</t>    <k>The 13-part Mozart on Tour series chronicles the journey of Mozart across Europe. Soloist Radu Lupu performs Mozart's Piano Concerto No</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-08 04:36:00" d="2020-06-08 06:00:00"><n>Semi Final II - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jan Hugo (1991, South Africa) performs Die drei Zigeuner (S383), Die Zelle in Nonnenwerth (S382bis) and La lugubre gondola (S134bis) during semi-final</k>  </p>
</a>
