<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="17" t="2020-05-10 04:38:17"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-17 06:00:00" d="2020-05-17 06:59:00"><n>Requiem: Ockeghem and De la Rue</n><t>M</t>    <k>&quot;Requiem&quot; – the first word of the Liturgy for the Dead – has become synonymous with a genre that has existed for more than five centuries. The polyphonist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-17 06:59:00" d="2020-05-17 08:14:00"><n>Frang, Schiff &amp; Zimmermann play Mozart and Brahms</n><t>M</t>    <k>Vilde Frang, Tabea Zimmermann and András Schiff team up for a concert at the 25th anniversary edition of the Swiss Verbier Festival in 2018</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-17 08:14:00" d="2020-05-17 09:00:00"><n u="Tchaikovsky - Piano Trio, Op.">Tchaikovsky - Piano Trio, Op. 50</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Zadig Trio consists of the two French childhood friends Boris Borgolotto (violin), Marc Girard Garcia (cello) and the American pianist Ian Barber</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-17 09:00:00" d="2020-05-17 09:59:00"><n u="Mozart - Piano Concerto No. 12, K">Mozart - Piano Concerto No. 12, K 414</n><t>M</t>    <k>Vladimir Ashkenazy performs as a soloist and conductor in Mozart's Piano Concerto No. 12, KV 414 at the Hampton Court Palace, London</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-17 09:59:00" d="2020-05-17 10:38:00"><n>Josquin -The Imitation Game</n><t>M</t>    <k>Is citation plagiarism? Not in the music of the Middle Ages and Renaissance. Composers cut, pasted, and conjured with existing melodies and created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-17 10:38:00" d="2020-05-17 11:40:00"><n u="Rachmaninov - Symphony No. 2, Op.">Rachmaninov - Symphony No. 2, Op. 27</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-17 11:40:00" d="2020-05-17 13:07:00"><n>Pianomania - Beatrice Rana</n><t>M</t>    <k>The young Italian pianist Beatrice Rana (1993) performs an interesting concert program featuring Schumann's Symphonic Etudes, Op. 13 and Blumenstück, Op</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-17 13:07:00" d="2020-05-17 14:00:00"><n>Discovering Masterpieces - Brandenburg Concertos</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of Discovering Masterpieces presents the Brandenburg Concertos by Johann Sebastian Bach (1685-1750). Musical excerpts played by the Freiburger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-17 14:00:00" d="2020-05-17 17:02:00"><n>Luigi Rossi - L'Orfeo</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Ensemble Pygmalion performs Luigi Rossi's (c. 1597-1653) l'Orfeo (1647), is an opera in three acts in a staging by Jetske Mijnssen. The Ensemble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-17 17:02:00" d="2020-05-17 18:43:00"><n>Kristine Opolais Recital</n><t>M</t>    <k>Kristine Opolais, the prima donna and star of the New York Metropolitan Opera, performs with the Latvian National Symphony Orchestra. Enjoy a beautiful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-17 18:43:00" d="2020-05-17 19:32:00"><n u="Beethoven - Violin Concerto in D major, Op.">Beethoven - Violin Concerto in D major, Op. 61</n><t>M</t>    <k>Israeli violinist Itzhak Perlman and the Berlin Philharmonic perform the Violin Concerto, Op. 61 by Ludwig van Beethoven, under the direction of Daniel Barenboim</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-17 19:32:00" d="2020-05-17 21:00:00"><n u="Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 12, Op.">Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 12, Op. 26</n><t>M</t>    <k>Italian pianist Riccardo Schwartz was born in Milan in 1986. One of his best known successes thus far, is the acclaimed concert cycle of Beethoven's 32 Sonatas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-17 21:00:00" d="2020-05-17 23:42:00"><n>Carmen - Bizet</n><t>M</t>    <k>Stefano Montanari conducts the Orchestra Choirs and Children's chorus of the Lyon Opera in a performance of Bizet's Carmen. Main soloists are Jose Maria</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-17 23:42:00" d="2020-05-18 00:00:00"><n>Stravinsky - Le Sacre - II: Le Sacrifice</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Berliner Philharmoniker plays Tchaikovsky's Fantasy Overture from &quot;Roméo et Juliette&quot;, Mozart is his famous Violin Concerto No. 3 in G major</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-18 00:00:00" d="2020-05-18 02:46:00"><n>Debussy - Pelléas et Melisande</n><t>M</t>    <k>Alain Altinoglu conducts a performance of Debussy's Pelléas et Mélisande at the Opernhaus Zürich in 2016. Main soloists are Brindley Sherratt (Arkel)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-18 02:46:00" d="2020-05-18 04:15:00"><n>Gala from Berlin 2004: Orff - Carmina Burana</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Gala from Berlin 2004 presents the outstanding Berlin Philharmonic conducted by Sir Simon Rattle, with Carl Orffs well-known 'Carmina Burana'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-18 04:15:00" d="2020-05-18 05:13:00"><n>Mozart on Tour - Episode 9 : Vienna and Prague</n><t>S</t>    <k>The 13-part Mozart on Tour series chronicles the journey of Mozart across Europe. Both soloist and conductor, Andre Previn performs with the Royal</k>  </p>
</a>
