<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="30" t="2020-04-09 04:38:19"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 06:00:00" d="2020-04-16 06:59:00"><n>The Leuven song book</n><t>M</t>    <k>The sensational Sollazzo Ensemble gives us two concerts of unique Burgundian repertoire. The Leuven Song Book, only recently discovered and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 06:59:00" d="2020-04-16 08:29:00"><n>House of Dreams</n><t>M</t>    <k>House of Dreams is an imaginative concert designed by Alison Mackay. It is a magical journey to the meeting places of baroque art and music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 08:29:00" d="2020-04-16 09:05:00"><n>CMIM - Finals - John Brancy</n><t>M</t>    <k>Peter Dugan accompanies baritone John Brancy (USA, 1988) during the finals of the Art Song competition of the Concours musical international de Montréal of 2018 (CMIM)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 09:05:00" d="2020-04-16 09:39:00"><n u="Brahms - Brahms - Violin Sonata No. 1, Op.">Brahms - Brahms - Violin Sonata No. 1, Op. 78</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this splendid 2013 concert from the Church of Verbier, Switzerland, Greek violinist Leonidas Kavakos and Chinese pianist Yuja Wang join forces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 09:39:00" d="2020-04-16 09:46:00"><n u="Bach - Well-Tempered Clavier, Book 2 No.">Bach - Well-Tempered Clavier, Book 2 No. 5</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this broadcast, Nikolai Demidenko plays Preludes and Fugues Nos. 1 to 12 (BWV 870-881) from Book Two of Bach's Well-Tempered Clavier, recorded</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 09:46:00" d="2020-04-16 09:55:00"><n>Chopin - Piano Concert No. 2 - II. Larghetto</n><t>L</t>    <k>In 1999 the annual Europa Konzert was performed in Krakow. Enjoy the Berliner Philharmoniker and Bernard Haitink in works by Mozart, Chopin and Schumann</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 09:55:00" d="2020-04-16 10:00:00"><n>Bach - The Well-Tempered Clavier Book 1 No.6</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Well-Tempered Clavier, BWV 846–893, is a collection of two series of Preludes and Fugues in all 24 major and minor keys, composed for solo keyboard by Bach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 10:00:00" d="2020-04-16 10:24:00"><n>Sons of Vienna: Part 4 - Cherchez la Femme</n><t>S</t>    <k>The six-part series Sons of Vienna portrays extraordinary composers who were active in the cultural city of Vienna and deserve the label of genius</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 10:24:00" d="2020-04-16 11:56:00"><n>Pianomania - Pedro Burmester &amp; Mário Laginha</n><t>M</t>    <k>Portuguese pianists Pedro Burmester and Mário Laginha bundle their forces in a diverse concert program with works by Piazzolla, Chopin, Debussy and Ravel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 11:56:00" d="2020-04-16 12:40:00"><n>Johan de Meij - Echoes of San Marco &amp; Fellini</n><t>M</t>    <k>Johan de Meij conducts two of his own works: &quot;Echoes of San Marco,&quot; a tribute to Giovanni Gabrielli and &quot;Fellini,&quot; a tribute to film composer Federico Fellini</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 12:40:00" d="2020-04-16 13:29:00"><n u="Tchaikovsky - Piano Trio, Op.">Tchaikovsky - Piano Trio, Op. 50</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Zadig Trio consists of the two French childhood friends Boris Borgolotto (violin), Marc Girard Garcia (cello) and the American pianist Ian Barber</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 13:29:00" d="2020-04-16 13:34:00"><n>Bach - The Well-Tempered Clavier Book 1 No.1</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Well-Tempered Clavier, BWV 846–893, is a collection of two series of Preludes and Fugues in all 24 major and minor keys, composed for solo keyboard by Bach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 13:34:00" d="2020-04-16 14:02:00"><n>Beethoven - Symphony No. 7 - IV. Allegro con brio</n><t>M</t>    <k>The beautiful Mariinsky Theatre in St. Petersburg formed the background for the 1996 edition of the annual Europe Concert of the Berliner Philharmoniker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 14:02:00" d="2020-04-16 16:40:00"><n>Prokofiev - Betrothal in a Monastery</n><t>M</t>    <k>This outstanding new staging of Betrothal in a Monastery was recorded at the Mariinsky Theatre in St. Petersburg, brilliantly performed by the Kirov Opera</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 16:40:00" d="2020-04-16 17:29:00"><n u="Brahms - Symphony No. 1, Op.">Brahms - Symphony No. 1, Op. 68</n><t>M</t>    <k>For over 20 years, the Berliner Philharmoniker have celebrated their foundation on May 1st with the annual Europa Konzert - the 2010 concert takes place in Oxford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 17:29:00" d="2020-04-16 19:03:00"><n>Riccardo Chailly conducts Mendelssohn</n><t>M</t>    <k>Riccardo Chailly's inaugural concert as Kapellmeister of the Leipzig Gewandhaus Orchestra capturing the full atmosphere of a unique musical occasion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 19:03:00" d="2020-04-16 19:26:00"><n>CMIM - Semi Finals - Clara Osowski</n><t>M</t>    <k>Olivier Godin accompanies mezzo-soprano Clara Osowski (USA, 1986) during the semi-finals of the Art Song competition of the Concours musical international</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 19:26:00" d="2020-04-16 19:51:00"><n>Semi Final II - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Alexander Ullman (1991, United Kingdom) performs Die drei Zigeuner (S383), Die Zelle in Nonnenwerth (S382bis) and La lugubre gondola, (S134bis) during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 19:51:00" d="2020-04-16 20:20:00"><n u="Brahms - Violin Sonata No. 3, op.">Brahms - Violin Sonata No. 3, op. 108</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this splendid 2013 concert from the Church of Verbier, Switzerland, Greek violinist Leonidas Kavakos and Chinese pianist Yuja Wang join forces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 20:20:00" d="2020-04-16 20:38:00"><n>Chabrier - Espana</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 20:38:00" d="2020-04-16 20:48:00"><n>Chabrier - Espana</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 20:48:00" d="2020-04-16 21:00:00"><n>Violin Concerto No. 3, K 216 - III. Rondo-allegro</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Berliner Philharmoniker plays Tchaikovsky's Fantasy Overture from &quot;Roméo et Juliette&quot;, Mozart is his famous Violin Concerto No. 3 in G major</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 21:00:00" d="2020-04-16 22:22:00"><n>Magifique</n><t>L</t>    <k>In Magifique, Thierry Malandain, director of Ballet Biarritz, dives into his memories. Set to the unifying theme of Tchaikovski's music, the show reaches</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 22:22:00" d="2020-04-16 23:26:00"><n u="Beethoven - Last Sonatas, Op. 109, 110 &amp;">Beethoven - Last Sonatas, Op. 109, 110 &amp; 111</n><t>M</t>    <k>Pianist Alexandre Tharaud's interpretation of Beethoven's last three sonatas - Opus 109, 110 and 111</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 23:26:00" d="2020-04-16 23:42:00"><n>Mozart - Symphony No. 29, K. 201 - I. Allegro</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Berlin Philharmonic, led by maestro Claudio Abbado, perform their first Europakonzert in Prague in 1991. Soloists in this first edition are soprano</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 23:42:00" d="2020-04-16 23:50:00"><n>Mozart - Violin Concerto No. 3, K 216 - II. Adagio</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Berliner Philharmoniker plays Tchaikovsky's Fantasy Overture from &quot;Roméo et Juliette&quot;, Mozart is his famous Violin Concerto No. 3 in G major</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-16 23:50:00" d="2020-04-17 00:00:00"><n>Brahms - Symphony No. 2 - IV. Allegro con spirito</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Berliner Philharmoniker, Daniel Barenboim and Claudio Abbado star at the Europakonzert 1994 in Meiningen, Germany, performing Ludwig van Beethoven's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-17 00:00:00" d="2020-04-17 02:52:00"><n>Rossini - La Cenerentola</n><t>M</t>    <k>This 2015 performance of La Cenerentola at the Opéra de Rennes is conducted by Darrell Ang and features the Symphonic Orchestra of Brittany and choir</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-17 02:52:00" d="2020-04-17 04:40:00"><n>Waldbühne 2016 - A Czech Night</n><t>M</t>    <k>For the 2016 edition of the Waldbühne, the Georgian violinist Lisa Batiashvili and the Québécois conductor Yannick Nézet-Séguin join the Berliner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-17 04:40:00" d="2020-04-17 05:03:00"><n>Sons of Vienna: Part 1 - Papa &amp; Wolfgang</n><t>S</t>    <k>The six-part series Sons of Vienna portrays extraordinary composers who were active in the cultural city of Vienna and deserve the label of genius</k>  </p>
</a>
