<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-05-13 04:38:28"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-20 06:00:00" d="2020-05-20 07:19:00"><n>Barati &amp; Debargue perform Debussy, Brahms &amp; Franck</n><t>M</t>    <k>Violinist Kristof Barati and Pianist Lucas Debargue pair for the first time in a duo concert at the 25th anniversary edition of the Swiss Verbier Festival in 2018</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-20 07:19:00" d="2020-05-20 08:09:00"><n>Dufay: A Burgundian in Italy</n><t>M</t>    <k>The career of Guillaume Dufay – figurehead of Burgundian polyphony – begins in Italy. He seems to have particularly strong ties with Florence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-20 08:09:00" d="2020-05-20 08:59:00"><n u="Schubert - Piano Trio No. 2, Op. 100, D.">Schubert - Piano Trio No. 2, Op. 100, D. 929</n><t>M</t>    <k>Ester Hoppe (violin), Christian Poltéra (cello) and Francesco Piemontesi (piano) perform Schubert's Piano Trio No. 2, Op. 100 (D. 929) during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-20 08:59:00" d="2020-05-20 10:00:00"><n>Ennio Morricone - Filmsuite in Duo</n><t>S</t>    <k>Pietro Tagliaferri (clarinet) and Francesco Attesti (piano) play a suite with film music (C'era una volta il West - Mission - Nuovo Cinema Paradiso)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-20 10:00:00" d="2020-05-20 10:59:00"><n u="Sibelius – Symphony No.">Sibelius – Symphony No. 6</n><t>M</t>    <k>Hannu Lintu, Finnish Radio Symphony Orchestra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-20 10:59:00" d="2020-05-20 12:15:00"><n>Legato - The World of the Piano</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Swedish pianist Roland Pontinen made his debut at 17 with the Royal Stockholm Philharmonic and has since performed with major orchestras worldwide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-20 12:15:00" d="2020-05-20 13:12:00"><n>Mozart on Tour - Episode 12: Munich</n><t>S</t>    <k>The 13-part Mozart on Tour series chronicles the journey of Mozart across Europe. Soloist Homero Francesch performs Mozart's Piano Concert No</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-20 13:12:00" d="2020-05-20 14:00:00"><n>Rachmaninoff &amp; Dvořák Trios</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Valerius Ensemble, consisting of Eeva Koskinen (violin), René Geesing (cello) and Ingo Lulofs (piano) plays Rachmaninoff's Trio élégiaque Nr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-20 14:00:00" d="2020-05-20 15:39:00"><n>Europakonzert 2011 - Madrid</n><t>M</t>    <k>This 2011 edition of the celebrated Europakonzert takes place in the beautiful Teatro Real Madrid in Spain. Under the baton of Sir Simon Rattle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-20 15:39:00" d="2020-05-20 16:18:00"><n u="Mozart - Piano Concertos No. 1 &amp; No.">Mozart - Piano Concertos No. 1 &amp; No. 4</n><t>M</t>    <k>Discover the soloist Heidrun Holtmann as she performs Mozart's Piano Concerto No. 1, KV 37 and Piano Concerto No. 4, KV 41, accompanied by the Orchestra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-20 16:18:00" d="2020-05-20 16:47:00"><n u="Mozart - Piano Quartet No. 1, K.">Mozart - Piano Quartet No. 1, K. 478</n><t>M</t>    <k>Christian Zacharias (piano), Frank Peter Zimmermann (violin), Tabea Zimmerman (viola) and Tilmann Wick (cello) perform Mozart's Piano Quartet No</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-20 16:47:00" d="2020-05-20 17:43:00"><n>Dufay - Missa Ave regina caelorum</n><t>M</t>    <k>Why make use of a brilliant idea only once. Guillaume Dufay upcycled his Marian antiphon Ave Regina Coeloruminto, a four-part mass, probably intended</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-20 17:43:00" d="2020-05-20 18:13:00"><n>Semi Final I - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Ayumu Yamanaka (1988, Japan) performs Selection from Harmonies poétiques et réligieuses, S173: VI. Hymne de l'enfant a son reveil VII. Funérailles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-20 18:13:00" d="2020-05-20 19:42:00"><n>A Night in Vienna</n><t>M</t>    <k>A Night in Vienna recreates the magical atmosphere of 19th century Viennese ballrooms. In the breathtaking setting of the Hofburg Palace in Vienna</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-20 19:42:00" d="2020-05-20 21:00:00"><n>Maestros in Democracy</n><t>L</t>    <k>The most extensive documentation ever produced about the Berliner Philharmoniker presents the significance of the election of Sir Simon Rattle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-20 21:00:00" d="2020-05-20 22:26:00"><n>Pierre Boulez conducts Modern Classics</n><t>M</t>    <k>Pierre Boulez (1925-2016) was undoubtedly one of the most important figures in modern music. In this performance by the Gustav Mahler Youth Orchestra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-20 22:26:00" d="2020-05-20 23:04:00"><n u="Beethoven - Symphony No. 7, Op.">Beethoven - Symphony No. 7, Op. 92</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sir Simon Rattle conducts the Berliner Philharmonic and Vadim Repin during the Europakonzert of 2008 from the Tchaikovsky Conservatory. On the program</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-20 23:04:00" d="2020-05-21 00:00:00"><n>GayBird Leung &amp; Zephyr Quartet</n><t>L</t>    <k>During this showcase at Classical: NEXT 2019 in Rotterdam, GayBird Leung and the Zephyr Quartet perform Leung 's composition 'Music in Anticlockwise' (2017)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-21 00:00:00" d="2020-05-21 02:33:00"><n>Verdi - Aida</n><t>M</t>    <k>Conductor Paolo Arrivabeni leads the Orchestre et Choeurs de l'Opéra Royal de Wallonie in this performance of Aida. Although Aida is considered</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-21 02:33:00" d="2020-05-21 03:56:00"><n>Veerhavenconcert 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>The 2018 edition of the Veerhavenconcert in Rotterdam offers an accessible program with operatic works by Verdi, Ponchielli, and Puccini. Maxim Emelyanchec</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-21 03:56:00" d="2020-05-21 04:26:00"><n>Discovering Masterpieces – Strauss</n><t>S</t>    <k>This 'Alpine Symphony' is one of Strauss' largest works outside of his operas. He considered it his best-wrought work in terms of its orchestration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-21 04:26:00" d="2020-05-21 06:00:00"><n u="Haydn - String Quartet in C Major Op. 54 No.">Haydn - String Quartet in C Major Op. 54 No. 2</n><t>M</t>    <k>The British String Quartet The Lindsays have recorded all substantial Haydn String Quartets during their active years, from 1965 to 2005</k>  </p>
</a>
