<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2021-07-11 05:03:59"><p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-18 05:01:00" d="2021-07-18 05:36:00"><n>Shchedrin - Double Concerto for Piano, Violoncello</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Lucerne Symphony Orchestra under the baton of Neeme Järvi will presents the world premiere of Rodion Shchedrin's new concerto for cello, piano and orchestra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-18 05:36:00" d="2021-07-18 06:00:00"><n>Escaich - Trois motets</n><t>M</t>    <k>In August 2020, the fifteenth edition of Festival de Rocamadour celebrated sacred music from the classical, baroque, and romantic periods</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-18 06:00:00" d="2021-07-18 07:05:00"><n>Rocamadour: W. A. Mozart's short Masses</n><t>M</t>    <k>On August 23 of 2020, French conductor Hervé Niquet led the ensemble Le Concert Spirituel, which he had personally founded in 1987, for a concert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-18 07:05:00" d="2021-07-18 08:06:00"><n u="Haydn - Symphony No. 83 &amp;">Haydn - Symphony No. 83 &amp; 84</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sir Roger Norrington conducts the Camerata Salzburg in a performance of Haydn's Symphony No. 83 in G minor, nicknamed La Poule (&quot;The Hen&quot;) and Symphony No</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-18 08:06:00" d="2021-07-18 08:54:00"><n u="Schubert - Piano Trio No. 2, Op. 100, D.">Schubert - Piano Trio No. 2, Op. 100, D. 929</n><t>M</t>    <k>Ester Hoppe (violin), Christian Poltéra (cello) and Francesco Piemontesi (piano) perform Schubert's Piano Trio No. 2, Op. 100 (D. 929) during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-18 08:54:00" d="2021-07-18 10:03:00"><n u="Tchaikovsky - Symphony No. 4, Op.">Tchaikovsky - Symphony No. 4, Op. 36</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2010, all six Tchaikovsky Symphonies with Valery Gergiev conducting the Mariinsky Orchestra were recorded at Salle Pleyel in Paris. This concert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-18 10:03:00" d="2021-07-18 11:14:00"><n>Orff - Carmina Burana</n><t>M</t>    <k>Rodolfo Barráez conducts the Orchestra and Choir of the Academia de Musica del Palacia de Mineria in a performance of Carl Orff's Carmina Burana</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-18 11:14:00" d="2021-07-18 11:55:00"><n>Debussy's Images Book II &amp; Franck's Violin Sonata</n><t>M</t>    <k>German violinist Christian Tetzlaff and Swiss pianist Francesco Piemontesi bundle their forces in a concert program featuring works by Claude Debussy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-18 11:55:00" d="2021-07-18 12:48:00"><n>Israel Philharmonic Orchestra: Coming Home</n><t>M</t>    <k>On the occasion of its 75th anniversary on the 24th of December, 2011, the Israel Philharmonic Orchestra celebrates with a beautiful documentary about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-18 12:48:00" d="2021-07-18 13:17:00"><n u="Fauré - Violin Sonata No. 1 in A major, Op.">Fauré - Violin Sonata No. 1 in A major, Op. 13</n><t>M</t>    <k>Over the course of eleven days in August 2020, the French town of Rocamadour hosted the fifteenth edition of Festival de Rocamadour, a music festival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-18 13:17:00" d="2021-07-18 14:04:00"><n u="Mendelssohn - Violin Concerto, Op.">Mendelssohn - Violin Concerto, Op. 64</n><t>L</t>    <k>Conductor Teodor Currentzis leads his ensemble MusicAeterna alongside violinist Patricia Kopatchinskaja in a performance of works by Brahms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-18 14:04:00" d="2021-07-18 18:12:00"><n>Wagner - Siegfried</n><t>M</t>    <k>Hartmut Haenchen conducts the Netherlands Philharmonic Orchestra and Dutch National Opera in a production of Richard Wagner's opera Siegfried, the third</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-18 18:12:00" d="2021-07-18 18:53:00"><n u="Dvořák - Symphony No. 7 in D minor, Op.">Dvořák - Symphony No. 7 in D minor, Op. 70</n><t>M</t>    <k>Soviet-born conductor Semyon Bychkov leads the Czech Philharmonic and London Voices in a concert recorded at the Rudolfinum, Dvořák Hall, Prague in October 2018</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-18 18:53:00" d="2021-07-18 19:06:00"><n u="Bach - Sonata No. 2 BWV">Bach - Sonata No. 2 BWV 1015</n><t>M</t>    <k>Frank Peter Zimmermann (violin), Enrico Pace (piano)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-18 19:06:00" d="2021-07-18 20:04:00"><n>Pierre Boulez and the Lucerne Festival Academy</n><t>M</t>    <k>This documentary by Gunter Atteln and Angelika Stiehler pays tribute to Pierre Boulez on the occasion of his 85th birthday on March 26, 2010</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-18 20:04:00" d="2021-07-18 21:00:00"><n u="Hummel - Piano Concerto No. 2, Op.">Hummel - Piano Concerto No. 2, Op. 85</n><t>M</t>    <k>Under the baton of conductor Mikhail Pletnev, the Russian National Orchestra and star-pianist Dmitry Shishkin interpret Johann Nepomuk Hummel's Piano Concerto No</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-18 21:00:00" d="2021-07-18 23:23:00"><n>Boito - Mefistofele</n><t>M</t>    <k>Stefan Soltesz conducts the Münchner Philharmoniker in a performance of Arrigo Boito's Mefistofele, with Erwin Schrott singing the title role. Mefistofele</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-18 23:23:00" d="2021-07-19 00:00:00"><n u="Strauss - Horn Concerto No. 1, Op.">Strauss - Horn Concerto No. 1, Op. 11</n><t>M</t>    <k>Fabio Luisi conducts the Danish National Symphony Orchestra in a performance of Strauss' Horn Concerto No. 1. This work is one of the most popular</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 00:00:00" d="2021-07-19 02:28:00"><n>Verdi - Luisa Miller</n><t>M</t>    <k>Under the musical direction of Massimo Zanetti, the Orchestre et Choeurs de l'Opéra Royal de Wallonie present the opera &quot;Luisa Miller&quot;. As the result</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 02:28:00" d="2021-07-19 04:00:00"><n>Prosseda performs Mozart, Schubert &amp; Chopin</n><t>S</t>    <k>Roberto Prosseda (1975) performs Mozart's Piano Sonata No. 5 (KV. 283) and four Impromptus Op. 90 by Franz Schubert. The performance ends with Chopin's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 04:00:00" d="2021-07-19 04:58:00"><n>Looking for Cole</n><t>M</t>    <k>The film &quot;Looking for Cole,&quot; by Wilfried van den Brande, recorded over the course of three years, gives a unique insight into Cole Porter's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 04:58:00" d="2021-07-19 05:21:00"><n u="Martinů - Double Concerto, H">Martinů - Double Concerto, H 271</n><t>M</t>    <k>On the program are excerpts from Smetana's The Bartered Bride, Martinů's Concerto for Piano and Timpani (H 271), and Dvořák's Symphony No. 9</k>  </p>
</a>
