<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2021-07-12 05:03:05"><p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 05:21:00" d="2021-07-19 06:00:00"><n>CMIM - Semi-final - John Brancy</n><t>M</t>    <k>US baritone John Brancy (1988) performs 'It is enough! O Lord, now take away my life' from Felix Mendelssohn's oratorio Elijah, 'Uzhel' ta samaya Tatyana'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 06:00:00" d="2021-07-19 06:49:00"><n>The Violin in Naples - Matteis and Guido</n><t>M</t>    <k>&quot;No mortal ever played the violin better than Signor Nichola.&quot; The English rubbed their eyes in disbelief when in the late 17th century Nicola Matteis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 06:49:00" d="2021-07-19 08:08:00"><n>Absolute Prokofiev: The Third Concert</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Mariinsky Theatre Symphony Orchestra under the baton of Valery Gergiev performs the complete cycle of Sergei Prokofiev's symphonies and piano concerti</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 08:08:00" d="2021-07-19 09:08:00"><n u="Schumann - Piano Quartet, Op.">Schumann - Piano Quartet, Op. 47</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Ébene Quartet, consisting of Daishin Kashimoto (violin), Lise Berthaud (viola), François Salque (cello) and Eric Le Sage (piano), performs Robert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 09:08:00" d="2021-07-19 10:02:00"><n u="Beethoven - Symphony No.">Beethoven - Symphony No. 7</n><t>M</t>    <k>In September 2016, we celebrated the birthday of one of Japan's best-known conductors: Seiji Ozawa. Renowned for his advocacy of modern composers, Ozawa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 10:02:00" d="2021-07-19 10:40:00"><n>Documentary: Ginandrea Noseda</n><t>L</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 10:40:00" d="2021-07-19 11:40:00"><n>Concerts in Quarantine: Works for Piano and Cello</n><t>S</t>    <k>Between March and May 2020, Schinkel Pavillon Berlin opened its unexpectedly vacated exhibition space for a concert series in isolation titled Concerts in Quarantine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 11:40:00" d="2021-07-19 12:23:00"><n>Johan de Meij - Echoes of San Marco &amp; Fellini</n><t>M</t>    <k>Johan de Meij conducts two of his own works: &quot;Echoes of San Marco,&quot; a tribute to Giovanni Gabrielli and &quot;Fellini,&quot; a tribute to film composer Federico Fellini</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 12:23:00" d="2021-07-19 12:53:00"><n>Semi Final I - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Ayumu Yamanaka (1988, Japan) performs Selection from Harmonies poétiques et réligieuses, S173: VI. Hymne de l'enfant a son reveil VII. Funérailles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 12:53:00" d="2021-07-19 13:15:00"><n>CMIM - Semi-final- Dilyara Idrisova</n><t>M</t>    <k>Russian soprano Dilyara Idrisova (1988) performs 'I'm sad, dear father!' from Mikhail Glinka's opera Ruslan und Ludmilla, 'Zerfließe, mein Herze' from</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 13:15:00" d="2021-07-19 14:07:00"><n>Liszt - Piano Concerto No. 2, S.125</n><t>M</t>    <k>Alexander Ullman (1991, United Kingdom) performs Franz Liszt's Piano Concerto No. 2 (S125) during the final of the 11th International Franz Liszt Piano</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 14:07:00" d="2021-07-19 15:51:00"><n>Abbado conducts Mahler and Schönberg</n><t>M</t>    <k>Together with the world's leading youth orchestra – the Gustav Mahler Jugendorchester (GMJO) – Abbado performs Gustav Mahler's Symphony No. 4 and Arnold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 15:51:00" d="2021-07-19 16:35:00"><n u="Tchaikovsky - Symphony No. 1, Op.">Tchaikovsky - Symphony No. 1, Op. 13</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2010, all six Tchaikovsky Symphonies with Valery Gergiev conducting the Mariinsky Orchestra were recorded at Salle Pleyel in Paris. This concert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 16:35:00" d="2021-07-19 17:12:00"><n u="Hummel - Piano Concerto No.">Hummel - Piano Concerto No. 2</n><t>M</t>    <k>Under the baton of conductor Mikhail Pletnev, the Russian National Orchestra and star-pianist Dmitry Shishkin interpret Johann Nepomuk Hummel's Piano Concerto No</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 17:12:00" d="2021-07-19 18:17:00"><n>Concerts in Quarantine: Debussy, Brahms et al.</n><t>M</t>    <k>Clarinettist Sharon Kam, soprano Jacquelyn Wagner and pianist Matan Porat bundle their forces in this recital from Schinkel Pavillon in Berlin on May 11, 2020</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 18:17:00" d="2021-07-19 20:01:00"><n u="Berio's Sinfonia &amp; Dvořák's Symphony No. 7, Op.">Berio's Sinfonia &amp; Dvořák's Symphony No. 7, Op. 70</n><t>M</t>    <k>Soviet-born conductor Semyon Bychkov leads the Czech Philharmonic and London Voices in a concert recorded at the Rudolfinum, Dvořák Hall, Prague in October 2018</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 20:01:00" d="2021-07-19 21:00:00"><n>Claudio Abbado &amp; Orchestra Mozart</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2004, Claudio Abbado founded the Orchestra Mozart in Bologna, Italy. The orchestra collects the best classical music performers of the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 21:00:00" d="2021-07-19 23:18:00"><n>Handel - The Triumph of Time and Truth</n><t>L</t>    <k>Emmanuelle Haim conducts Le Concert d'Astrée in Handel's oratorio &quot;Il Trionfo del Tempo e del Disinganno&quot; (The Triumph of Time and Truth). Sabine Devieilhe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-19 23:18:00" d="2021-07-20 00:00:00"><n>Britten - The Young Persons Guide to the Orchestra</n><t>M</t>    <k>Marin Alsop conducts the Britten-Pears Orchestra in a performance of Britten's The Young Person's Guide to the Orchestra. Recorded at Snape Maltings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-20 00:00:00" d="2021-07-20 02:46:00"><n>Bizet - Carmen</n><t>M</t>    <k>Louis Langrée conducts the Metropolitan Opera in a performance of Bizet's masterpiece of the Gypsy seductress, who lives by her own rules, no matter the cost</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-20 02:46:00" d="2021-07-20 04:39:00"><n>Shchedrin's Double Concerto, Franck and Dvorák</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Lucerne Symphony Orchestra under the baton of Neeme Järvi will presents the world premiere of Rodion Shchedrin's new concerto for cello, piano and orchestra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-20 04:39:00" d="2021-07-20 05:02:00"><n>Sons of Vienna: Part 3 - Man About Town</n><t>S</t>    <k>The six-part series Sons of Vienna portrays extraordinary composers who were active in the cultural city of Vienna and deserve the label of genius</k>  </p>
</a>
