<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2021-07-08 05:09:48"><p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-13 05:23:00" d="2021-07-13 06:00:00"><n>Berg - Sieben frühe Lieder</n><t>S</t>    <k>Between March and May 2020, Schinkel Pavillon Berlin opened its unexpectedly vacated exhibition space for a concert series in isolation titled Concerts in Quarantine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-13 06:00:00" d="2021-07-13 06:57:00"><n>Farina, Amodei - Serenatas &amp; Cantatas</n><t>M</t>    <k>During the 17th century the Neapolitan rich and famous gathered in droves for the Spassi di Posillipo, open-air festivals on the coast. The most famous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-13 06:57:00" d="2021-07-13 07:48:00"><n>Rachmaninov &amp; Gershwin: Rhapsodies</n><t>M</t>    <k>The National Philharmonic Orchestra of Russia and acclaimed Russian pianist Boris Berezovsky are conducted by Konstantin Khvatynets in an interpretation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-13 07:48:00" d="2021-07-13 08:48:00"><n u="Schumann - Piano Quartet, Op.">Schumann - Piano Quartet, Op. 47</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Ébene Quartet, consisting of Daishin Kashimoto (violin), Lise Berthaud (viola), François Salque (cello) and Eric Le Sage (piano), performs Robert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-13 08:48:00" d="2021-07-13 10:03:00"><n u="Tchaikovsky - Symphony No. 5 Op.">Tchaikovsky - Symphony No. 5 Op. 64</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2010, all six Tchaikovsky Symphonies with Valery Gergiev conducting the Mariinsky Orchestra were recorded at Salle Pleyel in Paris. This concert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-13 10:03:00" d="2021-07-13 11:09:00"><n u="Beethoven - Last Sonatas, Op. 109, 110 &amp;">Beethoven - Last Sonatas, Op. 109, 110 &amp; 111</n><t>M</t>    <k>Pianist Alexandre Tharaud's interpretation of Beethoven's last three sonatas - Opus 109, 110 and 111</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-13 11:09:00" d="2021-07-13 13:04:00"><n>The 12 Cellists of the Berliner Philharmoniker</n><t>M</t>    <k>Recorded in the Philharmonie Berlin on occasion of the 40th anniversary of the ensemble; soloists: Annette Dasch (soprano), Till Brönner (trumpet)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-13 13:04:00" d="2021-07-13 13:27:00"><n>Sons of Vienna: Part 5 - Dynasty of Dance</n><t>S</t>    <k>The six-part series Sons of Vienna portrays extraordinary composers who were active in the cultural city of Vienna and deserve the label of genius</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-13 13:27:00" d="2021-07-13 13:38:00"><n u="Schumann - Fantasiestücke for Clarinet, Op.">Schumann - Fantasiestücke for Clarinet, Op. 73</n><t>M</t>    <k>Tabea Zimmermann (viola) and Francesco Piemontesi (piano) performed live at Schinkel Pavillon in Berlin on April 17, 2020. On the program are Robert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-13 13:38:00" d="2021-07-13 14:01:00"><n>Smetana - Three dances from The Bartered Bride</n><t>M</t>    <k>On the program are excerpts from Smetana's The Bartered Bride, Martinů's Concerto for Piano and Timpani (H 271), and Dvořák's Symphony No. 9</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-13 14:01:00" d="2021-07-13 16:34:00"><n>Dvořák - Rusalka</n><t>M</t>    <k>Ádám Fischer conducts the orchestra and choir of La Monnaie in a performance of Dvořák's opera Rusalka. The work remains one of the cornerstones of Czech opera houses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-13 16:34:00" d="2021-07-13 17:28:00"><n u="Berlioz - Symphonie Fantastique, Op.">Berlioz - Symphonie Fantastique, Op. 14</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2001, the world-famous Berlin Philharmonic's annual Europakonzert took place at a very unusual location: the Hagia Irene in Istanbul. This Byzantine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-13 17:28:00" d="2021-07-13 19:11:00"><n>Haydn - The Creation</n><t>M</t>    <k>Together with the RIAS Kammerchor and several vocalists, the Verbier Festival Chamber Orchestra performs Joseph Haydn's The Creation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-13 19:11:00" d="2021-07-13 19:32:00"><n u="Brahms - Clarinet sonata No. 2, Op.">Brahms - Clarinet sonata No. 2, Op. 120</n><t>M</t>    <k>Clarinettist Sharon Kam, soprano Jacquelyn Wagner and pianist Matan Porat bundle their forces in this recital from Schinkel Pavillon in Berlin on May 11, 2020</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-13 19:32:00" d="2021-07-13 19:43:00"><n>Viardot - Five Songs</n><t>M</t>    <k>Olena Tokar (soprano) and Igor Grishin (piano) perform a lieder and piano program, recorded at Schinkel Pavillon in Berlin on March 30, 2020</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-13 19:43:00" d="2021-07-13 20:12:00"><n u="Mendelssohn - Violin Concerto, Op.">Mendelssohn - Violin Concerto, Op. 64</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sir Simon Rattle conducts the Berlin Philharmonic in the 2016 edition of the Europakonzert, in R?ros, Norway. On the program are Grieg's Lyrical Piece, Op</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-13 20:12:00" d="2021-07-13 21:00:00"><n>Martinů - Concerto for Two Pianos and Orchestra</n><t>M</t>    <k>Soviet-born conductor Semyon Bychkov leads the Czech Philharmonic in a concert featuring works by Bohuslav Martinů, Maurice Ravel and Henri Dutilleux</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-13 21:00:00" d="2021-07-13 21:58:00"><n>Antonio Manna: Il basso napolitano</n><t>M</t>    <k>Stefano Demicheli conducts the Ensemble Talenti Vulcanici and soloists Nicola Cianncio (bass) and Catherine Jones (cello) in a varied baroque music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-13 21:58:00" d="2021-07-13 23:11:00"><n>Conducting Mahler</n><t>M</t>    <k>This film by Frank Scheffer includes rehearsals and performances by the Amsterdam Concertgebouw, the Berlin Philharmonic, and the Vienna Philharmonic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-13 23:11:00" d="2021-07-14 00:00:00"><n>Classical:NEXT 2019 - Clarinet Factory</n><t>S</t>    <k>Considered to be one of the most unique ensembles to feature on the Czech scene in the last 25 years, the style of the Clarinet Factory hovers between</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 00:00:00" d="2021-07-14 02:46:00"><n>Debussy - Pelléas et Melisande</n><t>M</t>    <k>Alain Altinoglu conducts a performance of Debussy's Pelléas et Mélisande at the Opernhaus Zürich in 2016. Main soloists are Brindley Sherratt (Arkel)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 02:46:00" d="2021-07-14 04:34:00"><n>The Pyongang concert</n><t>M</t>    <k>This concert features the New York Philharmonic's performence in North Korea's capital Pyongyang in 2008. &quot;The concert was historic. Daniel J. Wakin, The New York Times</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 04:34:00" d="2021-07-14 05:04:00"><n>Discovering Masterpieces - Brandenburg Concertos</n><t>M</t>    <k>This episode of Discovering Masterpieces presents the Brandenburg Concertos by Johann Sebastian Bach (1685-1750). Musical excerpts played by the Freiburger</k>  </p>
</a>
