<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a><n>Danielpour - Elegies</n><s o="2020-06-04 12:14:00" d="2020-06-04 12:50:00" n="Brava HDTV" id_tv="560"></s><p><k>Hartmut Haenchen conducts the philharmonie zuid in a performance of Richard Danielpour's Elegies. Soloists are Marina Prudenskaya (mezzo-soprano), Thomas Oliemans (baritone). Recorded at Muziekgebouw Eindhoven, The Netherlands, 2019.</k><d>Richard Danielpour (.1956) is one of the most beloved American composers of his generation due to his frequent referencing of and connection with the past, being inspired by American icons such as Aaron Copland, Samuel Barber and Leonard Bernstein. His lush musical language is often infused with swingy jazz rhythms just as is the music of Copland and Bernstein. Thus, he conveys an intense musical experience to the listener with his intuitive musical style, his exquisite melodic lines and accessible harmonic language. All this makes him to be a hugely popular composer with American orchestras. The initial idea for the composition of a song cycle &quot;Elegies&quot; came from the American mezzo soprano Frederica von Stade who was born in 1945, the same year in which her father was killed when the Jeep he was driving drove over a land mine. Charles von Stade is buried at the American cemetery in Margraten (South Netherlands). His daughter could thus only create a picture of him for herself via family stories and through his letters. These letters form the basis of the text of the songs, where father and daughter &quot;meet&quot; and communicate for the first time. The first movement Vigil, depicts the arrival of the daughter who hopes for a spiritual connection with her father. The second movement describes the intense sorrow of her father at the horrors of war and is as if his daughter is calling on him to return to her. In the third movement we hear the father give his unborn daughter his blessing, &quot;Little soul, to where would you go from the darkness of the womb?&quot; Movement four is the preparation for the reunion of the souls of father and daughter which takes place in movement five, Paradise. Here the daughter welcomes her father's spiritual rest and sings, &quot;Peace, the air which I breathe&quot;. The philharmonie zuidnederland is conducted by Harmut Haenchen. The German born conductor who naturalized to become Dutch and was chief conductor of the Dutch Opera Amsterdam, the Dutch Philharmonic Orchestra and the Dutch Chamber Orchestra from 1986 to 1996. He was knighted for his services to Dutch music. Harmut Haenchen is a regular guest conductor with the philharmonie zuidnederland. Conductor: Hartmut Haenchen Orchestra: philharmonie zuidnederland Soloists: Marina Prudenskaya (mezzo-soprano), Thomas Oliemans (baritone)</d></p><i><w>http://tv.sms.cz/televize/brava-hdtv/20200604/1410021878-Danielpour-elegies</w></i><x></x></a>
