<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2020-04-16 04:39:26"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 05:02:00" d="2020-04-23 05:28:00"><n>CMIM - Semi Finals - Clara Osowski</n><t>M</t>    <k>Olivier Godin accompanies mezzo-soprano Clara Osowski (USA, 1986) during the semi-finals of the Art Song competition of the Concours musical international</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 05:28:00" d="2020-04-23 05:52:00"><n>Chopin - Piano Concert No. 2 - III. Allegro vivace</n><t>L</t>    <k>In 1999 the annual Europa Konzert was performed in Krakow. Enjoy the Berliner Philharmoniker and Bernard Haitink in works by Mozart, Chopin and Schumann</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 05:52:00" d="2020-04-23 06:00:00"><n u="Bach - Well-Tempered Clavier, Book 2 No.">Bach - Well-Tempered Clavier, Book 2 No. 4</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this broadcast, Nikolai Demidenko plays Preludes and Fugues Nos. 1 to 12 (BWV 870-881) from Book Two of Bach's Well-Tempered Clavier, recorded</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 06:00:00" d="2020-04-23 06:46:00"><n>Burgundian Alphabet III - De la Rue - Without name</n><t>M</t>    <k>Enjoy a genuine musical marathon as a prelude to the Utrecht Early Music Festival 2018. During three concerts, the Huelgas Ensemble sing an entire alphabet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 06:46:00" d="2020-04-23 08:13:00"><n u="Handel - Messiah, HWV">Handel - Messiah, HWV 56</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Messiah (HWV 56) by Georg Frederich Handel, tells the life and suffering of Christ: a story of passion, fire, and sacrifice. This performance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 08:13:00" d="2020-04-23 09:03:00"><n u="Schubert - Piano Trio No. 2, Op. 100, D.">Schubert - Piano Trio No. 2, Op. 100, D. 929</n><t>M</t>    <k>Ester Hoppe (violin), Christian Poltéra (cello) and Francesco Piemontesi (piano) perform Schubert's Piano Trio No. 2, Op. 100 (D. 929) during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 09:03:00" d="2020-04-23 09:28:00"><n u="Mozart - Piano Concerto No. 8, K">Mozart - Piano Concerto No. 8, K 246</n><t>M</t>    <k>Soloist Christian Zacharias performs Mozart's Piano Concerto No. 8, K 246, accompanied by the Radio-Sinfonieorchester Stuttgart and conducted by Gianluigi Gelmetti</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 09:28:00" d="2020-04-23 09:38:00"><n>Chabrier - Espana</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 09:38:00" d="2020-04-23 09:51:00"><n u="Debussy - First Rhapsody, L.">Debussy - First Rhapsody, L. 116</n><t>M</t>    <k>Wenzel Fuchs, Berlin Philharmonic, Sir Simon Rattle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 09:51:00" d="2020-04-23 10:00:00"><n>Beethoven - Symphony No. 7, Op. 92 - IV. Allegro</n><t>M</t>    <k>Berlin Philharmonic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 10:00:00" d="2020-04-23 10:24:00"><n>Sons of Vienna: Part 6 - Life Against the Odds</n><t>S</t>    <k>The six-part series Sons of Vienna portrays extraordinary composers who were active in the cultural city of Vienna and deserve the label of genius</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 10:24:00" d="2020-04-23 11:54:00"><n>Fomin plays Schumann, Beethoven and Tchaikovsky</n><t>M</t>    <k>Misha Fomin performs Schumann's Fantasy, Op. 17, Beethoven's Piano Sonata No. 30, and &quot;May&quot;, &quot;June&quot;, and &quot;October&quot; from Seasons, Op. 37b by Tchaikovsky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 11:54:00" d="2020-04-23 12:41:00"><n u="Tchaikovsky - Piano Trio, Op.">Tchaikovsky - Piano Trio, Op. 50</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Zadig Trio consists of the two French childhood friends Boris Borgolotto (violin), Marc Girard Garcia (cello) and the American pianist Ian Barber</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 12:41:00" d="2020-04-23 14:00:00"><n>Beethoven - Symphony No. 6 'Pastorale'</n><t>M</t>    <k>Conrad van Alphen conducts the Sinfonia Rotterdam Orchestra in an interpretation of Beethoven's Symphony No. 6, Pastoral, at the St. Willibrord Basilica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 14:00:00" d="2020-04-23 16:46:00"><n>Debussy - Pelléas et Melisande</n><t>M</t>    <k>Alain Altinoglu conducts a performance of Debussy's Pelléas et Mélisande at the Opernhaus Zürich in 2016. Main soloists are Brindley Sherratt (Arkel)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 16:46:00" d="2020-04-23 17:45:00"><n u="Sibelius – Symphony No.">Sibelius – Symphony No. 6</n><t>M</t>    <k>Hannu Lintu, Finnish Radio Symphony Orchestra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 17:45:00" d="2020-04-23 19:17:00"><n>Gala from Berlin 2016</n><t>M</t>    <k>Under the lead of Sir Simon Rattle, Deutsche Grammophone artist Daniil Trifonov and the Berliner Philharmoniker perform Rachmaninov's Third Piano Concerto</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 19:17:00" d="2020-04-23 19:35:00"><n>Semi Final II - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Leon Bernsdorf (1992, Germany) performs Epithalam zu Eduard Reményis Vermählungsfeier (S129) and Grand Duo concertant sur la Romance de 'Le Marin' (S128)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 19:35:00" d="2020-04-23 19:58:00"><n u="Haydn - String Quartet in C Major Op. 33 No.">Haydn - String Quartet in C Major Op. 33 No. 3</n><t>M</t>    <k>The British String Quartet The Lindsays have recorded all substantial Haydn String Quartets during their active years, from 1965 to 2005</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 19:58:00" d="2020-04-23 20:32:00"><n u="Mendelssohn - Violin Concerto, Op.">Mendelssohn - Violin Concerto, Op. 64</n><t>L</t>    <k>Conductor Teodor Currentzis leads his ensemble MusicAeterna alongside violinist Patricia Kopatchinskaja in a performance of works by Brahms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 20:32:00" d="2020-04-23 20:47:00"><n>Chabrier - Espana</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 20:47:00" d="2020-04-23 20:54:00"><n>Chabrier - Espana</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 20:54:00" d="2020-04-23 21:00:00"><n u="Beethoven - Romance for Violin No. 1, Op.">Beethoven - Romance for Violin No. 1, Op. 40</n><t>M</t>    <k>The beautiful Mariinsky Theatre in St. Petersburg formed the background for the 1996 edition of the annual Europe Concert of the Berliner Philharmoniker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 21:00:00" d="2020-04-23 22:27:00"><n>Pneuma</n><t>M</t>    <k>Choreographer Carolyn Carlson created the beautiful ballet 'Pneuma' especially for the Ballet of the Opéra national de Bordeaux in 2014</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 22:27:00" d="2020-04-23 23:30:00"><n u="Mahler - Symphony No.">Mahler - Symphony No. 1</n><t>M</t>    <k>Bernhard Haitink conducts the Berlin Philharmonic in a performance of Gustav Mahler's Symphony No. 1. Directed by Barry Gavin, this concert took place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 23:30:00" d="2020-04-23 23:35:00"><n>Mozart - Symphony No. 35, K. 385 - I. Allegro</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Berlin Philharmonic, led by maestro Claudio Abbado, perform their first Europakonzert in Prague in 1991. Soloists in this first edition are soprano</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 23:35:00" d="2020-04-23 23:50:00"><n>Berlioz - Hungarian March from La Damnation</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Europakonzert of 1992 from El Escorial in Madrid was conducted by Barenboim and features the world-renowned tenor Plácido Domingo. The program consists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-23 23:50:00" d="2020-04-24 00:00:00"><n>Brahms - Symphony No. 2 - II. Adagio non troppo</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Berliner Philharmoniker, Daniel Barenboim and Claudio Abbado star at the Europakonzert 1994 in Meiningen, Germany, performing Ludwig van Beethoven's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-24 00:00:00" d="2020-04-24 02:38:00"><n>Prokofiev - Betrothal in a Monastery</n><t>M</t>    <k>This outstanding new staging of Betrothal in a Monastery was recorded at the Mariinsky Theatre in St. Petersburg, brilliantly performed by the Kirov Opera</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-24 02:38:00" d="2020-04-24 03:53:00"><n>Frang, Schiff &amp; Zimmermann play Mozart and Brahms</n><t>M</t>    <k>Vilde Frang, Tabea Zimmermann and András Schiff team up for a concert at the 25th anniversary edition of the Swiss Verbier Festival in 2018</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-24 03:53:00" d="2020-04-24 04:24:00"><n>Teatro Regio behind the scenes</n><t>M</t>    <k>This documentary portrays the Teatro Regio of Turin. Pillar of local life and symbol of excellence of the Italian operatic tradition, the Teatro Regio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-24 04:24:00" d="2020-04-24 04:50:00"><n>CMIM - Semi Finals - Rihab Chaieb</n><t>M</t>    <k>Michel-Alexandre Broekaert accompanies mezzo-soprano Rihab Chaieb (Canada/Tunisia, 1987 during the semi-finals of the Art Song competition of the Concours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-24 04:50:00" d="2020-04-24 04:57:00"><n>Chabrier - Espana</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-24 04:57:00" d="2020-04-24 05:12:00"><n>Mahler - Symphony No. 2 - II. Andante moderato</n><t>M</t>    <k>Lucerne Festival Orchestra, Claudio Abbado</k>  </p>
</a>
