<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="23" t="2020-05-16 05:01:06"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 06:00:00" d="2020-05-23 07:58:00"><n u="J. S. Bach: Mass in B minor, BWV">J. S. Bach: Mass in B minor, BWV 232</n><t>M</t>    <k>Herbert Blomstedt conducts the Gewandhaus Orchestra and Kammerchor at the Leipzig Bachfest 2005 in a performance of J. S. Bach's Mass in B minor (BWV 232)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 07:58:00" d="2020-05-23 09:00:00"><n>The Argonauts - Quest for the Golden Fleece</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 1419 Philip the Good inherits a realm stretching from Dijon to deep into the Netherlands. In 1430, he founds his Order of the Golden Fleece, which</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 09:00:00" d="2020-05-23 09:31:00"><n>CMIM - Finals - Clara Osowski</n><t>M</t>    <k>Olivier Godin accompanies mezzo-soprano Clara Osowski (USA, 1986) during the finals of the Art Song competition of the Concours musical international</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 09:31:00" d="2020-05-23 10:00:00"><n u="Saint-Saëns - Intro and Rondo Capriccioso, Op.">Saint-Saëns - Intro and Rondo Capriccioso, Op. 28</n><t>M</t>    <k>The outstanding Berlin Philharmonic orchestra, under the baton of Neeme Järvi, s take us on a trip to Arabian &quot;Thousand and One Nights&quot;, with soloist Janine Jansen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 10:00:00" d="2020-05-23 10:58:00"><n u="Sibelius – Symphony No.">Sibelius – Symphony No. 3</n><t>M</t>    <k>Hannu Lintu, Finnish Radio Symphony Orchestra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 10:58:00" d="2020-05-23 12:54:00"><n>The 12 Cellists of the Berliner Philharmoniker</n><t>M</t>    <k>Recorded in the Philharmonie Berlin on occasion of the 40th anniversary of the ensemble; soloists: Annette Dasch (soprano), Till Brönner (trumpet)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 12:54:00" d="2020-05-23 13:16:00"><n>Sons of Vienna: Part 6 - Life Against the Odds</n><t>S</t>    <k>The six-part series Sons of Vienna portrays extraordinary composers who were active in the cultural city of Vienna and deserve the label of genius</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 13:16:00" d="2020-05-23 14:01:00"><n>CMIM - Semi Finals - Tomi Punkeri</n><t>M</t>    <k>Olivier Godin accompanies baritone Tomi Punkeri (Finland, 1991) during the semi-finals of the Art Song competition of the Concours musical international</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 14:01:00" d="2020-05-23 14:18:00"><n u="Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 22, Op.">Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 22, Op. 54</n><t>M</t>    <k>Italian pianist Riccardo Schwartz was born in Milan in 1986, and completed his studies at Conservatorio of Milan as a student of acclaimed musicians</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 14:18:00" d="2020-05-23 14:49:00"><n u="Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 23, Op.">Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 23, Op. 57</n><t>M</t>    <k>Italian pianist Riccardo Schwartz was born in Milan in 1986, and completed his studies at Conservatorio of Milan as a student of acclaimed musicians</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 14:49:00" d="2020-05-23 16:35:00"><n>Pianomania - Menahem Pressler</n><t>M</t>    <k>Menahem Pressler is the soloist in Mozart's Piano Concerto, No. 23. The Gulbenkian Orchestra is conducted by Leo Hussain in a concert program which</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 16:35:00" d="2020-05-23 17:12:00"><n u="Hummel - Piano Concerto No.">Hummel - Piano Concerto No. 2</n><t>M</t>    <k>Under the baton of conductor Mikhail Pletnev, the Russian National Orchestra and star-pianist Dmitry Shishkin interpret Johann Nepomuk Hummel's Piano Concerto No</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 17:12:00" d="2020-05-23 17:35:00"><n>Semi Final II - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Dina Ivanova (1994, Russia) performs La notte (S377a) and Hungarian Rhapsody No. 12, (S379a) during semi-final II (chamber music) of the 11th International</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 17:35:00" d="2020-05-23 18:18:00"><n>Brendel and Abbado at Lucerne Festival</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Lucerne Festival is one of the world's biggest and most important music festivals. During the 2005 edition, the Lucerne Festival Orchestra and Claudio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 18:18:00" d="2020-05-23 18:44:00"><n>CMIM - Semi Finals - Gemma Summerfield</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sebastian Wybrew accompanies soprano Gemma Summerfield (UK, 1990) during the semi-finals of the Art Song competition of the Concours musical international</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 18:44:00" d="2020-05-23 20:21:00"><n>Buxtehude - Abendmusik</n><t>M</t>    <k>Enjoy the Masques ensemble and the Vox Luminis choir and discover 17th century baroque music and the composer Buxtehude through his vocal compositions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 20:21:00" d="2020-05-23 21:00:00"><n u="Discovering Masterpieces – Beethoven No.">Discovering Masterpieces – Beethoven No. 5</n><t>S</t>    <k>In this documentary, Ludwig van Beethoven's 'Symphony No. 5' is discussed. The piece has the character of an appeal from the very start, when the four-note</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 21:00:00" d="2020-05-23 22:41:00"><n>Sol Gabetta at the Lucerne Festival 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>Argentinian cellist Sol Gabetta returned to the Lucerne Festival 2018 to perform a concert with the Mahler Chamber Orchestra led by François-Xavier Roth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 22:41:00" d="2020-05-23 23:13:00"><n u="Mozart - Symphony No. 36, K.">Mozart - Symphony No. 36, K. 425</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jeffrey Tate conducts the English Chamber Orchestra in a performance of Mozart's &quot;Linzer&quot; Symphony No. 36 (K. 425). Mozart composed the work in 1783</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 23:13:00" d="2020-05-24 00:00:00"><n>CMIM - Semi Finals - Clara Osowski</n><t>M</t>    <k>Olivier Godin accompanies mezzo-soprano Clara Osowski (USA, 1986) during the semi-finals of the Art Song competition of the Concours musical international</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-24 00:00:00" d="2020-05-24 02:48:00"><n>Haydn - Orlando Paladino</n><t>M</t>    <k>For more than 25 years, René Jacobs has dedicated his life to baroque operas and works with the best ensembles for early music. On occasion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-24 02:48:00" d="2020-05-24 04:20:00"><n>Gala from Berlin 2016</n><t>M</t>    <k>Under the lead of Sir Simon Rattle, Deutsche Grammophone artist Daniil Trifonov and the Berliner Philharmoniker perform Rachmaninov's Third Piano Concerto</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-24 04:20:00" d="2020-05-24 06:00:00"><n u="Discovering Masterpieces – Schubert">Discovering Masterpieces – Schubert 8</n><t>S</t>    <k>Franz Schubert's 'Symphony No. 8 in B minor', commonly known as 'the Unfinished'. Schubert started working on it in 1822, but he left only two movements</k>  </p>
</a>
