<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="36" t="2020-04-12 04:36:09"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 05:11:00" d="2020-04-19 05:27:00"><n>Tchaikovsky - The Nutcracker: Waltz of the Flowers</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Berliner Philharmoniker plays Tchaikovsky's Fantasy Overture from &quot;Roméo et Juliette&quot;, Mozart is his famous Violin Concerto No. 3 in G major</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 05:27:00" d="2020-04-19 05:38:00"><n>Beethoven - Symphony No. 7 - II. Allegretto</n><t>M</t>    <k>The beautiful Mariinsky Theatre in St. Petersburg formed the background for the 1996 edition of the annual Europe Concert of the Berliner Philharmoniker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 05:38:00" d="2020-04-19 05:45:00"><n>Mozart - Don Giovanni: Crudele! -Ah no, mio bene!</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Berlin Philharmonic, led by maestro Claudio Abbado, perform their first Europakonzert in Prague in 1991. Soloists in this first edition are soprano</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 05:45:00" d="2020-04-19 06:00:00"><n>Schumann - Symphony No. 1, Op. 38 - IV. Allegro</n><t>L</t>    <k>In 1999 the annual Europa Konzert was performed in Krakow. Enjoy the Berliner Philharmoniker and Bernard Haitink in works by Mozart, Chopin and Schumann</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 06:00:00" d="2020-04-19 07:23:00"><n>Jaroussky sings Bach &amp; Telemann</n><t>M</t>    <k>The film Jaroussky sings Bach &amp; Telemann is a portrait of a very special vocalist - and of two exceptional composers: Telemann and Bach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 07:23:00" d="2020-04-19 08:23:00"><n>St. Patrick's Day Concert</n><t>M</t>    <k>The annual celebration of Saint Patrick's Day is held on March 17, the traditional death date of Saint Patrick (385-461), who is known as Ireland's foremost patron saint</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 08:23:00" d="2020-04-19 08:58:00"><n>Lucerne Festival 2004 - Pollini plays Beethoven</n><t>M</t>    <k>Maurizio Pollini and the Lucerne Festival play under the baton of maestro Claudio Abbado. At the yearly Lucerne Festival in Switzerland they perform</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 08:58:00" d="2020-04-19 09:19:00"><n>Britten - The Young Persons Guide to the Orchestra</n><t>M</t>    <k>Marin Alsop conducts the Britten-Pears Orchestra in a performance of Britten's The Young Person's Guide to the Orchestra. Recorded at Snape Maltings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 09:19:00" d="2020-04-19 09:26:00"><n>Chabrier - Espana</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 09:26:00" d="2020-04-19 09:31:00"><n>Berlioz: Invocation a la nature Damnation de Faust</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Europakonzert of 1992 from El Escorial in Madrid was conducted by Barenboim and features the world-renowned tenor Plácido Domingo. The program consists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 09:31:00" d="2020-04-19 09:40:00"><n>Verdi - Quattro pezzi sacri: III. Laudi a. Vergine</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Europakonzert of 1998 was held in a unique location: The Vasa Museum in Stockholm. Under the baton of Claudia Abbado, they perform pieces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 09:40:00" d="2020-04-19 09:50:00"><n>Tchaikovsky - Waltz of the Flowers from Nutcracker</n><t>M</t>    <k>The beautiful Mariinsky Theatre in St. Petersburg formed the background for the 1996 edition of the annual Europe Concert of the Berliner Philharmoniker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 09:50:00" d="2020-04-19 10:00:00"><n>Brahms - Symphony No. 2 - II. Adagio non troppo</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Berliner Philharmoniker, Daniel Barenboim and Claudio Abbado star at the Europakonzert 1994 in Meiningen, Germany, performing Ludwig van Beethoven's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 10:00:00" d="2020-04-19 10:53:00"><n>Couperin - Third book: A New Path</n><t>M</t>    <k>With his third harpsichord book, Couperin discovered his own unique voice. The old-fashioned suite has had its day, the ordre reaches its peak</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 10:53:00" d="2020-04-19 12:08:00"><n u="Bach - Partitas for Solo Violin">Bach - Partitas for Solo Violin (BWV 1001-1006)</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2006, Gidon Kremer took on the greatest challenge for any violinist: Bach's &quot;Sonatas and Partitas for Solo Violin&quot; (BWV 1001-1006). With these pieces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 12:08:00" d="2020-04-19 13:16:00"><n>The Red Priest and the Tanguero</n><t>M</t>    <k>The set YES Camerata (Young European String Camerata) and the violinist William Hagen interpret The four seasons of Antonio Vivaldi and Las quatros</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 13:16:00" d="2020-04-19 13:42:00"><n>Solo Finals - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Alexander Ullman (1991, United Kingdom) performs Liszt's Études d'exécution transcendante, No. 11 Harmonies du soir (S139/11), Nuages gris (S199)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 13:42:00" d="2020-04-19 13:48:00"><n u="Bach - Well-Tempered Clavier, Book 2 No.">Bach - Well-Tempered Clavier, Book 2 No. 2</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this broadcast, Nikolai Demidenko plays Preludes and Fugues Nos. 1 to 12 (BWV 870-881) from Book Two of Bach's Well-Tempered Clavier, recorded</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 13:48:00" d="2020-04-19 14:02:00"><n>Schumann - Symphony No. 1, Op. 38 - III. Scherzo</n><t>L</t>    <k>In 1999 the annual Europa Konzert was performed in Krakow. Enjoy the Berliner Philharmoniker and Bernard Haitink in works by Mozart, Chopin and Schumann</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 14:02:00" d="2020-04-19 17:20:00"><n>Purcell - The Indian Queen</n><t>M</t>    <k>Peter Sellars created a fresh version of Purcell's last masterpiece &quot;The Indian Queen.&quot; He rewrote the text to translate the story into a 21th century perspective</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 17:20:00" d="2020-04-19 18:51:00"><n>Legato - World of the Piano</n><t>S</t>    <k>Montréal native Marc-André Hamelin is internationally renowned for his musical virtuosity and refined pianism. He plays works by Haydn (Piano sonata</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 18:51:00" d="2020-04-19 19:27:00"><n u="Saint-Saëns - Symphony No.">Saint-Saëns - Symphony No. 3</n><t>M</t>    <k>Conrad van Alphen conducts Sinfonia Rotterdam in a performance of Saint-Saëns' Symphony No. 3, Op. 78, recorded on October 20th, 2018 in Rotterdam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 19:27:00" d="2020-04-19 19:52:00"><n u="Mozart - Symphony in A Major, K.">Mozart - Symphony in A Major, K. 201</n><t>L</t>    <k>Claudio Abbado conducts the Berlin Philharmonic in a delighting performance of Mozart's Symphony No. 29 in A major (K. 201). The recording</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 19:52:00" d="2020-04-19 19:59:00"><n>Chabrier - Espana</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 19:59:00" d="2020-04-19 20:09:00"><n>Dvorák - Symphony No. 7, Op. 70 - III. Scherzo</n><t>M</t>    <k>Royal Stockholm Philharmonic Orchestra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 20:09:00" d="2020-04-19 20:27:00"><n>Beethoven - Symphony No. 3, Op. 55 - III. Scherzo</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Europakonzert of 1997 took place at the Royal Opera of Versailles. Featuring Daniel Barenboim, both as conductor and as soloist, he performs in one of W.A</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 20:27:00" d="2020-04-19 20:33:00"><n>Schumann - Symphony No. 1, Op. 38 - II. Larghetto</n><t>L</t>    <k>In 1999 the annual Europa Konzert was performed in Krakow. Enjoy the Berliner Philharmoniker and Bernard Haitink in works by Mozart, Chopin and Schumann</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 20:33:00" d="2020-04-19 20:40:00"><n u="Mozart - Ouverture from Don Giovanni, K.">Mozart - Ouverture from Don Giovanni, K. 527</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Berlin Philharmonic, led by maestro Claudio Abbado, perform their first Europakonzert in Prague in 1991. Soloists in this first edition are soprano</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 20:40:00" d="2020-04-19 21:00:00"><n>Grieg - Solveig's Song from Peer Gynt, Op. 55/4</n><t>M</t>    <k>The outstanding Berlin Philharmonic orchestra, under the baton of Neeme Järvi, s take us on a trip to Arabian &quot;Thousand and One Nights&quot;, with soloist Janine Jansen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 21:00:00" d="2020-04-19 23:48:00"><n>Haydn - Orlando Paladino</n><t>M</t>    <k>For more than 25 years, René Jacobs has dedicated his life to baroque operas and works with the best ensembles for early music. On occasion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-19 23:48:00" d="2020-04-20 00:00:00"><n>Ennio Morricone - Filmsuite in Duo</n><t>S</t>    <k>Pietro Tagliaferri (clarinet) and Francesco Attesti (piano) play a suite with film music (C'era una volta il West - Mission - Nuovo Cinema Paradiso)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-20 00:00:00" d="2020-04-20 02:46:00"><n>Debussy - Pelléas et Melisande</n><t>M</t>    <k>Alain Altinoglu conducts a performance of Debussy's Pelléas et Mélisande at the Opernhaus Zürich in 2016. Main soloists are Brindley Sherratt (Arkel)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-20 02:46:00" d="2020-04-20 03:30:00"><n>Brendel and Abbado at Lucerne Festival</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Lucerne Festival is one of the world's biggest and most important music festivals. During the 2005 edition, the Lucerne Festival Orchestra and Claudio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-20 03:30:00" d="2020-04-20 04:30:00"><n u="Mozart on Tour - Episode 7: Vienna -">Mozart on Tour - Episode 7: Vienna - I</n><t>S</t>    <k>The 13-part Mozart on Tour series chronicles the journey of Mozart across Europe. The performance of Mozart's Piano Concerto No. 17, KV 453 features</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-20 04:30:00" d="2020-04-20 04:59:00"><n u="Brahms - Brahms - Violin Sonata No. 1, Op.">Brahms - Brahms - Violin Sonata No. 1, Op. 78</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this splendid 2013 concert from the Church of Verbier, Switzerland, Greek violinist Leonidas Kavakos and Chinese pianist Yuja Wang join forces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-04-20 04:59:00" d="2020-04-20 05:06:00"><n>Chabrier - Espana</n><t>M</t>  </p>
</a>
