<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a><n>Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 14, Op. 27, No. 2</n><s o="2020-04-18 14:24:00" d="2020-04-18 14:49:00" n="Brava HDTV" id_tv="560"></s><p><k>Italian pianist Riccardo Schwartz was born in Milan in 1986. One of his best known successes thus far, is the acclaimed concert cycle of Beethoven's 32 Sonatas. This performance features Piano Sonata No. 14 in C minor &quot;Quasi una fantasia&quot;, Op. 27, No. 2. It was recorded in March 2019 at the Fazioli Concert Hall in Sacile.</k><d>Italian pianist Riccardo Schwartz was born in Milan in 1986, and completed his studies at Conservatorio of Milan as a student of acclaimed musicians such as Riccardo Risaliti, Leonardo Leonardi, and Annibale Rebaudengo. He graduated with Honorable Mention and continued his piano studies at the Accademia Pianistica of Imola. Throughout his career, he has had the privilege of performing as a soloist under the baton of outstanding conductors, among the likes of Gustav Kuhn and Yuri Temirkanov. His acclaimed performances include recitals and concertos for piano and orchestra in many prestigious concert halls. One of his best-known successes is the acclaimed concert cycle of Beethoven's 32 Sonatas. This performance features Piano Sonata No. 14 in C minor &quot;Quasi una fantasia&quot;, Op. 27, No. 2, famously known as his &quot;Moonlight Sonata&quot;. The name originates from remarks made by the German music critic and poet Ludwig Rellstab. In 1832, five years after Beethoven's death, Rellstab compared the effect of the first movement to that of moonlight shining upon Lake Lucerne. Within ten years, the name &quot;Moonlight Sonata&quot; (&quot;Mondscheinsonate&quot; in German) had been established throughout English and German publications. Later in the nineteenth century, the sonata was finally known by that name everywhere. This recital was recorded in March 2019 at the Fazioli Concert Hall in Sacile.</d></p><i><w>http://tv.sms.cz/televize/brava-hdtv/20200418/1390165454-Beethoven-piano-sonata-no-14-op-27-no-2</w></i><x></x></a>
