<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="20" t="2020-05-15 05:02:43"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-22 05:11:00" d="2020-05-22 06:00:00"><n u="Bach - The Well-Tempered Clavier No.">Bach - The Well-Tempered Clavier No. 24</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Well-Tempered Clavier, BWV 846–893, is a collection of two series of Preludes and Fugues in all 24 major and minor keys, composed for solo keyboard by Bach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-22 06:00:00" d="2020-05-22 07:41:00"><n>First Snow</n><t>M</t>    <k>One of the first Christmas carols ever written is Perotin the Great's Salvatoris Hodie. This brilliant 12th century composition, one of the first works</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-22 07:41:00" d="2020-05-22 08:27:00"><n>Burgundian Alphabet I - Anonymous to Incertus</n><t>M</t>    <k>Enjoy a genuine musical marathon as a prelude to the Utrecht Early Music Festival 2018. During three concerts, the Huelgas Ensemble sing an entire alphabet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-22 08:27:00" d="2020-05-22 09:03:00"><n>CMIM - Finals - John Brancy</n><t>M</t>    <k>Peter Dugan accompanies baritone John Brancy (USA, 1988) during the finals of the Art Song competition of the Concours musical international de Montréal of 2018 (CMIM)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-22 09:03:00" d="2020-05-22 10:00:00"><n>Tchaikovsky - Romeo &amp; Juliet - Fantasy Ouverture</n><t>M</t>    <k>Every year, the Europakonzert is hosted by the Berliner Philharmoniker in a notorious concert hall or on a special location. This years concert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-22 10:00:00" d="2020-05-22 11:09:00"><n u="Shostakovich - Symphony No. 4 in C minor, Op.">Shostakovich - Symphony No. 4 in C minor, Op. 43</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this 2018 concert, the Rotterdam Philharmonic Orchestra is lead by Canadian conductor and pianist Yannick Nézet-Séguin in a performance of Dmitri</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-22 11:09:00" d="2020-05-22 12:17:00"><n>The Red Priest and the Tanguero</n><t>M</t>    <k>The set YES Camerata (Young European String Camerata) and the violinist William Hagen interpret The four seasons of Antonio Vivaldi and Las quatros</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-22 12:17:00" d="2020-05-22 13:15:00"><n u="Mozart on Tour - Episode 13: Vienna">Mozart on Tour - Episode 13: Vienna III</n><t>S</t>    <k>The 13-part Mozart on Tour series chronicles the journeys of Mozart across Europe. Soloist Aleksander Madzar performs Mozart's Piano Concerto No</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-22 13:15:00" d="2020-05-22 14:00:00"><n u="Brahms - Violin Sonata No. 2, Op.">Brahms - Violin Sonata No. 2, Op. 100</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this splendid 2013 concert from the Church of Verbier, Switzerland, Greek violinist Leonidas Kavakos and Chinese pianist Yuja Wang join forces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-22 14:00:00" d="2020-05-22 15:12:00"><n>Big Nightmare Music</n><t>L</t>    <k>In &quot;Big Nightmare Music&quot;, Aleksey Igudesman and Hyung-ki Joo perform their unique interpretations of classical favorites next to several sketches</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-22 15:12:00" d="2020-05-22 16:36:00"><n u="Mahler - Symphony No.">Mahler - Symphony No. 9</n><t>L</t>    <k>This film on the performance of Mahler's 9th symphony by the Gustav Mahler Jugendorchester, under the baton of Claudio Abbado, was recorded at Accademia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-22 16:36:00" d="2020-05-22 18:24:00"><n u="Mahler - Symphony No.">Mahler - Symphony No. 3</n><t>M</t>    <k>Due to its 95-minute duration, Gustav Mahler's Symphony No. 3 is an imposing and mysterious work. This 1992 performance, directed by Bernhard Haitink</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-22 18:24:00" d="2020-05-22 19:11:00"><n>Josquin in Spain - Missa Hercules Dux Ferrariae</n><t>M</t>    <k>Spanish and Flemish musical chapels characterized the music practice at the courts of Charles V and Philip II. But how would Josquin sound in the Spanish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-22 19:11:00" d="2020-05-22 21:00:00"><n u="Elgar - Concerto for Cello, Op.">Elgar - Concerto for Cello, Op. 85</n><t>M</t>    <k>For over 20 years, the Berliner Philharmoniker have celebrated their foundation on May 1st with the annual Europa Konzert - the 2010 concert takes place in Oxford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-22 21:00:00" d="2020-05-22 23:23:00"><n>Boito - Mefistofele</n><t>M</t>    <k>Stefan Soltesz conducts the Münchner Philharmoniker in a performance of Arrigo Boito's Mefistofele, with Erwin Schrott singing the title role. Mefistofele</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-22 23:23:00" d="2020-05-23 00:00:00"><n u="Schubert - Overture to Rosamunde">Schubert - Overture to Rosamunde (D. 644)</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 00:00:00" d="2020-05-23 02:28:00"><n>Verdi - Luisa Miller</n><t>M</t>    <k>Under the musical direction of Massimo Zanetti, the Orchestre et Choeurs de l'Opéra Royal de Wallonie present the opera &quot;Luisa Miller&quot;. As the result</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 02:28:00" d="2020-05-23 03:47:00"><n>Absolute Prokofiev: The Third Concert</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Mariinsky Theatre Symphony Orchestra under the baton of Valery Gergiev performs the complete cycle of Sergei Prokofiev's symphonies and piano concerti</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 03:47:00" d="2020-05-23 04:41:00"><n>Mozart on Tour - Episode 1: London</n><t>S</t>    <k>The 13-part Mozart on Tour series chronicles the journey of Mozart across Europe. In this episode, Vladimir Ashkenazy performs as a soloist and conductor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-23 04:41:00" d="2020-05-23 06:00:00"><n u="Haydn - String Quartet in C Major Op. 33 No.">Haydn - String Quartet in C Major Op. 33 No. 3</n><t>M</t>    <k>The British String Quartet The Lindsays have recorded all substantial Haydn String Quartets during their active years, from 1965 to 2005</k>  </p>
</a>
