<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="20" t="2020-05-28 04:44:26"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-04 06:00:00" d="2020-06-04 07:34:00"><n>Bach - Motets</n><t>M</t>    <k>This festive concert from the Gethsemanekirche in Berlin marks the 60th anniversary of the RIAS Kammerchor. Under the new chief conductor Hans-Christoph</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-04 07:34:00" d="2020-06-04 08:24:00"><n>Josquin - Missa Ave Maris stella</n><t>M</t>    <k>&quot;Paradise on earth.&quot; Luther's words reflect the admiration that many generations of music fanatics have felt for Josquin Desprez. More than 500 years later</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-04 08:24:00" d="2020-06-04 08:59:00"><n>Semi Final I - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sergey Belyavskiy (1993, Russia) performs Rapsodie hongroise No. 9 'Carnival in Pest', S244/9 and Grandes Études de Paganini, S141 during semi-final</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-04 08:59:00" d="2020-06-04 10:01:00"><n u="Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 9, Op. 14, No.">Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 9, Op. 14, No. 1</n><t>M</t>    <k>Italian pianist Riccardo Schwartz was born in Milan in 1986. One of his best known successes thus far, is the acclaimed concert cycle of Beethoven's 32 Sonatas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-04 10:01:00" d="2020-06-04 10:59:00"><n>How to get out of the Cage - A year with John Cage</n><t>M</t>    <k>The compelling documentary How to Get Out of the Cage (2012), by award-winning filmmaker Frank Scheffer, presents an intimate portrait of John Cage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-04 10:59:00" d="2020-06-04 12:14:00"><n u="Bach - Partitas for Solo Violin">Bach - Partitas for Solo Violin (BWV 1001-1006)</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2006, Gidon Kremer took on the greatest challenge for any violinist: Bach's &quot;Sonatas and Partitas for Solo Violin&quot; (BWV 1001-1006). With these pieces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-04 12:14:00" d="2020-06-04 12:50:00" c="1"><n>Danielpour - Elegies</n><t>F</t>    <k>Hartmut Haenchen conducts the philharmonie zuid in a performance of Richard Danielpour's Elegies. Soloists are Marina Prudenskaya (mezzo-soprano), Thomas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-04 12:50:00" d="2020-06-04 14:01:00"><n u="Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 15, Op.">Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 15, Op. 28</n><t>M</t>    <k>Italian pianist Riccardo Schwartz was born in Milan in 1986. One of his best known successes thus far, is the acclaimed concert cycle of Beethoven's 32 Sonatas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-04 14:01:00" d="2020-06-04 16:34:00"><n>Dvořák - Rusalka</n><t>M</t>    <k>Ádám Fischer conducts the orchestra and choir of La Monnaie in a performance of Dvořák's opera Rusalka. The work remains one of the cornerstones of Czech opera houses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-04 16:34:00" d="2020-06-04 17:23:00"><n u="Brahms - Symphony No. 1, Op.">Brahms - Symphony No. 1, Op. 68</n><t>M</t>    <k>For over 20 years, the Berliner Philharmoniker have celebrated their foundation on May 1st with the annual Europa Konzert - the 2010 concert takes place in Oxford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-04 17:23:00" d="2020-06-04 19:12:00"><n>Waldbühne 2016 - A Czech Night</n><t>M</t>    <k>For the 2016 edition of the Waldbühne, the Georgian violinist Lisa Batiashvili and the Québécois conductor Yannick Nézet-Séguin join the Berliner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-04 19:12:00" d="2020-06-04 19:34:00"><n>CMIM - Semi Finals - Clara Osowski</n><t>M</t>    <k>Olivier Godin accompanies mezzo-soprano Clara Osowski (USA, 1986) during the semi-finals of the Art Song competition of the Concours musical international</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-04 19:34:00" d="2020-06-04 20:00:00"><n>CMIM - Semi Finals - Julien van Mellaerts</n><t>M</t>    <k>Joao Araújo accompanies baritone Julien van Mellaerts (New-Zealand/UK, 1988 during the semi-finals of the Art Song competition of the Concours musical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-04 20:00:00" d="2020-06-04 21:00:00"><n u="Mendelssohn - Violin Concerto, Op.">Mendelssohn - Violin Concerto, Op. 64</n><t>L</t>    <k>Conductor Teodor Currentzis leads his ensemble MusicAeterna alongside violinist Patricia Kopatchinskaja in a performance of works by Brahms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-04 21:00:00" d="2020-06-04 22:38:00"><n>Sleeping Beauty 2013</n><t>M</t>    <k>Set to the magnificent compositions of Pyotr Ilyich Tchaikovsky, The Sleeping Beauty on Ice retells the classic fairytale love story through sublime world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-04 22:38:00" d="2020-06-05 00:00:00"><n u="Berlioz - Symphonie Fantastique, Op.">Berlioz - Symphonie Fantastique, Op. 14</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2001, the world-famous Berlin Philharmonic's annual Europakonzert took place at a very unusual location: the Hagia Irene in Istanbul. This Byzantine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-05 00:00:00" d="2020-06-05 02:46:00"><n>Debussy - Pelléas et Melisande</n><t>M</t>    <k>Alain Altinoglu conducts a performance of Debussy's Pelléas et Mélisande at the Opernhaus Zürich in 2016. Main soloists are Brindley Sherratt (Arkel)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-05 02:46:00" d="2020-06-05 04:05:00"><n>Barati &amp; Debargue perform Debussy, Brahms &amp; Franck</n><t>M</t>    <k>Violinist Kristof Barati and Pianist Lucas Debargue pair for the first time in a duo concert at the 25th anniversary edition of the Swiss Verbier Festival in 2018</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-05 04:05:00" d="2020-06-05 04:33:00"><n>Discovering Masterpieces - Concerto for Orchestra</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bela Bartok's 'Concerto for Orchestra' is discussed. This piece is one of the most frequently performed works of the twentieth century. Pierre Boulez</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-05 04:33:00" d="2020-06-05 06:00:00"><n>Rachmaninoff &amp; Dvořák Trios</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Valerius Ensemble, consisting of Eeva Koskinen (violin), René Geesing (cello) and Ingo Lulofs (piano) plays Rachmaninoff's Trio élégiaque Nr</k>  </p>
</a>
