<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="21" t="2020-05-30 04:43:06"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-06 06:00:00" d="2020-06-06 06:36:00"><n>Valls - Missa Scala Aretina</n><t>M</t>    <k>Patrick Debrabandere conducts the Vox Mago choir and orchestra in a performance of the Missa scala aretina by the Spanish composer Francisco Valls (1672-1747)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-06 06:36:00" d="2020-06-06 07:57:00"><n>Legato - World of the Piano</n><t>S</t>    <k>French master pianist Pierre-Laurent Aimard performs excerpts from Bach's 'The Art of Fugue', Carter's 'Matribute', 'Two Diversions' and 'Caténaires'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-06 07:57:00" d="2020-06-06 08:35:00"><n>Semi Final I - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Wouter Bergenhuizen (1988, The Netherlands) performs Grandes Études de Paganini, S141 and Années de Pelerinage: Deuxieme Année (Italie), No. 1 Sposalizio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-06 08:35:00" d="2020-06-06 10:00:00"><n>Haydn - Symphony No. 94, Hob. I:94</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2001, the world-famous Berlin Philharmonic's annual Europakonzert took place at a very unusual location: the Hagia Irene in Istanbul. This Byzantine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-06 10:00:00" d="2020-06-06 11:03:00"><n u="Rachmaninov - Symphony No. 2, Op.">Rachmaninov - Symphony No. 2, Op. 27</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-06 11:03:00" d="2020-06-06 12:15:00"><n>Pianomania - Elisabeth Leonskaja</n><t>M</t>    <k>Elisabeth Leonskaja performs Beethoven's last piano sonatas (Op. 109, 110 &amp; 111) during a concert recorded in Lisbon, in 2018. These three sonatas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-06 12:15:00" d="2020-06-06 12:58:00"><n>My heart is burning</n><t>L</t>    <k>In the musical film My Heart Is Burning, René Pape sings and plays various roles that showcase the impressive versatility of his voice and the many facets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-06 12:58:00" d="2020-06-06 14:02:00"><n>Chamber Music by Mozart and Von Dohnányi</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Valerius Ensemble, consisting of Carola Ligt (flute), Robert Windak (violin), Eva Šušlíková (viola) and René Geesing (cello) play a varied concert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-06 14:02:00" d="2020-06-06 15:39:00"><n>Mikko Franck conducts Ravel</n><t>M</t>    <k>Mikko Franck conducts the Orchestre de Paris and soloist Nora Gubisch in an attractive concert prorgramme, exclusively dedicated to compositions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-06 15:39:00" d="2020-06-06 16:16:00"><n u="Saint-Saëns - Symphony No.">Saint-Saëns - Symphony No. 3</n><t>M</t>    <k>Conrad van Alphen conducts Sinfonia Rotterdam in a performance of Saint-Saëns' Symphony No. 3, Op. 78, recorded on October 20th, 2018 in Rotterdam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-06 16:16:00" d="2020-06-06 16:39:00"><n u="Brahms - Violin Sonata No. 2, Op.">Brahms - Violin Sonata No. 2, Op. 100</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this splendid 2013 concert from the Church of Verbier, Switzerland, Greek violinist Leonidas Kavakos and Chinese pianist Yuja Wang join forces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-06 16:39:00" d="2020-06-06 17:28:00"><n>Dufay: A Burgundian in Italy</n><t>M</t>    <k>The career of Guillaume Dufay – figurehead of Burgundian polyphony – begins in Italy. He seems to have particularly strong ties with Florence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-06 17:28:00" d="2020-06-06 17:47:00"><n>Semi Final II - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Leon Bernsdorf (1992, Germany) performs Epithalam zu Eduard Reményis Vermählungsfeier (S129) and Grand Duo concertant sur la Romance de 'Le Marin' (S128)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-06 17:47:00" d="2020-06-06 19:30:00"><n>The Divan Orchestra from the Alhambra</n><t>M</t>    <k>The members of the West-Eastern Divan Orchestra come from Israel, Palestine, Syria, Jordan, Egypt and Europe. The orchestra has taken on the complex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-06 19:30:00" d="2020-06-06 21:00:00"><n u="Mozart on Tour - Episode 7: Vienna -">Mozart on Tour - Episode 7: Vienna - I</n><t>S</t>    <k>The 13-part Mozart on Tour series chronicles the journey of Mozart across Europe. The performance of Mozart's Piano Concerto No. 17, KV 453 features</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-06 21:00:00" d="2020-06-06 21:53:00"><n>Robert Wilson: A Living Space</n><t>M</t>    <k>A Living Space is a unique documentary exploring 50 days of the Watermill Summer Program, run by visionary theatre director Robert Wilson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-06 21:53:00" d="2020-06-06 23:15:00"><n>Veerhavenconcert 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>The 2018 edition of the Veerhavenconcert in Rotterdam offers an accessible program with operatic works by Verdi, Ponchielli, and Puccini. Maxim Emelyanchec</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-06 23:15:00" d="2020-06-07 00:00:00"><n>CMIM - Semi Finals - Axelle Fanyo</n><t>M</t>    <k>Julien LeBlanc accompanies soprano Axelle Fanyo (France, 1989) during the semi-finals of the Art Song competition of the Concours musical international</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 00:00:00" d="2020-06-07 02:55:00"><n>Mozart - Cosi fan tutte</n><t>M</t>    <k>Stefano Montanari conducts Mozart's opera Cosi fan tutte in a staging by Adrian Noble. The major roles are played by Lionel Lhote, Daniel Behle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 02:55:00" d="2020-06-07 04:38:00"><n>Europakonzert 2007 - Berlin</n><t>M</t>    <k>The 2007 Europa-Konzert takes place in Berlin, on the occasion of the 125th anniversary of the Berliner Philharmoniker. Under the theme &quot;The Year 1882&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-07 04:38:00" d="2020-06-07 05:04:00"><n>Discovering Masterpieces – Mendelssohn</n><t>S</t>    <k>In this documentary, Felix Mendelssohn's 'Violin Concerto' is discussed. Felix Mendelssohn-Bartholdy (1809-1847) was the Gewandhaus Orchestra Leipzig's first conductor</k>  </p>
</a>
