<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="20" t="2020-06-01 04:37:57"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-08 06:00:00" d="2020-06-08 07:14:00"><n>A Mozart Concert from Berlin</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Carl Philipp Emanuel Bach Chamber Orchestra delivers a program entirely devoted to Mozart at the Konzerthaus in Berlin under the direction of Hartmut Haenchen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-08 07:14:00" d="2020-06-08 08:24:00"><n>Le Grand Orgue in Concert</n><t>L</t>    <k>Olivier Latry, the holder of the &quot;Great Organ of the Notre Dame,&quot; enchants with a masterful performance on the historic organ of Paris' most famous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-08 08:24:00" d="2020-06-08 09:00:00"><n>Semi Final I - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Minsoo Hong (1993, South Korea) performs Variationen über das Motif von J.S. Bach: 'Weinen, Klagen', S180, Gounod/Liszt - Les Adieux, Reverie sur un motif</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-08 09:00:00" d="2020-06-08 10:00:00"><n>Rodrigo - Concierto de Aranjuez</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-08 10:00:00" d="2020-06-08 10:35:00"><n>Mariinsky on Track</n><t>L</t>    <k>In this documentary we follow the Mariinsky Theatre Orchestra on this musical journey. By the use of interviews with the instrumentalists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-08 10:35:00" d="2020-06-08 11:57:00"><n u="Brahms - The 3 Violin Sonatas, Op. 78, 100 &amp;">Brahms - The 3 Violin Sonatas, Op. 78, 100 &amp; 108</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this splendid 2013 concert from the Church of Verbier, Switzerland, Greek violinist Leonidas Kavakos and Chinese pianist Yuja Wang join forces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-08 11:57:00" d="2020-06-08 12:44:00"><n>Rimsky-Korsakov Suites</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this exquisite concert 2016 from Moscow's Tchaikovsky Concert Hall, the Russian National Orchestra and star-pianist Boris Berezovsky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-08 12:44:00" d="2020-06-08 14:01:00"><n u="Beethoven - Piano Concerto No. 5, Op.">Beethoven - Piano Concerto No. 5, Op. 73</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Berliner Philharmoniker, Daniel Barenboim and Claudio Abbado star at the Europakonzert 1994 in Meiningen, Germany, performing Ludwig van Beethoven's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-08 14:01:00" d="2020-06-08 15:42:00"><n>Easter Concert in Baden-Baden 2016</n><t>M</t>    <k>Manfred Honeck conducts the Berlin Philharmonic during the 2016 Easter Concert from Baden-Baden. Yo-Yo Ma is the soloist in Schumann's Concerto for Cello, Op</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-08 15:42:00" d="2020-06-08 16:45:00"><n>Khachaturyan Piano Concerto &amp; Borodin</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Svetlanov Symphony Orchestra of Russia and pianist Boris Berezovsky are led by conductor Vladimir Verbitsky in a performance of works</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-08 16:45:00" d="2020-06-08 17:40:00"><n>Celebrate St. Patrick 2018</n><t>L</t>    <k>Join composer and presenter John Anderson as he conducts a reflective and celebratory event honouring Saint Patrick. In the St Patrick's RC Cathedral</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-08 17:40:00" d="2020-06-08 18:05:00"><n u="Haydn - String Quartet in C Major Op. 20 No.">Haydn - String Quartet in C Major Op. 20 No. 2</n><t>M</t>    <k>The British String Quartet The Lindsays have recorded all substantial Haydn String Quartets during their active years, from 1965 to 2005</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-08 18:05:00" d="2020-06-08 19:36:00"><n>Easter Concert in Baden-Baden 2015</n><t>M</t>    <k>Bernard Haitink conducts the Berliner Philharmoniker at the Easter Festival in Baden-Baden, 2015. On the program are Beethoven's Symphony No. 6, and Violin Concerto, Op</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-08 19:36:00" d="2020-06-08 21:00:00"><n>Claudio Abbado &amp; Orchestra Mozart</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2004, Claudio Abbado founded the Orchestra Mozart in Bologna, Italy. The orchestra collects the best classical music performers of the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-08 21:00:00" d="2020-06-08 22:56:00"><n u="Beethoven - Fidelio, Op.">Beethoven - Fidelio, Op. 72</n><t>M</t>    <k>Fidelio, Op. 72, is Ludwig van Beethoven's only opera. This 2018 opera film from the Swiss Theater St. Gallen is based on Jan Schmidt-Garre's highly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-08 22:56:00" d="2020-06-09 00:00:00"><n u="Brahms - Brahms - Violin Sonata No. 1, Op.">Brahms - Brahms - Violin Sonata No. 1, Op. 78</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this splendid 2013 concert from the Church of Verbier, Switzerland, Greek violinist Leonidas Kavakos and Chinese pianist Yuja Wang join forces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-09 00:00:00" d="2020-06-09 02:48:00"><n>Haydn - Orlando Paladino</n><t>M</t>    <k>For more than 25 years, René Jacobs has dedicated his life to baroque operas and works with the best ensembles for early music. On occasion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-09 02:48:00" d="2020-06-09 04:08:00"><n>Glass - Double Concerto for Two Pianos</n><t>M</t>    <k>As part of a new collaboration with the famous composer Philip Glass, French pianists Katia and Marielle Labeque perform the European premiere of Glass's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-09 04:08:00" d="2020-06-09 04:31:00"><n>Sons of Vienna: Part 3 - Man About Town</n><t>S</t>    <k>The six-part series Sons of Vienna portrays extraordinary composers who were active in the cultural city of Vienna and deserve the label of genius</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-09 04:31:00" d="2020-06-09 06:00:00"><n>CMIM - Semi Finals - Rihab Chaieb</n><t>M</t>    <k>Michel-Alexandre Broekaert accompanies mezzo-soprano Rihab Chaieb (Canada/Tunisia, 1987 during the semi-finals of the Art Song competition of the Concours</k>  </p>
</a>
