<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="20" t="2020-05-26 04:42:32"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-02 06:00:00" d="2020-06-02 07:06:00"><n>Josquin - Missa L'homme armé sexti toni</n><t>M</t>    <k>'Beware the armed man!' The warning about 'L'homme armé' sounds twice as powerful from the mouth of Josquin Desprez: he twice used the popular medieval</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-02 07:06:00" d="2020-06-02 08:25:00"><n>Evgeny Kissin plays Chopin, Schumann &amp; Debussy</n><t>M</t>    <k>Evgeny Kissin enchants with a magnificent piano recital of works by Chopin, Schumann and Debussy at the 25th anniversary edition of the Swiss Verbier</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-02 08:25:00" d="2020-06-02 08:57:00"><n>CMIM - Finals - Gemma Summerfield</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sebastian Wybrew accompanies soprano Gemma Summerfield (UK, 1990) during the finals of the Art Song competition of the Concours musical international</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-02 08:57:00" d="2020-06-02 10:02:00"><n u="Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 12, Op.">Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 12, Op. 26</n><t>M</t>    <k>Italian pianist Riccardo Schwartz was born in Milan in 1986. One of his best known successes thus far, is the acclaimed concert cycle of Beethoven's 32 Sonatas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-02 10:02:00" d="2020-06-02 11:27:00"><n u="Mahler - Symphony No.">Mahler - Symphony No. 9</n><t>L</t>    <k>This film on the performance of Mahler's 9th symphony by the Gustav Mahler Jugendorchester, under the baton of Claudio Abbado, was recorded at Accademia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-02 11:27:00" d="2020-06-02 12:53:00"><n u="Trios: Tchaikovsky, Op. 50 &amp; Shostakovich, Op.">Trios: Tchaikovsky, Op. 50 &amp; Shostakovich, Op. 67</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Zadig Trio consists of the two French childhood friends Boris Borgolotto (violin), Marc Girard Garcia (cello) and the American pianist Ian Barber</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-02 12:53:00" d="2020-06-02 13:16:00"><n>Sons of Vienna: Part 2 - A Lion's Roar</n><t>S</t>    <k>The six-part series Sons of Vienna portrays extraordinary composers who were active in the cultural city of Vienna and deserve the label of genius</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-02 13:16:00" d="2020-06-02 14:00:00"><n>Semi Final II - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jan Hugo (1991, South Africa) performs Die drei Zigeuner (S383), Die Zelle in Nonnenwerth (S382bis) and La lugubre gondola (S134bis) during semi-final</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-02 14:00:00" d="2020-06-02 16:47:00"><n>Debussy - Pelléas et Melisande</n><t>M</t>    <k>Alain Altinoglu conducts a performance of Debussy's Pelléas et Mélisande at the Opernhaus Zürich in 2016. Main soloists are Brindley Sherratt (Arkel)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-02 16:47:00" d="2020-06-02 17:42:00"><n u="Brahms - Piano Concerto No. 1, Op.">Brahms - Piano Concerto No. 1, Op. 15</n><t>M</t>    <k>Europakonzert 2004 was held in Athens, Greece. This concert featured the Berliner Philharmoniker performing live at the ancient Herodes Atticus Theatre</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-02 17:42:00" d="2020-06-02 19:22:00"><n>Bach - Brandenburg Concertos</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Orchestra Mozart, founded in 2004, under the baton of Claudio Abbado play Bach's Brandenburg Concertos. Recorded at the Teatro Municipale Valli, Reggio Emilia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-02 19:22:00" d="2020-06-02 19:34:00"><n u="Bach - The Well-Tempered Clavier No.">Bach - The Well-Tempered Clavier No. 24</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Well-Tempered Clavier, BWV 846–893, is a collection of two series of Preludes and Fugues in all 24 major and minor keys, composed for solo keyboard by Bach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-02 19:34:00" d="2020-06-02 19:59:00"><n>Solo Finals - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Dina Ivanova (1994, Russia) performs Liszt'sTotentanz (S525), Schubert/Liszt - Auf dem wasser zu singen (S558/2) and Erlkönig (S558/4) during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-02 19:59:00" d="2020-06-02 21:00:00"><n u="Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 10, Op. 14, No.">Beethoven - Piano Sonata No. 10, Op. 14, No. 2</n><t>M</t>    <k>Italian pianist Riccardo Schwartz was born in Milan in 1986. One of his best known successes thus far, is the acclaimed concert cycle of Beethoven's 32 Sonatas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-02 21:00:00" d="2020-06-02 22:31:00"><n>Penderecki - Symphony No. 7: 7 Gates of Jerusalem</n><t>M</t>    <k>One of the greatest composers of the latter half of the twentieth century, Krzysztof Penderecki conducts the Prague Radio Symphony Orchestra and Slovak</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-02 22:31:00" d="2020-06-02 23:30:00"><n>Looking for Cole</n><t>M</t>    <k>The film &quot;Looking for Cole,&quot; by Wilfried van den Brande, recorded over the course of three years, gives a unique insight into Cole Porter's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-02 23:30:00" d="2020-06-03 00:00:00"><n>Classical:NEXT 2019 - reConvert Project</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this performance from the 2019 edition of Classical:NEXT!, musicians Lorenzo Colombo (electronics and percussion) and Roberto Maqueda (electronics</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-03 00:00:00" d="2020-06-03 02:52:00"><n>Rossini - La Cenerentola</n><t>M</t>    <k>This 2015 performance of La Cenerentola at the Opéra de Rennes is conducted by Darrell Ang and features the Symphonic Orchestra of Brittany and choir</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-03 02:52:00" d="2020-06-03 04:13:00"><n>Mahler: 10th Symphony: Adagio &amp; Youth's Magic Horn</n><t>M</t>    <k>Pierre Boulez conducts the Cleveland Symphony Orchestra in a performance of the Adagio from Mahler's Symphony No. 10 and the song cycle Des Knaben Wunderhorn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-03 04:13:00" d="2020-06-03 06:00:00"><n>Mozart on Tour - Episode 2: Mantua</n><t>S</t>    <k>The 13-part Mozart on Tour series chronicles the journey of Mozart across Europe. Discover the soloist Heidrun Holtmann as she performs Mozart's Piano Concertos No</k>  </p>
</a>
