<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="25" t="2021-07-09 07:39:22"><p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 05:04:00" d="2021-07-14 05:32:00"><n u="Shostakovich - Symphony No. 9, Op.">Shostakovich - Symphony No. 9, Op. 70</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Lucerne Symphony Orchestra under the baton of Neeme Järvi will presents the world premiere of Rodion Shchedrin's new concerto for cello, piano and orchestra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 05:32:00" d="2021-07-14 06:00:00"><n>J.D. Heinichen - Magnificat in A</n><t>M</t>    <k>Patrick Debrabandere conducts the Vox Mago chamber choir in a performance of J. D. Heinichen's Magnificat in A</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 06:00:00" d="2021-07-14 07:11:00"><n>Between Church and Theatre: Jommelli and Scarlatti</n><t>M</t>    <k>To strengthen faith and stimulate piety: this was the role of music according to Pope Benedictus XIV, who in the 18th century carried out radical church reforms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 07:11:00" d="2021-07-14 08:38:00"><n>Abbado conducts Mahler No. 4 and Rückert-Lieder</n><t>M</t>    <k>Mezzo soprano Magdalena Kožená does not only make the heavenly joys resound in the final movement of Gustav Mahler's Symphony No</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 08:38:00" d="2021-07-14 09:10:00"><n u="Haydn - String Quartet in F minor Op. 20 No.">Haydn - String Quartet in F minor Op. 20 No. 5</n><t>M</t>    <k>The British String Quartet The Lindsays have recorded all substantial Haydn String Quartets during their active years, from 1965 to 2005</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 09:10:00" d="2021-07-14 10:00:00"><n u="Beethoven - Symphony No.">Beethoven - Symphony No. 2</n><t>M</t>    <k>In September 2016, we celebrated the birthday of one of Japan's best-known conductors: Seiji Ozawa. Renowned for his advocacy of modern composers, Ozawa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 10:00:00" d="2021-07-14 10:57:00"><n>Brahms - Violin Concerto &amp; Academic Ouverture</n><t>M</t>    <k>One of today's most distinguished conductors, Franz Welser-Möst conducts The Cleveland Orchestra in a performance featuring works from the oeuvre of Johannes Brahms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 10:57:00" d="2021-07-14 12:00:00"><n>Roberto Giordano plays Brahms and Beethoven</n><t>M</t>    <k>Roberto Giordano plays the Six Pieces for Piano, op. 118 of Brahms, as well as the famous Moonlight Sonata and Sonata No. 31, op. 110 of Beethoven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 12:00:00" d="2021-07-14 12:58:00"><n u="Mozart on Tour - Episode 13: Vienna">Mozart on Tour - Episode 13: Vienna III</n><t>S</t>    <k>The 13-part Mozart on Tour series chronicles the journeys of Mozart across Europe. Soloist Aleksander Madzar performs Mozart's Piano Concerto No</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 12:58:00" d="2021-07-14 13:20:00"><n>Solo Finals - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Alexander Ullman (1991, United Kingdom) performs Liszt's Études d'exécution transcendante, No. 11 Harmonies du soir (S139/11), Nuages gris (S199)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 13:20:00" d="2021-07-14 14:00:00"><n>Haydn - Symphony No. 45 'Farewell'</n><t>M</t>    <k>Under the direction of Conrad van Alphen, the Sinfonia Rotterdam Orchestra performs Haydn's Symphony No. 45. In this piece nicknamed &quot;Farewell&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 14:00:00" d="2021-07-14 15:43:00"><n>Scandale</n><t>M</t>    <k>Pianists Alice Sara Ott and Francesco Tristan perform at the Heidelberger Frühling of 2015, a festival for contemporary classical music. On the program</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 15:43:00" d="2021-07-14 16:15:00"><n>Dutilleux - Symphony No. 2 'Le Double'</n><t>M</t>    <k>Soviet-born conductor Semyon Bychkov leads the Czech Philharmonic in a concert featuring works by Bohuslav Martinů, Maurice Ravel and Henri Dutilleux</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 16:15:00" d="2021-07-14 17:24:00"><n>Works for Flute &amp; Oboe: Haydn, Schumann, Bach</n><t>M</t>    <k>On April 9th, 2020, the day concert life was forced to stop, flutist Ana de la Vega and oboist Ramón Ortega Quero were already on tour. They played their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 17:24:00" d="2021-07-14 18:10:00"><n u="Tchaikovsky - Piano Trio, Op.">Tchaikovsky - Piano Trio, Op. 50</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Zadig Trio consists of the two French childhood friends Boris Borgolotto (violin), Marc Girard Garcia (cello) and the American pianist Ian Barber</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 18:10:00" d="2021-07-14 19:41:00"><n>Gabriela Montero plays Ravel &amp; Montero</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Venezuelan pianist Gabriela Montero is accompanied by the Youth Orchestra of the Americas conducted by Carlos Miguel Prieto. On the program are Ravel's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 19:41:00" d="2021-07-14 21:00:00"><n>Mozart on Tour - Episode 2: Mantua</n><t>S</t>    <k>The 13-part Mozart on Tour series chronicles the journey of Mozart across Europe. Discover the soloist Heidrun Holtmann as she performs Mozart's Piano Concertos No</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 21:00:00" d="2021-07-14 22:31:00"><n>Misha Fomin at the Concertgebouw 2018</n><t>M</t>    <k>Musical critics from North America, Europe, and Russia praise Nalchik-born pianist Misha Fomin for his subtlety of touch and phrasing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 22:31:00" d="2021-07-14 23:10:00"><n u="Beethoven - Symphony No. 7, Op.">Beethoven - Symphony No. 7, Op. 92</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sir Simon Rattle conducts the Berliner Philharmonic and Vadim Repin during the Europakonzert of 2008 from the Tchaikovsky Conservatory. On the program</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 23:10:00" d="2021-07-14 23:34:00"><n>Semi Final II - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Wouter Bergenhuizen (1988, The Netherlands) performs Die drei Zigeuner (S383), Die Zelle in Nonnenwerth (S382bis) and La lugubre gondola (S134bis) during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-14 23:34:00" d="2021-07-15 00:00:00"><n>Chopin - Etudes</n><t>M</t>    <k>Russian pianist Zlata Chochieva performed live at Schinkel Pavillon in Berlin on April 13, 2020. The program opens with a selection of Felix Mendelssohn's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-15 00:00:00" d="2021-07-15 02:48:00"><n>Haydn - Orlando Paladino</n><t>M</t>    <k>For more than 25 years, René Jacobs has dedicated his life to baroque operas and works with the best ensembles for early music. On occasion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-15 02:48:00" d="2021-07-15 03:48:00"><n>Tribute to Debussy</n><t>M</t>    <k>On the occasion of Claude Debussy's 150th anniversary, Jean-Claude Casadesus conducts the Orchestre National de Lille and choir of the Opéra de Lille</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-15 03:48:00" d="2021-07-15 04:40:00"><n>The Violin's Voice</n><t>M</t>    <k>The tale of world-renowned violinist Frank Peter Zimmerman's separation and reunion with his beloved 1711 Stradivarius is intertwined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-15 04:40:00" d="2021-07-15 05:23:00"><n u="Beethoven - Violin Concerto, Opus">Beethoven - Violin Concerto, Opus 61</n><t>M</t>    <k>Bernard Haitink conducts the Berliner Philharmoniker at the Easter Festival in Baden-Baden, 2015. On the program are Beethoven's Symphony No. 6, and Violin Concerto, Op</k>  </p>
</a>
