<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2020-05-14 05:03:00"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-21 06:00:00" d="2020-05-21 07:22:00"><n>Legato - World of the Piano</n><t>S</t>    <k>French master pianist Pierre-Laurent Aimard performs excerpts from Bach's 'The Art of Fugue', Carter's 'Matribute', 'Two Diversions' and 'Caténaires'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-21 07:22:00" d="2020-05-21 08:35:00"><n>A Mozart Concert from Berlin</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Carl Philipp Emanuel Bach Chamber Orchestra delivers a program entirely devoted to Mozart at the Konzerthaus in Berlin under the direction of Hartmut Haenchen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-21 08:35:00" d="2020-05-21 09:09:00"><n u="Gliere, Op. 20 and Shostakovich, Op.">Gliere, Op. 20 and Shostakovich, Op. 57</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Valerius Ensemble, consisting of Robert Windak (violin), Michael Rein (violin), Eva Šušlíková (viola), Judith Chapman (cello) and Ingo Lylofs (piano)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-21 09:09:00" d="2020-05-21 10:01:00"><n u="Mozart - Symphony No. 35, K.">Mozart - Symphony No. 35, K. 385</n><t>M</t>    <k>Claudio Abbado conducts the Berlin Philharmonic in a performance of Mozart's &quot;Haffner&quot; Symphony No. 35, K. 385, recording during the very first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-21 10:01:00" d="2020-05-21 10:26:00"><n>Sons of Vienna: Part 1 - Papa &amp; Wolfgang</n><t>S</t>    <k>The six-part series Sons of Vienna portrays extraordinary composers who were active in the cultural city of Vienna and deserve the label of genius</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-21 10:26:00" d="2020-05-21 11:58:00"><n>Legato - World of the Piano</n><t>S</t>    <k>Montréal native Marc-André Hamelin is internationally renowned for his musical virtuosity and refined pianism. He plays works by Haydn (Piano sonata</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-21 11:58:00" d="2020-05-21 12:36:00"><n u="Shostakovich - Piano Trio No.2, Op.">Shostakovich - Piano Trio No.2, Op. 67</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Zadig Trio consists of the two French childhood friends Boris Borgolotto (violin), Marc Girard Garcia (cello) and the American pianist Ian Barber</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-21 12:36:00" d="2020-05-21 14:02:00"><n>Khachaturyan Piano Concerto &amp; Borodin</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Svetlanov Symphony Orchestra of Russia and pianist Boris Berezovsky are led by conductor Vladimir Verbitsky in a performance of works</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-21 14:02:00" d="2020-05-21 16:51:00"><n>Haydn - Orlando Paladino</n><t>M</t>    <k>For more than 25 years, René Jacobs has dedicated his life to baroque operas and works with the best ensembles for early music. On occasion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-21 16:51:00" d="2020-05-21 17:45:00"><n u="Berlioz - Symphonie Fantastique, Op.">Berlioz - Symphonie Fantastique, Op. 14</n><t>M</t>    <k>In 2001, the world-famous Berlin Philharmonic's annual Europakonzert took place at a very unusual location: the Hagia Irene in Istanbul. This Byzantine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-21 17:45:00" d="2020-05-21 19:19:00"><n>Europakonzert 2016 from R?ros</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sir Simon Rattle conducts the Berlin Philharmonic in the 2016 edition of the Europakonzert, in R?ros, Norway. On the program are Grieg's Lyrical Piece, Op</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-21 19:19:00" d="2020-05-21 19:35:00"><n u="Haydn - String Quartet in D minor Op.">Haydn - String Quartet in D minor Op. 42</n><t>S</t>    <k>The British String Quartet The Lindsays have recorded all substantial Haydn String Quartets during their active years, from 1965 to 2005</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-21 19:35:00" d="2020-05-21 19:59:00"><n>Semi Final II - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Wouter Bergenhuizen (1988, The Netherlands) performs Die drei Zigeuner (S383), Die Zelle in Nonnenwerth (S382bis) and La lugubre gondola (S134bis) during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-21 19:59:00" d="2020-05-21 21:00:00"><n>Britten - The Young Persons Guide to the Orchestra</n><t>M</t>    <k>Marin Alsop conducts the Britten-Pears Orchestra in a performance of Britten's The Young Person's Guide to the Orchestra. Recorded at Snape Maltings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-21 21:00:00" d="2020-05-21 22:44:00"><n>Music and Dance for a While</n><t>M</t>    <k>In Music and Dance for a While we will immerse into a unique atmosphere, in which marvelous musicians from all over the world get together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-21 22:44:00" d="2020-05-22 00:00:00"><n u="Beethoven - Symphony No.">Beethoven - Symphony No. 9</n><t>M</t>    <k>Beethoven's Symphony no 9 is interpreted by the Berlin Philharmonic under former chief conductor Claudio Abbado at the Berliner Philharmonie in 2001</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-22 00:00:00" d="2020-05-22 02:52:00"><n>Rossini - La Cenerentola</n><t>M</t>    <k>This 2015 performance of La Cenerentola at the Opéra de Rennes is conducted by Darrell Ang and features the Symphonic Orchestra of Brittany and choir</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-22 02:52:00" d="2020-05-22 04:44:00"><n>Shalyapin Gala - Kazan Opera</n><t>M</t>    <k>Valery Gergiev and Renat Salavatov conduct the Orchestra of the Mariinsky Theatre and the Chorus of the Tartar State Academic Opera in a Gala concert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-05-22 04:44:00" d="2020-05-22 05:11:00"><n u="Discovering Masterpieces – Beethoven No.">Discovering Masterpieces – Beethoven No. 5</n><t>S</t>    <k>In this documentary, Ludwig van Beethoven's 'Symphony No. 5' is discussed. The piece has the character of an appeal from the very start, when the four-note</k>  </p>
</a>
