<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="20" t="2020-05-29 04:38:37"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-05 06:00:00" d="2020-06-05 07:17:00"><n>Bruges: The Burgundian Metropolis</n><t>M</t>    <k>By the 14th century, the Duchy of Burgundy had made Bruges its official residence. The city became a magnet for artists. The Gruuthuse manuscript</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-05 07:17:00" d="2020-06-05 08:39:00"><n>Jaroussky sings Bach &amp; Telemann</n><t>M</t>    <k>The film Jaroussky sings Bach &amp; Telemann is a portrait of a very special vocalist - and of two exceptional composers: Telemann and Bach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-05 08:39:00" d="2020-06-05 09:11:00"><n u="Haydn - String Quartet in F minor Op. 20 No.">Haydn - String Quartet in F minor Op. 20 No. 5</n><t>M</t>    <k>The British String Quartet The Lindsays have recorded all substantial Haydn String Quartets during their active years, from 1965 to 2005</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-05 09:11:00" d="2020-06-05 10:00:00"><n u="Schubert - Overture to Rosamunde">Schubert - Overture to Rosamunde (D. 644)</n><t>M</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-05 10:00:00" d="2020-06-05 11:37:00"><n u="Mahler - Symphony No.">Mahler - Symphony No. 6</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sir Simon Rattle conducts the Berlin Philharmonic in a performance of Mahler's Symphony No. 6. The concert is Rattle's last time as chief conductor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-05 11:37:00" d="2020-06-05 12:41:00"><n>Roberto Giordano plays Brahms and Beethoven</n><t>M</t>    <k>Roberto Giordano plays the Six Pieces for Piano, op. 118 of Brahms, as well as the famous Moonlight Sonata and Sonata No. 31, op. 110 of Beethoven</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-05 12:41:00" d="2020-06-05 12:56:00"><n>Summertime at the Domaine Forget</n><t>M</t>    <k>The documentary Summertime at the Domaine Forget introduces internationally renowned treasure: Domaine Forget festival in Saint-Irénée, Québec</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-05 12:56:00" d="2020-06-05 14:04:00"><n>Semi Final I - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Alexander Ullman (1991, United Kingdom) performs Wagner/Liszt - Isoldens Liebestod: Schlußszene aus Tristan und Isolde, S447 and Beethoven/Liszt - Symphony No</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-05 14:04:00" d="2020-06-05 15:34:00"><n>Classical Film Music</n><t>M</t>    <k>English conductor and pianist Wayne Marshall leads the Orchestre national d'Île-de-France in a special concert celebrating classical music in film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-05 15:34:00" d="2020-06-05 16:43:00"><n u="Sibelius - Symphony No.">Sibelius - Symphony No. 4</n><t>M</t>    <k>Finnish Radio Symphony Orchestra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-05 16:43:00" d="2020-06-05 18:11:00"><n u="Mahler - Symphony No.">Mahler - Symphony No. 2</n><t>M</t>    <k>The then-newly founded Lucerne Festival Orchestra presents this stunning performance of Mahler's Resurrection Symphony in August 2003, under the baton</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-05 18:11:00" d="2020-06-05 19:00:00"><n>TeoTronico - The Robot Pianist</n><t>L</t>    <k>Meet Teotronico, the pianist robot! TeoTronico can read musical scores in digital or MIDI format, playing them on the piano in a literal way. Accompanied</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-05 19:00:00" d="2020-06-05 21:00:00"><n u="Tchaikovsky - Piano Trio, Op.">Tchaikovsky - Piano Trio, Op. 50</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Zadig Trio consists of the two French childhood friends Boris Borgolotto (violin), Marc Girard Garcia (cello) and the American pianist Ian Barber</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-05 21:00:00" d="2020-06-05 22:24:00"><n>Violin Sonatas - Debussy, Ravel &amp; Beethoven</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this beautiful concert from the Tchaikovsky Concert Hall of Moscow, the two exceptional Russian soloists Vadim Repin (violin) and Nikolay Lugansky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-05 22:24:00" d="2020-06-05 23:29:00"><n>Nino Rota - I due timidi</n><t>L</t>    <k>Nino Rota's I due timidi (1950), performed by the Reate Festival Orchestra, under the baton of Gabriele Bonolis at the Reate Festival in Rieti, Italy, in 2017</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-05 23:29:00" d="2020-06-06 00:00:00"><n>Britten - The Young Persons Guide to the Orchestra</n><t>M</t>    <k>Marin Alsop conducts the Britten-Pears Orchestra in a performance of Britten's The Young Person's Guide to the Orchestra. Recorded at Snape Maltings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-06 00:00:00" d="2020-06-06 02:28:00"><n>Verdi - Luisa Miller</n><t>M</t>    <k>Under the musical direction of Massimo Zanetti, the Orchestre et Choeurs de l'Opéra Royal de Wallonie present the opera &quot;Luisa Miller&quot;. As the result</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-06 02:28:00" d="2020-06-06 04:00:00"><n>Prosseda performs Mozart, Schubert &amp; Chopin</n><t>S</t>    <k>Roberto Prosseda (1975) performs Mozart's Piano Sonata No. 5 (KV. 283) and four Impromptus Op. 90 by Franz Schubert. The performance ends with Chopin's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-06 04:00:00" d="2020-06-06 04:58:00"><n>The 12 Cellists - Documentary</n><t>M</t>    <k>This documentary made in 2012 by Enrique Sánchez Lansch follows the 12 cellists of the Berlin Philharmonic, who since 1972 have been a staple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-06 04:58:00" d="2020-06-06 06:00:00"><n u="Haydn - String Quartet in D minor Op.">Haydn - String Quartet in D minor Op. 42</n><t>S</t>    <k>The British String Quartet The Lindsays have recorded all substantial Haydn String Quartets during their active years, from 1965 to 2005</k>  </p>
</a>
