<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2021-07-09 07:39:43"><p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-16 05:20:00" d="2021-07-16 06:00:00"><n>Graupner - Magnificat anima mea</n><t>M</t>    <k>Patrick Debrabandere conducts the Vox Mago chamber choir in a performance of Christoph Graupner's (1683-1760) cantata Magnificat anima mea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-16 06:00:00" d="2021-07-16 07:27:00"><n u="Handel - Messiah, HWV">Handel - Messiah, HWV 56</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Messiah (HWV 56) by Georg Frederich Handel, tells the life and suffering of Christ: a story of passion, fire, and sacrifice. This performance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-16 07:27:00" d="2021-07-16 08:23:00"><n>Rocamadour 2020: La Sportelle sings Motets</n><t>O</t>    <k>Over the course of eleven days in August 2020, the French town of Rocamadour hosted the fifteenth edition of Festival de Rocamadour, a music festival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-16 08:23:00" d="2021-07-16 09:01:00"><n u="Shostakovich - Piano Trio No.2, Op.">Shostakovich - Piano Trio No.2, Op. 67</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Zadig Trio consists of the two French childhood friends Boris Borgolotto (violin), Marc Girard Garcia (cello) and the American pianist Ian Barber</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-16 09:01:00" d="2021-07-16 10:05:00"><n u="Brahms - Symphony No. 4 in E minor, Op.">Brahms - Symphony No. 4 in E minor, Op. 98</n><t>M</t>    <k>The 2007 Europa-Konzert takes place in Berlin, on the occasion of the 125th anniversary of the Berliner Philharmoniker. Under the theme &quot;The Year 1882&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-16 10:05:00" d="2021-07-16 11:10:00"><n u="Bruckner - Symphony No.">Bruckner - Symphony No. 7</n><t>Z</t>    <k>In a 2019 performance from the Muziekgebouw in Eindhoven, Hartmut Haenchen conducts the philharmonie zuidnederland for this performance of Anton Bruckner's Symphony No</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-16 11:10:00" d="2021-07-16 12:14:00"><n>Mosaique Project - Canadian Piano Quartets</n><t>M</t>    <k>This very special concert event celebrates the diversity and richness of Canada through the eyes and ears of its people. Ensemble Made in Canada's Mosaique</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-16 12:14:00" d="2021-07-16 13:10:00"><n>How to get out of the Cage - A year with John Cage</n><t>M</t>    <k>The compelling documentary How to Get Out of the Cage (2012), by award-winning filmmaker Frank Scheffer, presents an intimate portrait of John Cage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-16 13:10:00" d="2021-07-16 13:26:00"><n u="Bach - Sonata No. 3 BWV">Bach - Sonata No. 3 BWV 1016</n><t>M</t>    <k>Frank Peter Zimmerman, Enrico Pace</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-16 13:26:00" d="2021-07-16 14:00:00"><n u="Dvořák - The Golden Spinning Wheel, Op.">Dvořák - The Golden Spinning Wheel, Op. 109</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sir Simon Rattle conducts the Czech Philharmonic in this concert program featuring works by Antonín Dvořák and Gustav Mahler, recorded at the Rudolfinum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-16 14:00:00" d="2021-07-16 15:28:00"><n>Rogerio Tutti in Concert</n><t>L</t>    <k>Recorded at the Citibank Hall in Sao Paulo, Brazilian conductor, pianist, and composer Rogerio Tutti and his orchestra perform a mix of famous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-16 15:28:00" d="2021-07-16 16:31:00"><n u="Bruckner - Symphony No.">Bruckner - Symphony No. 9</n><t>M</t>    <k>Anton Bruckner's Symphony No. 9 can be seen as a farewell to life. The details of this architectural colossus are worked out with astonishing transparency</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-16 16:31:00" d="2021-07-16 17:06:00"><n u="Nielsen - Symphony No.">Nielsen - Symphony No. 6</n><t>M</t>    <k>Fabio Luisi conducts the Danish National Symphony Orchestra in this powerful performance taken from the 150th Anniversary celebrations of Denmark's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-16 17:06:00" d="2021-07-16 18:07:00"><n u="Beethoven - Piano Sonatas No. 1, 14 &amp;">Beethoven - Piano Sonatas No. 1, 14 &amp; 32</n><t>M</t>    <k>French pianist Anne Queffélec performs Ludwig van Beethoven's Piano Sonata No. 1 in F minor, Op. 2/1, Piano Sonata No. 14 (&quot;Moonlight&quot;) in C-sharp minor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-16 18:07:00" d="2021-07-16 18:54:00"><n>Rimsky-Korsakov Suites</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this exquisite concert 2016 from Moscow's Tchaikovsky Concert Hall, the Russian National Orchestra and star-pianist Boris Berezovsky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-16 18:54:00" d="2021-07-16 21:00:00"><n u="Chopin - Sonata for cello and piano, Op.">Chopin - Sonata for cello and piano, Op. 65</n><t>S</t>    <k>Between March and May 2020, Schinkel Pavillon Berlin opened its unexpectedly vacated exhibition space for a concert series in isolation titled Concerts in Quarantine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-16 21:00:00" d="2021-07-16 21:40:00"><n u="Saint-Saëns - Piano Concerto No. 2, Op.">Saint-Saëns - Piano Concerto No. 2, Op. 22</n><t>M</t>    <k>Pianist Mikhail Pletnev is accompanied by the Russian National Orchestra led by Kirill Karabits in a performance of Camille Saint-Saëns's Piano Concerto No</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-16 21:40:00" d="2021-07-17 00:00:00"><n>Janáček - Jenůfa</n><t>M</t>    <k>In a 2013 production from the stage of the Théâtre Royal de la Monnaie in Brussels, the La Monnaie Symphony Orchestra &amp; Chorus present Leoš Janáček's Jenůfa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-17 00:00:00" d="2021-07-17 02:08:00"><n>Lully - Persée</n><t>M</t>    <k>Hervé Niquet conducts the Tafelmusik Baroque Orchestra and Chamber Choir in a stage production of Jean Baptiste Lully's opera Persée (1632-1687) by Opera</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-17 02:08:00" d="2021-07-17 03:42:00"><n>Nelsons conducts Berg and Mendelssohn</n><t>M</t>    <k>Andris Nelsons's starts off his official opening concert as principal conductor of the Gewandhausorchester with the world premiere of Steffen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-17 03:42:00" d="2021-07-17 04:42:00"><n u="Mozart on Tour - Episode 7: Vienna -">Mozart on Tour - Episode 7: Vienna - I</n><t>S</t>    <k>The 13-part Mozart on Tour series chronicles the journey of Mozart across Europe. The performance of Mozart's Piano Concerto No. 17, KV 453 features</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2021-07-17 04:42:00" d="2021-07-17 05:24:00"><n u="Beethoven - Symphony No. 7, Op.">Beethoven - Symphony No. 7, Op. 92</n><t>M</t>    <k>Fabio Luisi conducts the Danish National Symphony Orchestra in a performance of Strauss' Horn Concerto No. 1. This work is one of the most popular</k>  </p>
</a>
