<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="22" t="2020-05-27 04:38:18"><p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-03 06:00:00" d="2020-06-03 06:45:00"><n u="Händel - Dettingen Te Deum">Händel - Dettingen Te Deum (HV 283)</n><t>M</t>    <k>Patrick Debrabandere conducts the Vox Mago choir in a performance of The Dettingen Te Deum (HWV 283), a canticle composed by George Frideric Handel, in 1743</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-03 06:45:00" d="2020-06-03 07:46:00"><n>Ladies first, From Marian motet to love song</n><t>M</t>    <k>Despite his motto 'Aultre n'auray' ('I shall never have another'), Philip the Good was known for his passion for the fairer sex. Could this explain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-03 07:46:00" d="2020-06-03 08:36:00"><n u="Schubert - Piano Trio No. 2, Op. 100, D.">Schubert - Piano Trio No. 2, Op. 100, D. 929</n><t>M</t>    <k>Ester Hoppe (violin), Christian Poltéra (cello) and Francesco Piemontesi (piano) perform Schubert's Piano Trio No. 2, Op. 100 (D. 929) during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-03 08:36:00" d="2020-06-03 10:01:00"><n u="Mozart - Violin Concerto No. 3, K.">Mozart - Violin Concerto No. 3, K. 216</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Berliner Philharmoniker plays Tchaikovsky's Fantasy Overture from &quot;Roméo et Juliette&quot;, Mozart is his famous Violin Concerto No. 3 in G major</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-03 10:01:00" d="2020-06-03 11:01:00"><n u="Mahler - Symphony No.">Mahler - Symphony No. 1</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jean Paul's novel 'Titan', inspired Gustav Mahler to compose his Symphony No. 1. Performed by Sächsische Staatskapelle Dresden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-03 11:01:00" d="2020-06-03 12:00:00"><n>L'Amante Segreto</n><t>M</t>    <k>Céline Scheen (soprano), Giovanna Pessi (harp)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-03 12:00:00" d="2020-06-03 12:58:00"><n>Looking for Cole</n><t>M</t>    <k>The film &quot;Looking for Cole,&quot; by Wilfried van den Brande, recorded over the course of three years, gives a unique insight into Cole Porter's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-03 12:58:00" d="2020-06-03 14:01:00"><n>CMIM - Semi Finals - John Brancy</n><t>M</t>    <k>Peter Dugan accompanies baritone John Brancy (USA, 1988) during the semi-finals of the Art Song competition of the Concours musical international</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-03 14:01:00" d="2020-06-03 15:39:00"><n>Berlioz - Romeo et Juliette</n><t>M</t>    <k>In this ground-breaking take on William Shakespeare's bittersweet tragedy, Hector Berlioz combines the playwright's influence with all the musical drama</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-03 15:39:00" d="2020-06-03 16:16:00"><n u="Hummel - Piano Concerto No.">Hummel - Piano Concerto No. 2</n><t>M</t>    <k>Under the baton of conductor Mikhail Pletnev, the Russian National Orchestra and star-pianist Dmitry Shishkin interpret Johann Nepomuk Hummel's Piano Concerto No</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-03 16:16:00" d="2020-06-03 16:43:00"><n>Shostakovich - Chamber Symphony Op. 110a</n><t>M</t>    <k>The Casco Phil, The Chamber Music Orchestra of Belgium, conducted by Benjamin Haemhouts, performs Shostakovich's Chamber Symphony, Op</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-03 16:43:00" d="2020-06-03 18:05:00"><n>A Russian in Paris</n><t>M</t>    <k>The renowned Russian conductor Yuri Temirkanov conducts the Orchestre de Paris in a program that includes works by Prokofiev, Tchaikovsky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-03 18:05:00" d="2020-06-03 18:28:00"><n u="Haydn - String Quartet in C Major Op. 33 No.">Haydn - String Quartet in C Major Op. 33 No. 3</n><t>M</t>    <k>The British String Quartet The Lindsays have recorded all substantial Haydn String Quartets during their active years, from 1965 to 2005</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-03 18:28:00" d="2020-06-03 19:59:00"><n>Seong-Jin Cho plays Debussy, Schumann &amp; Chopin</n><t>L</t>    <k>In this performance from the 25th anniversary edition of the Verbier Festival, Seong-Jin Cho pays tribute to Debussy on the occasion of the 100th</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-03 19:59:00" d="2020-06-03 21:00:00"><n>Discovering Masterpieces – Symphonie Fantastique</n><t>S</t>    <k>Hector Berlioz' Fantastic Symphony' is widely regarded as one of the most important pieces of the early Romantic period. Leonard Bernstein once called</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-03 21:00:00" d="2020-06-03 22:27:00"><n>Rachmaninov - The Last Romantic</n><t>M</t>    <k>Lead by Yuri Termikanov, Russian pianist Denis Matsuev and the St. Petersburg Philharmonic close the fourth edition of the Annecy Festival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-03 22:27:00" d="2020-06-03 23:10:00"><n>Johan de Meij - Echoes of San Marco &amp; Fellini</n><t>M</t>    <k>Johan de Meij conducts two of his own works: &quot;Echoes of San Marco,&quot; a tribute to Giovanni Gabrielli and &quot;Fellini,&quot; a tribute to film composer Federico Fellini</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-03 23:10:00" d="2020-06-04 00:00:00"><n>Classical:NEXT 2019 - Dublin Guitar Quartet</n><t>L</t>    <k>The Dublin Guitar Quartet consists of Brian Bolger, Pat Brunnock, Tomas O'Durcain, and Chien Buggle. During this showcase at Classical:NEXT</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-04 00:00:00" d="2020-06-04 02:33:00"><n>Verdi - Aida</n><t>M</t>    <k>Conductor Paolo Arrivabeni leads the Orchestre et Choeurs de l'Opéra Royal de Wallonie in this performance of Aida. Although Aida is considered</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-04 02:33:00" d="2020-06-04 03:59:00"><n>Järvi conducts Dubugnon, Bernstein and Prokofiev</n><t>M</t>    <k>Paavo Järvi conducts the Orchestre de Paris and Labeque sisters during a concert in the Salle Pleyel in Paris, 2012. The programme features Dubugnon's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-04 03:59:00" d="2020-06-04 04:30:00"><n>Teatro Regio behind the scenes</n><t>M</t>    <k>This documentary portrays the Teatro Regio of Turin. Pillar of local life and symbol of excellence of the Italian operatic tradition, the Teatro Regio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="560" o="2020-06-04 04:30:00" d="2020-06-04 06:00:00"><n>Semi Final I - Liszt Competition 2017</n><t>M</t>    <k>Ayumu Yamanaka (1988, Japan) performs Selection from Harmonies poétiques et réligieuses, S173: VI. Hymne de l'enfant a son reveil VII. Funérailles</k>  </p>
</a>
