<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="70" t="2020-04-10 04:31:04"><p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 05:00:00" d="2020-04-17 05:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Catboy has two concert tickets and must decide which friend to take. Gekko loses the Gekko-Mobile when they need it the most!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 05:25:00" d="2020-04-17 05:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Gekko has a plan for stopping Luna Girl stealing things all over the city but it fails and Gekko needs to improvise, helped by his loyal Lionel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 05:30:00" d="2020-04-17 05:55:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo turns Owlette's Flossy Flash toy into a device that transforms the PJ Masks into action toys! Night Ninja steals an ancient gong to awaken a Dragon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 05:55:00" d="2020-04-17 06:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons III (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Minnie, Daisy, and Cuckoo-Loca are making a pet salon calendar but discover photographing animals can be difficult. Then an accident helps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 06:00:00" d="2020-04-17 06:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% With Beshte alone in the Outlands, Scar uses the opportunity to attack the Lion Guard’s strongest member</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 06:30:00" d="2020-04-17 07:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Everyone ends up with mixed-up roadsters when Chip 'n Dale add a few ideas to Mickey's new Motor Lab invention. The gang turns window washing into a friendly competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 07:00:00" d="2020-04-17 07:30:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vee's friends try to keep her surprise party a secret, then learn it's the guests that get the surprises. Vee and Poppy set off a dance craze that could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 07:30:00" d="2020-04-17 07:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dad gets embroiled in a game of Hotel, where Bluey and Bingo run a crazy hotel and Dad is the beleaguered guest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 07:40:00" d="2020-04-17 07:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey’s struggling to ride her bike. But inspired by her friends, she refuses to give up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 07:50:00" d="2020-04-17 08:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s Bingo’s turn with Kindy’s Bob Bilby puppet and she’s going to show him a good time!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 08:00:00" d="2020-04-17 08:30:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First III (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Sofia’s amulet summons her to help another princess, Princess Charlotte of Isleworth, who has been cursed by an enchantress and turned into a beast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 08:30:00" d="2020-04-17 09:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% When Victor, Carla and Ash capture Elena and her friends, Naomi must trust her instincts to save them!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 09:00:00" d="2020-04-17 09:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dad gets embroiled in a game of Hotel, where Bluey and Bingo run a crazy hotel and Dad is the beleaguered guest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 09:10:00" d="2020-04-17 09:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey’s struggling to ride her bike. But inspired by her friends, she refuses to give up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 09:20:00" d="2020-04-17 09:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s Bingo’s turn with Kindy’s Bob Bilby puppet and she’s going to show him a good time!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 09:30:00" d="2020-04-17 09:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Spy Game: A game in the park goes haywire when Bingo stops playing. Now Bluey must win her back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 09:40:00" d="2020-04-17 09:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Five minutes feels like an eternity as Dad and the kids wait for their takeaway order. (S1Ep14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 09:50:00" d="2020-04-17 10:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Playing Butterflies in the backyard is great fun, until Bluey runs away with Judo leaving Bingo all alone. Now poor Bingo’s heartbroken and Bluey needs to make amends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 10:00:00" d="2020-04-17 11:00:00"><n>Battle for the Pride Lands</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Scar devises a scheme to destroy the Lion Guard, which leaves them forever changed. Following the battle, the Lion Guard sets off for the Tree of Life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 11:00:00" d="2020-04-17 11:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip and Freddy deliver a baby penguin to Pip's home town. When Pip and Freddy break the conveyor belt at T.O.T.S. they are determined to fix it on their own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 11:30:00" d="2020-04-17 11:55:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Freddy and Pip try their hardest to keep a baby tiger prince clean. When a baby arrives on its birthday, Freddy tries to find the perfect birthday present</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 11:55:00" d="2020-04-17 12:00:00"><n u="Marvel Super Hero Adventures">Marvel Super Hero Adventures I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>During a frustrating chase to stop Stegron from destroying a museum, Spider-Man gets a boost from his pal Reptil, who teaches him the power of positive thinking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 12:00:00" d="2020-04-17 12:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJ Masks get locked in the lab and it's up to PJ Robot to rescue them! Gekko is on the case when animals keep disappearing from the city</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 12:30:00" d="2020-04-17 13:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Ninja uses Armadylan's dream of becoming a kung fu movie star to break into a museum. While Gekko and Armadylan guard the city, their watch turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 13:00:00" d="2020-04-17 13:30:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor (12)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 13:30:00" d="2020-04-17 14:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When a cheetah is set loose at T.O.T.S., Pip and Freddy must play a game of tag to catch it! The Junior Fliers lead a class trip of storks and teach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 14:00:00" d="2020-04-17 14:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After KC gets sick, Pip and Freddy try to watch the babies in the Nursery for her. When delivery batches of bunnies get mixed up, the Junior Fliers figure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 14:30:00" d="2020-04-17 15:30:00"><n>Sofia the First: The Floating...</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Sofia’s amulet lets her become a mermaid. Her family’s floating palace is blocking the sunlight, endangering the mermaids' kingdom. Can she get it moved</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 15:30:00" d="2020-04-17 16:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% When a female rock creature is unhappy, Elena enlists the help of Charoca to find out why before she causes a monfuego to erupt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 16:00:00" d="2020-04-17 16:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey sends a video to Bingo in hospital to show her that everyone gets sick sometimes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 16:10:00" d="2020-04-17 16:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dad can’t go to work until he has played all of Bluey and Bingo’s trampoline games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 16:20:00" d="2020-04-17 16:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>On a car trip to the dump, Bluey discovers that Dad is throwing out her old drawings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 16:30:00" d="2020-04-17 17:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mia loses Lovey, so Pip and Freddy go on a wild chase to find it. But are they too late? The Fliers' delivery is in jeopardy when their puppy student</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 17:00:00" d="2020-04-17 17:15:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy tries to keep an old toy from being sold without revealing she still cares about a &quot;baby toy&quot;. (S1 Ep11a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 17:15:00" d="2020-04-17 17:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy produces Lionel's first comedy show but he is too nervous to perform! (S1 Ep 11b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 17:30:00" d="2020-04-17 18:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vampirina loses her voice just before a Ghoul Girls performance in Transylvania. Vee, Bridget and Poppy meet a friendly, but dramatic ghost on a field</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 18:00:00" d="2020-04-17 18:15:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (96)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% PJ Robot tries to turn Romeo's Flying Factory into a Flying Party. (S3 Ep22b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 18:15:00" d="2020-04-17 18:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (95)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJ Masks must wear ear-protecting helmets when Romeo writes a song that turns listeners into his servant. (S3 Ep22a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 18:30:00" d="2020-04-17 19:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% When Makini chases some mysterious blue lights, she and Ono get trapped in a cave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 19:00:00" d="2020-04-17 19:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First (111)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 19:25:00" d="2020-04-17 19:30:00"><n u="Music Lullabies">Music Lullabies I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lambie is helping Doc fall asleep by counting sheep. Pretty soon all Doc’s toys join in!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 19:30:00" d="2020-04-17 19:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey sends a video to Bingo in hospital to show her that everyone gets sick sometimes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 19:40:00" d="2020-04-17 19:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dad can’t go to work until he has played all of Bluey and Bingo’s trampoline games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 19:50:00" d="2020-04-17 20:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>On a car trip to the dump, Bluey discovers that Dad is throwing out her old drawings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 20:00:00" d="2020-04-17 20:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It's Mini-Mechanics Day and Mickey's number one fan can't wait to get to work! The Happy Helpers are busy pet-sitting while everyone heads to the Fancy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 20:30:00" d="2020-04-17 21:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% When a female rock creature is unhappy, Elena enlists the help of Charoca to find out why before she causes a monfuego to erupt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 21:00:00" d="2020-04-17 21:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Freddy's status as the best hide-and-seeker is challenged after he and Pip lose a baby fox. Pip and Freddy help K.C. earn her first Golden Feather on Cleaning Day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 21:30:00" d="2020-04-17 22:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vampirina loses her voice just before a Ghoul Girls performance in Transylvania. Vee, Bridget and Poppy meet a friendly, but dramatic ghost on a field</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 22:00:00" d="2020-04-17 22:15:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (96)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% PJ Robot tries to turn Romeo's Flying Factory into a Flying Party. (S3 Ep22b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 22:15:00" d="2020-04-17 22:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (95)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJ Masks must wear ear-protecting helmets when Romeo writes a song that turns listeners into his servant. (S3 Ep22a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 22:30:00" d="2020-04-17 23:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% When Makini chases some mysterious blue lights, she and Ono get trapped in a cave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 23:00:00" d="2020-04-17 23:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First (111)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 23:25:00" d="2020-04-17 23:30:00"><n u="Music Lullabies">Music Lullabies I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lambie is helping Doc fall asleep by counting sheep. Pretty soon all Doc’s toys join in!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-17 23:30:00" d="2020-04-18 00:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus (13)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 00:00:00" d="2020-04-18 00:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJ Masks must wear ear-protecting helmets when Romeo writes a song that turns listeners into his servant. PJ Robot tries to turn Romeo's Flying Factory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 00:30:00" d="2020-04-18 01:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Armadylan saves the city. Romeo tries to use Armadylan's powers to improve his lab</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 01:00:00" d="2020-04-18 01:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou finds a dinosaur egg and takes it home, hoping it will hatch. But Zavier and Zelda realise it is not an egg but an important piece of ceramic art</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 01:15:00" d="2020-04-18 01:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A power cut stops Zou and Elzee playing a video game. Grandpa teaches them some old-fashioned games which Zou loves and carries on playing after the power returns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 01:30:00" d="2020-04-18 02:00:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry organises a spectacular finale for Summer’s show, to make up for letting her down. Cobby invents The Hugglebike to get the family to the fireworks display</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 02:00:00" d="2020-04-18 02:30:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry chases Daddo's birthday cake that’s caught on a balloon. Henry must save the monsterpets when they are swept into an airship on a windy day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 02:30:00" d="2020-04-18 02:40:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia make Bigfoot angry without meaning to. But Bigfoot has never been angry before, and doesn’t understand what’s happening to him. The twins try to help him. (S1 Ep18a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 02:40:00" d="2020-04-18 02:55:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou doesn’t stick to the rules when playing football with Elzee, and upsets Zak and Poc. He realises it’s better to enjoy yourself rather than being too strict</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 02:55:00" d="2020-04-18 03:10:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nanna shows Zou how to make pom-poms, and then pom-pom animals, to sell at the school fete. He calls them monsters, and they sell really well</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 03:10:00" d="2020-04-18 03:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Nanna gently bemoans the fact that in her young days, things were all so much slower; and everyone was more polite, Zou tries to recreate those days for her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 03:25:00" d="2020-04-18 03:35:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Both Olivia and Stan realize that Stan can’t keep a secret. Olivia offers to help her brother, and gives him advice. (S1 Ep3b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 03:35:00" d="2020-04-18 03:45:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia aren’t allowed to go down the Scary-Big-Slide without a cuddly toy and they don’t even have one. They decide to make their own! (S1 Ep3c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 03:45:00" d="2020-04-18 03:55:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia realize that they’re playing in the park in their pyjamas! How embarrassing! What if someone sees them? (S1 Ep4c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 03:55:00" d="2020-04-18 04:10:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry wants to put on a spectacular show like his sister Summer. (S1 Ep3a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 04:10:00" d="2020-04-18 04:35:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus (4)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 04:35:00" d="2020-04-18 05:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu must do the impossible to protect a helpless dragonfly from raptors. Rocky suppresses his tough side and learns to be gentle with an egg he’s found</k>  </p>
</a>
