<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="74" t="2021-07-09 06:46:26"><p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 05:00:00" d="2021-07-15 05:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Four young dinosaurs explore a prehistoric world of adventure where the most exciting mystery of all is Gigantosaurus, the biggest and fiercest dinosaur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 05:30:00" d="2021-07-15 06:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Four young dinosaurs explore a prehistoric world of adventure where the most exciting mystery of all is Gigantosaurus, the biggest and fiercest dinosaur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 06:00:00" d="2021-07-15 06:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (64)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey and Bingo won't leave for their playdate with Judo until a sticky rubber gecko falls down from the ceiling!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 06:10:00" d="2021-07-15 06:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (65)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo is the model citizen… commuting to work on the Dad-Train, dropping her daughter at day care and working as a vet. Bluey on the other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 06:20:00" d="2021-07-15 06:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (66)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo and Bluey take turns being the Queen and her butler. When they both want to be butler, Mum gets crowned after Dad's short stint as a chaotic Queen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 06:30:00" d="2021-07-15 06:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (67)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>As Mum and Dad put together their new flat pack patio swing-seat, Bluey and Bingo use the cardboard and bubble wrap to construct their own mini-civilization</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 06:40:00" d="2021-07-15 06:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (68)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>On Jack's first day at Bluey's school, Calypso suggests he plays Army outside with Rusty in the bush</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 06:50:00" d="2021-07-15 07:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (69)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey and Bingo want Mum and Dad to be romantic, so they set up a fancy restaurant and invite them along for a romantic night out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 07:00:00" d="2021-07-15 07:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (77)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Goofy and Elray audition for their favorite magician, Trikini! When art teacher, Mrs. Matisse, leaves to have her baby, the Happy Helpers fill in at the school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 07:30:00" d="2021-07-15 08:00:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (134)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% When Lambie is mistakenly transported to Lost and Found Land, it's up to Doc and the gang to save Lambie and find homes for all the misplaced toys stranded</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 08:00:00" d="2021-07-15 08:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (125)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% When Cece accidentally gets hold of Lambie's Toysponder and transports herself to McStuffinsville, Doc and the gang must embark on a rollicking adventure to find her!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 08:30:00" d="2021-07-15 08:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (70)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While the dads pull stumps in the garden, Bluey, Bingo and Muffin turn one stump into a nail bar. When it comes time to pull the girls' stump, the dads must strike a deal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 08:40:00" d="2021-07-15 08:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (71)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo is upset when she spills her Mum's Mother's Day breakfast-in-bed so Bluey finds a way to cheer her sister up. hey'll put on a show instead!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 08:50:00" d="2021-07-15 09:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (72)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When the kids want to play a game of Tickle Crabs, Dad must learn to endure the pain, and is finally rescued by a friendly seagull</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 09:00:00" d="2021-07-15 09:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (103)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% When Night Ninja needs the PJs' help, our heroes can't help taking advantage of it. Pharaoh Boy absorbs the PJ's powers into his boomerangs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 09:30:00" d="2021-07-15 10:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (86)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% With the PJ Masks’ help, Newton learns that he’s not just &quot;brains&quot;! After his experience with Romeo, Newton has sworn off fighting villains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 10:00:00" d="2021-07-15 10:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (73)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mum and Dad tell the girls that they're dropping them off at Nana’s so they can have some time to themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 10:10:00" d="2021-07-15 10:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (74)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Heelers play a game of 'Bus' with Dad as the driver, Mum as a regular passenger and Bluey and Bingo as. he Grannies!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 10:20:00" d="2021-07-15 10:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (75)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mum and Bluey play 'Mum School' where Mum agrees to teach Bluey how to corral her rowdy kids and be a better mum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 10:30:00" d="2021-07-15 11:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (75)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Minnie suggests that Mickey give some of his hot dog-shaped collectibles away. Penelope gets jealous when Minnie practices with Cassidy for the horse show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 11:00:00" d="2021-07-15 11:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (134)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% When Lambie is mistakenly transported to Lost and Found Land, it's up to Doc and the gang to save Lambie and find homes for all the misplaced toys stranded</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 11:30:00" d="2021-07-15 12:00:00"><n u="Mira, Royal Detective">Mira, Royal Detective I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mira's friends help solve the case when she loses a game passed down through her family. The archery arrows go missing during the Jalpur Games so Mira must find them!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 12:00:00" d="2021-07-15 12:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (76)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Heelers are taking a late afternoon walk when Bingo decides she’s too tired to walk any further and needs a piggyback</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 12:10:00" d="2021-07-15 12:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>As Bluey and Bingo squabble over their magic xylophone (that has the power to freeze Dad in space and time) Dad seizes control and freezes Bluey, leaving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 12:20:00" d="2021-07-15 12:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Doctor Bluey is needed when Dad gets a very curious x-ray from Nurse Bingo. It seems he has a cat in his tummy, leaving Bluey no choice but to operate immediately!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 12:30:00" d="2021-07-15 13:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% When Gregoria's soft and sweet brother, Hugo, visits, will the Hauntley's like him more? Uncle Bigfoot misses check-in, so Vee sets Edgar, Bigfoot's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 13:00:00" d="2021-07-15 13:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip the Penguin and Freddy the Flamingo are Junior Fliers at T.O.T.S., (the Tiny Ones Transport Service), where they’re tasked with delivering baby animals to their parents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 13:30:00" d="2021-07-15 14:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (104)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Octobella’s vendetta against Gekko builds to unseen heights. CatBoy and Owlette build a new vehicle of discovery and exploration – the PJ Sub</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 14:00:00" d="2021-07-15 14:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Four young dinosaurs explore a prehistoric world of adventure where the most exciting mystery of all is Gigantosaurus, the biggest and fiercest dinosaur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 14:30:00" d="2021-07-15 14:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>At school, Bluey and her friends throw themselves into various games. Teacher Calypso keeps her charges on track with a wise word and a song</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 14:40:00" d="2021-07-15 14:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Honey is stuck waiting for Dr. Bingo’s as the other, more exciting injuries get seen before her. Receptionist Bluey tells her to be patient, some of these</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 14:50:00" d="2021-07-15 15:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Bluey and Bingo are unable to grab a prize on a Magic Claw machine, Mum and Dad create their own version at home. But Dad isn't about to make winning easy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 15:00:00" d="2021-07-15 15:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Bluey visits the markets with five bucks from the tooth fairy, the options are endless. But as she and Indy scour the stalls for the perfect purchase</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 15:10:00" d="2021-07-15 15:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey, Bingo, Mum and Dad play a game of hand puppets, exploring the land beyond the Blue Mountains where they outsmart the Cheeky Fox to find the softest beds in the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 15:20:00" d="2021-07-15 15:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Packing for the pool, Bluey and Dad tease Mum about being so fussy with what to take. But when they arrive underprepared, they realise a little planning goes a long way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 15:30:00" d="2021-07-15 16:00:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Jo Jo has an imaginary friend. Can Nancy make perfect handprints in a newly cemented path?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 16:00:00" d="2021-07-15 16:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. II (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A baby wolf longs to see the moon! Pip and Freddy embark on a mission to make her dream come true. During photo day, JP entrusts a photo-ready Lucky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 16:30:00" d="2021-07-15 17:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. II (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mia loses her Auntie Cora’s wedding ring! Pip and Freddy deliver an energetic baby bull early and must keep him out of trouble until his mom gets home!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 17:00:00" d="2021-07-15 17:25:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (57)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mickey accidentally turns his roadster into a monster truck! Daisy and Cuckoo Loca worry that Minnie is moving out!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 17:25:00" d="2021-07-15 17:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus S1 Shorts">Gigantosaurus S1 Shorts I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Tiny and Rocky invite the children to guess the mysterious dino: the stegosaurus, the parasaurolophus or the compsognathus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 17:30:00" d="2021-07-15 17:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>On a picnic in the park, Bluey and her friends play Shadowlands. But when Coco keeps taking shortcuts, Bluey has to show her that following the rules</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 17:40:00" d="2021-07-15 17:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>At the weekend, Bluey and Bingo are playing in the garden with Dad. But Bingo gets upset, when she discovers a walking leaf insect and Dad is too caught</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 17:50:00" d="2021-07-15 18:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s lunchtime on Blueys back deck! But every BBQ needs a side salad, so Bingo’s relaxing sit-down will have to wait until she finds every colour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 18:00:00" d="2021-07-15 18:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Not wanting to go to bed, Bluey tries to dream about being a nocturnal fruit bat so she can stay up all night long and soon finds herself flying through the night sky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 18:10:00" d="2021-07-15 18:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Bluey forgets to put her favourite toy away, cousin Socks grabs it and won’t let go! The kids stage a horsey wedding to distract</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 18:20:00" d="2021-07-15 18:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dad gets embroiled in a game of 'Hotel', where Bluey and Bingo run a crazy hotel and Dad is the beleaguered guest. But when Bluey starts to control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 18:30:00" d="2021-07-15 19:00:00"><n u="Mira, Royal Detective">Mira, Royal Detective I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When the special scarf Priya designed for the Queen goes missing, it's up to Mira to help find it! Mira juggles babysitting her cousin and searching for a missing bike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 19:00:00" d="2021-07-15 19:30:00"><n u="The Rocketeer">The Rocketeer I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Tesh gives his bike an extreme makeover that isn't as helpful as he hoped. Kit, Tesh and Butch raise money to repair the statue of the original Hughesville Rocketeer statue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 19:30:00" d="2021-07-15 20:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo and Rolly's neighbor, Keia, joins the team as they embark on even more missions to help their owners while having fun along the way!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 20:00:00" d="2021-07-15 20:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The pups travel to an archeology site to find Bob's sister. When a squirrel in the attic keeps distracting Bob, the pugs make it their mission to return it to its family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 20:30:00" d="2021-07-15 21:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (93)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% PJR wants to be Newton's Space Buddy. But first he needs to power up! Cat Boy wants to be able to teleport to the moon like Motsuki</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 21:00:00" d="2021-07-15 21:25:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A falling meteorite forces the herd to move, leaving Giganto behind!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 21:25:00" d="2021-07-15 21:50:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Four young dinosaurs explore a prehistoric world of adventure where the most exciting mystery of all is Gigantosaurus, the biggest and fiercest dinosaur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 21:50:00" d="2021-07-15 22:15:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Four young dinosaurs explore a prehistoric world of adventure where the most exciting mystery of all is Gigantosaurus, the biggest and fiercest dinosaur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 22:15:00" d="2021-07-15 22:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While on a fishing trip to the beach with Grandpa, Zou learns that it’s not always those with the expensive equipment that have the most success</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 22:30:00" d="2021-07-15 22:45:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (102)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zinnia and her family have come back from a visit to a winter games spectacular. Zou decides that he’d like to take part in something similar, so various</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 22:45:00" d="2021-07-15 23:00:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou runs out of paint and can’t finish painting the garage. He meets two artist friends of Elzee’s mum and ends up with a great picture to decorate the blank space</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 23:00:00" d="2021-07-15 23:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou and Elzee camp in the garden. Grandpa tells them stories of animals he met while camping in Africa. They are scared and imagine wild animals outside their tent too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 23:15:00" d="2021-07-15 23:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou and his Dad are gardening but birds eat the seeds they are planting. They make a scarecrow. It turns out to be pretty effective, scaring several of Zou’s family!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 23:25:00" d="2021-07-15 23:50:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry helps Summer make a film to represent their roarsome family. Henry helps at the Cafe when Signor Roartonio's assistant is ill on Monster Pizza Day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 23:50:00" d="2021-07-16 00:15:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry’s friend Roddy arrives for a play date, but bad boy Roddy comes too. When he rips Summer’s autographed pic of Isabella, Henry dresses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 00:15:00" d="2021-07-16 00:40:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Who will win the school science fair - Cobby’s toast-a-rrific invention or Hildy’s doughnut volcano? Henry and Denzel fall out, so Cobby builds him a robot friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 00:40:00" d="2021-07-16 01:05:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Henry has a bad day a Grr Cloud appears over his head. Henry finds the perfect Monster Mama’s Day present - a fluffy mini-monster pet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 01:05:00" d="2021-07-16 01:30:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The twins have trouble saying No to some intrusive seagulls. Olivia forgets the secret code to get into the playhouse. The twins can't be patient</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 01:30:00" d="2021-07-16 01:55:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Olivia gets her portrait wrong. The twins make themselves a triplet. The twins play at running a restaurant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 01:55:00" d="2021-07-16 02:20:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Four young dinosaurs explore a prehistoric world of adventure where the most exciting mystery of all is Gigantosaurus, the biggest and fiercest dinosaur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 02:20:00" d="2021-07-16 02:45:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Four young dinosaurs explore a prehistoric world of adventure where the most exciting mystery of all is Gigantosaurus, the biggest and fiercest dinosaur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 02:45:00" d="2021-07-16 03:10:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It's the start of the holidays. Henry decides to fix Grando's old van to take them to see favourite band, Sonic Growl. But as usual in Roarsville, it doesn’t go smoothly!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 03:10:00" d="2021-07-16 03:35:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry’s upset he’s not invited to Summer’s sleepover so holds his own. Henry’s in charge while the mayor’s away and soon learns why rules exist. ( S2 Ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 03:35:00" d="2021-07-16 04:00:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry’s organising Roarsville’s big wedding and asks Summer to be the flower monster. Henry and Denzel decide to start a boy band</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 04:00:00" d="2021-07-16 04:25:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Disney’s Mickey Mouse Clubhouse is the first Mickey Mouse series created specifically for preschoolers. The show introduces a whole new generation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 04:25:00" d="2021-07-16 04:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Hot Diggity-Dog Tales">Mickey Mouse Hot Diggity-Dog Tales I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Mickey and Pluto get stuck on a runaway tractor, they create a series of happy accidents that leads to Clarabelle's most moo-velous apple pie ever!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 04:30:00" d="2021-07-16 04:55:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Disney’s Mickey Mouse Clubhouse is the first Mickey Mouse series created specifically for preschoolers. The show introduces a whole new generation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 04:55:00" d="2021-07-16 05:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Convinced Minnie needs more time to relax, Daisy orders a bow-making robot. But Daisy breaks the remote, and the Bow-Bot goes haywire, turning everything into bows</k>  </p>
</a>
