<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="60" t="2020-05-30 04:33:25"><p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 05:00:00" d="2020-06-06 05:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% PJ Masks try to prevent Luna Girl improving her powers. Catboy and Gekko are imprisoned and need Gekko's help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 05:25:00" d="2020-06-06 05:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks Music Video">PJ Masks Music Video I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Music accompanies clips from the popular show featuring pyjama-clad heroes Catboy, Gekko and Owlette, who have adventures, solve mysteries, and learn valuable lessons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 05:30:00" d="2020-06-06 05:55:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% While Catboy is too busy trying to impress An Yu, Night Ninja enters the pagoda. An Yu tries to solve an ancient riddle to become a true Mountain Master</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 05:55:00" d="2020-06-06 06:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A Pizza Parlour mix up sends Minnie and Daisy to Luigi’s Pizzeria, to make pizzas for the hungry crowd. Minnie and Daisy make some funny looking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 06:00:00" d="2020-06-06 06:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% Janja replaces Chungu and Cheezi with two new hyenas in an attempt to sideline the Lion Guard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 06:30:00" d="2020-06-06 07:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse (77)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Donald finds an egg but neither he nor Mickey know what sort of animal lays such an egg. Led by Goofy, the chums try to discover what sort of chick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 07:00:00" d="2020-06-06 07:30:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vee and her family are so excited because they're going on a beach day with the Peeplesons. Vee and Demi help Gregoria learn how to fly!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 07:30:00" d="2020-06-06 07:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A trip to the pool’s great fun, until Dad forgets the towels, lunch and everything else!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 07:40:00" d="2020-06-06 07:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Playing Shops is the best game ever for Bluey and her friends - if they can ever get started! With Bluey questioning the rules and changing who’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 07:50:00" d="2020-06-06 08:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey loses patience when Dad keeps stopping to chat with grown-ups on the way to the park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 08:00:00" d="2020-06-06 08:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo steals Gekko’s voice, but Gekko’s not sure he wants it back before his poetry presentation. Night Ninja has stolen Master Fang’s prized sword!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 08:30:00" d="2020-06-06 09:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip and Freddy must deliver a baby panda that is so cute, that it makes it hard to say goodbye. The Junior Fliers have trouble delivering a baby skunk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 09:00:00" d="2020-06-06 09:30:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% Elena officially becomes crown princess and rescues her sister, Isabel, from Noblins, elf-like shapeshifting creatures based on a Chilean peuchen myth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 09:30:00" d="2020-06-06 10:00:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Sofia encourages kitchen maid Gwen to pursue her dream of being an inventor. Together they invent a contraption that will automatically paint bowls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 10:00:00" d="2020-06-06 10:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mickey accidentally turns his roadster into a monster truck. Daisy and Cuckoo Loca worry that Minnie is moving out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 10:30:00" d="2020-06-06 11:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Luna Girl steals the moon crystal to power up her Luna Fortress’ Mega-Magnet, which creates a portal that pulls stuff up from the city. The PJ Masks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 11:00:00" d="2020-06-06 12:00:00"><n>Lion Guard: Rise of Scar</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Guard meets Rafiki's new apprentice, Moniki. Meanwhile Ushari conspires with the hyenas to seek the help of the Pride Lands' greatest villain, Scar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 12:00:00" d="2020-06-06 12:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins II (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Stuntman Stan’s helmet falls off. He stops working. Doc tells how important a helmet is. Dress-Up Daisy is stuck in a tree after a parachute accident</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 12:30:00" d="2020-06-06 13:00:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Doc explains some toys are indoor and some outdoor when Donny’s glider planes wreak havoc. Dress Up Daisy cracks her arm, so Doc fits a cast on her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 13:00:00" d="2020-06-06 13:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins II (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% The Wicked King and Sir Kirby get stuck together. Doc comes to the rescue. Doc uses Bubble Monkey to show the toys how to blow their noses properly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 13:30:00" d="2020-06-06 14:00:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins II (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Professor Hootsburgh has been flattened so Doc suggests jumping jacks to get her in shape. Doc prescribes cream for toy gorilla Gloria’s cracked leather tummy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 14:00:00" d="2020-06-06 14:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Doc tells some old friends how to avoid spreading diseases. Donny leaves his quiz machine in the sun so it overheats. Doc helps it cool down</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 14:30:00" d="2020-06-06 15:00:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins II (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Doc gets homesick on a sleepover. Her friends try to cure her. Donny’s new toy is covered in spots. Doc explains they help her camouflage herself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 15:00:00" d="2020-06-06 15:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy’s horrified when Dad builds a non-fancy playhouse! Nancy starts a charm school to teach friends to be fancy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 15:30:00" d="2020-06-06 16:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu makes Archie a pair of wings to help him fly. Marsh copies Rocky's every move while Rocky copies Giganto</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 16:00:00" d="2020-06-06 16:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A trip to the pool’s great fun, until Dad forgets the towels, lunch and everything else!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 16:10:00" d="2020-06-06 16:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Playing Shops is the best game ever for Bluey and her friends - if they can ever get started! With Bluey questioning the rules and changing who’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 16:20:00" d="2020-06-06 16:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey loses patience when Dad keeps stopping to chat with grown-ups on the way to the park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 16:30:00" d="2020-06-06 17:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A unicorn is spotted in Hot Dog Hills. Minnie and Daisy love horses, but do they know enough to give horseback riding lessons?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 17:00:00" d="2020-06-06 17:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Freddy has to scare Pip. Pip and Freddy race a drone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 17:30:00" d="2020-06-06 18:30:00"><n>The Lion Guard: Return of the Roar</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In this enchanting Lion King spin-off, Simba and Nala’s cub Kion becomes leader of the Lion Guard, a team of animals comprising the Pride Lands’ fiercest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 18:30:00" d="2020-06-06 19:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo steals Catboy's powers while wearing his costume. Can Gekko help Catboy and Owlette stop Night Ninja?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 19:00:00" d="2020-06-06 19:30:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First II (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% It's the day of the dance, but Sofia's friend arrives early, and she promised to show her around. Sofia discovers a way she can be in two places at once</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 19:30:00" d="2020-06-06 20:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% When a wicked wizard named Fiero turns Elena's family to stone, Elena enlists the help of Mateo, her newly appointed Royal Wizard, to undo the spell and save her family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 20:00:00" d="2020-06-06 20:30:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vee has the most important job at Frankenstein and the Bride of Frankenstein's wedding! Gregoria sculpts the family for an art show, but Vee's not ready</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 20:30:00" d="2020-06-06 21:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Catboy works too fast to kick back moonfizzle balls. Owlette must coach Catboy and Gekko to defeat Night Ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 21:00:00" d="2020-06-06 21:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Gekko’s pet, Lionel, becomes a monster, wreaking havoc. Catboy confesses he has a cuddly toy to Owlette and Gekko</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 21:30:00" d="2020-06-06 22:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The pugs look for a leopard to help Bob finish his puzzle. The pugs help Bob enjoy his favourite music at a concert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 22:00:00" d="2020-06-06 22:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The pugs must brave a legendary fish to retrieve Bob's pole. A huge visiting pup wreaks havoc and the pugs must cope</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 22:30:00" d="2020-06-06 23:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rocky gets jealous when Tiny suddenly becomes the go-to hero! Mazu may be a slow runner but is a quick thinker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 23:00:00" d="2020-06-06 23:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bill accidentally changes Cretacia’s ecosystem when he eats too many rare swamp flowers. Dilo pulls pranks on the dinos!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-06 23:30:00" d="2020-06-07 00:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (1)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 00:00:00" d="2020-06-07 00:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJ Masks get locked in the lab and it's up to PJ Robot to rescue them! Gekko is on the case when animals keep disappearing from the city</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 00:25:00" d="2020-06-07 00:50:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (1)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 00:50:00" d="2020-06-07 01:00:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia are fascinated by Sheriff Pearl, and decide to become sheriffs themselves. Well, it’s not that simple! Both Olivia and Stan realize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 01:00:00" d="2020-06-07 01:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou and his friends are trying to build aeroplanes, so use the feathers from what they think is Nanna's old hat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 01:15:00" d="2020-06-07 01:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou and Grandma bake a surprise Mother’s Day cake but Dad eats it so Zou makes another without Grandma's help and makes a dreadful mess. Mum ends up coming to the rescue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 01:30:00" d="2020-06-07 01:55:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry organises a spectacular finale for Summer’s show, to make up for letting her down. Cobby invents The Hugglebike to get the family to the fireworks display</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 01:55:00" d="2020-06-07 02:20:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry’s organising Roarsville’s big wedding and asks Summer to be the flower monster. Henry and Denzel decide to start a boy band</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 02:20:00" d="2020-06-07 02:30:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Olivia forgot to prepare her bag. (S1 Ep15b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 02:30:00" d="2020-06-07 02:40:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan doesn’t like his piggy laugh and decides to stop laughing for good. (S1 Ep15c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 02:40:00" d="2020-06-07 02:55:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zinnia asks Zou to join her ballet class. At first he declines because he thinks it’s boring but soon learns it’s athletic, muscular and a lot of fun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 02:55:00" d="2020-06-07 03:10:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou and his friends are learning how to play cricket on the beach when they discover a chest of gold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 03:10:00" d="2020-06-07 03:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou (110)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 03:25:00" d="2020-06-07 03:35:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The twins play ‘Astronauts’, and build a rocket. But when it’s time to take off with his friends, Stan realizes he’s afraid of space-travel! (S1 Ep1a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 03:35:00" d="2020-06-07 03:45:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Twins discover that the ice cube Bigfoot gave them has vanished from Olivia’s pocket - no doubt stolen! Stan and Olivia begin an investigation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 03:45:00" d="2020-06-07 03:55:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan wants Olivia to play with him instead of reading her book. (S1 Ep11c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 03:55:00" d="2020-06-07 04:10:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry tries to teach his friends Gertie and Denzel to fly by demonstrating with his Enormo-wings.(S2 Ep3b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 04:10:00" d="2020-06-07 04:35:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A falling meteorite forces the herd to move, leaving Giganto behind!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 04:35:00" d="2020-06-07 05:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu must do the impossible to protect a helpless dragonfly from raptors. Rocky suppresses his tough side and learns to be gentle with an egg he’s found</k>  </p>
</a>
