<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="69" t="2019-07-11 00:20:29"><p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 05:00:00" d="2019-07-16 05:15:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (72)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Night Ninja steals an ancient gong to awaken a real Dragon! (S2 Ep23b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 05:15:00" d="2019-07-16 05:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Gekko doesn't want to admit he needs help underwater trying to fight Romeo's Roboctopus, but in the end he has to tell Catboy and Owlette in order</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 05:30:00" d="2019-07-16 05:55:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Gekko fights the evil alter egos of Catboy and Owlette. Romeo, Luna Girl and Night Ninja team up to catch P J Masks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 05:55:00" d="2019-07-16 06:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Minnie, Daisy, and Cuckoo-Loca are having fun in the park with their pups, until the dogs escape from their leashes. Minnie finds a fun way to control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 06:00:00" d="2019-07-16 06:15:00"><n u="Muppet Babies">Muppet Babies (12)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 06:15:00" d="2019-07-16 06:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Gekko doesn't want to admit he needs help underwater trying to fight Romeo's Roboctopus, but in the end he has to tell Catboy and Owlette in order</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 06:30:00" d="2019-07-16 07:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (17)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 07:00:00" d="2019-07-16 07:30:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vee's friends try to keep her surprise party a secret, then learn it's the guests that get the surprises. Vee and Poppy set off a dance craze that could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 07:30:00" d="2019-07-16 08:00:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy wants to win a poetry contest but gets writer’s block. Nancy’s Valentine’s card is accidentally delivered to Grace</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 08:00:00" d="2019-07-16 08:30:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First IV (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Sofia searches for an animal helper to assist her with a school presentation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 08:30:00" d="2019-07-16 09:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor (14)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 09:00:00" d="2019-07-16 09:20:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins (115)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>69% When Chuck the wind-up chicken crosses the street without looking, he unintentionally causes accidents. (S4 Ep13a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 09:20:00" d="2019-07-16 09:40:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins (116)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>69% When Doc and the toys discover a broken birthday present, they rush to fix it before its child returns. (S4 Ep13b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 09:40:00" d="2019-07-16 09:55:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins (117)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>69% When flying Pegasus toy Get-Well Gus crashes and breaks off one of his wings, Doc outfits him with a prosthetic. (S4 Ep14a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 09:55:00" d="2019-07-16 10:00:00"><n u="Cars Toons">Cars Toons I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mater is a rock star in a heavy metal band. He starts a band called Mater and the Gas Caps and has a hit with a song in which the drummer goes crazy trying to kill a fly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 10:00:00" d="2019-07-16 10:20:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (58)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Courtesy of Romeo’s Invisibility Ray, Owlette becomes invisible. Gekko and Catboy try to reverse the process but forget to include Owlette in their plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 10:20:00" d="2019-07-16 10:40:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (59)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% The P J Masks are happy to share Mystery Mountain, but the Wolfy kids want it for themselves. Their battle upsets the mountain which threatens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 10:40:00" d="2019-07-16 11:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (60)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% The Moon Crystal has been stolen from the PJM and though PJ Robot tries to warn them Romeo did this, the PJM are convinced Luna Girl is the culprit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 11:00:00" d="2019-07-16 11:20:00"><n u="Mickey and The Roadster Racers">Mickey and The Roadster Racers (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>61% Minnie’s dream of living as a simple farm mouse comes true when Clara Cluck asks the Happy Helpers to watch her farm for a couple of days. They discover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 11:20:00" d="2019-07-16 11:40:00"><n u="Mickey and The Roadster Racers">Mickey and The Roadster Racers (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>61% Mickey takes a day off to have lunch with Pluto but is called back to the garage when things go wrong. (S1 Ep24a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 11:40:00" d="2019-07-16 12:00:00"><n u="Mickey and The Roadster Racers">Mickey and The Roadster Racers I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>61% The Happy Helpers are looking after Mrs. Sweetums’ sweet shop and must fill a ginormous Hot Dog shaped pińata with candy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 12:00:00" d="2019-07-16 12:20:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Nancy’s favourite waitress gives Jo Jo special attention, Nancy’s behaviour threatens to ruin dinner. (S1 Ep13b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 12:20:00" d="2019-07-16 12:40:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When a neighborhood climibng tree is declared off-limits, Nancy shows her friends how to stand up for they believe in. (S1 Ep14a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 12:40:00" d="2019-07-16 13:00:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy dreams of becoming a synchronized swimmer, but first must overcome her fear of going underwater. (S1 Ep14b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 13:00:00" d="2019-07-16 13:20:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Oxana is thrilled to have the bed and breakfast open, but when it gets double booked with humans and vampires things get a little complicated. (S1 Ep1b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 13:20:00" d="2019-07-16 13:40:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vee invites Poppy and Bridget for a sleepover, then realises it's a full moon. What's more pet Wolfie has escaped. Can Vee keep the humans and the vampires apart? (S1 Ep2a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 13:40:00" d="2019-07-16 14:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vee's nervous when she’s due to have her school photo taken and flips, becoming a bat. She learns that's why vampires usually have their portraits painted. (S1 Ep2b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 14:00:00" d="2019-07-16 14:20:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rocky sets out to prove that he's the ultimate tough guy, like Giganto, but discovers that everyone needs help sometimes. (S1 Ep4b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 14:20:00" d="2019-07-16 14:40:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu makes Archie a pair of wings to help him fly. (S1 Ep5a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 14:40:00" d="2019-07-16 15:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Marsh copies Rocky's every move while Rocky copies Giganto. (S1 Ep5b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 15:00:00" d="2019-07-16 15:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% The Lion Guard must work together to chase away a baboon comedy troupe that has been distracting the other animals with their antics and stealing their food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 15:30:00" d="2019-07-16 16:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Skylar must overcome his carefree ways when he is chosen to guide three jaquins, including his younger brother, across the kingdom to Avalor City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 16:00:00" d="2019-07-16 16:25:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus (4)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 16:25:00" d="2019-07-16 16:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks Shorts">PJ Masks Shorts II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Catboy and Night Ninja embark on a competition to ascertain who's the Master of the Mountain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 16:30:00" d="2019-07-16 17:00:00"><n u="Mickey and The Roadster Racers">Mickey and The Roadster Racers I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>61% On Halloween Mickey meets the legendary Haunted Hot Rod. Can he beat him? Three real ghosts sabotage Pete’s Haunted House party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 17:00:00" d="2019-07-16 17:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy (16)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 17:30:00" d="2019-07-16 18:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The class parrot tells Edgar what has been going on. Vee and Poppy swap identities. Can they swap back?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 18:00:00" d="2019-07-16 18:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Romeo creates a space laser to carve his face on the moon. Romeo plans to use a device to make everyone so clumsy that they can’t stop him!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 18:30:00" d="2019-07-16 19:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The pups return Chloe's lost toy to her at Space Camp. Bob throws a ball too hard. The pugs follow clues to find it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 19:00:00" d="2019-07-16 19:25:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% The Pride Landers panic when Scar appears in the flames that destroy Mizimu Grove</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 19:25:00" d="2019-07-16 19:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks Shorts">PJ Masks Shorts II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Catboy and Night Ninja embark on a competition to ascertain who's the Master of the Mountain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 19:30:00" d="2019-07-16 20:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Elena takes up fencing, with Gabe acting as her coach, but finds out Francisco has told Gabe to let her win. Determined to prove she's really</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 20:00:00" d="2019-07-16 20:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus (4)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 20:30:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00"><n u="Mickey and The Roadster Racers">Mickey and The Roadster Racers I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>61% On Halloween Mickey meets the legendary Haunted Hot Rod. Can he beat him? Three real ghosts sabotage Pete’s Haunted House party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 21:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy (16)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 21:30:00" d="2019-07-16 22:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The class parrot tells Edgar what has been going on. Vee and Poppy swap identities. Can they swap back?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 22:00:00" d="2019-07-16 22:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Romeo creates a space laser to carve his face on the moon. Romeo plans to use a device to make everyone so clumsy that they can’t stop him!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 22:30:00" d="2019-07-16 23:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The pups return Chloe's lost toy to her at Space Camp. Bob throws a ball too hard. The pugs follow clues to find it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 23:00:00" d="2019-07-16 23:25:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% The Pride Landers panic when Scar appears in the flames that destroy Mizimu Grove</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 23:25:00" d="2019-07-16 23:30:00"><n u="Disney Junior Music Nursery Rhymes">Disney Junior Music Nursery Rhymes I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Sofia is enjoying the sunny garden when a mischievous Cedric conjures up some rain clouds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-16 23:30:00" d="2019-07-17 00:00:00"><n u="Trulli Tales">Trulli Tales I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zip wants to repeat a game of Trulliball because he lost. Stella wants to make the costumes for the ballet gala</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-17 00:00:00" d="2019-07-17 00:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Romeo discovers P. J. Masks’ HQ’s secret rocket ship ability. Catboy learns appearances don’t matter as long as you save the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-17 00:25:00" d="2019-07-17 00:50:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% The Wolfies run amok. Gekko doubts if he can be good. The Wolfies get into the HQ and transform it into their den!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-17 00:50:00" d="2019-07-17 01:00:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive I (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% When Pappa tries to get fit, he discovers that doing a good deed can be just as good as a strict exercise programme!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-17 01:00:00" d="2019-07-17 01:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou must bake a cake for the sale so he can go on a school trip. Mum is away, and Grandpa and Dad end up making pancakes. Happily, Mum gets back in time to help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-17 01:15:00" d="2019-07-17 01:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou and Elzee are playing in go karts Grandpa made. Dad has hurt his foot and is bored. Grandpa adapts Dad’s wheelchair so he can play with them and join in the race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-17 01:30:00" d="2019-07-17 01:55:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry's thrilled when Gertie turns up, but she's come for a piano lesson with Momma so he tries to sabotage it! Henry goes to the wave park. He's scared</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-17 01:55:00" d="2019-07-17 02:20:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry searches Roarsville for Beckett when he runs off to play with Meg's monsterpet Shakey. Henry tries to teach his friends Gertie and Denzel to fly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-17 02:20:00" d="2019-07-17 02:30:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive (88)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-17 02:30:00" d="2019-07-17 02:40:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Buzzbee overhears a conversation and thinks Miss Ladybird is leaving. He organises a surprise party for her, but she’s not going. He learns to listen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-17 02:40:00" d="2019-07-17 02:55:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou discovers Grandpa’s old walkie talkie and is allowed to play with it. He finds it very useful when he runs errands for Nanna</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-17 02:55:00" d="2019-07-17 03:10:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zak’s cuddly toy, Zeeboy, is missing. Zou helps look for it, but has no luck. Zinnia finds it and wants to keep it. Zou persuades her to give it back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-17 03:10:00" d="2019-07-17 03:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The youngsters must decide which gymnastic activity to do. Zou fancies Slacklining but he needs three companions. Zinnia’s not keen. Zou learns she’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-17 03:25:00" d="2019-07-17 03:35:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive (100)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Barnabee wants to train as a firefighter and learns that firefighters help with more than just fires</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-17 03:35:00" d="2019-07-17 03:45:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive I (59)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Buzzbee and his classmates are in for a surprise when Miss Ladybird goes away for the day!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-17 03:45:00" d="2019-07-17 04:10:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry searches Roarsville for Beckett when he runs off to play with Meg's monsterpet Shakey. Henry tries to teach his friends Gertie and Denzel to fly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-17 04:10:00" d="2019-07-17 04:35:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry and Denzel are coaching their Grandmonsters for the Iron Granny competition. Grando lends Henry a Monster Coin that spins on its own, but it spins away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-17 04:35:00" d="2019-07-17 04:45:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive (107)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Rubee decides she wants a sister but when she tries to get one she discovers that a best friend is just as good</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-07-17 04:45:00" d="2019-07-17 05:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% During a scavenger hunt, Owlette is tricked by Night Ninja to find ingredients for his dastardly new invention, heavy splat, which he plans to use on HQ.(S2 Ep5b)</k>  </p>
</a>
