<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="58" t="2019-08-13 02:04:58"><p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 05:00:00" d="2019-08-18 05:15:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Romeo uses his newest device to make the PJ Masks and their HQ float away! (S1 Ep17a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 05:15:00" d="2019-08-18 05:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Catboy only has two tickets to the Jayden Houston concert and has to decide which of his best friends to take. (S1 Ep11a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 05:30:00" d="2019-08-18 05:55:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (15)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 05:55:00" d="2019-08-18 06:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Minnie and friends decide to redecorate Minnie's Bow-tique. ( S2 Ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 06:00:00" d="2019-08-18 06:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse (90)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Daisy needs rain to make the flowers in her garden grow. Professor von Drake shows her how to make clouds the same shape as her garden and ensure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 06:30:00" d="2019-08-18 07:00:00"><n u="Muppet Babies">Muppet Babies I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>75% Kermit becomes a pirate captain and goes on a treasure hunt. Queen Piggy imposes strict rules on the blanket fort kingdom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 07:00:00" d="2019-08-18 07:20:00"><n u="Claude">Claude (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Claude and Sir Bobblysock are very excited about Pawhaven’s Summer Fete. And when they end up looking after the First Aid Tent they turn it into the place to be. (S1 Ep23b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 07:20:00" d="2019-08-18 07:40:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (57)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% The PJ Masks meet Armadylan and first think he is a super-hero like them… Until they find out how he intends to save the city and have to work together to defeat him. (S2 Ep16a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 07:40:00" d="2019-08-18 08:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (58)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Courtesy of Romeo’s Invisibility Ray, Owlette becomes invisible. Gekko and Catboy try to reverse the process but forget to include Owlette in their plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 08:00:00" d="2019-08-18 08:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>69% After Chilly accidentally blasts off on Luna's rocket to an unexplored planet, it's up to Doc and her friends to bring him and Luna's robot dog back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 08:30:00" d="2019-08-18 08:45:00"><n u="Mickey &amp; The Roadster Racers">Mickey &amp; The Roadster Racers (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pop star Nina Glitter's manager hires the Happy Helpers to see she makes it to the show on time. When the tour bus develops a mind of its own and takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 08:45:00" d="2019-08-18 09:00:00"><n u="Mickey &amp; The Roadster Racers">Mickey &amp; The Roadster Racers (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Donald doubts Chip and Dale’s ability to win races, so they get Professor Von Drake to shrink everyone down to their size to see what it’s like to be small. (S2 Ep13b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 09:00:00" d="2019-08-18 09:30:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% After Shuriki attacks Elena on the West Coast of Avalor, Elena tries to forge an alliance with the underwater creatures, Sirenas, in order to defeat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 09:30:00" d="2019-08-18 10:00:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Sofia is upset when her mum invites Amber and James to their Mother’s Day picnic. She learns a valuable lesson when little witch Lucinda grants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 10:00:00" d="2019-08-18 11:00:00"><n>Sofia the First: The Curse...</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Amber steals Sofia’s magical amulet it retaliates, summoning evil Princess Ivy, who wants to destroy Enchancia. Amber and Sofia join forces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 11:00:00" d="2019-08-18 11:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins Toy Hospital">Doc McStuffins Toy Hospital IV (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>CeCe gets muddy and needs a bath, but she’s scared. The Wicked King slips and hurts himself. He has to go to hospital and must learn to be a good patient</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 11:30:00" d="2019-08-18 12:00:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins Toy Hospital">Doc McStuffins Toy Hospital IV (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The giant snow globe is shaken and the Snow Peeps are broken up. Hallie's due to sing at the Toy Fooseball game but loses her voice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 12:00:00" d="2019-08-18 12:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins Toy Hospital">Doc McStuffins Toy Hospital (101)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 12:30:00" d="2019-08-18 13:00:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins Toy Hospital">Doc McStuffins Toy Hospital IV (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nikki is worried when she must stay in hospital overnight. Doc stresses it’s important to not wander off while exploring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 13:00:00" d="2019-08-18 13:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins Toy Hospital">Doc McStuffins Toy Hospital IV (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Some toys are injured while bouncing at Boppy's party. Stuffy sneaks Squibbles into hospital to try to cheer up a patient</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 13:30:00" d="2019-08-18 14:00:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins Toy Hospital">Doc McStuffins Toy Hospital IV (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mayor Billington gets the stuckies, like stutters, while making a speech. Hermie says he's been injured by a bathtub monster. It turns out to be Squeakers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 14:00:00" d="2019-08-18 14:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins Toy Hospital">Doc McStuffins Toy Hospital IV (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Chuck the wind-up chicken unintentionally causes accidents. Doc and the toys rush to fix a broken birthday present before its child returns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 14:30:00" d="2019-08-18 15:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus (4)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 15:00:00" d="2019-08-18 15:30:00"><n u="Mickey &amp; The Roadster Racers">Mickey &amp; The Roadster Racers II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mickey's pals are mending his first roadster as a present. Can the Happy Helpers stop their favourite band breaking up?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 15:30:00" d="2019-08-18 16:00:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy must improvise when a storm ruins the family campout. Nancy wants Grandma's vanity, but it holds special memories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 16:00:00" d="2019-08-18 16:30:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Elena is torn between a promise she made to help Isabel and fulfilling her royal duties as crown princess. George Takei (Star Trek) guest stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 16:30:00" d="2019-08-18 17:00:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First IV (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% On School Swap Day, Jade lives like a princess for a day at Royal Prep and Amber takes her place in the village at Dunwiddie School</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 17:00:00" d="2019-08-18 17:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>69% After Chilly accidentally blasts off on Luna's rocket to an unexplored planet, it's up to Doc and her friends to bring him and Luna's robot dog back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 17:30:00" d="2019-08-18 18:30:00"><n>Welcome to McStuffinsville</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Doc and the toys get a big surprise when Grandma takes them to McStuffinsville, a town made of toys. Doc is in charge of the town's hospital</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 18:30:00" d="2019-08-18 19:00:00"><n u="Mickey &amp; The Roadster Racers">Mickey &amp; The Roadster Racers II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Heist's cat gets the Smarty Hat and takes over his plot. The Helpers accidentally shave the current dog show champ,</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 19:00:00" d="2019-08-18 19:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo and Rolly accidentally chew Bob's childhood toy. When Bob's icemaker breaks, the pugs go to Antarctica to get him ice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 19:30:00" d="2019-08-18 20:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Edna enters a gardening contest but her plants are spooky. At a museum the kids meet an old family friend - a mummy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 20:00:00" d="2019-08-18 20:31:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Romeo turns people into babies. Gekko babysits his mates. Owlette must get back Luna Girl’s board and magnet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 20:31:00" d="2019-08-18 21:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% The Lion Guard worries that Fuli spends too much time on her own, so they start including her in their own family activities, which leads to repeated comic disaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 21:00:00" d="2019-08-18 21:35:00"><n u="Claude">Claude I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Claude investigates some strange and spooky bumps in the night at Armslength Keep. Claude goes on stage without Sir Bobblysock and gets stage fright</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 21:35:00" d="2019-08-18 22:10:00"><n u="Trulli Tales">Trulli Tales I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Copperpot sets free a powerful genie that gets out of control. Stella accidentally knocks some ink onto Sun's notebook</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 22:10:00" d="2019-08-18 22:41:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Catboy hears of a way to increase his cat power. A Romeo remote makes Catboy's night last forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 22:41:00" d="2019-08-18 23:15:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Catboy is turned into a cat by Romeo. Gekko needs Catboy and Owlette's help to fight a Roboctopus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 23:15:00" d="2019-08-18 23:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>As part of a project Zou tries to make a copy of an old puppet belonging to Grandpa. His first attempts don’t work, but eventually they are a success</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 23:30:00" d="2019-08-19 00:00:00"><n u="Trulli Tales">Trulli Tales I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Copperpot makes the village stink so people will leave and he can look for the magic cookbook. Sun changes Grandma’s recipe and the result is awful!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-19 00:00:00" d="2019-08-19 00:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (2)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-19 00:25:00" d="2019-08-19 00:50:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Romeo turns people into babies. Gekko babysits his mates. Owlette must get back Luna Girl’s board and magnet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-19 00:50:00" d="2019-08-19 01:00:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive (83)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-19 01:00:00" d="2019-08-19 01:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While clearing out old toys Zou finds his teething ring, which Mum has kept. At first he hides it from people, but then keeps it to show how grown up he is now</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-19 01:15:00" d="2019-08-19 01:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou helps Uncle Zavier with a big delivery. He wonders why the shop is now selling groceries, then realises two deliveries have been taken to the wrong shops</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-19 01:30:00" d="2019-08-19 01:55:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry’s troop needs a new leader. Roddy must prove he deserves a chance. Henry and Denzel swap to see what it’s like living in each other’s houses.( S2 Ep17)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-19 01:55:00" d="2019-08-19 02:20:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rain stops Henry going to the Monster Wave Park, so he comes up with a novel way to have a swim. Summer loses Momma’s necklace so she runs away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-19 02:20:00" d="2019-08-19 02:30:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Dr Beetle’s giving a first aid lesson when there’s an emergency. The kids have been practising bandaging on him and he’s stuck, so Jasper and Buzzbee come to the rescue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-19 02:30:00" d="2019-08-19 02:40:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive I (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Buzzbee and Rubee learn to appreciate each other, even though it's not always easy!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-19 02:40:00" d="2019-08-19 02:55:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou and his friends are trying to build aeroplanes, so use the feathers from what they think is Nanna's old hat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-19 02:55:00" d="2019-08-19 03:10:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou gets a drum kit for his birthday and plays it so loudly he drives everyone crazy. It's up to Nanna to show him that it's not volume that makes a great drummer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-19 03:10:00" d="2019-08-19 03:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>With a family photo coming up Zou tries to keep his clothes clean. Grandpa comes up with a game that is both clean and magical - blowing soap bubbles. Will he keep clean?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-19 03:25:00" d="2019-08-19 03:35:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Buzzbee and Barnabee are horrified at the mess in the playground, then realise they made it. They clean up, then lcampaign to keep it clean, and even get a litter bin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-19 03:35:00" d="2019-08-19 03:45:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% When a windy day causes chaos, Buzzbee and friends have to decide who needs their help first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-19 03:45:00" d="2019-08-19 04:10:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rain stops Henry going to the Monster Wave Park, so he comes up with a novel way to have a swim. Summer loses Momma’s necklace so she runs away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-19 04:10:00" d="2019-08-19 04:35:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After seeing sister Summer's show, Henry decides to do his own. But it proves harder than it looked, and after a disaster Henry asks Summer's advice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-19 04:35:00" d="2019-08-19 04:45:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Barnabee’s sick - he has a droopy antenna. Buzzbee thinks he’s faking it to practise football for the big game, so pretends he’s sick too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-19 04:45:00" d="2019-08-19 05:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (20)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
</a>
