<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="58" t="2019-08-11 01:29:08"><p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 05:00:00" d="2019-08-17 05:15:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Night Ninja creates a fortress of his own to take down the PJ Masks. (S1 Ep15a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 05:15:00" d="2019-08-17 05:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% It's Gekko's birthday and he's excited for his lizard themed party until Night Ninja steals everything! (S1 Ep9a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 05:30:00" d="2019-08-17 05:55:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Romeo’s new robot, Robette, decides to take over the world. Owlette wants to be a pet owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 05:55:00" d="2019-08-17 06:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Minnie and Daisy are left to babysit Baby Oinky, who turns out to be a bit of a handful. ( S2 Ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 06:00:00" d="2019-08-17 06:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse (89)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Goofy has gone missing and his friends are worried he may have been abducted by a monster. So they use their special spy and superhero powers to find him. (S3 Ep 24)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 06:30:00" d="2019-08-17 07:00:00"><n u="Muppet Babies">Muppet Babies I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>75% Kermit has to learn how to dance quickly for a dance-off. Trying to be big, Summer zaps herself with a super ray</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 07:00:00" d="2019-08-17 07:20:00"><n u="Claude">Claude (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Claude is inspired by his favourite Saturday morning TV show to become Super Paw - a masked superhero who super-helps the community, ut his over-zealous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 07:20:00" d="2019-08-17 07:40:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (55)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Robot made a Catboy costume for Romeo, who steals Catboy's powers as well. In order to stop him, Catboy will have to learn to be a super hero without any super power. (S2 Ep15a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 07:40:00" d="2019-08-17 08:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (56)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Night Ninja transformed the Mystery Mountain into a Splatcano and Gekko thinks he can't help Catboy and Owlette stop him because he is only the muscles. (S2 Ep15b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 08:00:00" d="2019-08-17 08:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>69% Hallie must decide between making a perfect pet or choosing to take in a toy pup without a home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 08:30:00" d="2019-08-17 08:45:00"><n u="Mickey &amp; The Roadster Racers">Mickey &amp; The Roadster Racers (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When the Professor’s pushy cousin Doctor Victor Von Goose challenges him to a challenging race against his latest invention Professor Von Drake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 08:45:00" d="2019-08-17 09:00:00"><n u="Mickey &amp; The Roadster Racers">Mickey &amp; The Roadster Racers (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pete accidentally turns on Professor Von Drake’s latest invention. The results are &quot;monstrous&quot; -- especially when Goofy’s sandwich gets mixed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 09:00:00" d="2019-08-17 09:30:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Elena visits the west coast of Avalor, where she encounters relatives she hasn’t seen in years, mysterious underwater creatures called Sirenas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 09:30:00" d="2019-08-17 10:00:00"><n u="Sofia the First">Sofia the First I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Sofia invites village friends Jade and Ruby to join her and Amber in the annual parade of flying coaches. But when they become friends with Amber she finds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 10:00:00" d="2019-08-17 11:00:00"><n>Welcome to McStuffinsville</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Doc and the toys get a big surprise when Grandma takes them to McStuffinsville, a town made of toys. Doc is in charge of the town's hospital</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 11:00:00" d="2019-08-17 11:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% The Guard must help two zany gorilla princes return to their home in the snowy Rwenzori Mountains</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 11:30:00" d="2019-08-17 12:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Ono fills in for a rhino’s seeing-eye bird while the Guard helps the rhino and tickbird resolve their differences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 12:00:00" d="2019-08-17 12:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Kion is dismayed when upstart Makuu wins the challenge for leadership of the crocodiles. He believes there's more to leadership than just aggression and strength</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 12:30:00" d="2019-08-17 13:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard (4)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 13:00:00" d="2019-08-17 13:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% While stranded in the Outlands, Kion meets Jasiri, a female hyena, who rescues him when he falls into a ravine. He learns that not all hyenas are bad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 13:30:00" d="2019-08-17 14:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% When Simba leaves Kiara in charge of Pride Rock for the first time, Kion reluctantly agrees to obey her. This proves difficult when Janja tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 14:00:00" d="2019-08-17 14:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard (7)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 14:30:00" d="2019-08-17 15:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Timid Bill and brave Rocky end up stranded on an island, however Rocky suddenly becomes the scared one! Trey warns the little dinos about a cave monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 15:00:00" d="2019-08-17 15:30:00"><n u="Mickey and The Roadster Racers">Mickey and The Roadster Racers I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>61% Billy Beagle invites the gang to compete in Billy B's Hot Rod Switcheroo! The Happy Helpers must find a shy panda for a little girl’s picture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 15:30:00" d="2019-08-17 16:00:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy and Bree create a Pas de Deux for dance class. Nancy finds the shoes of her dreams but can't afford them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 16:00:00" d="2019-08-17 16:30:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Elena officially becomes crown princess and rescues her sister, Isabel, from Noblins, elf-like shapeshifting creatures based on a Chilean peuchen myth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 16:30:00" d="2019-08-17 17:00:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First IV (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% After spending time learning to be royal, Sofia’s ready to discover some of Enchancia’s secrets as she releases a genie, finds a secret library and learns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 17:00:00" d="2019-08-17 17:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>69% Hallie must decide between making a perfect pet or choosing to take in a toy pup without a home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 17:30:00" d="2019-08-17 18:30:00"><n>Sofia the First: The Curse...</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Amber steals Sofia’s magical amulet it retaliates, summoning evil Princess Ivy, who wants to destroy Enchancia. Amber and Sofia join forces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 18:30:00" d="2019-08-17 19:00:00"><n u="Mickey &amp; The Roadster Racers">Mickey &amp; The Roadster Racers II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Rolling Roadster Runner is stolen with the gang inside! Will Hilda make the grade as a warrior?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 19:00:00" d="2019-08-17 19:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bongo and Rolly travel to Egypt to find the Great Pyramids. The pugs try to deliver a Mother's Day card for Bob</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 19:30:00" d="2019-08-17 20:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vee's friends try to keep her surprise party a secret, then learn it's the guests that get the surprises. Vee and Poppy set off a dance craze that could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 20:00:00" d="2019-08-17 20:31:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Gekko’s pet, Lionel, becomes a monster, wreaking havoc. Catboy confesses he has a cuddly toy to Owlette and Gekko</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 20:31:00" d="2019-08-17 21:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Kion inadvertently leads a pack of jackals into the Pride Lands, where they wreak havoc during a highly regarded Pride Lands ceremony</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 21:00:00" d="2019-08-17 21:35:00"><n u="Claude">Claude I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Claude is left in charge of Gloria Swoon’s new hairdo. Claude accompanies PC Anne Cuffs to the Harvest Ball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 21:35:00" d="2019-08-17 22:10:00"><n u="Trulli Tales">Trulli Tales I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Copperpot makes the village stink so people will leave and he can look for the magic cookbook. Sun changes Grandma’s recipe and the result is awful!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 22:10:00" d="2019-08-17 22:41:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Romeo turns people into babies. Gekko babysits his mates. Owlette must get back Luna Girl’s board and magnet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 22:41:00" d="2019-08-17 23:15:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% PJ Masks try to prevent Luna Girl improving her powers. Catboy and Gekko are imprisoned and need Gekko's help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 23:15:00" d="2019-08-17 23:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou (115)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 23:30:00" d="2019-08-18 00:00:00"><n u="Trulli Tales">Trulli Tales I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>As princess for a day, Sun bosses everyone around. Zip wonders what Stella is hiding and finds she was preparing a surprise for them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 00:00:00" d="2019-08-18 00:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (1)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 00:25:00" d="2019-08-18 00:50:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Gekko’s pet, Lionel, becomes a monster, wreaking havoc. Catboy confesses he has a cuddly toy to Owlette and Gekko</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 00:50:00" d="2019-08-18 01:00:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive (82)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 01:00:00" d="2019-08-18 01:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Poc is unwell and Zou needs to be immunised so they both need to go to see the doctor. They hide, but when they do go it's not as bad as they had feared</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 01:15:00" d="2019-08-18 01:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou (79)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou loses his scarf and notebook and decides to find a way take better care of his things. In the process he finds things other people have lost</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 01:30:00" d="2019-08-18 01:55:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Trouble erupts at summer camp when the girls get too competitive. There’s a surprise party for Momma’s birthday but an unusual cake threatens to ruin it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 01:55:00" d="2019-08-18 02:20:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Talent contest The Grr Factor is in town. Henry wants Daddo to demonstrate his juggling. Momma and Daddo leave Cobby to babysit and the power goes to his head</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 02:20:00" d="2019-08-18 02:30:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Pappa Bee takes Buzzbee and Barnabee camping. During the night they hear a strange noise. Buzzbee investigates and gets frightened too. The noise has a surprising origin!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 02:30:00" d="2019-08-18 02:40:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive I (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% When Pappa tries to get fit, he discovers that doing a good deed can be just as good as a strict exercise programme!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 02:40:00" d="2019-08-18 02:55:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>On a snowy day Zou attempts to build an igloo. His engineering skills are challenged but with Grandpa's help he learns the value of perseverance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 02:55:00" d="2019-08-18 03:10:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou and his Dad are gardening but birds eat the seeds they are planting. They make a scarecrow. It turns out to be pretty effective, scaring several of Zou’s family!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 03:10:00" d="2019-08-18 03:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou finds his father's old model sail boat in the shed and with Grandpa's help gets it ready to race against Zinnia's remote controlled boat at the beach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 03:25:00" d="2019-08-18 03:35:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Buzzbee doesn’t like bananas, but he has to have one if he wants a biscuit. He tries to hide them, but the smell gives him away. Miss Ladybird introduces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 03:35:00" d="2019-08-18 03:45:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive II (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% When Mrs Wasp goes away for the weekend, Jasper gets homesick and needs Buzzbee's special cure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 03:45:00" d="2019-08-18 04:10:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Talent contest The Grr Factor is in town. Henry wants Daddo to demonstrate his juggling. Momma and Daddo leave Cobby to babysit and the power goes to his head</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 04:10:00" d="2019-08-18 04:35:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When baking, Henry adds too much yeast and makes a giant dough ball that escapes. Henry's scout troop builds racing cars and he's flattered when Roberto copies him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 04:35:00" d="2019-08-18 04:45:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Debee has a brand new scooter and Buzzbee gets a chance to ride it, but it’s really hard. Rubee finds it easy, and Buzzbee’s annoyed, until he realises</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-18 04:45:00" d="2019-08-18 05:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (18)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
</a>
