<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="61" t="2021-07-11 04:55:58"><p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 05:00:00" d="2021-07-18 05:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Four young dinosaurs explore a prehistoric world of adventure where the most exciting mystery of all is Gigantosaurus, the biggest and fiercest dinosaur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 05:30:00" d="2021-07-18 06:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When a runaway boulder ruins Mazu’s invention, she sets out to find what set it in motion. Bill is tired of being a little brachiosaurus, so he looks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 06:00:00" d="2021-07-18 06:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey can’t wait to get to the monkey bars as Dad takes her and Bingo on a wagon ride to the park. But her patience is tested when Dad keeps stopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 06:10:00" d="2021-07-18 06:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey is running a taxi service. Her first passenger is Businessman Dad, who is in a rush to get to the airport. But with unexpected delays, Dad’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 06:20:00" d="2021-07-18 06:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>As Mum goes for a walk along the beach, Bluey runs to catch up with her. Along the way, she has a series of encounters that both excite and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 06:30:00" d="2021-07-18 06:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s adventure on the high seas as Bluey, Bingo and Missy play Pirates on the hammock swing, but they’ll need to find their courage to withstand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 06:40:00" d="2021-07-18 06:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A game of ‘Grannies’ is fun, until Bingo and Bluey can’t agree on one simple question: Can Grannies do the floss dance? Now they need to video call Nana to get the answer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 06:50:00" d="2021-07-18 07:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bored of the local playground, Dad and the kids go bush on a journey to their local creek. Cast out of her comfort zone, Bluey’s eyes are opened</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 07:00:00" d="2021-07-18 07:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (128)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% After offering to watch over the Nursery, Chilly is too afraid to ask questions and gets in way over his head!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 07:30:00" d="2021-07-18 08:00:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (133)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Chilly forms a special bond with Mumbo, a rambunctious baby mammoth. When Mumbo is ready to be delivered to the Toyartic, Chilly must find</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 08:00:00" d="2021-07-18 08:30:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Elena travels to the realm of the jaquins!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 08:30:00" d="2021-07-18 09:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% After Elena travels to the realm of the jaquins, she inadvertently releases a mythical forest spirit that could endanger Avalor!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 09:00:00" d="2021-07-18 10:00:00"><n>The Lion Guard: Return of the Roar</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In this enchanting Lion King spin-off, Simba and Nala’s cub Kion becomes leader of the Lion Guard, a team of animals comprising the Pride Lands’ fiercest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 10:00:00" d="2021-07-18 10:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rocky wants a tail as powerful as Giganto’s, but with great power comes great responsibility! Bill discovers that ‘crying wolf’ lets him avoid doing things</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 10:30:00" d="2021-07-18 11:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The dinos have a falling out. After Archie saves Tiny, the little dino must repay the favor and honor Triceratops Code</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 11:00:00" d="2021-07-18 11:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Rugo tries to collect all of the coconuts in Cretacia, Bill sets out to get them back! Tiny and Totor discover they have a lot in common</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 11:30:00" d="2021-07-18 12:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu and Rocky must work together to save Tiny and Bill from Terminonator. Bill and Marsh are separated from their friends in a storm and must face their fears to get home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 12:00:00" d="2021-07-18 12:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Tiny throws a party but can she deliver on the outrageous promises she made? When Mazu wants to see a once-in-a-lifetime comet, everyone else's needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 12:30:00" d="2021-07-18 13:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A falling meteorite forces the herd to move, leaving Giganto behind!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 13:00:00" d="2021-07-18 13:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. II (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mr. Woodbird’s big-o-nator is accidentally used on a baby gorilla! When Pip and Freddy are left out of Captain Beakman’s secret mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 13:30:00" d="2021-07-18 14:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Luna Girl creates a giant moon ball, and hides the toys she’s stolen inside: Romeo and Night Ninja try to shrink the PJ Masks with Romeo’s invention</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 14:00:00" d="2021-07-18 14:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rocky decides not to practice for a talent show but his partner in the show is Giganto. Marsh is tricked by raptors to play a game, but they're really</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 14:30:00" d="2021-07-18 15:30:00"><n>The Lion Guard: Return of the Roar</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In this enchanting Lion King spin-off, Simba and Nala’s cub Kion becomes leader of the Lion Guard, a team of animals comprising the Pride Lands’ fiercest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 15:30:00" d="2021-07-18 16:00:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (126)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% After making a big mistake at the McStuffinsville Toy Hospital, Doc begins to wonder if her patients would have been better off if she hadn't been there at all</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 16:00:00" d="2021-07-18 16:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (129)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Hallie switches places with her lookalike, the famous Hallie the Entertainer! She learns firsthand what it's like to be a star and what happens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 16:30:00" d="2021-07-18 17:00:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (133)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Chilly forms a special bond with Mumbo, a rambunctious baby mammoth. When Mumbo is ready to be delivered to the Toyartic, Chilly must find</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 17:00:00" d="2021-07-18 17:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (134)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% When Lambie is mistakenly transported to Lost and Found Land, it's up to Doc and the gang to save Lambie and find homes for all the misplaced toys stranded</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 17:30:00" d="2021-07-18 17:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Playing ‘Shops’ is the best game ever for Bluey and her friends - if they can ever get started! With Bluey questioning the rules and changing who’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 17:40:00" d="2021-07-18 17:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey can’t wait to get to the monkey bars as Dad takes her and Bingo on a wagon ride to the park. But her patience is tested when Dad keeps stopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 17:50:00" d="2021-07-18 18:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey is running a taxi service. Her first passenger is Businessman Dad, who is in a rush to get to the airport. But with unexpected delays, Dad’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 18:00:00" d="2021-07-18 18:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>As Mum goes for a walk along the beach, Bluey runs to catch up with her. Along the way, she has a series of encounters that both excite and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 18:10:00" d="2021-07-18 18:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s adventure on the high seas as Bluey, Bingo and Missy play Pirates on the hammock swing, but they’ll need to find their courage to withstand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 18:20:00" d="2021-07-18 18:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A game of ‘Grannies’ is fun, until Bingo and Bluey can’t agree on one simple question: Can Grannies do the floss dance? Now they need to video call Nana to get the answer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 18:30:00" d="2021-07-18 19:00:00"><n u="Mira, Royal Detective">Mira, Royal Detective I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Prince Neel's sitar goes missing, can Mira find it before Great Aunt Rupa finds out? Mira goes on a mysterious underground adventure to find toy boats for a race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 19:00:00" d="2021-07-18 19:30:00"><n u="The Rocketeer">The Rocketeer I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Kit uses a haunted house to spook Orsino as he tries to steal the Rocketeer's rocket-pack! Kit rounds up a stampede of cows, used as a distraction for a Halloween heist!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 19:30:00" d="2021-07-18 20:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (53)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The pups lose an important part of Bob's presentation during Take Your Dog to Work Day. Bob, the pugs and Keia run out of popcorn at their first slumber party!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 20:00:00" d="2021-07-18 20:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Bob loses his lucky shirt before an important meeting, the pups stage a heist to get it back. Bob's mother's pet-sits the pugs while Bob's at work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 20:30:00" d="2021-07-18 21:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (96)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Feeling bad about his ninja past, Teeny Weeny tries to help defeat the ninjas using his monster powers. The Wolfies want their own robo-servant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 21:00:00" d="2021-07-18 21:25:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Four young dinosaurs explore a prehistoric world of adventure where the most exciting mystery of all is Gigantosaurus, the biggest and fiercest dinosaur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 21:25:00" d="2021-07-18 21:50:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bill wishes Giganto would go away forever after his coconut lunch is disrupted. Ayati sends the four friends off on a quest to find a legendary land called Dinosia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 21:50:00" d="2021-07-18 22:15:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Four young dinosaurs explore a prehistoric world of adventure where the most exciting mystery of all is Gigantosaurus, the biggest and fiercest dinosaur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 22:15:00" d="2021-07-18 22:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou is making a tapestry in art class. Zena suggests adding beads but Zou has given his to Zak. So Grandpa suggests using shells instead and it’s a triumph</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 22:30:00" d="2021-07-18 22:45:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou decides to become a record breaker but his attempts are in vain – until he discovers that he already holds a record, he is the little zebra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 22:45:00" d="2021-07-18 23:00:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou’s invited to join Zinnia and her parents on a trip to visit the beach and have a swim. He’s strangely reluctant until Grandpa realises Zou can’t</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 23:00:00" d="2021-07-18 23:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou wants to go cycling but has no bike. Luckily Grandpa has an old one. Zak’s scooter falls to bits so Grandpa uses them with bike parts to make a cycle-cum-scooter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 23:15:00" d="2021-07-18 23:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou decides he wants to be a postman. At first he's helpful delivering things but gets too confident and things start going to the wrong places, so Grandpa has to help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 23:25:00" d="2021-07-18 23:50:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mama is to be Roarsville's official music maker so everyone must help at home. Henry thinks Denzel is moving away so plans a party for his best friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-18 23:50:00" d="2021-07-19 00:15:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry plans Ivor's first birthday party then realises it’s what he, not Ivor, would like. It's Spring Cleaning Day and there are lots of bubbles!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 00:15:00" d="2021-07-19 00:40:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry works at the radio station and upsets people when he tells their secrets. Henry’s upset when Ivor starts day care so breaks in to get him! ( S2 Ep22)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 00:40:00" d="2021-07-19 01:05:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The two monster families get competitive on a snow day. Will Santa Claws arrive in time for Henry’s festive TV show?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 01:05:00" d="2021-07-19 01:30:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>No hurdle’s too high for the Paprika twins Olivia and Stan as they turn everyday life into wonderful, colourful adventures!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 01:30:00" d="2021-07-19 01:55:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>No hurdle’s too high for the Paprika twins Olivia and Stan as they turn everyday life into wonderful, colourful adventures!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 01:55:00" d="2021-07-19 02:20:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rocky decides not to practice for a talent show but his partner in the show is Giganto. Marsh is tricked by raptors to play a game, but they're really</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 02:20:00" d="2021-07-19 02:45:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu sees life through a raptor’s eyes when she gets stuck to Cror by some tar. Rocky hopes to get the best viewing spot to watch the &quot;winter lights&quot; dance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 02:45:00" d="2021-07-19 03:10:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry shows Gertie it’s fun to have new experiences and not plan everything in advance. Henry agrees to practice piano if Momma learns how to skate ( S1 Ep14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 03:10:00" d="2021-07-19 03:35:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Trouble erupts at summer camp when the girls get too competitive. There’s a surprise party for Momma’s birthday but an unusual cake threatens to ruin it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 03:35:00" d="2021-07-19 04:00:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry adds powerful beans and explosive corn to the punch for Cobby’s first Halloween party. They turn into rocket fuel that blasts the Hugglemonster house into outer space!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 04:00:00" d="2021-07-19 04:25:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Disney’s Mickey Mouse Clubhouse is the first Mickey Mouse series created specifically for preschoolers. The show introduces a whole new generation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 04:25:00" d="2021-07-19 04:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Hot Diggity-Dog Tales">Mickey Mouse Hot Diggity-Dog Tales I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mickey and Pluto are having a tough time learning to surf, but when a pair of playful seals lend a flipper, Mickey and his pup are transformed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 04:30:00" d="2021-07-19 04:55:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Disney’s Mickey Mouse Clubhouse is the first Mickey Mouse series created specifically for preschoolers. The show introduces a whole new generation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 04:55:00" d="2021-07-19 05:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons II (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Daisy Duck wins a prize and is excited when a grand piano arrives, but it won’t fit through the door of the Bowtique. They solve the problem</k>  </p>
</a>
