<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="57" t="2020-05-16 04:47:33"><p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 05:00:00" d="2020-05-23 05:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Rip tries to gather feathers from Owlette's wings to let the Wolfies fly. Skeletons are stolen from the museum!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 05:30:00" d="2020-05-23 05:55:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Timid Bill and brave Rocky end up stranded on an island, however Rocky suddenly becomes the scared one! Trey warns the little dinos about a cave monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 05:55:00" d="2020-05-23 06:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Convinced Minnie needs more time to relax, Daisy orders a bow-making robot. But Daisy breaks the remote, and the Bow-Bot goes haywire, turning everything into bows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 06:00:00" d="2020-05-23 06:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% When Simba leaves Kiara in charge of Pride Rock for the first time, Kion reluctantly agrees to obey her. This proves difficult when Janja tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 06:30:00" d="2020-05-23 07:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A unicorn is spotted in Hot Dog Hills. Minnie and Daisy love horses, but do they know enough to give horseback riding lessons?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 07:00:00" d="2020-05-23 07:30:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A magical book that wreaks havoc is accidentally selected as Vee's first book club read. The girls come up with a haunted plan to keep people from wanting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 07:30:00" d="2020-05-23 07:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Playing Shops is the best game ever for Bluey and her friends - if they can ever get started! With Bluey questioning the rules and changing who’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 07:40:00" d="2020-05-23 07:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>With five bucks from the tooth fairy, Bluey is overwhelmed with possibilities at the markets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 07:50:00" d="2020-05-23 08:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey and Chloe embark on a quest to save their playground kingdom from the Greedy Queen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 08:00:00" d="2020-05-23 08:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% When the Wolfies steal a local dog, the PJ Masks must try to get it back! The PJ Masks team up with Night Ninja to stop the Wolfies from destroying Mystery Mountain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 08:30:00" d="2020-05-23 09:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>On Pip and Freddy’s first day, they deliver a kitten who mistakes them as her parents. When there is a two-ton baby whale delivery, the fliers compete</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 09:00:00" d="2020-05-23 09:30:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% Isabel enters the Science Fair with her friends but ignores Elena’s advice about teamwork and tries to do everything herself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 09:30:00" d="2020-05-23 10:00:00"><n u="Sofia the First">Sofia the First I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Sofia becomes Cedric the Royal Sorcerer’s apprentice, to learn for a sorcery test, not realising Cedric has a scheme to steal her amulet and take over the kingdom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 10:00:00" d="2020-05-23 10:30:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A magical book that wreaks havoc is accidentally selected as Vee's first book club read. The girls come up with a haunted plan to keep people from wanting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 10:30:00" d="2020-05-23 11:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Trying to help Bob meet an alien, the Pugs meet UFO fans. The pugs try to reunite a lost toy dog with its owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 11:00:00" d="2020-05-23 12:00:00"><n>Lion Guard: Rise of Scar</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Guard meets Rafiki's new apprentice, Moniki. Meanwhile Ushari conspires with the hyenas to seek the help of the Pride Lands' greatest villain, Scar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 12:00:00" d="2020-05-23 12:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy fakes being sick but regrets it when her family throws a party that she'll have to miss. Nancy faces Rhonda and Wanda to determine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 12:30:00" d="2020-05-23 13:00:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy grows jealous of Bree’s friendship with a girl from summer camp. Nancy dreams of the heroic accolades that will be bestowed on her if she saves a lost kitten</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 13:00:00" d="2020-05-23 13:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Nancy tries to win a contest for the fanciest Easter bonnet, she attracts a swarm of bugs to her bonnet. Nancy organizes a stakeout to find the Easter Bunny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 13:30:00" d="2020-05-23 14:00:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy writes a gossip column and gets a little fancy with the facts. Nancy falls in love with Grace's pony</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 14:00:00" d="2020-05-23 14:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy rebels against her favorite teenage babysitter when she doesn't treat Nancy like a peer. Nancy regrets trading a piece of jewelry with Jo Jo and tries to trade back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 14:30:00" d="2020-05-23 15:00:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy worries Lionel’s art isn't pretty enough to put in her new museum. When Nancy imitates a fancy superhero, she winds up discovering she has a super</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 15:00:00" d="2020-05-23 15:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy worries Lionel’s art isn't pretty enough to put in her new museum. When Nancy imitates a fancy superhero, she winds up discovering she has a super</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 15:30:00" d="2020-05-23 16:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% When Elena travels to the realm of the Jaquins, she inadvertently allows a mythical forest spirit to be released who could endanger Avalor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 16:00:00" d="2020-05-23 16:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey needs Mum's advice when her couch-cushion playhouse has noisy neighbours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 16:10:00" d="2020-05-23 16:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mum and Dad are going on an adventure with Bluey and Bingo as their backpacks!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 16:20:00" d="2020-05-23 16:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey needs Mum's advice when her couch-cushion playhouse has noisy neighbours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 16:30:00" d="2020-05-23 17:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mickey must turn lemons into lemonade when he's having 'one of those days!' Cuckoo Loca's cousins visit from Paris!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 17:00:00" d="2020-05-23 17:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When a cheetah is set loose at T.O.T.S., Pip and Freddy must play a game of tag to catch it! The Junior Fliers lead a class trip of storks and teach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 17:30:00" d="2020-05-23 18:30:00"><n>Battle for the Pride Lands</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Scar devises a scheme to destroy the Lion Guard, which leaves them forever changed. Following the battle, the Lion Guard sets off for the Tree of Life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 18:30:00" d="2020-05-23 19:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Catboy is turned into a cat by Romeo. Gekko needs Catboy and Owlette's help to fight a Roboctopus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 19:00:00" d="2020-05-23 19:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bob signs up for a game show with Bingo and Rolly. When Bob's trip to the Empire State Building is cancelled the Pugs and ARF head to NYC to bring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 19:30:00" d="2020-05-23 20:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% When Zuzo goes missing in the spirit world, Elena enlists the helps of other spirit guides to find him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 20:00:00" d="2020-05-23 20:30:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First IV (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% After seeing Sofia being rewarded as a Protector, Clover takes her place on a mission in the Mystic Isles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 20:30:00" d="2020-05-23 21:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJ Masks get locked in the lab and it's up to PJ Robot to rescue them! Gekko is on the case when animals keep disappearing from the city</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 21:00:00" d="2020-05-23 21:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Ninja uses Armadylan's dream of becoming a kung fu movie star to break into a museum. While Gekko and Armadylan guard the city, their watch turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 21:30:00" d="2020-05-23 22:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo and Rolly help a baby whale that has been separated from her family. The pugs retrace their steps to remember where they buried Bob's unicycle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 22:00:00" d="2020-05-23 22:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bob is worried about a lost butterfly so the pugs see it home. Bob wants a seat at the theatre so the pugs push one there</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 22:30:00" d="2020-05-23 23:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bill’s friends pretend he is invisible so he can win at hide-and-seek. Mazu invents eyeglasses to help near-sighted Patchy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 23:00:00" d="2020-05-23 23:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus (12)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-23 23:30:00" d="2020-05-24 00:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo steals Catboy's powers while wearing his costume. Can Gekko help Catboy and Owlette stop Night Ninja?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-24 00:00:00" d="2020-05-24 00:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJ Masks face the newest villains in town: the Wolfies. Gekko's knowledge of dinosaurs helps the team get back prehistoric bones from the Wolfy Kids</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-24 00:30:00" d="2020-05-24 01:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJ Masks must prevent Night Ninja stealing a magic ring. The P J Masks must get a magical ring from Mystery Mountain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-24 01:00:00" d="2020-05-24 01:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou decides he'd like to be an inventor so he creates many inventions to help his family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-24 01:15:00" d="2020-05-24 01:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After Zac takes a tumble and is bandaged up, Zou decides he wants to be a first aider, and finds the household full of willing patients</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-24 01:30:00" d="2020-05-24 01:55:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry and Denzel learn their mums were in rock band Grrr Power. They try to stage a reunion concert. Henry’s loose fang affects his roar. His friends think it sounds cool!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-24 01:55:00" d="2020-05-24 02:20:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry’s really excited about the Halloween parade, and hopes to get a Hugglebar from the Treats Balloon. But the balloon blows away and it’s up to Henry to save the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-24 02:20:00" d="2020-05-24 02:30:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia are fascinated by Sheriff Pearl, and decide to become sheriffs themselves. Well, it’s not that simple! Both Olivia and Stan realize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-24 02:30:00" d="2020-05-24 02:40:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Both Olivia and Stan realize that Stan can’t keep a secret. Olivia offers to help her brother, and gives him advice. (S1 Ep3b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-24 02:40:00" d="2020-05-24 02:55:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou decides Zigmund and Zoroaster need to get fit and appoints himself their personal trainer. But he makes it too hard and finds he is training all by himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-24 02:55:00" d="2020-05-24 03:10:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zowie and Zinnia are taking a cycling proficiency course. Zinnia is over-enthusiastic so Zou must show her where she’s going wrong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-24 03:10:00" d="2020-05-24 03:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou is looking after Elzee’s fern while she’s away. It seems to have died and she’s upset, but is it really dead?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-24 03:25:00" d="2020-05-24 03:35:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia aren’t allowed to go down the Scary-Big-Slide without a cuddly toy and they don’t even have one. They decide to make their own! (S1 Ep3c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-24 03:35:00" d="2020-05-24 03:45:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (10)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-24 03:45:00" d="2020-05-24 04:00:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry practises his magic show. Summer and Denzel both want to be his assistant, but when they accidentally get tied together they must work together as a team.( S2 E18a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-24 04:00:00" d="2020-05-24 04:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu makes Archie a pair of wings to help him fly. Marsh copies Rocky's every move while Rocky copies Giganto</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-24 04:30:00" d="2020-05-24 05:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo’s multiplying machine accidentally makes Catboy copies. Night Ninja challenges the PJ Masks to a game of Capture the Flag with the PJ Mask headquarters as the prize</k>  </p>
</a>
