<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="58" t="2020-04-11 04:30:16"><p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 05:00:00" d="2020-04-18 05:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Something is fishy when Catboy gets a gift of a scooter from an unknown aunt. Gekko’s got the sneezes and his friends want him to rest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 05:25:00" d="2020-04-18 05:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Musical fun with our night-time heroes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 05:30:00" d="2020-04-18 05:55:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% An evil plan from Night Ninja divides the P J Masks. Our heroes team up with other villains to defeat Romeo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 05:55:00" d="2020-04-18 06:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons III (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Minnie and Daisy have a disaster when all their Sticky Tricky Treats are ruined before the trick-or-treaters arrive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 06:00:00" d="2020-04-18 06:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% Ono grudgingly hatches and fosters a cuckoo egg left in his nest, then joins forces with the cuckoo mom when the baby is captured by vultures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 06:30:00" d="2020-04-18 07:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A unicorn is spotted in Hot Dog Hills. Minnie and Daisy love horses, but do they know enough to give horseback riding lessons?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 07:00:00" d="2020-04-18 07:30:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vampirina decides to run for class president. Poppy wants a pet bunny, but first she has to show her mum she's ready to have a pet by looking after Wolfie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 07:30:00" d="2020-04-18 07:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Spy Game: A game in the park goes haywire when Bingo stops playing. Now Bluey must win her back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 07:40:00" d="2020-04-18 07:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Five minutes feels like an eternity as Dad and the kids wait for their takeaway order. (S1Ep14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 07:50:00" d="2020-04-18 08:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Playing Butterflies in the backyard is great fun, until Bluey runs away with Judo leaving Bingo all alone. Now poor Bingo’s heartbroken and Bluey needs to make amends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 08:00:00" d="2020-04-18 08:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Luna Girl steals the moon crystal to power up her Luna Fortress’ Mega-Magnet, which creates a portal that pulls stuff up from the city. The PJ Masks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 08:30:00" d="2020-04-18 09:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip and Freddy must deliver a baby panda that is so cute, that it makes it hard to say goodbye. The Junior Fliers have trouble delivering a baby skunk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 09:00:00" d="2020-04-18 09:30:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% Elena flies to a magical realm to learn how to master her Scepter of Light, but a crisis draws her back when Shuriki reappears in Avalor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 09:30:00" d="2020-04-18 10:00:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First (79)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% &quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 10:00:00" d="2020-04-18 10:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Ninja uses Armadylan's dream of becoming a kung fu movie star to break into a museum. While Gekko and Armadylan guard the city, their watch turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 10:30:00" d="2020-04-18 11:00:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A neighbourhood climbing tree is declared off-limits, Nancy and friends protest. Nancy dreams of becoming a synchronized swimmer, but is afraid of water</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 11:00:00" d="2020-04-18 12:00:00"><n>The Lion Guard: Return of the Roar</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In this enchanting Lion King spin-off, Simba and Nala’s cub Kion becomes leader of the Lion Guard, a team of animals comprising the Pride Lands’ fiercest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 12:00:00" d="2020-04-18 12:30:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Demi brings the infamous Chef Remy Bones to the Scare B&amp;B to help with the meal preparations. Vee joins Poppy and Bridget at a Woodchuck Wooodsie event</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 12:30:00" d="2020-04-18 13:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Boris learns humans sell antiques and wants to sell some of his own, but Gregoria gets mixed up with them. Edna is to be a dog show judge. Vee and Poppy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 13:00:00" d="2020-04-18 13:30:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Scream Girls visit and help Vee and friends overcome stage fright. Vee invites her friends over for family game night and teaches them some of her favourite games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 13:30:00" d="2020-04-18 14:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vee’s Grandmother visits to help her cook a vampire dish. Chaos ensues when two-headed monster sisters come to stay</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 14:00:00" d="2020-04-18 14:30:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bridget disappears during a game of hide and shriek. Vee helps a young witch learn some techniques</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 14:30:00" d="2020-04-18 15:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The class parrot tells Edgar what has been going on. Vee and Poppy swap identities. Can they swap back?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 15:00:00" d="2020-04-18 15:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy wants to win a poetry contest but gets writer’s block. Nancy’s Valentine’s card is accidentally delivered to Grace</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 15:30:00" d="2020-04-18 16:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% When Zuzo goes missing in the spirit world, Elena enlists the helps of other spirit guides to find him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 16:00:00" d="2020-04-18 16:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Doctor Bluey is needed when Dad gets a very curious x-ray from Nurse Bingo. It seems he has a cat in his tummy, leaving Bluey no choice but to operate immediately!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 16:10:00" d="2020-04-18 16:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey, Bingo and Mum are enjoying playing Keepy Uppy around the house with their last balloon, when Dad joins in and the game becomes the ultimate test of skill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 16:20:00" d="2020-04-18 16:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey and Bingo don't want to tidy the playroom, so they get Daddy Robot to do it for them. But when Bluey takes things too far, Daddy Robot malfunctions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 16:30:00" d="2020-04-18 17:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A special winner gets mixed-up for the day. When Clarabelle ends up with the hidden royal sceptre, everyone thinks she's the new princess</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 17:00:00" d="2020-04-18 17:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip and Freddy teach a lion cub the difference between his indoor and outdoor roar. When a porcupine is scared of the delivery tube, K.C. and the Fliers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 17:30:00" d="2020-04-18 18:30:00"><n>Lion Guard: Rise of Scar</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Guard meets Rafiki's new apprentice, Moniki. Meanwhile Ushari conspires with the hyenas to seek the help of the Pride Lands' greatest villain, Scar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 18:30:00" d="2020-04-18 19:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJ Masks must race against time to get a stolen cup back. Luna Girl steals Gekko’s special rock and uses it to super power her magnet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 19:00:00" d="2020-04-18 19:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Bob stays late at work to do a presentation and forgets his dinner, the pugs decide to bring it to him. Keia’s new caterpillar friend goes missing!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 19:30:00" d="2020-04-18 20:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% Skylar must overcome his carefree ways when he is chosen to guide three jaquins, including his younger brother, across the kingdom to Avalor City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 20:00:00" d="2020-04-18 20:30:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First IV (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% After spending time learning to be royal, Sofia’s ready to discover some of Enchancia’s secrets as she releases a genie, finds a secret library and learns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 20:30:00" d="2020-04-18 21:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo turns Owlette's Flossy Flash toy into a device that transforms the PJ Masks into action toys! Night Ninja steals an ancient gong to awaken a Dragon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 21:00:00" d="2020-04-18 21:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% An evil plan from Night Ninja divides the P J Masks. Our heroes team up with other villains to defeat Romeo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 21:30:00" d="2020-04-18 22:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bob signs up for a game show with Bingo and Rolly. When Bob's trip to the Empire State Building is cancelled the Pugs and ARF head to NYC to bring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 22:00:00" d="2020-04-18 22:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When a puppy gets lost at Adopt-A-Palooza, it's up to the pugs, Keia and their new friend to find it. Bingo, Rolly and Keia go off in search of Captain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 22:30:00" d="2020-04-18 23:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus (16)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 23:00:00" d="2020-04-18 23:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus (17)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-18 23:30:00" d="2020-04-19 00:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Catboy hears of a way to increase his cat power. A Romeo remote makes Catboy's night last forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 00:00:00" d="2020-04-19 00:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% &quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 00:30:00" d="2020-04-19 01:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo turns Owlette's Flossy Flash toy into a device that transforms the PJ Masks into action toys! Night Ninja steals an ancient gong to awaken a Dragon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 01:00:00" d="2020-04-19 01:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Grandpa wants to take Zou and Elzee kayaking but the boats are being serviced. So they buy some inflatables from the shop instead and have lots of fun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 01:15:00" d="2020-04-19 01:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou visits the aquarium and decides he wants one of his own. Mum tells him what hard work looking after one is, so Grandpa suggests making a model</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 01:30:00" d="2020-04-19 02:00:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Geri Halliwell stars in this episode in which Summer auditions to sing with her idol Isabella Roarson. Henry keeps a tiny hugglefish as a pet, but it grows huge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 02:00:00" d="2020-04-19 02:30:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry searches Roarsville for Beckett when he runs off to play with Meg's monsterpet Shakey. Henry tries to teach his friends Gertie and Denzel to fly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 02:30:00" d="2020-04-19 02:40:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (54)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Olivia decides to play in bed today: it’s so cosy… other friends join in, but Stan refuses and ends up by himself: beds are made for sleeping! (S1 Ep18c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 02:40:00" d="2020-04-19 02:55:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou learns about making promises, and makes them to anyone who asks. He promises more than he can deliver, and ends up having to make a list of what he’s promised to do</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 02:55:00" d="2020-04-19 03:10:00"><n u="Zou">Zou (100)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Uncle Zavier has been presented with a VIZ, a Very Important Zebra award. Zou wishes his Dad was important too. Grandpa shows Zou just how important</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 03:10:00" d="2020-04-19 03:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou helps Mrs Zolli find her nephew’s tortoise that’s missing. He realises it’s hibernating, and that gives him a theme for his school project on autumn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 03:25:00" d="2020-04-19 03:35:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (10)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 03:35:00" d="2020-04-19 03:45:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Today, everything Stan and Olivia try to do goes wrong. Uh oh, what if their day is sick? They try to make it better! (S1 Ep4b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 03:45:00" d="2020-04-19 03:55:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The twins have saved a sparkly play-clay pot for a special occasion. They’re dying to open it. will they ever find that truly special occasion? (S1 Ep5a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 03:55:00" d="2020-04-19 04:10:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry and his friends use Cobby's newest invention, Megabouncer Boots, to bounce all over Roarsville, but they end up shaking the ground and ruining others' fun. (S1 Ep3b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 04:10:00" d="2020-04-19 04:35:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu makes Archie a pair of wings to help him fly. Marsh copies Rocky's every move while Rocky copies Giganto</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 04:35:00" d="2020-04-19 05:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ayati falls over. Mazu must come up with an idea to help. A crevice rips through the ground and traps four little dinos in Giganto's path</k>  </p>
</a>
