<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="57" t="2020-05-10 04:30:45"><p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 05:00:00" d="2020-05-17 05:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo steals Catboy's powers while wearing his costume. Can Gekko help Catboy and Owlette stop Night Ninja?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 05:30:00" d="2020-05-17 05:55:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus (13)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 05:55:00" d="2020-05-17 06:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Minnie and Daisy are making rubber bows for the walrus ballerina's underwater ballet. When the Bowtique's water pipes burst, the rubber</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 06:00:00" d="2020-05-17 06:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% The Guard’s ability to find the Tree of Life disappears when Makini’s staff is stolen by a scheming Binturong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 06:30:00" d="2020-05-17 07:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mickey, Donald, Goofy, Minnie and Daisy run a garage in Hot Dog Hills and compete with their transforming roadsters in races around the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 07:00:00" d="2020-05-17 07:30:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Poppy writes a song for the Ghoul Girls to use in the school talent show. Vee and her friends are invited to a sleepover at the museum hosted by King Pepi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 07:30:00" d="2020-05-17 07:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Mum takes a walk along the beach, Bluey follows behind on her first solo adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 07:40:00" d="2020-05-17 07:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey has to appease invisible mischief-making fairies, who have infested the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 07:50:00" d="2020-05-17 08:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo causes chaos at Bluey’s backyard zoo, when she sneaks into Daddy Gorilla’s cage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 08:00:00" d="2020-05-17 08:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJ Masks get locked in the lab and it's up to PJ Robot to rescue them! Gekko is on the case when animals keep disappearing from the city</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 08:30:00" d="2020-05-17 09:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Freddy's status as the best hide-and-seeker is challenged after he and Pip lose a baby fox. Pip and Freddy help K.C. earn her first Golden Feather on Cleaning Day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 09:00:00" d="2020-05-17 09:30:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor (26)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 09:30:00" d="2020-05-17 10:00:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First (111)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 10:00:00" d="2020-05-17 10:30:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vee puts a Transylvania twist on Boris’ park idea and presents it to the Board. A family of ghosts stay at the B&amp;B while they finish their business before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 10:30:00" d="2020-05-17 11:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bob is learning to yodel, The Pugs go to the Alps for tips. It’s Bob’s birthday and his sister Bonnie is acting sneaky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 11:00:00" d="2020-05-17 12:00:00"><n>First Responders to the Rescue</n><t>Q</t>    <k>With the help of a young boy, the First Responders assemble for the first time in McStuffinsville to help endangered toys as quickly as possible</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 12:00:00" d="2020-05-17 12:30:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Sofia is upset when her mum invites Amber and James to their Mother’s Day picnic. She learns a valuable lesson when little witch Lucinda grants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 12:30:00" d="2020-05-17 13:00:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Sofia must learn to trust her instincts, helped by legendary Disney Princess Snow White, when she suspects a visiting sorceress is not what she seems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 13:00:00" d="2020-05-17 13:30:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Sofia discovers twins Amber and James’s don’t like sharing a birthday so she tries to solve the problem with Cedric the Magician’s help. Unfortunately</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 13:30:00" d="2020-05-17 14:00:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Sofia must teach Prince Hugo the meaning of teamwork after Prince James gets injured right before the big flying derby race and she gets paired</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 14:00:00" d="2020-05-17 14:30:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Sofia meets her hero, brave but silent knight Sir Bartleby. She learns he has two secrets: he is silent because he's ashamed of his voice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 14:30:00" d="2020-05-17 15:00:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Sofia and friends pair up for a science fair. They get too competitive trying to reach the same ingredient and lose it. They realize friendship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 15:00:00" d="2020-05-17 15:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy II (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy rebels against her favorite teenage babysitter when she doesn't treat Nancy like a peer. Nancy regrets trading a piece of jewelry with Jo Jo and tries to trade back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 15:30:00" d="2020-05-17 16:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor (8)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 16:00:00" d="2020-05-17 16:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey, Bingo and Mum are enjoying playing Keepy Uppy around the house with their last balloon, when Dad joins in and the game becomes the ultimate test of skill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 16:10:00" d="2020-05-17 16:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s lunchtime on Bluey's back deck! But every BBQ needs a side salad, so Bingo’s relaxing sit-down will have to wait until she finds every colour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 16:20:00" d="2020-05-17 16:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A trip to the local creek opens Bluey’s eyes to the simple beauty of nature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 16:30:00" d="2020-05-17 17:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It's Mini-Mechanics Day and Mickey's number one fan can't wait to get to work! The Happy Helpers are busy pet-sitting while everyone heads to the Fancy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 17:00:00" d="2020-05-17 17:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip and Freddy teach a lion cub the difference between his indoor and outdoor roar. When a porcupine is scared of the delivery tube, K.C. and the Fliers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 17:30:00" d="2020-05-17 18:30:00"><n>Welcome to McStuffinsville</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Doc and the toys get a big surprise when Grandma takes them to McStuffinsville, a town made of toys. Doc is in charge of the town's hospital</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 18:30:00" d="2020-05-17 19:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% PJ Masks try to prevent Luna Girl improving her powers. Catboy and Gekko are imprisoned and need Gekko's help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 19:00:00" d="2020-05-17 19:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Bob's lucky baseball bat breaks, the pups go on a mission to find a new one in time for the championship game. The pugs help a group of lost moles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 19:30:00" d="2020-05-17 20:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% Elena and her friends race against Shuriki and her evil minions to find the hidden first piece of the dangerous Scepter of Night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 20:00:00" d="2020-05-17 20:30:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First IV (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Sofia must decide what school is right for her. James fears he may not be talented enough to make it as a knight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 20:30:00" d="2020-05-17 21:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Armadylan steals the PJ Masks' vehicles. Kevin turns full wolfy on a trip to the moon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 21:00:00" d="2020-05-17 21:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Night Ninja tricks Armadylan into stealing An Yu's bo staff and takes control of the Mountain again. An Yu tries to train Teeny Weeny into the Mystery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 21:30:00" d="2020-05-17 22:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bob mistakes a mud-covered pig for Rolly and accidentally leaves him behind on the farm. When the Mona Lisa goes missing, the Pugs go looking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 22:00:00" d="2020-05-17 22:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The pugs misinterpret Bob's wish for his own art exhibit. Bob can't wait for snow so the pugs go looking for it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 22:30:00" d="2020-05-17 23:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu and her three besties map the stars. Tiny’s artistic skills are put to use when the dinos are lost in the desert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 23:00:00" d="2020-05-17 23:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Tiny and Mazu treat Giganto's toothache. Every dino in Cretacia tries to claim a beautiful pebble!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-17 23:30:00" d="2020-05-18 00:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJ Masks face the newest villains in town: the Wolfies. Gekko's knowledge of dinosaurs helps the team get back prehistoric bones from the Wolfy Kids</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-18 00:00:00" d="2020-05-18 00:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Catboy works too fast to kick back moonfizzle balls. Owlette must coach Catboy and Gekko to defeat Night Ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-18 00:30:00" d="2020-05-18 01:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJ Masks must race against time to get a stolen cup back. Luna Girl steals Gekko’s special rock and uses it to super power her magnet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-18 01:00:00" d="2020-05-18 01:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou accuses Poc of breaking his model plane when he finds feathers in the wreckage. Grandma admits she did it but Zou doesn’t apologise until he realises how upset Poc is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-18 01:15:00" d="2020-05-18 01:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A power cut stops Zou and Elzee playing a video game. Grandpa teaches them some old-fashioned games which Zou loves and carries on playing after the power returns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-18 01:30:00" d="2020-05-18 01:55:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After seeing sister Summer's show, Henry decides to do his own. But it proves harder than it looked, and after a disaster Henry asks Summer's advice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-18 01:55:00" d="2020-05-18 02:20:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry's thrilled when Gertie turns up, but she's come for a piano lesson with Momma so he tries to sabotage it! Henry goes to the wave park. He's scared</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-18 02:20:00" d="2020-05-18 02:30:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia make Bigfoot angry without meaning to. But Bigfoot has never been angry before, and doesn’t understand what’s happening to him. The twins try to help him. (S1 Ep18a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-18 02:30:00" d="2020-05-18 02:40:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (53)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan encourages his friends to throw away things they don’t need anymore, and dresses up as a big friendly bin. He discovers that you can become attached to things. (S1 Ep18b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-18 02:40:00" d="2020-05-18 02:55:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zavier and Zelda are going on a ski-ing holiday with Zinnia but find themselves snowed in. Zou and Grandpa come to the rescue with their home-made snow plough</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-18 02:55:00" d="2020-05-18 03:10:00"><n u="Zou">Zou (122)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-18 03:10:00" d="2020-05-18 03:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou researches into yawns for a school project but no-one is tired and yawns are thin on the ground. When he does find one he discovers that yawning is contagious!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-18 03:25:00" d="2020-05-18 03:35:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia make Bigfoot angry without meaning to. But Bigfoot has never been angry before, and doesn’t understand what’s happening to him. The twins try to help him. (S1 Ep18a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-18 03:35:00" d="2020-05-18 03:45:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (55)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and his club of Serious Friends invite Sheriff Pearl to do some serious activities with them. But when she’s not on-duty, the Sheriff isn’t</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-18 03:45:00" d="2020-05-18 04:00:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>To help the Roarsville grandmonsters create a knitted playground, Henry and Cobby invent a Knit-O-Bot robot.(S2 Ep4a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-18 04:00:00" d="2020-05-18 04:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus (16)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-05-18 04:30:00" d="2020-05-18 05:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (15)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
</a>
