<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="69" t="2020-04-16 04:30:49"><p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 05:00:00" d="2020-04-23 05:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (17)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 05:25:00" d="2020-04-23 05:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Even his speed can't help him crossing the river to stop Romeo before he takes over the world, so Catboy must face his biggest fear and drop himself into the water</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 05:30:00" d="2020-04-23 05:55:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% PJ Robot persuades the PJMs to journey towards a comet which he thinks it’ll give HQ extra power. Luna’s teasing Romeo with her newly super-charged moths</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 05:55:00" d="2020-04-23 06:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons III (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While at a traditional Japanese Kabuki show Minnie and Daisy get caught up in the acrobatic action after being mistaken for dancers, and show Cuckoo-Loca</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 06:00:00" d="2020-04-23 06:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% Zazu is taken by the hyenas, and the Guard must rescue him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 06:30:00" d="2020-04-23 07:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>For Thanksgiving this year, Mickey and the gang race Thanksgiving-themed racers. Minnie, Daisy and Cuckoo Loca invite all of their friends for Thanksgiving dinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 07:00:00" d="2020-04-23 07:30:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Demi brings the infamous Chef Remy Bones to the Scare B&amp;B to help with the meal preparations. Vee joins Poppy and Bridget at a Woodchuck Wooodsie event</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 07:30:00" d="2020-04-23 07:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo and Bluey can’t agree on one simple question: Can Grannies do the floss dance?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 07:40:00" d="2020-04-23 07:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A trip to the local creek opens Bluey’s eyes to the simple beauty of nature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 07:50:00" d="2020-04-23 08:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey has to appease invisible mischief-making fairies, who have infested the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 08:00:00" d="2020-04-23 08:30:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First (84)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 08:30:00" d="2020-04-23 09:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% Elena officially becomes crown princess and rescues her sister, Isabel, from Noblins, elf-like shapeshifting creatures based on a Chilean peuchen myth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 09:00:00" d="2020-04-23 09:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>On a car trip to the dump, Bluey discovers that Dad is throwing out her old drawings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 09:10:00" d="2020-04-23 09:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo causes chaos at Bluey’s backyard zoo, when she sneaks into Daddy Gorilla’s cage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 09:20:00" d="2020-04-23 09:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mum and Dad are going on an adventure with Bluey and Bingo as their backpacks!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 09:30:00" d="2020-04-23 09:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey and Chloe embark on a quest to save their playground kingdom from the Greedy Queen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 09:40:00" d="2020-04-23 09:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey’s having fun copying Dad, but her game takes a turn when Bluey finds a hurt budgie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 09:50:00" d="2020-04-23 10:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey and Bingo’s plans to stay up late are derailed when Muffin misses her nap</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 10:00:00" d="2020-04-23 11:00:00"><n>A Goofy Fairy Tale</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Goofy's magic trick accidently makes all the bedtime stories disappear from the Clubhouse, he must find a way to bring them back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 11:00:00" d="2020-04-23 11:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Freddy has to scare Pip. Pip and Freddy race a drone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 11:30:00" d="2020-04-23 11:55:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mia loses Lovey, so Pip and Freddy go on a wild chase to find it. But are they too late? The Fliers' delivery is in jeopardy when their puppy student</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 11:55:00" d="2020-04-23 12:00:00"><n u="Marvel Super Hero Adventures">Marvel Super Hero Adventures I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Spidey and Ant-Man try to rescue people off a collapsing bridge, Hulk decides to pitch in but his smashing makes things worse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 12:00:00" d="2020-04-23 12:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Night Ninja steals everything from Gekko's party. Luna Girl turns a sleep-walking Cameron into her puppet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 12:30:00" d="2020-04-23 13:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Night Ninja steals the school bus and converts it into his very own super-vehicle! The PJ Masks discover a super teeny Ninjalino at HQ</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 13:00:00" d="2020-04-23 13:30:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% When Zuzo goes missing in the spirit world, Elena enlists the helps of other spirit guides to find him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 13:30:00" d="2020-04-23 14:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Freddy and Pip try their hardest to keep a baby tiger prince clean. When a baby arrives on its birthday, Freddy tries to find the perfect birthday present</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 14:00:00" d="2020-04-23 14:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Pip gets locked inside a crate with a baby kangaroo, can he get her to stop bouncing? Pip and Freddy teach squabbling kitten and puppy siblings to share</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 14:30:00" d="2020-04-23 15:30:00"><n u="Pets">Pets I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% This extra-long adventure features four stories involving some of the pets and animals in this series, including Romeo’s robot Robette and his Roboctopus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 15:30:00" d="2020-04-23 16:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% While her magical sceprer isn't working properly, Elena is forced to face a fire starting creature without her magic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 16:00:00" d="2020-04-23 16:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Five minutes feels like an eternity as Dad and the kids wait for their takeaway order. (S1Ep14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 16:10:00" d="2020-04-23 16:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Playing Butterflies in the backyard is great fun, until Bluey runs away with Judo leaving Bingo all alone. Now poor Bingo’s heartbroken and Bluey needs to make amends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 16:20:00" d="2020-04-23 16:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>On a car trip to the dump, Bluey discovers that Dad is throwing out her old drawings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 16:30:00" d="2020-04-23 17:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip and Freddy deliver a baby penguin to Pip's home town. When Pip and Freddy break the conveyor belt at T.O.T.S. they are determined to fix it on their own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 17:00:00" d="2020-04-23 17:15:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy wants to win a Valentine’s Day poetry contest but gets a terrible case of writer’s block. (S1 Ep15a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 17:15:00" d="2020-04-23 17:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Nancy’s Valentine’s Day card to Bree is accidentally delivered to Grace, Grace believes she and Nancy are now best friends! (S1 Ep15b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 17:30:00" d="2020-04-23 18:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vee puts a Transylvania twist on Boris’ park idea and presents it to the Board. A family of ghosts stay at the B&amp;B while they finish their business before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 18:00:00" d="2020-04-23 18:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJ Masks discover Romeo's Sky Factory and send PJ Robot as a mole. When the Sky Factory produces a pollution pancake over the city, the PJ Masks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 18:30:00" d="2020-04-23 19:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard III (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% Ever closer to the Tree of Life, Kion’s scar bothers him more than ever! Bunga thinks that this un-Kion-like behaviour is proof the venom in Kion’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 19:00:00" d="2020-04-23 19:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% When Cedric finally gets a hold of Sofia's amulet and is repeatedly cursed by the gem, he realizes that the amulet's powers are only granted by acts of kindness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 19:25:00" d="2020-04-23 19:30:00"><n u="Music Lullabies">Music Lullabies I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Minnie and Mickey skip and splash their way through a magical summer rainstorm!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 19:30:00" d="2020-04-23 19:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>As Bluey and Bingo squabble over their magic xylophone (that has the power to freeze Dad in space and time) Dad seizes control and freezes Bluey, leaving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 19:40:00" d="2020-04-23 19:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Doctor Bluey is needed when Dad gets a very curious x-ray from Nurse Bingo. It seems he has a cat in his tummy, leaving Bluey no choice but to operate immediately!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 19:50:00" d="2020-04-23 20:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey, Bingo and Mum are enjoying playing Keepy Uppy around the house with their last balloon, when Dad joins in and the game becomes the ultimate test of skill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 20:00:00" d="2020-04-23 20:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Everyone ends up with mixed-up roadsters when Chip 'n Dale add a few ideas to Mickey's new Motor Lab invention. The gang turns window washing into a friendly competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 20:30:00" d="2020-04-23 21:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% While her magical sceprer isn't working properly, Elena is forced to face a fire starting creature without her magic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 21:00:00" d="2020-04-23 21:15:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After encouraging Jo Jo to create an imaginary friend, Nancy becomes jealous of their relationship.(S1 Ep4a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 21:15:00" d="2020-04-23 21:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy tries to leave the perfect handprints in a newly cemented walkway. (S1 Ep4b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 21:30:00" d="2020-04-23 22:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vee puts a Transylvania twist on Boris’ park idea and presents it to the Board. A family of ghosts stay at the B&amp;B while they finish their business before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 22:00:00" d="2020-04-23 22:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJ Masks discover Romeo's Sky Factory and send PJ Robot as a mole. When the Sky Factory produces a pollution pancake over the city, the PJ Masks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 22:30:00" d="2020-04-23 23:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard III (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% Ever closer to the Tree of Life, Kion’s scar bothers him more than ever! Bunga thinks that this un-Kion-like behaviour is proof the venom in Kion’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 23:00:00" d="2020-04-23 23:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% When Cedric finally gets a hold of Sofia's amulet and is repeatedly cursed by the gem, he realizes that the amulet's powers are only granted by acts of kindness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 23:25:00" d="2020-04-23 23:30:00"><n u="Music Lullabies">Music Lullabies I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Minnie and Mickey skip and splash their way through a magical summer rainstorm!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 23:30:00" d="2020-04-24 00:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus (17)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-24 00:00:00" d="2020-04-24 00:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo steals Gekko’s voice, but Gekko’s not sure he wants it back before his poetry presentation. Night Ninja has stolen Master Fang’s prized sword!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-24 00:30:00" d="2020-04-24 01:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Armadylan and sidekick Robette fight with Romeo to determine whose sidekick is better. After Armadylan loses his temper again, the PJ Masks take him on a zen trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-24 01:00:00" d="2020-04-24 01:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou discovers a rare brain coral at the beach, which gives him the idea of starting a museum. He collects interesting objects for the museum – including</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-24 01:15:00" d="2020-04-24 01:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou, Elzee and Grandpa play a game of hide and seek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-24 01:30:00" d="2020-04-24 02:00:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry sells sweet flower juice but uses them all up. Cobby builds a robot DJ to provide music for Henry’s party but won’t come as he can’t dance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-24 02:00:00" d="2020-04-24 02:30:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry helps Summer make a film to represent their roarsome family. Henry helps at the Cafe when Signor Roartonio's assistant is ill on Monster Pizza Day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-24 02:30:00" d="2020-04-24 02:40:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (64)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan, Olivia and Bigfoot each have an amusing musical instrument. But that doesn’t mean they can make beautiful music together. (S1 Ep22a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-24 02:40:00" d="2020-04-24 02:55:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Zou accidentally knocks over a pile of apples in Mr Zooey's shop, his attempts to rescue them remind Mr Zoey of a clown - and Zou decides he'd like to be a clown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-24 02:55:00" d="2020-04-24 03:10:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After a storm Zou finds lots of wood on the beach. Zigmund and Zoroaster tell him it’s just driftwood, but can be made into a very interesting sculpture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-24 03:10:00" d="2020-04-24 03:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou is fed up after being told not to be noisy, and to tidy his room. He decides to leave home, but after talking to Grandpa wonders if he's made the right decision</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-24 03:25:00" d="2020-04-24 03:35:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The twins decide to make themselves a triplet to do all sorts of fun activities with them. But their talents fall short of their ambitions, and their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-24 03:35:00" d="2020-04-24 03:45:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia play &quot;Restaurant&quot;. But Bigfoot opens a restaurant too, and Stan is a little jealous of their friend’s talents– he’s getting lots more customers. (S1 Ep7c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-24 03:45:00" d="2020-04-24 03:55:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia set up a surprise party for Bigfoot. But it’s awfully hard for them to wait until their friend gets back. (S1 Ep6c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-24 03:55:00" d="2020-04-24 04:10:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Summer feels down about having to leave the family's monsterpet Beckett at home while the family goes camping to Rainbow Falls, so Henry figures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-24 04:10:00" d="2020-04-24 04:35:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bill’s friends pretend he is invisible so he can win at hide-and-seek. Mazu invents eyeglasses to help near-sighted Patchy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-24 04:35:00" d="2020-04-24 05:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bill accidentally changes Cretacia’s ecosystem when he eats too many rare swamp flowers. Dilo pulls pranks on the dinos!</k>  </p>
</a>
