<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="58" t="2020-04-12 04:28:53"><p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 05:00:00" d="2020-04-19 05:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo creates a space laser to carve his face on the moon. Romeo plans to use a device to make everyone so clumsy that they can’t stop him!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 05:25:00" d="2020-04-19 05:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Night Ninja makes a speech about how cool it is to be a villain but his sidekicks, the ninjalinos, behave badly, turning his great plans into jokes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 05:30:00" d="2020-04-19 05:55:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Gekko fights the evil alter egos of Catboy and Owlette. Romeo, Luna Girl and Night Ninja team up to catch P J Masks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 05:55:00" d="2020-04-19 06:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons III (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Minnie and Daisy struggle to get past the palace guards in order to deliver a hat to the Queen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 06:00:00" d="2020-04-19 06:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% The Lion Guard must work together to chase away a baboon comedy troupe that has been distracting the other animals with their antics and stealing their food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 06:30:00" d="2020-04-19 07:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang transforms roadsters into their favourite animals for the Safari Park race. When Lazlo, Commander Heist's cat, runs away, the Happy Helpers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 07:00:00" d="2020-04-19 07:30:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vee and the girls are getting ready to go on their very first hiking trip with the Woodchuck Woodsies. One of Vee’s oldest friends from Transylvania</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 07:30:00" d="2020-04-19 07:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When horsing around with Dad goes too far, Bingo learns about finding her big girl voice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 07:40:00" d="2020-04-19 07:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>At school, Bluey and her friends throw themselves into various games. Teacher Calypso keeps her charges on track with a wise word and a song - all except</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 07:50:00" d="2020-04-19 08:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Honey’s trip to see Dr. Bingo keeps getting interrupted by other, more exciting patients</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 08:00:00" d="2020-04-19 08:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Armadylan and sidekick Robette fight with Romeo to determine whose sidekick is better. After Armadylan loses his temper again, the PJ Masks take him on a zen trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 08:30:00" d="2020-04-19 09:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A delivery crate containing a baby octopus springs a leak. Pip and Freddy deliver a mysterious striped animal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 09:00:00" d="2020-04-19 09:30:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% When Isabel takes her first class at the Science Academy with her heroine, Professor Ochoa, she learns how to overcome failure and let it lead her to success</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 09:30:00" d="2020-04-19 10:00:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First (80)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Sofia must stop Lucinda’s good and evil friends from ruining her special witch ceremony. (S3 Ep24)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 10:00:00" d="2020-04-19 10:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJ Masks discover Romeo's Sky Factory and send PJ Robot as a mole. When the Sky Factory produces a pollution pancake over the city, the PJ Masks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 10:30:00" d="2020-04-19 11:00:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy wants to win a poetry contest but gets writer’s block. Nancy’s Valentine’s card is accidentally delivered to Grace</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 11:00:00" d="2020-04-19 12:00:00"><n>Lion Guard: Rise of Scar</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Guard meets Rafiki's new apprentice, Moniki. Meanwhile Ushari conspires with the hyenas to seek the help of the Pride Lands' greatest villain, Scar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 12:00:00" d="2020-04-19 12:30:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First (111)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 12:30:00" d="2020-04-19 13:00:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First (112)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 13:00:00" d="2020-04-19 13:30:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First IV (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% When Sofia, Amber and James are left in charge of the castle for the day, they attempt to make peace between the River Elves and the Tree Elves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 13:30:00" d="2020-04-19 14:00:00"><n u="Sofia the First">Sofia the First I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Sofia wants to join the Royal Prep’s flying horse racing team, so James teaches her to ride. She must also learn to ride neurotic horse Minimus to achieve her goal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 14:00:00" d="2020-04-19 14:30:00"><n u="Sofia the First">Sofia the First I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Sofia invites two village friends for a sleepover. She is horrified when her posh princess pals look down on her less wealthy friends and tries to help them get along</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 14:30:00" d="2020-04-19 15:00:00"><n u="Sofia the First">Sofia the First I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Sofia befriends some cave trolls and finds a misunderstanding caused the rift between them and the humans. She manages to persuade King Roland to get to know them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 15:00:00" d="2020-04-19 15:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy (16)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 15:30:00" d="2020-04-19 16:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% When Elena tries to get a Unity Pact signed between humans and the Sirenas, a distrustful Sirena and evil shape shifting dolphins disrupt the peace</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 16:00:00" d="2020-04-19 16:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>On a picnic in the park, Bluey and her friends play Shadowlands. But when Coco keeps taking shortcuts, Bluey has to show her that following the rules</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 16:10:00" d="2020-04-19 16:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>At the weekend, Bluey and Bingo are playing in the garden with Dad. But Bingo gets upset, when she discovers a walking leaf insect and Dad is too caught</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 16:20:00" d="2020-04-19 16:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s lunchtime on Bluey's back deck! But every BBQ needs a side salad, so Bingo’s relaxing sit-down will have to wait until she finds every colour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 16:30:00" d="2020-04-19 17:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It's Mini-Mechanics Day and Mickey's number one fan can't wait to get to work! The Happy Helpers are busy pet-sitting while everyone heads to the Fancy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 17:00:00" d="2020-04-19 17:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip and Freddy must deliver a baby panda that is so cute, that it makes it hard to say goodbye. The Junior Fliers have trouble delivering a baby skunk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 17:30:00" d="2020-04-19 18:30:00"><n>The Lion Guard: Return of the Roar</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In this enchanting Lion King spin-off, Simba and Nala’s cub Kion becomes leader of the Lion Guard, a team of animals comprising the Pride Lands’ fiercest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 18:30:00" d="2020-04-19 19:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Catboy works too fast to kick back moonfizzle balls. Owlette must coach Catboy and Gekko to defeat Night Ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 19:00:00" d="2020-04-19 19:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The pugs go to Madagascar to learn about lemurs. When a big dog takes Keia's toy at the dog park, Bingo and Rolly make it their mission to retrieve the toy!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 19:30:00" d="2020-04-19 20:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor (16)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 20:00:00" d="2020-04-19 20:30:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First IV (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% On School Swap Day, Jade lives like a princess for a day at Royal Prep and Amber takes her place in the village at Dunwiddie School</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 20:30:00" d="2020-04-19 21:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Gekko fights the evil alter egos of Catboy and Owlette. Romeo, Luna Girl and Night Ninja team up to catch P J Masks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 21:00:00" d="2020-04-19 21:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJM have to protect all the kids from Luna Girl, Night Ninja and the Wolfy Kids who have got together to steal their goody bags</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 21:30:00" d="2020-04-19 22:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While in New Zealand, the pugs try to return a large egg before it hatches. When Chloe and Keia lose a special canoe paddle, the pups embark</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 22:00:00" d="2020-04-19 22:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bob wants to wake up on his dream vacation, so the pugs try to get him to Tahiti while he sleeps. Bingo and Rolly search all around the golf course</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 22:30:00" d="2020-04-19 23:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus (18)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 23:00:00" d="2020-04-19 23:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rocky gets carried away being the leader in a game of Follow the Leader. When Trey injures himself in a tree toppling accident, Tiny helps him find his inner artist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-19 23:30:00" d="2020-04-20 00:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The moths and ninjalinos team up to form one evil villain. Night Ninja plans to use his dastardly new invention on HQ</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-20 00:00:00" d="2020-04-20 00:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% &quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-20 00:30:00" d="2020-04-20 01:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% An evil plan from Night Ninja divides the P J Masks. Our heroes team up with other villains to defeat Romeo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-20 01:00:00" d="2020-04-20 01:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Grandpa helps Zou see up a tree with a home-made periscope. It’s such a success Zou makes a home-made submarine next!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-20 01:15:00" d="2020-04-20 01:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou accidentally breaks Zac’s car. He’s worried about owning up and tries to distract Zac with other toys and games. When he eventually confesses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-20 01:30:00" d="2020-04-20 02:00:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Daddo can’t go sledging in the snow because he’s ill, so Henry turns the house into a sledge. Daddo’s in charge while Mum’s away and chaos ensues until</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-20 02:00:00" d="2020-04-20 02:30:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry and Cobby invent a robot to help the grandmonsters create a knitted playground. Henry's scout troop competes against its rivals on Scouts’ Game Day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-20 02:30:00" d="2020-04-20 02:40:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (56)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Olivia makes some big super-hero arms out of play-clay. Now that she’s super-strong, she can help all her friends. But once she starts, can’t stop helping people! (S1 Ep19b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-20 02:40:00" d="2020-04-20 02:55:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zinnia finds a caterpillar and mistakes it for a worm. She’s scared but Zou explains what it is and that it will turn into a beautiful butterfly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-20 02:55:00" d="2020-04-20 03:10:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While on a fishing trip to the beach with Grandpa, Zou learns that it’s not always those with the expensive equipment that have the most success</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-20 03:10:00" d="2020-04-20 03:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zigmund and Zoroaster make a waxwork model of Zou. It’s so realistic, when it’s put in the window of Uncle Zavier’s shop it’s mistaken for</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-20 03:25:00" d="2020-04-20 03:35:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia realize that they’re playing in the park in their pyjamas! How embarrassing! What if someone sees them? (S1 Ep4c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-20 03:35:00" d="2020-04-20 03:45:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The twins have saved a sparkly play-clay pot for a special occasion. They’re dying to open it. will they ever find that truly special occasion? (S1 Ep5a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-20 03:45:00" d="2020-04-20 03:55:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The twins play with their electronic image console, calling out the names of objects around them. Until they stumble on an unidentified &quot;thingy&quot;. (S1 Ep5b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-20 03:55:00" d="2020-04-20 04:10:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry is looking for someone to play with but Gertie is having a piano lesson with Momma. (S1 Ep4a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-20 04:10:00" d="2020-04-20 04:35:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rocky gets jealous when Tiny suddenly becomes the go-to hero! Mazu may be a slow runner but is a quick thinker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-20 04:35:00" d="2020-04-20 05:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Timid Bill and brave Rocky end up stranded on an island, however Rocky suddenly becomes the scared one! Trey warns the little dinos about a cave monster</k>  </p>
</a>
