<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="66" t="2020-06-01 04:32:00"><p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 05:00:00" d="2020-06-08 05:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Will Romeo's All-in-One belt for his robot defeat the team? The PJ Masks must trust Luna Girl to heal the Moon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 05:25:00" d="2020-06-08 05:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks Music Video">PJ Masks Music Video I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The PJ Masks are on their way to save the day! Music accompanies clips from the popular show featuring pyjama-clad heroes Catboy, Gekko and Owlette</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 05:30:00" d="2020-06-08 05:55:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% A new villain is hatched from a strange crystal on the moon! Gekko is forced to confiscate Luna Girl and Motsuki's powers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 05:55:00" d="2020-06-08 06:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>At a Mexican fiesta, Minnie and Daisy enter the Hat Dance competition, but it’s Clarabelle who feels the groove and gets into the Moo-sic after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 06:00:00" d="2020-06-08 06:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% When tales of a mysterious creature plague the Pride Lands, the Guard must conquer their fears and track down the beast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 06:30:00" d="2020-06-08 07:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse (81)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Martian Mickey visits and brings his pet shapes - cone, cylinder, pyramid, cube and sphere. He loses them so everyone helps find them, hiding among similar Earth shapes. (S3 E16)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 07:00:00" d="2020-06-08 07:30:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vee and her family paint spooky-themed eggs for Vee’s first Easter egg hunt! Family Heritage Day is coming up at school and Vee is excited to make a family tree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 07:30:00" d="2020-06-08 07:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>As Bluey and Bingo squabble over their magic xylophone (that has the power to freeze Dad in space and time) Dad seizes control and freezes Bluey, leaving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 07:40:00" d="2020-06-08 07:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Doctor Bluey is needed when Dad gets a very curious x-ray from Nurse Bingo. It seems he has a cat in his tummy, leaving Bluey no choice but to operate immediately!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 07:50:00" d="2020-06-08 08:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey, Bingo and Mum are enjoying playing Keepy Uppy around the house with their last balloon, when Dad joins in and the game becomes the ultimate test of skill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 08:00:00" d="2020-06-08 08:30:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First IV (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% After a secret meeting of sorcerers, Cedric must choose between taking over the kingdom and maintaining his friendship with Sofia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 08:30:00" d="2020-06-08 09:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor (6)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 09:00:00" d="2020-06-08 10:00:00"><n>Sofia the First: The Curse...</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Amber steals Sofia’s magical amulet it retaliates, summoning evil Princess Ivy, who wants to destroy Enchancia. Amber and Sofia join forces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 10:00:00" d="2020-06-08 10:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mickey and pals travel to New Delhi for a wedding and help with the ceremony. The Happy Helpers assist wiith a Tuk-Tuk business</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 10:30:00" d="2020-06-08 11:00:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy’s horrified when Dad builds a non-fancy playhouse! Nancy starts a charm school to teach friends to be fancy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 11:00:00" d="2020-06-08 11:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Jo Jo has an imaginary friend. Can Nancy make perfect handprints in a newly cemented path?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 11:30:00" d="2020-06-08 12:00:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy learns she must practise to be a great ice skater. Nancy makes a mess painting a portrait. Jo Jo is blamed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 12:00:00" d="2020-06-08 12:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Everything seems to be going well for Nancy and Bree's new cafe until Grace the food critic shows up! When Mom has the sniffles, Nancy takes over as Mom for the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 12:30:00" d="2020-06-08 13:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mickey, Donald, Goofy, Minnie and Daisy run a garage in Hot Dog Hills and compete with their transforming roadsters in races around the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 13:00:00" d="2020-06-08 13:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Catboy works too fast to kick back moonfizzle balls. Owlette must coach Catboy and Gekko to defeat Night Ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 13:30:00" d="2020-06-08 14:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Gekko’s pet, Lionel, becomes a monster, wreaking havoc. Catboy confesses he has a cuddly toy to Owlette and Gekko</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 14:00:00" d="2020-06-08 14:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo turns people into babies. Gekko babysits his mates. Owlette must get back Luna Girl’s board and magnet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 14:30:00" d="2020-06-08 15:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Catboy hears of a way to increase his cat power. A Romeo remote makes Catboy's night last forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 15:00:00" d="2020-06-08 15:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The moths and ninjalinos team up to form one evil villain. Night Ninja plans to use his dastardly new invention on HQ</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 15:25:00" d="2020-06-08 15:30:00"><n u="Playtime With Puppy Dog Pals">Playtime With Puppy Dog Pals I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Come play with the Puppy Dog Pals!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 15:30:00" d="2020-06-08 16:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% While visiting a neighbouring kingdom Elena is convinced by a spoiled prince to set aside her better judgement and take a break, resulting in unforeseen problems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 16:00:00" d="2020-06-08 16:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>As Bluey and Bingo squabble over their magic xylophone (that has the power to freeze Dad in space and time) Dad seizes control and freezes Bluey, leaving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 16:10:00" d="2020-06-08 16:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Doctor Bluey is needed when Dad gets a very curious x-ray from Nurse Bingo. It seems he has a cat in his tummy, leaving Bluey no choice but to operate immediately!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 16:20:00" d="2020-06-08 16:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey, Bingo and Mum are enjoying playing Keepy Uppy around the house with their last balloon, when Dad joins in and the game becomes the ultimate test of skill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 16:30:00" d="2020-06-08 17:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A special winner gets mixed-up for the day. When Clarabelle ends up with the hidden royal sceptre, everyone thinks she's the new princess</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 17:00:00" d="2020-06-08 17:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Can the pups find Chloe's lost puppy before she returns? Chloe wishes for a unicorn. The pups set out to find one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 17:30:00" d="2020-06-08 18:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vee and her family go on a camping trip. A monster gets lost on his way to the Scare B&amp;B and ends up at the wrong house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 18:00:00" d="2020-06-08 18:15:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (58)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJ Masks team up with Night Ninja to stop the Wolfies from destroying Mystery Mountain. (S3 Ep3b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 18:15:00" d="2020-06-08 18:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo is turning everyone into babies and Gekko has to baby-sit his two team-mates Kitty Boy and Chiclet, and save the world. (S2 Ep2a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 18:30:00" d="2020-06-08 19:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% When Scar’s minions take over the Kilio Valley, the Pride Lands must adjust to an influx of elephants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 19:00:00" d="2020-06-08 19:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Sofia and Clover stumble through a portal at the bottom of a silver tree and enter the magical, enchanted world of Elvenmoor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 19:25:00" d="2020-06-08 19:30:00"><n u="Playtime With Puppy Dog Pals">Playtime With Puppy Dog Pals I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Come play with the Puppy Dog Pals!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 19:30:00" d="2020-06-08 20:00:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Sofia and friends pair up for a science fair. They get too competitive trying to reach the same ingredient and lose it. They realize friendship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 20:00:00" d="2020-06-08 20:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A special winner gets mixed-up for the day. When Clarabelle ends up with the hidden royal sceptre, everyone thinks she's the new princess</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 20:30:00" d="2020-06-08 21:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% While visiting a neighbouring kingdom Elena is convinced by a spoiled prince to set aside her better judgement and take a break, resulting in unforeseen problems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 21:00:00" d="2020-06-08 21:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Can the pups find Chloe's lost puppy before she returns? Chloe wishes for a unicorn. The pups set out to find one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 21:30:00" d="2020-06-08 22:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vee and her family go on a camping trip. A monster gets lost on his way to the Scare B&amp;B and ends up at the wrong house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 22:00:00" d="2020-06-08 22:15:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (100)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Gekko wants to stop the Ninjalinos on his own, Night Ninja tries to take over HQ! (S3 Ep24b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 22:15:00" d="2020-06-08 22:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (99)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Gekko finds a crystal that gives him powers, but it seems they are too strong! (S3 Ep24a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 22:30:00" d="2020-06-08 23:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% When Scar’s minions take over the Kilio Valley, the Pride Lands must adjust to an influx of elephants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 23:00:00" d="2020-06-08 23:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Sofia and Clover stumble through a portal at the bottom of a silver tree and enter the magical, enchanted world of Elvenmoor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 23:25:00" d="2020-06-08 23:30:00"><n u="Playtime With Puppy Dog Pals">Playtime With Puppy Dog Pals I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Come play with the Puppy Dog Pals!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 23:30:00" d="2020-06-09 00:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rocky gets jealous when Tiny suddenly becomes the go-to hero! Mazu may be a slow runner but is a quick thinker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-09 00:00:00" d="2020-06-09 00:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Luna Girl creates a giant moon ball, and hides the toys she’s stolen inside: Romeo and Night Ninja try to shrink the PJ Masks with Romeo’s invention</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-09 00:25:00" d="2020-06-09 00:50:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (6)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-09 00:50:00" d="2020-06-09 01:00:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia aren’t allowed to go down the Scary-Big-Slide without a cuddly toy and they don’t even have one. They decide to make their own! (S1 Ep3c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-09 01:00:00" d="2020-06-09 01:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou decides he wants to be a waiter, and his uncle lets him serve the guests at a special party at the shop. Zinnea turns out to be hopeless, but Zou gets the blame</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-09 01:15:00" d="2020-06-09 01:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou wants a pet. He ends up with an army of ants but they cause chaos in the house. Fortunately Poc comes to the rescue. Zou realises he already has a great pet - Poc!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-09 01:30:00" d="2020-06-09 01:55:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry and Denzel are coaching their Grandmonsters for the Iron Granny competition. Grando lends Henry a Monster Coin that spins on its own, but it spins away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-09 01:55:00" d="2020-06-09 02:20:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry’s friend Roddy arrives for a play date, but bad boy Roddy comes too. When he rips Summer’s autographed pic of Isabella, Henry dresses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-09 02:20:00" d="2020-06-09 02:30:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia invite Bigfoot to sleep over. But Stan is terrified of Bigfoot’s clown cuddly toy! Bigfoot won’t sleep without it, so the evening could be cancelled. (S1 Ep16c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-09 02:30:00" d="2020-06-09 02:40:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Olivia gets ready to go to her Collectors' Club Meeting. Stan would love to go along and be part of the club too, but he doesn’t have a collection. (S1 Ep17a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-09 02:40:00" d="2020-06-09 02:55:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The youngsters must decide which gymnastic activity to do. Zou fancies Slacklining but he needs three companions. Zinnia’s not keen. Zou learns she’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-09 02:55:00" d="2020-06-09 03:10:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It's the lollipop lady's birthday. She’d like a trip around the world - but that’s too expensive, so Zou looks for something cheaper that’s just as good</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-09 03:10:00" d="2020-06-09 03:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou’s invited to join Zinnia and her parents on a trip to visit the beach and have a swim. He’s strangely reluctant until Grandpa realises Zou can’t</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-09 03:25:00" d="2020-06-09 03:35:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia decide to clean up their room, but they need to come up with a method that works. (S1 Ep2b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-09 03:35:00" d="2020-06-09 03:45:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Time for Puff’s nap: the twins offer help her get to sleep, instead of Sheriff Pearl. It’s harder than they expect! (S1 Ep2c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-09 03:45:00" d="2020-06-09 03:55:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Captain Stan has to come up with an idea in order to get Olivia free. (S1 Ep12b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-09 03:55:00" d="2020-06-09 04:10:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry's scout troop, The Roarers, competes against its rivals on Scouts’ Game Day.(S2 Ep4b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-09 04:10:00" d="2020-06-09 04:35:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus (4)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-09 04:35:00" d="2020-06-09 05:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu makes Archie a pair of wings to help him fly. Marsh copies Rocky's every move while Rocky copies Giganto</k>  </p>
</a>
