<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="60" t="2020-05-31 04:32:52"><p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 05:00:00" d="2020-06-07 05:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Catboy is turned into a cat by Romeo. Gekko needs Catboy and Owlette's help to fight a Roboctopus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 05:25:00" d="2020-06-07 05:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks Music Video">PJ Masks Music Video I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s time for teamwork! Music accompanies clips from the popular show featuring pyjama-clad heroes Catboy, Gekko and Owlette, who have adventures, solve</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 05:30:00" d="2020-06-07 05:55:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% After their powers are stolen and given to the Woflies, the PJ Masks ally with them to vanquish Romeo. Night Ninja hypnotizes all of the school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 05:55:00" d="2020-06-07 06:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Minnie, Daisy, and Cuckoo-Loca are having fun in the park with their pups, until the dogs escape from their leashes. Minnie finds a fun way to control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 06:00:00" d="2020-06-07 06:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% The Guard rescues a baby baboon. They want to return it to its family but must also rescue Tiifu and Zuri who are trapped on a rapidly eroding island</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 06:30:00" d="2020-06-07 07:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse (79)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Mickey and the gang look at various ways of getting fit, and help motivate Pete to exercise. He also learns about the importance of drinking water while exercising. (S3 E14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 07:00:00" d="2020-06-07 07:30:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The family celebrates Mummy's Day and gives Oxana a day off. Will Vee's Dance-lvania party be spoiled by a zombie guest?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 07:30:00" d="2020-06-07 07:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>With Bluey as his taxi driver, Dad’s got no chance of making it the airport on time!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 07:40:00" d="2020-06-07 07:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Mum takes a walk along the beach, Bluey follows behind on her first solo adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 07:50:00" d="2020-06-07 08:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s adventure on the high seas as Bluey and Bingo play Pirates on the hammock swing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 08:00:00" d="2020-06-07 08:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Catboy has to get Amaya’s and Greg’s stolen superhero pyjamas back from Romeo! Owlette’s prized Giving Owl statue is stolen by Luna Girl to decorate her new headquarters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 08:30:00" d="2020-06-07 09:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A delivery crate containing a baby octopus springs a leak. Pip and Freddy deliver a mysterious striped animal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 09:00:00" d="2020-06-07 09:30:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% Elena is torn between a promise she made to help Isabel and fulfilling her royal duties as crown princess. George Takei (Star Trek) guest stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 09:30:00" d="2020-06-07 10:00:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Disney princess Mulan arrives to help Sofia, Amber and Princess Jun work together to rescue their fathers and brothers who are trapped in a jaguar's den</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 10:00:00" d="2020-06-07 10:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A special winner gets mixed-up for the day. When Clarabelle ends up with the hidden royal sceptre, everyone thinks she's the new princess</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 10:30:00" d="2020-06-07 11:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Armadylan and sidekick Robette fight with Romeo to determine whose sidekick is better. After Armadylan loses his temper again, the PJ Masks take him on a zen trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 11:00:00" d="2020-06-07 12:00:00"><n>The Lion Guard: Return of the Roar</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In this enchanting Lion King spin-off, Simba and Nala’s cub Kion becomes leader of the Lion Guard, a team of animals comprising the Pride Lands’ fiercest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 12:00:00" d="2020-06-07 12:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% Ono grudgingly hatches and fosters a cuckoo egg left in his nest, then joins forces with the cuckoo mom when the baby is captured by vultures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 12:30:00" d="2020-06-07 13:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% The Lion Guard must work together to chase away a baboon comedy troupe that has been distracting the other animals with their antics and stealing their food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 13:00:00" d="2020-06-07 13:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% When a raucous bachelor herd moves in next to Rafiki, the Guard tries to help find new homes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 13:30:00" d="2020-06-07 14:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% An infestation of tsetse flies forces the Lion Guard to bring Thurston the Zebra with them on a mission to rescue Jasiri and two hyena cubs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 14:00:00" d="2020-06-07 14:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% A ferocious monitor lizard named Kenge bites some of the members of the Lion Guard, temporarily paralyzing them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 14:30:00" d="2020-06-07 15:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% Zazu is taken by the hyenas, and the Guard must rescue him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 15:00:00" d="2020-06-07 15:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy's attempts to give Mom a perfect spa day go wrong. Nancy becomes Dad's assistant and causes an office disaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 15:30:00" d="2020-06-07 16:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rocky gets jealous when Tiny suddenly becomes the go-to hero! Mazu may be a slow runner but is a quick thinker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 16:00:00" d="2020-06-07 16:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>With Bluey as his taxi driver, Dad’s got no chance of making it the airport on time!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 16:10:00" d="2020-06-07 16:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Mum takes a walk along the beach, Bluey follows behind on her first solo adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 16:20:00" d="2020-06-07 16:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s adventure on the high seas as Bluey and Bingo play Pirates on the hammock swing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 16:30:00" d="2020-06-07 17:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mickey and pals travel to New Delhi for a wedding and help with the ceremony. The Happy Helpers assist wiith a Tuk-Tuk business</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 17:00:00" d="2020-06-07 17:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip and Freddy deliver a baby penguin to Pip's home town. When Pip and Freddy break the conveyor belt at T.O.T.S. they are determined to fix it on their own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 17:30:00" d="2020-06-07 18:30:00"><n>Lion Guard: Rise of Scar</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Guard meets Rafiki's new apprentice, Moniki. Meanwhile Ushari conspires with the hyenas to seek the help of the Pride Lands' greatest villain, Scar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 18:30:00" d="2020-06-07 19:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% PJ Masks meet Armadylan and learn he's not what he seems. Courtesy of Romeo’s ray, Owlette becomes invisible</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 19:00:00" d="2020-06-07 19:30:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First II (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Sofia visits Mystic Meadows, a retirement home for sorcerers. Can she help Cedric reconcile with his father so the old wizard will hand down the powerful family wand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 19:30:00" d="2020-06-07 20:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor (6)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 20:00:00" d="2020-06-07 20:30:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vampirina decides to run for class president. Poppy wants a pet bunny, but first she has to show her mum she's ready to have a pet by looking after Wolfie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 20:30:00" d="2020-06-07 21:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo turns people into babies. Gekko babysits his mates. Owlette must get back Luna Girl’s board and magnet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 21:00:00" d="2020-06-07 21:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Catboy hears of a way to increase his cat power. A Romeo remote makes Catboy's night last forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 21:30:00" d="2020-06-07 22:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The friends help when Bob can't go to the parade. The pugs head to England to see how to treat a queen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 22:00:00" d="2020-06-07 22:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A Pyramid Scheme/Special Delivery: Bongo and Rolly travel to Egypt to find the Great Pyramids. The pugs try to deliver a Mother's Day card for Bob</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 22:30:00" d="2020-06-07 23:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu and her three besties map the stars. Tiny’s artistic skills are put to use when the dinos are lost in the desert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 23:00:00" d="2020-06-07 23:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Tiny and Mazu treat Giganto's toothache. Every dino in Cretacia tries to claim a beautiful pebble!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-07 23:30:00" d="2020-06-08 00:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (2)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 00:00:00" d="2020-06-08 00:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (2)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 00:25:00" d="2020-06-08 00:50:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (3)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 00:50:00" d="2020-06-08 01:00:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Both Olivia and Stan realize that Stan can’t keep a secret. Olivia offers to help her brother, and gives him advice. (S1 Ep3b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 01:00:00" d="2020-06-08 01:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou and his grandfather spend the day tracking mysterious footprints in the snow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 01:15:00" d="2020-06-08 01:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou decides he wants to be King of the Household, but when he finds out all the work it entails he decides it might be better if Mum and Dad were King and Queen instead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 01:30:00" d="2020-06-08 01:55:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Geri Halliwell stars in this episode in which Summer auditions to sing with her idol Isabella Roarson. Henry keeps a tiny hugglefish as a pet, but it grows huge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 01:55:00" d="2020-06-08 02:20:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry helps Summer make a film to represent their roarsome family. Henry helps at the Cafe when Signor Roartonio's assistant is ill on Monster Pizza Day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 02:20:00" d="2020-06-08 02:30:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan has promised to help his friends but gets stuck in a traffic jam with his pedal car. Olivia says she can replace him, and do everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 02:30:00" d="2020-06-08 02:40:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia learn that repeating something you hear is tattling. When Podium gets stuck in a tree, they hesitate: would it be tattling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 02:40:00" d="2020-06-08 02:55:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The sports sessions have been muddled up. Zou and Zak’s tennis has been double booked with Elzee’s and Zinnia’s ballet so the world’s first ballet/tennis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 02:55:00" d="2020-06-08 03:10:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou enters a sandcastle competition. His parents help but get too competitive, with disastrous results</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 03:10:00" d="2020-06-08 03:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou decides to become a record breaker but his attempts are in vain – until he discovers that he already holds a record, he is the little zebra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 03:25:00" d="2020-06-08 03:35:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The twins make up a lovely song for Podium, but they just can’t remember the words (S1 Ep1c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 03:35:00" d="2020-06-08 03:45:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia try to take good care of Puff’s silly hat, but they end up losing it. They realize that taking care of things isn’t always easy. (S1 Ep2a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 03:45:00" d="2020-06-08 03:55:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan wants to give Bigfoot a present, but the twins can’t help doing everything together. How can he find a way to make his present by himself? (S1 Ep12a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 03:55:00" d="2020-06-08 04:10:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>To help the Roarsville grandmonsters create a knitted playground, Henry and Cobby invent a Knit-O-Bot robot.(S2 Ep4a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 04:10:00" d="2020-06-08 04:35:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ayati falls over. Mazu must come up with an idea to help. A crevice rips through the ground and traps four little dinos in Giganto's path</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-06-08 04:35:00" d="2020-06-08 05:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Timid Bill and brave Rocky end up stranded on an island, however Rocky suddenly becomes the scared one! Trey warns the little dinos about a cave monster</k>  </p>
</a>
