<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="70" t="2020-04-15 04:30:28"><p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 05:00:00" d="2020-04-22 05:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% &quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 05:25:00" d="2020-04-22 05:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Because they are arguing on which of them has to clean the streets, the PJ Masks don't notice Romeo is attacking them in the rear and learn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 05:30:00" d="2020-04-22 05:55:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% When the Wolfies steal a local dog, the PJ Masks must try to get it back! The PJ Masks team up with Night Ninja to stop the Wolfies from destroying Mystery Mountain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 05:55:00" d="2020-04-22 06:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons III (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Daisy’s made a mess of the apartment and Minnie is on her way home a day early from a trip. With Cuckoo-Loca’s help, and a few short cuts, Minnie races</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 06:00:00" d="2020-04-22 06:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% A ferocious monitor lizard named Kenge bites some of the members of the Lion Guard, temporarily paralyzing them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 06:30:00" d="2020-04-22 07:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It's Mini-Mechanics Day and Mickey's number one fan can't wait to get to work! The Happy Helpers are busy pet-sitting while everyone heads to the Fancy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 07:00:00" d="2020-04-22 07:30:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vee and her family go on a camping trip. A monster gets lost on his way to the Scare B&amp;B and ends up at the wrong house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 07:30:00" d="2020-04-22 07:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>With Bluey as his taxi driver, Dad’s got no chance of making it the airport on time!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 07:40:00" d="2020-04-22 07:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Mum takes a walk along the beach, Bluey follows behind on her first solo adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 07:50:00" d="2020-04-22 08:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s adventure on the high seas as Bluey and Bingo play Pirates on the hammock swing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 08:00:00" d="2020-04-22 08:30:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First III (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Sofia, Amber and James head off to summer camp. James gets homesick, so he uses a boat race to hatch a plan to escape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 08:30:00" d="2020-04-22 09:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% After Shuriki attacks Elena on the West Coast of Avalor, Elena tries to forge an alliance with the underwater creatures, Sirenas, in order to defeat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 09:00:00" d="2020-04-22 09:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo and Bluey can’t agree on one simple question: Can Grannies do the floss dance?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 09:10:00" d="2020-04-22 09:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A trip to the local creek opens Bluey’s eyes to the simple beauty of nature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 09:20:00" d="2020-04-22 09:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey has to appease invisible mischief-making fairies, who have infested the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 09:30:00" d="2020-04-22 09:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In a game of Work, Bluey and Bingo are the latest hires at Dad’s drainpipe factory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 09:40:00" d="2020-04-22 09:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey sends a video to Bingo in hospital to show her that everyone gets sick sometimes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 09:50:00" d="2020-04-22 10:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dad can’t go to work until he has played all of Bluey and Bingo’s trampoline games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 10:00:00" d="2020-04-22 11:00:00"><n u="Pets">Pets I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>80% This extra-long adventure features four stories involving some of the pets and animals in this series, including Romeo’s robot Robette and his Roboctopus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 11:00:00" d="2020-04-22 11:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After KC gets sick, Pip and Freddy try to watch the babies in the Nursery for her. When delivery batches of bunnies get mixed up, the Junior Fliers figure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 11:30:00" d="2020-04-22 11:55:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A delivery crate containing a baby octopus springs a leak. Pip and Freddy deliver a mysterious striped animal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 11:55:00" d="2020-04-22 12:00:00"><n u="Marvel Super Hero Adventures">Marvel Super Hero Adventures I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After a battle with Doc Ock, Spidey and Miles Morales scare a cat named Mittens, sending her scampering into the city. Our heroes try to catch the runaway feline</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 12:00:00" d="2020-04-22 12:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (6)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 12:30:00" d="2020-04-22 13:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo steals Gekko’s voice, but Gekko’s not sure he wants it back before his poetry presentation. Night Ninja has stolen Master Fang’s prized sword!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 13:00:00" d="2020-04-22 13:30:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% Elena and her grandfather team up to complete a mission he started many years ago</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 13:30:00" d="2020-04-22 14:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip and Freddy deliver a baby penguin to Pip's home town. When Pip and Freddy break the conveyor belt at T.O.T.S. they are determined to fix it on their own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 14:00:00" d="2020-04-22 14:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mia loses Lovey, so Pip and Freddy go on a wild chase to find it. But are they too late? The Fliers' delivery is in jeopardy when their puppy student</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 14:30:00" d="2020-04-22 15:00:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% When Stuffy wants to join the First Responders after seeing them save the day, Doc suggests they start a rescue team to save pets while the First Responders are busy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 15:00:00" d="2020-04-22 15:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% After Chilly accidentally blasts off on Luna's rocket to an unexplored planet, it's up to Doc and her friends to bring him and Luna's robot dog back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 15:30:00" d="2020-04-22 16:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% Elena and her grandfather team up to complete a mission he started many years ago</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 16:00:00" d="2020-04-22 16:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Indy and Rusty play a game of Mums and Dads, they can’t agree on who goes to work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 16:10:00" d="2020-04-22 16:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey needs to stay focused and not get distracted, during a family game of hide and seek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 16:20:00" d="2020-04-22 16:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While camping in the bush, Bluey makes a new friend who doesn't speak the same language</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 16:30:00" d="2020-04-22 17:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Freddy has to scare Pip. Pip and Freddy race a drone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 17:00:00" d="2020-04-22 17:15:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When a neighborhood climibng tree is declared off-limits, Nancy shows her friends how to stand up for they believe in. (S1 Ep14a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 17:15:00" d="2020-04-22 17:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy dreams of becoming a synchronized swimmer, but first must overcome her fear of going underwater. (S1 Ep14b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 17:30:00" d="2020-04-22 18:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A family of mariachi skeletons have been caught in a storm and need a room at the B&amp;B! Chef Remy bakes Crystal Ball cupcakes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 18:00:00" d="2020-04-22 18:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Ninja uses Armadylan's dream of becoming a kung fu movie star to break into a museum. While Gekko and Armadylan guard the city, their watch turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 18:30:00" d="2020-04-22 19:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% The Guard’s ability to find the Tree of Life disappears when Makini’s staff is stolen by a scheming Binturong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 19:00:00" d="2020-04-22 19:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First III (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Sofia returns to the underwater kingdom of Merroway Cove where she is reunited with mermaid friend Oona and meets new mer-boy Fluke. Trying to impress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 19:25:00" d="2020-04-22 19:30:00"><n u="Music Lullabies">Music Lullabies I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fancy Nancy is helping her little sister, JoJo, get ready for bed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 19:30:00" d="2020-04-22 19:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Indy and Rusty play a game of Mums and Dads, they can’t agree on who goes to work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 19:40:00" d="2020-04-22 19:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey needs to stay focused and not get distracted, during a family game of hide and seek</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 19:50:00" d="2020-04-22 20:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While camping in the bush, Bluey makes a new friend who doesn't speak the same language</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 20:00:00" d="2020-04-22 20:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mickey, Donald, Goofy, Minnie and Daisy run a garage in Hot Dog Hills and compete with their transforming roadsters in races around the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 20:30:00" d="2020-04-22 21:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% Elena and her grandfather team up to complete a mission he started many years ago</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 21:00:00" d="2020-04-22 21:15:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy dreams of giving Mom a perfect spa day, but things go wrong when her homemade spa products are mistaken for snacks. (S1 Ep3a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 21:15:00" d="2020-04-22 21:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Dad works from home, Nancy becomes his assistant and accidentally creates an office disaster. (S1 Ep3b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 21:30:00" d="2020-04-22 22:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A family of mariachi skeletons have been caught in a storm and need a room at the B&amp;B! Chef Remy bakes Crystal Ball cupcakes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 22:00:00" d="2020-04-22 22:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Ninja uses Armadylan's dream of becoming a kung fu movie star to break into a museum. While Gekko and Armadylan guard the city, their watch turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 22:30:00" d="2020-04-22 23:00:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% The Guard’s ability to find the Tree of Life disappears when Makini’s staff is stolen by a scheming Binturong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 23:00:00" d="2020-04-22 23:25:00"><n u="Sofia The First">Sofia The First III (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Sofia returns to the underwater kingdom of Merroway Cove where she is reunited with mermaid friend Oona and meets new mer-boy Fluke. Trying to impress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 23:25:00" d="2020-04-22 23:30:00"><n u="Music Lullabies">Music Lullabies I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fancy Nancy is helping her little sister, JoJo, get ready for bed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-22 23:30:00" d="2020-04-23 00:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus (16)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 00:00:00" d="2020-04-23 00:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (6)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 00:30:00" d="2020-04-23 01:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks III (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Luna Girl steals the moon crystal to power up her Luna Fortress’ Mega-Magnet, which creates a portal that pulls stuff up from the city. The PJ Masks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 01:00:00" d="2020-04-23 01:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou’s invited to join Zinnia and her parents on a trip to visit the beach and have a swim. He’s strangely reluctant until Grandpa realises Zou can’t</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 01:15:00" d="2020-04-23 01:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou learns he has to be patient when he has to wait an hour for Elzee to come over and he keeps watching the clock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 01:30:00" d="2020-04-23 02:00:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Sneezo sneezes so hard she blows away. They chase her on Henry’s bike. Henry’s unhappy he and Summer are team co-captains for the Huggleball game against the parents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 02:00:00" d="2020-04-23 02:30:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry’s organising Roarsville’s big wedding and asks Summer to be the flower monster. Henry and Denzel decide to start a boy band</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 02:30:00" d="2020-04-23 02:40:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (62)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia don’t want anyone to wake up Magma during his nap. They keep watch so that none of their friends make any noise. (S1 Ep21b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 02:40:00" d="2020-04-23 02:55:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou is disappointed when the local pantomime is cancelled, so decides to stage his own. On the day of the performance Zou gets stage fright</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 02:55:00" d="2020-04-23 03:10:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou must bake a cake for the sale so he can go on a school trip. Mum is away, and Grandpa and Dad end up making pancakes. Happily, Mum gets back in time to help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 03:10:00" d="2020-04-23 03:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Nanna gets her piano back after lending it for the disco, it isn’t playing properly. Zavier has lost his shop keys – could this have anything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 03:25:00" d="2020-04-23 03:35:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan and Olivia set up a surprise party for Bigfoot. But it’s awfully hard for them to wait until their friend gets back. (S1 Ep6c)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 03:35:00" d="2020-04-23 03:45:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Olivia paints Stan’s portrait, but Podium doesn’t think it’s good. livia is vexed, and tries to improve the portrait without understanding what’s wrong. (S1 Ep7a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 03:45:00" d="2020-04-23 03:55:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The twins decide there should be a secret code to get into the playhouse, but Olivia forgets it straight off. Now she can’t even play with her brother. (S1 Ep6b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 03:55:00" d="2020-04-23 04:10:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After losing his voice while practicing for the Loudest Roar in the Roar-Off competition, Henry figures out a way still to participate. (S1 Ep5b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 04:10:00" d="2020-04-23 04:35:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Tiny and Mazu treat Giganto's toothache. Every dino in Cretacia tries to claim a beautiful pebble!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2020-04-23 04:35:00" d="2020-04-23 05:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rocky gets jealous when Tiny suddenly becomes the go-to hero! Mazu may be a slow runner but is a quick thinker</k>  </p>
</a>
