<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="75" t="2021-07-13 04:57:58"><p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 05:00:00" d="2021-07-20 05:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rocky has to get nectar from a special flower to get his Giganto cards back from the raptors. Tiny and Bill accidentally clog up Cretacia's water source</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 05:30:00" d="2021-07-20 05:45:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus S2 Splits">Gigantosaurus S2 Splits II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Tiny gets Giganto to join her and her besties in activities together to show how much they care</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 05:45:00" d="2021-07-20 06:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus S2 Splits">Gigantosaurus S2 Splits II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Trey and Hegen start a dino protection service, Guardians of the Herds!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 06:00:00" d="2021-07-20 06:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A quick trip to the shops proves tricky for Dad, when Bingo and Bluey want to play a game of ‘Kids’. Now Bluey is Mum, Bingo’s her baby and Dad is a very naughty boy!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 06:10:00" d="2021-07-20 06:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s bedtime and Bingo can’t remember where she left her beloved Floppy! Retracing their steps, Bingo and Bluey lead Mum through their bizzare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 06:20:00" d="2021-07-20 06:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey needs Mum’s advice on dealing with a troublesome neighbour, when the serenity of her couch cushion playhouse is threatened by Bingo’s growing stable of animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 06:30:00" d="2021-07-20 06:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey, Bingo and Mum get into a debate with Dad about the definition of teasing. As they recall all the times he’s been a &quot;Big Teaser&quot;, Dad argues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 06:40:00" d="2021-07-20 06:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dad tells Bluey to mind her manners at the table - they’re not animals! But when Bluey gets her hands on a stick of magic asparagus, she shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 06:50:00" d="2021-07-20 07:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey and Bingo want a pet! To show them how much work they’d be in for, Dad transforms his hand into their old friend Shaun, a chaotic, undisciplined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 07:00:00" d="2021-07-20 07:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (53)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The gang transforms their roadsters into their favorite animals for the Safari Park race! When Lazlo, Commander Heist's cat, runs away, the Happy Helpers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 07:30:00" d="2021-07-20 08:00:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins Toy Hospital">Doc McStuffins Toy Hospital IV (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A tin toy mole keeps bumping into things and getting dented. Squibbles gets scared and runs amok through McStuffinsville</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 08:00:00" d="2021-07-20 08:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (129)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Hallie switches places with her lookalike, the famous Hallie the Entertainer! She learns firsthand what it's like to be a star and what happens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 08:30:00" d="2021-07-20 08:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Mum goes out to a baby shower, Dad takes charge of the girls’ evening routine. But with Bluey missing Mum, Dad has to pull out all the games he knows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 08:40:00" d="2021-07-20 08:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s Christmas and Bluey is very focused on being good to get more presents. But when a game of Verandah Santa leaves cousin Socks upset, Bluey must learn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 08:50:00" d="2021-07-20 09:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (53)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Chilli and Bandit are keen to get a new pizza oven like their neighbours’ so they all go on a trip to Hammerbarn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 09:00:00" d="2021-07-20 09:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo steals Gekko’s voice, but Gekko’s not sure he wants it back before his poetry presentation. Night Ninja has stolen Master Fang’s prized sword!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 09:30:00" d="2021-07-20 10:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (89)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Cat Boy enlists Munki-Gu to go aboard the Flying Factory to distract Romeo. Kevin doesn’t think he’ll ever be top dog; he's not wolfy enough to find the legendary bone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 10:00:00" d="2021-07-20 10:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (54)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When a passing cockatoo drops a feather, Bingo has an idea for a new game. By waving her featherwand she can make objects impossibly heavy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 10:10:00" d="2021-07-20 10:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (55)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dad eats Bingo's last chip and as payback, Bingo has three 'dance mode' wishes to use at will</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 10:20:00" d="2021-07-20 10:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (56)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Uncle Stripe and Bandit are playing squash with the help of their controllers, Bingo and Bluey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 10:30:00" d="2021-07-20 11:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (78)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Goofy's &quot;birdy call&quot; works a little too well when dozens of Canada Geese descend upon Hot Dog Hills! Billy Beagle struggles with the difference of inside and outside voices</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 11:00:00" d="2021-07-20 11:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (130)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Doc and friends venture deep into the jungle to find a bedazzling jewel that will help the Duchess of Dazzle regain her strength</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 11:30:00" d="2021-07-20 12:00:00"><n u="Mira, Royal Detective">Mira, Royal Detective I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mira and her friends find a treasure map that leads to the mysterious tunnels under the palace. A mystery polo player appears while Mira and her team are playing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 12:00:00" d="2021-07-20 12:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (57)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey and Bingo spend the day at Nana's along with their cousins!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 12:10:00" d="2021-07-20 12:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (58)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo has to play at home without her sister and she’s having trouble getting started</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 12:20:00" d="2021-07-20 12:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (59)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Heelers take turns remembering their favourite thing from the day at dinnertime, but when Bluey laughs at something her sister said earlier, Bingo’s mood darkens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 12:30:00" d="2021-07-20 13:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% When Edgar crashes the annual Ghoul Guides Extravaganza vamping trip in Transylvania, Vee and the girls must come clean about Vee's family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 13:00:00" d="2021-07-20 13:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. II (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip and Freddy try to get JP into the Halloween spirit! When Gio won’t fit inside the tiny home of his mouse parents, Pip and Freddy build a house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 13:30:00" d="2021-07-20 14:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Catboy has to get Amaya’s and Greg’s stolen superhero pyjamas back from Romeo! Owlette’s prized Giving Owl statue is stolen by Luna Girl to decorate her new headquarters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 14:00:00" d="2021-07-20 14:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus II (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Tiny gets Giganto to join her and her besties in activities together to show how much they care. Trey and Hegen start a dino protection service, Guardians of the Herds!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 14:30:00" d="2021-07-20 14:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey’s backyard zoo is home to wonderful animals, especially the big blue Daddy Gorilla. But when he grabs visitor Bingo and escapes, Zookeeper Bluey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 14:40:00" d="2021-07-20 14:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mum and Dad are going on an adventure wearing the kids as their cheeky backpacks! Seeing the sights and buying street food, backpackings a blast - until</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 14:50:00" d="2021-07-20 15:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Princesses, horses and magic wands. Bluey and Chloe can play any role they want, when they embark on an adventure to save their playground kingdom from the Greedy Queen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 15:00:00" d="2021-07-20 15:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey’s having fun copying everything Dad says and does, but the game takes a serious turn when Bluey finds a hurt budgie and they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 15:10:00" d="2021-07-20 15:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A sleepover with their cousin means Bluey and Bingo get to stay up late! But when Muffin shows up exhausted after missing a nap, the girls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 15:20:00" d="2021-07-20 15:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey’s playgroup is at odds when Indy’s baby hospital collides with Rusty’s knights and dragons. But in explaining themselves, they find the games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 15:30:00" d="2021-07-20 16:00:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy replaces Frenchy with a well-trained but snooty dog. When Marabelle goes missing, Nancy becomes a sleuth to find out who took her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 16:00:00" d="2021-07-20 16:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. II (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After Lucky nearly ruins Totsgiving, Pip, Freddy, and KC set out to save the holiday. Mr. Woodbird always dreamed of making a baby delivery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 16:30:00" d="2021-07-20 17:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. II (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip and Freddy learn that there are no shortcuts to understanding a baby’s true needs. Pip and Freddy show a baby seal how to love the water. little bit at a time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 17:00:00" d="2021-07-20 17:25:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (60)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It's time for the annual Hot Dog Hillympics! As the reigning champ, Mickey is ready to win again, unless Pete has something to do with it! The Happy Helpers coach a baseball team!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 17:25:00" d="2021-07-20 17:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus S1 Shorts">Gigantosaurus S1 Shorts I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bill and Rocky invite the children to guess the mysterious dino: the brachiosaurus, the stegosaurus or the pachycephalosaurus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 17:30:00" d="2021-07-20 17:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey’s backyard zoo is home to wonderful animals, especially the big blue Daddy Gorilla. But when he grabs visitor Bingo and escapes, Zookeeper Bluey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 17:40:00" d="2021-07-20 17:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mum and Dad are going on an adventure wearing the kids as their cheeky backpacks! Seeing the sights and buying street food, backpackings a blast - until</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 17:50:00" d="2021-07-20 18:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Princesses, horses and magic wands. Bluey and Chloe can play any role they want, when they embark on an adventure to save their playground kingdom from the Greedy Queen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 18:00:00" d="2021-07-20 18:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey’s having fun copying everything Dad says and does, but the game takes a serious turn when Bluey finds a hurt budgie and they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 18:10:00" d="2021-07-20 18:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A sleepover with their cousin means Bluey and Bingo get to stay up late! But when Muffin shows up exhausted after missing a nap, the girls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 18:20:00" d="2021-07-20 18:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey’s playgroup is at odds when Indy’s baby hospital collides with Rusty’s knights and dragons. But in explaining themselves, they find the games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 18:30:00" d="2021-07-20 19:00:00"><n u="Mira, Royal Detective">Mira, Royal Detective I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When the royal sword goes missing, Mira agrees to help Veer find it! Mira is tasked with finding the tapestry created by Priya for the town's 400th anniversary party!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 19:00:00" d="2021-07-20 19:30:00"><n u="The Rocketeer">The Rocketeer I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Valerie creates her own superhero identity, the Valkyrie! The Cast-Iron Chef makes another attempt at stealing Kit's family cookbook from the Bulldog Cafe!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 19:30:00" d="2021-07-20 20:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (55)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Bob discovers he lost a library book, the Pugs race out on a mission to get it before it’s due. The Pugs go on a last minute mission for party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 20:00:00" d="2021-07-20 20:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After Rolly chews up Bob's prized boomerang, the pugs head to Australia to find a new one. When Bob brings home a pet fish, the dogs try to play puppy games with it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 20:30:00" d="2021-07-20 21:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (98)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% The PJs need to meditate with great seriousness, but they can’t when Munki-gu gets involved. The PJs try to stop Munki-gu's shenanigans, but get played</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 21:00:00" d="2021-07-20 21:25:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rocky has to get nectar from a special flower to get his Giganto cards back from the raptors. Tiny and Bill accidentally clog up Cretacia's water source</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 21:25:00" d="2021-07-20 21:50:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu invents the world's first go-carts to beat Giganto in a race. When Bill's food stash is raided, he makes it his mission to find the culprit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 21:50:00" d="2021-07-20 22:15:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When everyone blames Giganto for damaging the lake, the Dinos try to prove his innocence. Rocky wants to roar like Giganto, so he sets out to capture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 22:15:00" d="2021-07-20 22:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>As part of a project Zou tries to make a copy of an old puppet belonging to Grandpa. His first attempts don’t work, but eventually they are a success</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 22:30:00" d="2021-07-20 22:45:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou has nothing and no-one to play with, until Mum has a washing machine delivered - in a big cardboard box</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 22:45:00" d="2021-07-20 23:00:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou and his friends are having an art class at the beach. Zou is being constantly harassed by a hungry magpie and decides to paint it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 23:00:00" d="2021-07-20 23:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Poc is unwell and Zou needs to be immunised so they both need to go to see the doctor. They hide, but when they do go it's not as bad as they had feared</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 23:15:00" d="2021-07-20 23:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While clearing out old toys Zou finds his teething ring, which Mum has kept. At first he hides it from people, but then keeps it to show how grown up he is now</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 23:25:00" d="2021-07-20 23:50:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Cobby’s model spaceship flies away and Henry rescues it. Henry loses his voice while practising for the loudest roar contest but still helps by running the Roar-o-Meter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 23:50:00" d="2021-07-21 00:15:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Summer is upset when Beckett can’t come camping, so Henry cheers her up. Beckett’s noisy birthday party upsets a new-born baby bird, so they have a quiet joint party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-21 00:15:00" d="2021-07-21 00:40:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry organises a spectacular finale for Summer’s show, to make up for letting her down. Cobby invents The Hugglebike to get the family to the fireworks display</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-21 00:40:00" d="2021-07-21 01:05:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Geri Halliwell stars in this episode in which Summer auditions to sing with her idol Isabella Roarson. Henry keeps a tiny hugglefish as a pet, but it grows huge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-21 01:05:00" d="2021-07-21 01:30:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Olivia stands in for Stan. The twins don’t want to be tattlers. Stan is scared of Bigfoot’s cuddly toy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-21 01:30:00" d="2021-07-21 01:55:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan wants to be in Olivia’s secret Collectors’ Club. The twins are impatient for Bigfoot to open his letter. The twins play Toy Hospital</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-21 01:55:00" d="2021-07-21 02:20:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When everyone blames Giganto for damaging the lake, the Dinos try to prove his innocence. Rocky wants to roar like Giganto, so he sets out to capture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-21 02:20:00" d="2021-07-21 02:45:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Turf rights to the playground are at stake when the raptors challenge the four Dinos to a game of basketball. Rocky tries to convince everyone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-21 02:45:00" d="2021-07-21 03:10:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mama is to be Roarsville's official music maker so everyone must help at home. Henry thinks Denzel is moving away so plans a party for his best friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-21 03:10:00" d="2021-07-21 03:35:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry plans Ivor's first birthday party then realises it’s what he, not Ivor, would like. It's Spring Cleaning Day and there are lots of bubbles!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-21 03:35:00" d="2021-07-21 04:00:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry works at the radio station and upsets people when he tells their secrets. Henry’s upset when Ivor starts day care so breaks in to get him! ( S2 Ep22)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-21 04:00:00" d="2021-07-21 04:25:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse II (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% At Mickey Mouse Clubhouse the fun never stops! Come along while Minnie plans a picnic, Daisy takes care of new pets, and Professor Von Drake’s latest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-21 04:25:00" d="2021-07-21 04:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Hot Diggity-Dog Tales">Mickey Mouse Hot Diggity-Dog Tales I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>‘Tis the season for Christmas rivalry when Mickey and Pete get into a holiday decorations battle of lights! May the best bulbs win</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-21 04:30:00" d="2021-07-21 04:55:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse II (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% At Mickey Mouse Clubhouse the fun never stops! Come along while Minnie plans a picnic, Daisy takes care of new pets, and Professor Von Drake’s latest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-21 04:55:00" d="2021-07-21 05:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons II (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Minnie and Daisy are locked out of the Bow-tique. They try to get the key under the door so they can unlock it. Then a customer comes in, and walks</k>  </p>
</a>
