<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="74" t="2021-07-09 06:46:52"><p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 05:00:00" d="2021-07-16 05:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu makes Archie a pair of wings to help him fly. Marsh copies Rocky's every move while Rocky copies Giganto</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 05:30:00" d="2021-07-16 06:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Four young dinosaurs explore a prehistoric world of adventure where the most exciting mystery of all is Gigantosaurus, the biggest and fiercest dinosaur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 06:00:00" d="2021-07-16 06:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey, Bingo and Mum are enjoying playing Keepy-Uppy around the house with their last balloon, when Dad joins in and the game becomes the ultimate test of skill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 06:10:00" d="2021-07-16 06:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey and Bingo don’t want to tidy the playroom, so they get Daddy Robot to do it for them. But when Bluey takes things too far, Daddy Robot malfunctions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 06:20:00" d="2021-07-16 06:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>On a picnic in the park, Bluey and her friends play Shadowlands. But when Coco keeps taking shortcuts, Bluey has to show her that following the rules</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 06:30:00" d="2021-07-16 06:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>At the weekend, Bluey and Bingo are playing in the garden with Dad. But Bingo gets upset, when she discovers a walking leaf insect and Dad is too caught</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 06:40:00" d="2021-07-16 06:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s lunchtime on Blueys back deck! But every BBQ needs a side salad, so Bingo’s relaxing sit-down will have to wait until she finds every colour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 06:50:00" d="2021-07-16 07:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Not wanting to go to bed, Bluey tries to dream about being a nocturnal fruit bat so she can stay up all night long and soon finds herself flying through the night sky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 07:00:00" d="2021-07-16 07:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (78)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Goofy's &quot;birdy call&quot; works a little too well when dozens of Canada Geese descend upon Hot Dog Hills! Billy Beagle struggles with the difference of inside and outside voices</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 07:30:00" d="2021-07-16 08:00:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (129)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Hallie switches places with her lookalike, the famous Hallie the Entertainer! She learns firsthand what it's like to be a star and what happens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 08:00:00" d="2021-07-16 08:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (126)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% After making a big mistake at the McStuffinsville Toy Hospital, Doc begins to wonder if her patients would have been better off if she hadn't been there at all</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 08:30:00" d="2021-07-16 08:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Bluey forgets to put her favourite toy away, cousin Socks grabs it and won’t let go! The kids stage a horsey wedding to distract</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 08:40:00" d="2021-07-16 08:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dad gets embroiled in a game of 'Hotel', where Bluey and Bingo run a crazy hotel and Dad is the beleaguered guest. But when Bluey starts to control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 08:50:00" d="2021-07-16 09:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>At the park, Bluey is struggling to learn how to ride her bike. But as she and Dad watch her friends determination with their own tasks, Bluey is inspired</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 09:00:00" d="2021-07-16 09:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% When the new Fairground Flyer Train goes missing, Owlette is determined to get it back. Catboy must save the summer from Luna Girl, but to do so he’ll</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 09:30:00" d="2021-07-16 10:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (87)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Newton thinks Owlette stole a precious asteroid – but she’s been framed by Romeo. Romeo needs the PJs' help bringing his Flying Factory under control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 10:00:00" d="2021-07-16 10:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When it’s Bingo’s turn to bring her Kindy’s Bob Bilby puppet home and record their weekend in the scrapbook, the family resolve to put down their screens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 10:10:00" d="2021-07-16 10:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Bingo stops playing Bluey’s spy game in the park, their device to control the grownups stops working properly! Bluey now sees how important Bingo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 10:20:00" d="2021-07-16 10:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Forced to wait five minutes in front of a restaurant for their takeaway order, Bluey and Bingo become restless for entertainment, pushing the very limits of Dad’s patience</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 10:30:00" d="2021-07-16 11:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (76)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Who will be the winner of the prize to prove the legendary, Scronchasaur exists in Hot Dog Hills Lake? Daisy believes her GramQuacker Lily is living</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 11:00:00" d="2021-07-16 11:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (129)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Hallie switches places with her lookalike, the famous Hallie the Entertainer! She learns firsthand what it's like to be a star and what happens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 11:30:00" d="2021-07-16 12:00:00"><n u="Mira, Royal Detective">Mira, Royal Detective I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mira must track down the oil used to light lamps throughout the town. Mira investigates sightings of a legendary gator who is known to be a mischievous shoe thief</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 12:00:00" d="2021-07-16 12:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Playing ‘Butterflies’ in the backyard is great fun, until Bluey runs away with Judo leaving Bingo all alone. Now poor Bingo’s heartbroken and Bluey needs to make amends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 12:10:00" d="2021-07-16 12:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo loves horsing around with Dad, but sometimes he forgets Bingo is smaller than her sister. Mum teaches Bingo how to use her big</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 12:20:00" d="2021-07-16 12:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>At school, Bluey and her friends throw themselves into various games. Teacher Calypso keeps her charges on track with a wise word and a song</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 12:30:00" d="2021-07-16 13:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% When Remy says, &quot;Au Revoir&quot; to the Hauntley's to chase his dream as a chef at a fancy restaurant, a spookghetti monster pops up! Oxana adds a spooky flair to the school fair</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 13:00:00" d="2021-07-16 13:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip the Penguin and Freddy the Flamingo are Junior Fliers at T.O.T.S., (the Tiny Ones Transport Service), where they’re tasked with delivering baby animals to their parents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 13:30:00" d="2021-07-16 14:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo erases stories from books, so Owlette enlists the help of Flossy Flash. Romeo uses boxing gloves to steal a jetpack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 14:00:00" d="2021-07-16 14:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Four young dinosaurs explore a prehistoric world of adventure where the most exciting mystery of all is Gigantosaurus, the biggest and fiercest dinosaur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 14:30:00" d="2021-07-16 14:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Playing ‘Shops’ is the best game ever for Bluey and her friends - if they can ever get started! With Bluey questioning the rules and changing who’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 14:40:00" d="2021-07-16 14:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey can’t wait to get to the monkey bars as Dad takes her and Bingo on a wagon ride to the park. But her patience is tested when Dad keeps stopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 14:50:00" d="2021-07-16 15:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey is running a taxi service. Her first passenger is Businessman Dad, who is in a rush to get to the airport. But with unexpected delays, Dad’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 15:00:00" d="2021-07-16 15:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>As Mum goes for a walk along the beach, Bluey runs to catch up with her. Along the way, she has a series of encounters that both excite and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 15:10:00" d="2021-07-16 15:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s adventure on the high seas as Bluey, Bingo and Missy play Pirates on the hammock swing, but they’ll need to find their courage to withstand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 15:20:00" d="2021-07-16 15:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A game of ‘Grannies’ is fun, until Bingo and Bluey can’t agree on one simple question: Can Grannies do the floss dance? Now they need to video call Nana to get the answer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 15:30:00" d="2021-07-16 16:00:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy learns she must practise to be a great ice skater. Nancy makes a mess painting a portrait. Jo Jo is blamed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 16:00:00" d="2021-07-16 16:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. II (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Freddy can’t fall asleep on their first overnight delivery and worries that he won’t get the rest he needs! Pip and Freddy show Mia the joys of giving away her old toys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 16:30:00" d="2021-07-16 17:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. II (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Professor Peacock's latest invention of robotic loveys cause havoc and threaten the babies’ deliveries! Freddy believes baby Narwhal Nathan is magical!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 17:00:00" d="2021-07-16 17:25:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (58)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A special winner gets mixed-up for the day! When Clarabelle ends up with the hidden royal scepter, everyone in Royalandia thinks she's the new princess!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 17:25:00" d="2021-07-16 17:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus S1 Shorts">Gigantosaurus S1 Shorts I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rocky and Mazu invite the children to guess the mysterious dino: the rugosodon, the ankylosaurus or the dilophosaurus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 17:30:00" d="2021-07-16 17:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>At the park, Bluey is struggling to learn how to ride her bike. But as she and Dad watch her friends determination with their own tasks, Bluey is inspired</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 17:40:00" d="2021-07-16 17:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When it’s Bingo’s turn to bring her Kindy’s Bob Bilby puppet home and record their weekend in the scrapbook, the family resolve to put down their screens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 17:50:00" d="2021-07-16 18:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Bingo stops playing Bluey’s spy game in the park, their device to control the grownups stops working properly! Bluey now sees how important Bingo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 18:00:00" d="2021-07-16 18:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Forced to wait five minutes in front of a restaurant for their takeaway order, Bluey and Bingo become restless for entertainment, pushing the very limits of Dad’s patience</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 18:10:00" d="2021-07-16 18:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Playing ‘Butterflies’ in the backyard is great fun, until Bluey runs away with Judo leaving Bingo all alone. Now poor Bingo’s heartbroken and Bluey needs to make amends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 18:20:00" d="2021-07-16 18:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo loves horsing around with Dad, but sometimes he forgets Bingo is smaller than her sister. Mum teaches Bingo how to use her big</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 18:30:00" d="2021-07-16 19:00:00"><n u="Mira, Royal Detective">Mira, Royal Detective I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mikku and Chikku go undercover as puppets so they can help Mira catch a pickpocket. When a new kid in town is blamed for stealing an earring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 19:00:00" d="2021-07-16 19:30:00"><n u="The Rocketeer">The Rocketeer I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Great Orsino and his travelling carnival show up in Hughesville to steal Kit's rocket-pack.Kit befriends a former pilot and helps her find the courage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 19:30:00" d="2021-07-16 20:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After Cupcake hurts Rufus' feelings, Bingo and Rolly reunite the best friends. Bob forgets his camera on the trolley before his photography class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 20:00:00" d="2021-07-16 20:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The pups split up to go on a gift-giving mission for each other's birthday. When Bob needs to learn how to dance, Bingo and Rolly enlist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 20:30:00" d="2021-07-16 21:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (94)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% — ›żÍ˝± ş±ą · śżÄĂżÍşą ÁŻÇ˝żĹ˝ Äż Ľ±ł˝®Ä· Ä·Â ›żÍ˝± ĂÄ· ¤¬ĆÁż ş±ą '­Çż˝Ä±ą Ä· ˛ż®¸µą± Ä·Â źşÄżĽŔ­»»±. — śżÄĂżÍşą ˝µĹÁą¬¶µą ĚÄ±˝ Ä·Â »­˝µ, ĚÄą µŻ˝±ą &quot;ĽąşÁ®&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 21:00:00" d="2021-07-16 21:25:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Four young dinosaurs explore a prehistoric world of adventure where the most exciting mystery of all is Gigantosaurus, the biggest and fiercest dinosaur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 21:25:00" d="2021-07-16 21:50:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Four young dinosaurs explore a prehistoric world of adventure where the most exciting mystery of all is Gigantosaurus, the biggest and fiercest dinosaur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 21:50:00" d="2021-07-16 22:15:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu makes Archie a pair of wings to help him fly. Marsh copies Rocky's every move while Rocky copies Giganto</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 22:15:00" d="2021-07-16 22:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou must bake a cake for the sale so he can go on a school trip. Mum is away, and Grandpa and Dad end up making pancakes. Happily, Mum gets back in time to help</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 22:30:00" d="2021-07-16 22:45:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After a storm Zou finds lots of wood on the beach. Zigmund and Zoroaster tell him it’s just driftwood, but can be made into a very interesting sculpture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 22:45:00" d="2021-07-16 23:00:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou is doing a project on camouflage. Grandpa teaches him about the different ways animals and insects camouflage themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 23:00:00" d="2021-07-16 23:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou gets a drum kit for his birthday and plays it so loudly he drives everyone crazy. It's up to Nanna to show him that it's not volume that makes a great drummer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 23:15:00" d="2021-07-16 23:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou and Grandma bake a surprise Mother’s Day cake but Dad eats it so Zou makes another without Grandma's help and makes a dreadful mess. Mum ends up coming to the rescue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 23:25:00" d="2021-07-16 23:50:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry reassures Denzel, who’s scared of the spooky Fun House at the Monster Fair. Henry encourages his team when they lose the season’s first games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-16 23:50:00" d="2021-07-17 00:15:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry is in the Roarsville Roar-Plane Race with his hero, Captain Hollander. Henry convinces Daddo to enter the parent and child Monster-a-Muck contest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-17 00:15:00" d="2021-07-17 00:40:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry shows Gertie it’s fun to have new experiences and not plan everything in advance. Henry agrees to practice piano if Momma learns how to skate ( S1 Ep14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-17 00:40:00" d="2021-07-17 01:05:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Trouble erupts at summer camp when the girls get too competitive. There’s a surprise party for Momma’s birthday but an unusual cake threatens to ruin it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-17 01:05:00" d="2021-07-17 01:30:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>No hurdle’s too high for the Paprika twins Olivia and Stan as they turn everyday life into wonderful, colourful adventures!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-17 01:30:00" d="2021-07-17 01:55:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The twins spend the day at Magma’s. The twins tell a few little lies. Stan teaches Olivia good manners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-17 01:55:00" d="2021-07-17 02:20:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Four young dinosaurs explore a prehistoric world of adventure where the most exciting mystery of all is Gigantosaurus, the biggest and fiercest dinosaur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-17 02:20:00" d="2021-07-17 02:45:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bill wishes Giganto would go away forever after his coconut lunch is disrupted. Ayati sends the four friends off on a quest to find a legendary land called Dinosia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-17 02:45:00" d="2021-07-17 03:10:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry helps Summer make a film to represent their roarsome family. Henry helps at the Cafe when Signor Roartonio's assistant is ill on Monster Pizza Day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-17 03:10:00" d="2021-07-17 03:35:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry’s friend Roddy arrives for a play date, but bad boy Roddy comes too. When he rips Summer’s autographed pic of Isabella, Henry dresses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-17 03:35:00" d="2021-07-17 04:00:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Who will win the school science fair - Cobby’s toast-a-rrific invention or Hildy’s doughnut volcano? Henry and Denzel fall out, so Cobby builds him a robot friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-17 04:00:00" d="2021-07-17 04:25:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Disney’s Mickey Mouse Clubhouse is the first Mickey Mouse series created specifically for preschoolers. The show introduces a whole new generation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-17 04:25:00" d="2021-07-17 04:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Hot Diggity-Dog Tales">Mickey Mouse Hot Diggity-Dog Tales I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While enjoying the Great Outdoors, Mickey and Pluto keep getting pestered by a pop-up weasel. But when they get in trouble on the river, the weasel is there to help!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-17 04:30:00" d="2021-07-17 04:55:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Disney’s Mickey Mouse Clubhouse is the first Mickey Mouse series created specifically for preschoolers. The show introduces a whole new generation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-17 04:55:00" d="2021-07-17 05:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Otto the Mole has bought his brother a toy plane. He asks Minnie to wrap it, but the propeller breaks. Minnie saves the day by replacing</k>  </p>
</a>
