<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="74" t="2021-07-09 06:46:00"><p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 05:00:00" d="2021-07-14 05:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Tiny throws a party but can she deliver on the outrageous promises she made? When Mazu wants to see a once-in-a-lifetime comet, everyone else's needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 05:30:00" d="2021-07-14 06:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A falling meteorite forces the herd to move, leaving Giganto behind!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 06:00:00" d="2021-07-14 06:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dad tells Bluey to mind her manners at the table - they’re not animals! But when Bluey gets her hands on a stick of magic asparagus, she shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 06:10:00" d="2021-07-14 06:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey and Bingo want a pet! To show them how much work they’d be in for, Dad transforms his hand into their old friend Shaun, a chaotic, undisciplined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 06:20:00" d="2021-07-14 06:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Mum goes out to a baby shower, Dad takes charge of the girls’ evening routine. But with Bluey missing Mum, Dad has to pull out all the games he knows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 06:30:00" d="2021-07-14 06:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s Christmas and Bluey is very focused on being good to get more presents. But when a game of Verandah Santa leaves cousin Socks upset, Bluey must learn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 06:40:00" d="2021-07-14 06:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (53)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Chilli and Bandit are keen to get a new pizza oven like their neighbours’ so they all go on a trip to Hammerbarn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 06:50:00" d="2021-07-14 07:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (54)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When a passing cockatoo drops a feather, Bingo has an idea for a new game. By waving her featherwand she can make objects impossibly heavy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 07:00:00" d="2021-07-14 07:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (76)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Who will be the winner of the prize to prove the legendary, Scronchasaur exists in Hot Dog Hills Lake? Daisy believes her GramQuacker Lily is living</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 07:30:00" d="2021-07-14 08:00:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (126)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% After making a big mistake at the McStuffinsville Toy Hospital, Doc begins to wonder if her patients would have been better off if she hadn't been there at all</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 08:00:00" d="2021-07-14 08:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins Toy Hospital">Doc McStuffins Toy Hospital IV (120)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>With the help of a young boy, the First Responders assemble for the first time in McStuffinsville to help endangered toys as quickly as possible</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 08:30:00" d="2021-07-14 08:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (55)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dad eats Bingo's last chip and as payback, Bingo has three 'dance mode' wishes to use at will</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 08:40:00" d="2021-07-14 08:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (56)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Uncle Stripe and Bandit are playing squash with the help of their controllers, Bingo and Bluey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 08:50:00" d="2021-07-14 09:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (57)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey and Bingo spend the day at Nana's along with their cousins!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 09:00:00" d="2021-07-14 09:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (101)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Romeo plans to use everyone's obsession with the new Jaden Concert to take over the world! When the Wolfies start their own band their sonic howls create</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 09:30:00" d="2021-07-14 10:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (85)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Owlette causes an asteroid accident. While trying to make it right, the PJ Masks meet another night-time hero, Newton! Newton likes the PJ Masks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 10:00:00" d="2021-07-14 10:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (58)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo has to play at home without her sister and she’s having trouble getting started</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 10:10:00" d="2021-07-14 10:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (59)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Heelers take turns remembering their favourite thing from the day at dinnertime, but when Bluey laughs at something her sister said earlier, Bingo’s mood darkens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 10:20:00" d="2021-07-14 10:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (60)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s Dad’s turn to give the kids breakfast and drop them off at school, but Bluey and Bingo are not going to make it easy to get there on time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 10:30:00" d="2021-07-14 11:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (73)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Pete needs a place to crash, Mickey offers to let him stay at his place. Unfortunately, Pete is the worst roommate ever! The Happy Helpers redecorate Mr. Doozy's hotel!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 11:00:00" d="2021-07-14 11:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (126)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% After making a big mistake at the McStuffinsville Toy Hospital, Doc begins to wonder if her patients would have been better off if she hadn't been there at all</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 11:30:00" d="2021-07-14 12:00:00"><n u="Mira, Royal Detective">Mira, Royal Detective I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Mikku and Chikku mix up the tiffin delivery for the day, Mira helps set things right. At the Jalpur Invention Fair, an important piece of Dhruv's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 12:00:00" d="2021-07-14 12:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (61)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>As Mum finishes reading bedtime stories to Bingo and kisses her goodnight, Bingo tells Mum tomorrow morning she will be waking up in her own bed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 12:10:00" d="2021-07-14 12:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (62)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey and Bingo are living on a desert island in the back garden when they discover Dad washed up on the beach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 12:20:00" d="2021-07-14 12:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (63)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hairdressers Bluey and Bingo discover that their customer Bert Handsome has nits!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 12:30:00" d="2021-07-14 13:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Vee goes overboard growing the largest pumpkin for a carving contest. When the Tundra-nator breaks at the B&amp;B, Oxana accidentally starts a winter storm</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 13:00:00" d="2021-07-14 13:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip the Penguin and Freddy the Flamingo are Junior Fliers at T.O.T.S., (the Tiny Ones Transport Service), where they’re tasked with delivering baby animals to their parents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 13:30:00" d="2021-07-14 14:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (102)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Catboy is taken by the idea of having a cat sidekick. The PJ Masks think Luna and Motsuki are causing moon trouble, but it's Pharaoh</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 14:00:00" d="2021-07-14 14:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Four young dinosaurs explore a prehistoric world of adventure where the most exciting mystery of all is Gigantosaurus, the biggest and fiercest dinosaur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 14:30:00" d="2021-07-14 14:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>At the park, Bluey is struggling to learn how to ride her bike. But as she and Dad watch her friends determination with their own tasks, Bluey is inspired</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 14:40:00" d="2021-07-14 14:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When it’s Bingo’s turn to bring her Kindy’s Bob Bilby puppet home and record their weekend in the scrapbook, the family resolve to put down their screens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 14:50:00" d="2021-07-14 15:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Bingo stops playing Bluey’s spy game in the park, their device to control the grownups stops working properly! Bluey now sees how important Bingo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 15:00:00" d="2021-07-14 15:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Forced to wait five minutes in front of a restaurant for their takeaway order, Bluey and Bingo become restless for entertainment, pushing the very limits of Dad’s patience</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 15:10:00" d="2021-07-14 15:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Playing ‘Butterflies’ in the backyard is great fun, until Bluey runs away with Judo leaving Bingo all alone. Now poor Bingo’s heartbroken and Bluey needs to make amends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 15:20:00" d="2021-07-14 15:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo loves horsing around with Dad, but sometimes he forgets Bingo is smaller than her sister. Mum teaches Bingo how to use her big</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 15:30:00" d="2021-07-14 16:00:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy's attempts to give Mom a perfect spa day go wrong. Nancy becomes Dad's assistant and causes an office disaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 16:00:00" d="2021-07-14 16:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. II (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Paulie’s glasses break, so Pip and Freddy take over his Control Tower duties. Lucy the Snow Leopard becomes attached to Pip after losing her lovey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 16:30:00" d="2021-07-14 17:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. II (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pip and Freddy must get their delivery back from Zed, Red, and Jed, precocious kid storks! Pip and Freddy become &quot;helicopter parents!&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 17:00:00" d="2021-07-14 17:25:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (56)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>For Thanksgiving this year, Mickey and the gang race Thanksgiving-themed racers! Minnie, Daisy and Cuckoo Loca invite all of their friends for Thanksgiving dinner!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 17:25:00" d="2021-07-14 17:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus S1 Shorts">Gigantosaurus S1 Shorts I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bill and Mazu invite the children to guess the mysterious dino: the pteranodon, the brachiosaurus or the triceratops</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 17:30:00" d="2021-07-14 17:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (75)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mum and Bluey play 'Mum School' where Mum agrees to teach Bluey how to corral her rowdy kids and be a better mum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 17:40:00" d="2021-07-14 17:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey II (76)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Heelers are taking a late afternoon walk when Bingo decides she’s too tired to walk any further and needs a piggyback</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 17:50:00" d="2021-07-14 18:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>As Bluey and Bingo squabble over their magic xylophone (that has the power to freeze Dad in space and time) Dad seizes control and freezes Bluey, leaving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 18:00:00" d="2021-07-14 18:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Doctor Bluey is needed when Dad gets a very curious x-ray from Nurse Bingo. It seems he has a cat in his tummy, leaving Bluey no choice but to operate immediately!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 18:10:00" d="2021-07-14 18:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey, Bingo and Mum are enjoying playing Keepy-Uppy around the house with their last balloon, when Dad joins in and the game becomes the ultimate test of skill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 18:20:00" d="2021-07-14 18:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey and Bingo don’t want to tidy the playroom, so they get Daddy Robot to do it for them. But when Bluey takes things too far, Daddy Robot malfunctions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 18:30:00" d="2021-07-14 19:00:00"><n u="Mira, Royal Detective">Mira, Royal Detective I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Queen Shanti's lost jewelry suddenly turns up, Mira enlists the Queen to join her on the case. Mira asks her friend, Pinky, the goat expert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 19:00:00" d="2021-07-14 19:30:00"><n u="The Rocketeer">The Rocketeer I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Sylvester Slapdash, disguised as the Costumed Bandit, plots to rob the Bulldog Café. Butch must rescue his new friend, Honey, the golden doodle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 19:30:00" d="2021-07-14 20:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A flat tire derails Bob's road trip with the Pugs. When Bob's Mom loses her locket in the Okavango Delta, the Pugs look for the special item with help from the locals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 20:00:00" d="2021-07-14 20:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After Bob loses his favorite fishing pole, Bingo and Rolly must confront a legendary creature to get it back. The pugs look after a puppy who turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 20:30:00" d="2021-07-14 21:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (92)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% There’s a new octopus-girl in the city, who wants to be friends with the PJ Masks, but her actions tell a different story. Octobella ruins Gekko's hero reputation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 21:00:00" d="2021-07-14 21:25:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Rugo tries to collect all of the coconuts in Cretacia, Bill sets out to get them back! Tiny and Totor discover they have a lot in common</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 21:25:00" d="2021-07-14 21:50:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu and Rocky must work together to save Tiny and Bill from Terminonator. Bill and Marsh are separated from their friends in a storm and must face their fears to get home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 21:50:00" d="2021-07-14 22:15:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Tiny throws a party but can she deliver on the outrageous promises she made? When Mazu wants to see a once-in-a-lifetime comet, everyone else's needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 22:15:00" d="2021-07-14 22:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou wants to do something special for his mum for Mother’s Day. He gets inspiration in the garage and makes some wind chimes. Zou also helps Zavier</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 22:30:00" d="2021-07-14 22:45:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nanna shows Zou how to make pom-poms, and then pom-pom animals, to sell at the school fete. He calls them monsters, and they sell really well</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 22:45:00" d="2021-07-14 23:00:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Uncle Zavier has been presented with a VIZ, a Very Important Zebra award. Zou wishes his Dad was important too. Grandpa shows Zou just how important his Dad really is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 23:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou is fed up after being told not to be noisy, and to tidy his room. He decides to leave home, but after talking to Grandpa wonders if he's made the right decision</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 23:15:00" d="2021-07-14 23:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou decides he wants to be a mountaineer when he grows up. He and Grandpa find some old climbing equipment in the garage and climb to the top of the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 23:25:00" d="2021-07-14 23:50:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry and Cobby invent a robot to help the grandmonsters create a knitted playground. Henry's scout troop competes against its rivals on Scouts’ Game Day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-14 23:50:00" d="2021-07-15 00:15:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It's the start of the holidays. Henry decides to fix Grando's old van to take them to see favourite band, Sonic Growl. But as usual in Roarsville, it doesn’t go smoothly!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 00:15:00" d="2021-07-15 00:40:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry’s upset he’s not invited to Summer’s sleepover so holds his own. Henry’s in charge while the mayor’s away and soon learns why rules exist. ( S2 Ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 00:40:00" d="2021-07-15 01:05:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry’s organising Roarsville’s big wedding and asks Summer to be the flower monster. Henry and Denzel decide to start a boy band</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 01:05:00" d="2021-07-15 01:30:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The twins play trains with Bigfoot but it’s slow.They are having a bad day.The twins are ashamed of being outside in their pyjamas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 01:30:00" d="2021-07-15 01:55:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The twins are eager to open a special play-clay pot. Stan is obsessed by an object he doesn’t recognize. The twins try to make friend with a seagull</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 01:55:00" d="2021-07-15 02:20:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu makes Archie a pair of wings to help him fly. Marsh copies Rocky's every move while Rocky copies Giganto</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 02:20:00" d="2021-07-15 02:45:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Four young dinosaurs explore a prehistoric world of adventure where the most exciting mystery of all is Gigantosaurus, the biggest and fiercest dinosaur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 02:45:00" d="2021-07-15 03:10:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry chases Daddo's birthday cake that’s caught on a balloon. Henry must save the monsterpets when they are swept into an airship on a windy day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 03:10:00" d="2021-07-15 03:35:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry searches Roarsville for Beckett when he runs off to play with Meg's monsterpet Shakey. Henry tries to teach his friends Gertie and Denzel to fly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 03:35:00" d="2021-07-15 04:00:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry and Cobby invent a robot to help the grandmonsters create a knitted playground. Henry's scout troop competes against its rivals on Scouts’ Game Day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 04:00:00" d="2021-07-15 04:25:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Disney’s Mickey Mouse Clubhouse is the first Mickey Mouse series created specifically for preschoolers. The show introduces a whole new generation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 04:25:00" d="2021-07-15 04:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Hot Diggity-Dog Tales">Mickey Mouse Hot Diggity-Dog Tales I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mickey and Minnie take to the skies when Pluto and Figaro float away in a hot air balloon! Now they have to save their beloved pets!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 04:30:00" d="2021-07-15 04:55:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Disney’s Mickey Mouse Clubhouse is the first Mickey Mouse series created specifically for preschoolers. The show introduces a whole new generation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-15 04:55:00" d="2021-07-15 05:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Clarabelle’s looking forward to going to the Snow Ball with Goofy, but doesn’t seem to be able to dance. Then Minnie fixes her droopy dress, and suddenly</k>  </p>
</a>
