<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="65" t="2019-08-10 01:35:59"><p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 05:00:00" d="2019-08-16 05:15:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (28)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 05:15:00" d="2019-08-16 05:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Catboy has to get Amaya’s and Greg’s stolen superhero pajamas back from Romeo! (S1 Ep8a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 05:30:00" d="2019-08-16 05:55:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Romeo creates a space laser to carve his face on the moon. Romeo plans to use a device to make everyone so clumsy that they can’t stop him!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 05:55:00" d="2019-08-16 06:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Minnie and Daisy have a large order to complete so they get a new ribbon machine to help them. But things don’t go as smoothly as they’d hoped. ( S2 Ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 06:00:00" d="2019-08-16 06:15:00"><n u="Muppet Babies">Muppet Babies (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>75% The Muppets try to convince Miss Nanny that they are ready for a puppy by taking care of a practice puppy called Rizzo for the day. What could possibly go wrong? (S1 Ep20a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 06:15:00" d="2019-08-16 06:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (71)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Romeo turns Owlette's Flossy Flash figure into a device that transforms the other PJ Masks into action toys! (S2 Ep23a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 06:30:00" d="2019-08-16 07:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Romeo steals Catboy's powers while wearing his costume. Can Gekko help Catboy and Owlette stop Night Ninja?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 07:00:00" d="2019-08-16 07:30:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When female vampire Vee is stressed she gets the battys and flips from girl to vampire and back. The bed and breakfast is open, but gets double booked</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 07:30:00" d="2019-08-16 08:00:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Everything seems to be going well for Nancy and Bree's new cafe until Grace the food critic shows up! When Mom has the sniffles, Nancy takes over as Mom for the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 08:00:00" d="2019-08-16 08:30:00"><n u="Sofia the First">Sofia the First I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% When King Roland wishes for a different job, then wakes to find he and the family are the local bakers, he soon realises it’s hard work. Can Sofia reverse the spell?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 08:30:00" d="2019-08-16 09:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% When Isabel takes her first class at the Science Academy with her heroine, Professor Ochoa, she learns how to overcome failure and let it lead her to success</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 09:00:00" d="2019-08-16 09:20:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Nancy wants her Grandma's vanity, she learns it holds special memories for her Grandpa.(S1 Ep10b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 09:20:00" d="2019-08-16 09:40:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy tries to keep an old toy from being sold without revealing she still cares about a &quot;baby toy&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 09:40:00" d="2019-08-16 10:00:00"><n u="Muppet Babies">Muppet Babies (15)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 10:00:00" d="2019-08-16 11:00:00"><n>Connect and Protect</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Miles, Loretta, Haruna, Blodger and Mirandos are recruited to be the first cadets of the TTA Mission Academy, they are assigned an urgent mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 11:00:00" d="2019-08-16 11:20:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Blaming her moths for past defeats, Luna Girl steals a swarm of butterflies to be her new sidekick.(S1 Ep6a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 11:20:00" d="2019-08-16 11:40:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (12)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 11:40:00" d="2019-08-16 12:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Romeo steals Gekko’s voice, but Gekko’s not sure he wants it back before his poetry presentation. (S1 Ep7a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 12:00:00" d="2019-08-16 12:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Catboy has to get Amaya’s and Greg’s stolen superhero pyjamas back from Romeo! Owlette’s prized Giving Owl statue is stolen by Luna Girl to decorate her new headquarters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 12:30:00" d="2019-08-16 12:50:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nanpire wants to pass her tradition of holding tea parties on to Vee. But she doesn't know that the tea set is magical, and chaos ensues. (S1 Ep22b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 12:50:00" d="2019-08-16 13:10:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After a visiting Mummy tells Vee about Mummy's Day, the family decides to celebrate it in Pennsylvania and give Oxana a day off. It's hard work and makes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 13:10:00" d="2019-08-16 13:30:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vee is celebrating Dance-lvania day, her favourite Transylvanian holiday by hosting a dance party. She's worried a visiting zombie will spoil things</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 13:30:00" d="2019-08-16 14:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nanpire and Grandpop the Greats visit for the Blood Moon Festival, meet the Peeplesons and learn to embrace human traditions and food. Vee is disappointed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 14:00:00" d="2019-08-16 14:20:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Keia’s new caterpillar friend goes missing! (S2 Ep7b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 14:20:00" d="2019-08-16 14:40:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The pugs go to Madagascar to learn about lemurs. (S2 Ep8a)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 14:40:00" d="2019-08-16 15:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When a big dog takes Keia's toy at the dog park, Bingo and Rolly make it their mission to retrieve the toy! (S2 Ep8b)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 15:00:00" d="2019-08-16 15:30:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% When Mtoto overhears a plot against the giraffes’ leader, the Lion Guard must save her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 15:30:00" d="2019-08-16 16:00:00"><n u="Elena of Avalor">Elena of Avalor II (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% When a visit from his older brother makes Armando feel insecure and inept, Elena helps Armando regain the confidence to succeed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 16:00:00" d="2019-08-16 16:25:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bill accidentally changes Cretacia’s ecosystem when he eats too many rare swamp flowers. Dilo pulls pranks on the dinos!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 16:25:00" d="2019-08-16 16:30:00"><n u="Paprika S1 Shorts">Paprika S1 Shorts I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan, Olivia end their friends love being together all the time, but Stan has to go off to brush his teeth. It’ll be difficult to be away from each other for that long!!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 16:30:00" d="2019-08-16 17:00:00"><n u="Mickey &amp; The Roadster Racers">Mickey &amp; The Roadster Racers II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Professor Von Drake super-charges Mickey’s roadster. Monstrous results when a sandwich is mixed into a formula</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 17:00:00" d="2019-08-16 17:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy replaces Frenchy with a well-trained but snooty dog. When Marabelle goes missing, Nancy becomes a sleuth to find out who took her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 17:30:00" d="2019-08-16 18:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vee and friends volunteer to babysit for her baby cousin. A family of ghost hunters visits the B&amp;B. Vee and family must prove their house is not haunted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 18:00:00" d="2019-08-16 18:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Catboy is turned into a cat by Romeo. Gekko needs Catboy and Owlette's help to fight a Roboctopus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 18:30:00" d="2019-08-16 19:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Can the pups find Chloe's lost puppy before she returns? Chloe wishes for a unicorn. The pups set out to find one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 19:00:00" d="2019-08-16 19:25:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% While creating Hippo Lanes through the flood plains after heavy rains, Beshte’s dad is injured and he must step into help, even though he’s never done it before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 19:25:00" d="2019-08-16 19:30:00"><n u="Paprika S1 Shorts">Paprika S1 Shorts I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stan, Olivia end their friends love being together all the time, but Stan has to go off to brush his teeth. It’ll be difficult to be away from each other for that long!!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 19:30:00" d="2019-08-16 20:00:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins Toy Hospital">Doc McStuffins Toy Hospital IV (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Doc learns wild animals shouldn’t be pets. Lambie and Stuffy are in a dance competition. Stuffy gets hurt. Should he carry on, or help his friend?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 20:00:00" d="2019-08-16 20:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bill accidentally changes Cretacia’s ecosystem when he eats too many rare swamp flowers. Dilo pulls pranks on the dinos!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 20:30:00" d="2019-08-16 21:00:00"><n u="Mickey &amp; The Roadster Racers">Mickey &amp; The Roadster Racers II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Professor Von Drake super-charges Mickey’s roadster. Monstrous results when a sandwich is mixed into a formula</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 21:00:00" d="2019-08-16 21:30:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy replaces Frenchy with a well-trained but snooty dog. When Marabelle goes missing, Nancy becomes a sleuth to find out who took her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 21:30:00" d="2019-08-16 22:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vee and friends volunteer to babysit for her baby cousin. A family of ghost hunters visits the B&amp;B. Vee and family must prove their house is not haunted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 22:00:00" d="2019-08-16 22:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Catboy is turned into a cat by Romeo. Gekko needs Catboy and Owlette's help to fight a Roboctopus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 22:30:00" d="2019-08-16 23:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Can the pups find Chloe's lost puppy before she returns? Chloe wishes for a unicorn. The pups set out to find one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 23:00:00" d="2019-08-16 23:25:00"><n u="The Lion Guard">The Lion Guard I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% While creating Hippo Lanes through the flood plains after heavy rains, Beshte’s dad is injured and he must step into help, even though he’s never done it before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 23:25:00" d="2019-08-16 23:30:00"><n u="Disney Junior Music Nursery Rhymes">Disney Junior Music Nursery Rhymes I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mickey Mouse is our host in this celestial symphony, featuring all the Disney Junior characters playing in the night sky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-16 23:30:00" d="2019-08-17 00:00:00"><n u="Trulli Tales">Trulli Tales I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Copperpot learns how Sun has grown her giant tomatoes. Grandma sets the Wizard Chefs a test to see who's best</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 00:00:00" d="2019-08-17 00:25:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Gekko fights the evil alter egos of Catboy and Owlette. Romeo, Luna Girl and Night Ninja team up to catch P J Masks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 00:25:00" d="2019-08-17 00:50:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% Catboy works too fast to kick back moonfizzle balls. Owlette must coach Catboy and Gekko to defeat Night Ninja</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 00:50:00" d="2019-08-17 01:00:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive (81)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 01:00:00" d="2019-08-17 01:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After watching his favourite TV show, Zou decides he wants to be a detective. His first case involves finding Nanna's false teeth, which he eventually does by accident!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 01:15:00" d="2019-08-17 01:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou (78)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou must do a project on animals who carry their homes on their back, but those he can think of have been picked by his friends. Inspiration strikes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 01:30:00" d="2019-08-17 01:55:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry shows Gertie it’s fun to have new experiences and not plan everything in advance. Henry agrees to practice piano if Momma learns how to skate ( S1 Ep14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 01:55:00" d="2019-08-17 02:20:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry and Denzel learn their mums were in rock band Grrr Power. They try to stage a reunion concert. Henry’s loose fang affects his roar. His friends think it sounds cool!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 02:20:00" d="2019-08-17 02:30:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Buzzbee has never had a letter and feels left out. When Postman Spider sprains his ankle, Buzzbee takes over, and does such a good job he gets lots of thank you letters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 02:30:00" d="2019-08-17 02:40:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive I (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Lord Bartlebee learns how to have fun with a little help from some of the younger residents of The Hive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 02:40:00" d="2019-08-17 02:55:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After Zac takes a tumble and is bandaged up, Zou decides he wants to be a first aider, and finds the household full of willing patients</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 02:55:00" d="2019-08-17 03:10:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou and Elzee camp in the garden. Grandpa tells them stories of animals he met while camping in Africa. They are scared and imagine wild animals outside their tent too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 03:10:00" d="2019-08-17 03:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou II (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Grandad has some tomatoes for a picnic and asks Zou and friends to deliver them on their train</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 03:25:00" d="2019-08-17 03:35:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Buzzbee and Jasper decide they want to play with Jump, but Rubee and Debee got to him first, and have dressed him up like a baby. They squabble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 03:35:00" d="2019-08-17 03:45:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive (96)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Barnabee wants to train as a firefighter and learns that firefighters help with more than just fires</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 03:45:00" d="2019-08-17 04:10:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry and Denzel learn their mums were in rock band Grrr Power. They try to stage a reunion concert. Henry’s loose fang affects his roar. His friends think it sounds cool!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 04:10:00" d="2019-08-17 04:35:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Hugglemonsters move their house to help the Huggleflower bloom. Henry and Summer find getting Ivor to sleep is not as easy as they thought</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 04:35:00" d="2019-08-17 04:45:00"><n u="The Hive">The Hive I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Miss Ladybird asks Buzzbee to bring Jump to school to show everyone how to look after a pet. But he ignores Grandma’s advice to put Jump on a lead, and soon regrets it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2019-08-17 04:45:00" d="2019-08-17 05:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks (16)</n><t>Q</t>  </p>
</a>
