<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="75" t="2021-07-12 04:55:07"><p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 05:00:00" d="2021-07-19 05:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu sees life through a raptor’s eyes when she gets stuck to Cror by some tar. Rocky hopes to get the best viewing spot to watch the &quot;winter lights&quot; dance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 05:30:00" d="2021-07-19 05:45:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus S2 Splits">Gigantosaurus S2 Splits II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>With Termy banished, life in Cretacia is pretty good, until the dinos realize that his absence is causing an ecological disaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 05:45:00" d="2021-07-19 06:00:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus S2 Splits">Gigantosaurus S2 Splits II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rocky sets out to break all of Roger's records!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 06:00:00" d="2021-07-19 06:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey’s house has fairies! Tails are being braided, stickers are everywhere, and Mum’s got a peg beard. Now the family must band together to hunt for these</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 06:10:00" d="2021-07-19 06:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In a game of ‘Work’, Dad hires Bluey and Bingo at his drainpipe factory. But when Bluey takes charge, Dad finds his new boss pretty tough, especially her no dancing rule!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 06:20:00" d="2021-07-19 06:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo is sick in hospital, so Bluey and Dad sent her a homemade video to lift her spirits. It tells the tale of Barnicus’ quest to heal her spotty dog named Bumpy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 06:30:00" d="2021-07-19 06:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Dad has to stop having fun with the girls and go to work, Bluey and Bingo scramble to keep him playing games with them on the trampoline as long as possible!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 06:40:00" d="2021-07-19 06:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>On a trip to the dump Dad claims he’s the best at everything. But Bluey discovers that Dad’s throwing out her old drawings and questions if he really</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 06:50:00" d="2021-07-19 07:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey’s backyard zoo is home to wonderful animals, especially the big blue Daddy Gorilla. But when he grabs visitor Bingo and escapes, Zookeeper Bluey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 07:00:00" d="2021-07-19 07:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Everyone ends up with mixed-up roadsters when Chip 'n Dale add a few of their ideas to Mickey's new Motor Lab invention! The gang turns window washing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 07:30:00" d="2021-07-19 08:00:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins Toy Hospital">Doc McStuffins Toy Hospital IV (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Can Doc and her students convince toy camel Camille to go to the hospital? Doc can’t see inside a toy's fluffy cheek, so decides to do a CAT scan to figure out the problem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 08:00:00" d="2021-07-19 08:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (127)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Stuffy ventures deep into the jungle in search of Dragon Mountain, a legendary place where he hopes to find a dragon family of his own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 08:30:00" d="2021-07-19 08:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mum and Dad are going on an adventure wearing the kids as their cheeky backpacks! Seeing the sights and buying street food, backpackings a blast - until</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 08:40:00" d="2021-07-19 08:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Princesses, horses and magic wands. Bluey and Chloe can play any role they want, when they embark on an adventure to save their playground kingdom from the Greedy Queen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 08:50:00" d="2021-07-19 09:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey’s having fun copying everything Dad says and does, but the game takes a serious turn when Bluey finds a hurt budgie and they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 09:00:00" d="2021-07-19 09:30:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Luna Girl is stealing Christmas presents to spoil Christmas. Gekko wants to stop her but first he must learn to ride her Luna Board. Romeo plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 09:30:00" d="2021-07-19 10:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (88)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Gekko tries to train a naughty monkey. The PJ Masks' team spirit falls apart when Munkigu sabotages their mission with hilarious pranks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 10:00:00" d="2021-07-19 10:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A sleepover with their cousin means Bluey and Bingo get to stay up late! But when Muffin shows up exhausted after missing a nap, the girls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 10:10:00" d="2021-07-19 10:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey’s playgroup is at odds when Indy’s baby hospital collides with Rusty’s knights and dragons. But in explaining themselves, they find the games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 10:20:00" d="2021-07-19 10:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Indy and Rusty play Mum and Dads, they can’t agree on who should go to work, so they part company. Indy has a hard time finding a babysitter, while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 10:30:00" d="2021-07-19 11:00:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (77)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Goofy and Elray audition for their favorite magician, Trikini! When art teacher, Mrs. Matisse, leaves to have her baby, the Happy Helpers fill in at the school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 11:00:00" d="2021-07-19 11:30:00"><n u="Doc McStuffins">Doc McStuffins V (128)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% After offering to watch over the Nursery, Chilly is too afraid to ask questions and gets in way over his head!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 11:30:00" d="2021-07-19 12:00:00"><n u="Mira, Royal Detective">Mira, Royal Detective I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mira must figure out who is sabotaging performances at the dance competition. When decorations for Priya and Meena’s entry into the camel fair go missing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 12:00:00" d="2021-07-19 12:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s time for a family game of hide and seek! Everyone hides, while Bluey counts to twenty, but will she be able to stay focused on the</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 12:10:00" d="2021-07-19 12:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>While on a camping holiday, Bluey makes a new friend called Jean-Luc. Bluey may not understand him, but they find a common language playing and hunting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 12:20:00" d="2021-07-19 12:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo and Bluey have five minutes to bed, just enough time to race to the summit of Mt MumandDad! But between powerful storms, avalanches and stinky spots</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 12:30:00" d="2021-07-19 13:00:00"><n u="Vampirina">Vampirina II (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Vee writes a song made of a spell that gets the whole town singing! Before the Hauntley's can restore the B&amp;B to it's spooky state, an inspector</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 13:00:00" d="2021-07-19 13:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. II (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>KC joins Pip and Freddy for T.O.T.S.’ first-ever mid-air baby preparation. While delivering Calvin, a baby caterpillar, Pip and Freddy witness the greatest magic show of all!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 13:30:00" d="2021-07-19 14:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Luna blames her moths for defeats and steals butterflies to replace them. Luna Girl and Owlette compete to win the biggest, best toy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 14:00:00" d="2021-07-19 14:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus II (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>With Termy banished, life in Cretacia is pretty good, until the dinos realize that his absence is causing an ecological disaster. Rocky sets out to break</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 14:30:00" d="2021-07-19 14:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bored of the local playground, Dad and the kids go bush on a journey to their local creek. Cast out of her comfort zone, Bluey’s eyes are opened</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 14:40:00" d="2021-07-19 14:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey’s house has fairies! Tails are being braided, stickers are everywhere, and Mum’s got a peg beard. Now the family must band together to hunt for these</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 14:50:00" d="2021-07-19 15:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In a game of ‘Work’, Dad hires Bluey and Bingo at his drainpipe factory. But when Bluey takes charge, Dad finds his new boss pretty tough, especially her no dancing rule!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 15:00:00" d="2021-07-19 15:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo is sick in hospital, so Bluey and Dad sent her a homemade video to lift her spirits. It tells the tale of Barnicus’ quest to heal her spotty dog named Bumpy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 15:10:00" d="2021-07-19 15:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Dad has to stop having fun with the girls and go to work, Bluey and Bingo scramble to keep him playing games with them on the trampoline as long as possible!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 15:20:00" d="2021-07-19 15:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>On a trip to the dump Dad claims he’s the best at everything. But Bluey discovers that Dad’s throwing out her old drawings and questions if he really</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 15:30:00" d="2021-07-19 16:00:00"><n u="Fancy Nancy Clancy">Fancy Nancy Clancy I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nancy has a sleepover at Mrs. Devine's. Nancy feels threatened when her boy cousin is fancier than she is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 16:00:00" d="2021-07-19 16:30:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. II (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stanley the baby Shark has trouble making friends when his big pointy teeth scare everyone away! Pip and Freddy help JP one-up his older brother!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 16:30:00" d="2021-07-19 17:00:00"><n u="T.O.T.S.">T.O.T.S. II (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Freddy enters a surf contest to win baby Sandy the top prize! Retired T.O.T.S. flier Grandpa Hank joins Pip and Freddy to deliver his grand-stork</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 17:00:00" d="2021-07-19 17:25:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures">Mickey Mouse Mixed-Up Adventures III (59)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A unicorn is spotted in Hot Dog Hills! Minnie and Daisy love horses, but do they know enough to give horseback riding lessons?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 17:25:00" d="2021-07-19 17:30:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus S1 Shorts">Gigantosaurus S1 Shorts I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bill and Tiny invite the children to guess the mysterious dino: the plesiosaurus, the triceratops or the velociraptor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 17:30:00" d="2021-07-19 17:40:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bored of the local playground, Dad and the kids go bush on a journey to their local creek. Cast out of her comfort zone, Bluey’s eyes are opened</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 17:40:00" d="2021-07-19 17:50:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bluey’s house has fairies! Tails are being braided, stickers are everywhere, and Mum’s got a peg beard. Now the family must band together to hunt for these</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 17:50:00" d="2021-07-19 18:00:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>In a game of ‘Work’, Dad hires Bluey and Bingo at his drainpipe factory. But when Bluey takes charge, Dad finds his new boss pretty tough, especially her no dancing rule!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 18:00:00" d="2021-07-19 18:10:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bingo is sick in hospital, so Bluey and Dad sent her a homemade video to lift her spirits. It tells the tale of Barnicus’ quest to heal her spotty dog named Bumpy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 18:10:00" d="2021-07-19 18:20:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Dad has to stop having fun with the girls and go to work, Bluey and Bingo scramble to keep him playing games with them on the trampoline as long as possible!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 18:20:00" d="2021-07-19 18:30:00"><n u="Bluey">Bluey I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>On a trip to the dump Dad claims he’s the best at everything. But Bluey discovers that Dad’s throwing out her old drawings and questions if he really</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 18:30:00" d="2021-07-19 19:00:00"><n u="Mira, Royal Detective">Mira, Royal Detective I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mira searches for the culprit when people start receiving anonymous gifts. When Pinky’s dishes for the Queen's cooking contest seem to be sabotaged, Mira is on the case!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 19:00:00" d="2021-07-19 19:30:00"><n u="The Rocketeer">The Rocketeer I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Kit volunteers at the Bulldog Cafe in order to prove she's responsible enough to enroll in the Valkyrie Flight School. Kit befriends Valeri d'Avion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 19:30:00" d="2021-07-19 20:00:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals II (54)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When Bob can't fix ARF's voice box, Bingo and Rolly race to find an inventor. Bob's favorite knight goes missing at a jousting event, plunging</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 20:00:00" d="2021-07-19 20:30:00"><n u="Puppy Dog Pals">Puppy Dog Pals I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After losing a collar at a pumpkin patch, Bingo, Hissy and Rolly return after dark to find it. The pups go looking for a neighborhood kid's missing costume</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 20:30:00" d="2021-07-19 21:00:00"><n u="PJ Masks">PJ Masks IV (97)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>56% Armadylan tries to fix a museum artifact without telling the PJ Masks. Romeo wants to create the ultimate trap for the PJ Masks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 21:00:00" d="2021-07-19 21:25:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When a runaway boulder ruins Mazu’s invention, she sets out to find what set it in motion. Bill is tired of being a little brachiosaurus, so he looks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 21:25:00" d="2021-07-19 21:50:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rocky decides not to practice for a talent show but his partner in the show is Giganto. Marsh is tricked by raptors to play a game, but they're really</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 21:50:00" d="2021-07-19 22:15:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu sees life through a raptor’s eyes when she gets stuck to Cror by some tar. Rocky hopes to get the best viewing spot to watch the &quot;winter lights&quot; dance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 22:15:00" d="2021-07-19 22:30:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou discovers a rare brain coral at the beach, which gives him the idea of starting a museum. He collects interesting objects for the museum – including</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 22:30:00" d="2021-07-19 22:45:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou and Grandpa find some old picture frames and decide to renovate them. The new, decorated frames attract the attention of Uncle Zavier and Aunt Zelda</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 22:45:00" d="2021-07-19 23:00:00"><n u="Zou">Zou III (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou is reading an exciting mystery story. Trouble is the last page is missing. Zou’s hunt for the author reveals a very unlikely writer indeed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 23:00:00" d="2021-07-19 23:15:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Zou, Elzee and Zinnia are due to go to the park but the weather is awful so they have a Halloween toffee apple hunt around the house instead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 23:15:00" d="2021-07-19 23:25:00"><n u="Zou">Zou I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After watching his favourite TV show, Zou decides he wants to be a detective. His first case involves finding Nanna's false teeth, which he eventually does by accident!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 23:25:00" d="2021-07-19 23:50:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Hugglemonsters move their house to help the Huggleflower bloom. Henry and Summer find getting Ivor to sleep is not as easy as they thought</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-19 23:50:00" d="2021-07-20 00:15:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>When baking, Henry adds too much yeast and makes a giant dough ball that escapes. Henry's scout troop builds racing cars and he's flattered when Roberto copies him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 00:15:00" d="2021-07-20 00:40:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>After seeing sister Summer's show, Henry decides to do his own. But it proves harder than it looked, and after a disaster Henry asks Summer's advice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 00:40:00" d="2021-07-20 01:05:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry's thrilled when Gertie turns up, but she's come for a piano lesson with Momma so he tries to sabotage it! Henry goes to the wave park. He's scared</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 01:05:00" d="2021-07-20 01:30:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>No hurdle’s too high for the Paprika twins Olivia and Stan as they turn everyday life into wonderful, colourful adventures!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 01:30:00" d="2021-07-20 01:55:00"><n u="Paprika">Paprika I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>No hurdle’s too high for the Paprika twins Olivia and Stan as they turn everyday life into wonderful, colourful adventures!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 01:55:00" d="2021-07-20 02:20:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rocky has to get nectar from a special flower to get his Giganto cards back from the raptors. Tiny and Bill accidentally clog up Cretacia's water source</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 02:20:00" d="2021-07-20 02:45:00"><n u="Gigantosaurus">Gigantosaurus I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mazu invents the world's first go-carts to beat Giganto in a race. When Bill's food stash is raided, he makes it his mission to find the culprit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 02:45:00" d="2021-07-20 03:10:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry’s troop needs a new leader. Roddy must prove he deserves a chance. Henry and Denzel swap to see what it’s like living in each other’s houses.( S2 Ep17)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 03:10:00" d="2021-07-20 03:35:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry and friends get tied together and must work as a team to get free. The new monster turns out to be friendly, not scary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 03:35:00" d="2021-07-20 04:00:00"><n u="Henry Hugglemonster">Henry Hugglemonster II (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Henry needs to be in three places at once so creates more Henrys using Cobby’s Copytron. Can Henry help Roddy prove he's up to being the new scout leader?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 04:00:00" d="2021-07-20 04:25:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse II (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% At Mickey Mouse Clubhouse the fun never stops! Come along while Minnie plans a picnic, Daisy takes care of new pets, and Professor Von Drake’s latest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 04:25:00" d="2021-07-20 04:30:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Hot Diggity-Dog Tales">Mickey Mouse Hot Diggity-Dog Tales I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>It’s almost Dance Party time and Mickey must come up with a brand new, tail-shaking dance to show Minnie, Goofy, and all of his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 04:30:00" d="2021-07-20 04:55:00"><n u="Mickey Mouse Clubhouse">Mickey Mouse Clubhouse II (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>59% At Mickey Mouse Clubhouse the fun never stops! Come along while Minnie plans a picnic, Daisy takes care of new pets, and Professor Von Drake’s latest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="567" o="2021-07-20 04:55:00" d="2021-07-20 05:00:00"><n u="Minnie's Bow-Toons">Minnie's Bow-Toons II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Minnie and Daisy need to fix the Bowtique’s sign. Daisy holds the ladder and Minnie goes up it, with hilarious consequences. While up there, Minnie finds a bird’s nest. ( S2 Ep2)</k>  </p>
</a>
