<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="42" t="2021-07-09 06:58:04"><p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 05:00:00" d="2021-07-14 05:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 05:30:00" d="2021-07-14 06:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 06:00:00" d="2021-07-14 06:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 06:30:00" d="2021-07-14 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 07:00:00" d="2021-07-14 08:00:00"><n>Jamie's American Road Trip</n><t>D</t>    <k>Just weeks after Hurricane Gustav wreaked havoc on Louisiana, Jamie Oliver visits the state, hoping to understand how food helps to maintain people's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 08:00:00" d="2021-07-14 08:30:00"><n>Valerie's Home Cooking</n><t>D</t>    <k>Valerie Bertinelli makes the most of the warm weather by throwing an Italian-style backyard beach party, where she serves up fried clams and antipasto pasta salad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 08:30:00" d="2021-07-14 09:00:00"><n>Valerie's Home Cooking</n><t>D</t>    <k>Valerie Bertinelli comes up with some inventive combinations for her taco-centric menu. Dishes include chicken tinga tacos and Neapolitan dessert tacos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 09:00:00" d="2021-07-14 09:30:00"><n>Giada at Home</n><t>D</t>    <k>Giada is hosting a pool party, so creates a menu to enjoy in the sunshine. She serves up burgers a la pizzaiola, penne with brown butter and a tropical watermelon sorbet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 09:30:00" d="2021-07-14 10:00:00"><n>Giada at Home</n><t>D</t>    <k>Giada celebrates Easter with her family in the backyard, where she gives lamb a twist with a quinoa crust accompanied by orzo with a smoky vinaigrette</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 10:00:00" d="2021-07-14 10:30:00"><n>Forever Summer with Nigella</n><t>D</t>    <k>Nigella Lawson prepares spiced pink soup and black olive salad with feta</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 10:30:00" d="2021-07-14 11:00:00"><n>Forever Summer with Nigella</n><t>D</t>    <k>The food writer heads to the seaside for a weekend away in Whitstable, Kent, and rustles up ricotta hotcakes with strawberries, a golden coconut</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 11:00:00" d="2021-07-14 11:30:00"><n>Farmhouse Rules</n><t>D</t>    <k>Chef Nancy Fuller gathers the best the land has to offer and feeds her friends and family classic, farm-fresh meals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 11:30:00" d="2021-07-14 12:00:00"><n>Farmhouse Rules</n><t>D</t>    <k>Chef Nancy Fuller gathers the best the land has to offer and feeds her friends and family classic, farm-fresh meals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 12:00:00" d="2021-07-14 12:30:00"><n>Girl Meets Farm</n><t>D</t>    <k>Molly Yeh treats her friends to her best brunch dishes after a night out in Grand Forks. The menu includes mini quiches with peas and bacon and garlic lemon kale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 12:30:00" d="2021-07-14 13:00:00"><n>Girl Meets Farm</n><t>D</t>    <k>Molly puts a fresh twist on classic farm lunch staples for a picnic. She serves up garlic and onion Challah bread, home-made hummus, and olive oil blondies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 13:00:00" d="2021-07-14 13:30:00"><n>Rachel Khoo: My Swedish Kitchen</n><t>D</t>    <k>Rachel Khoo embarks on a culinary journey through Sweden. This time, she makes a traditional pea soup with smoked bacon, and a mushroom risotto</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 13:30:00" d="2021-07-14 14:00:00"><n>Rachel Khoo: My Swedish Kitchen</n><t>D</t>    <k>Rachel Khoo explores the culinary specialities of Sweden. Today, she prepares Swedish butternut squash waffles with sweet and savoury toppings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 14:00:00" d="2021-07-14 15:00:00"><n>Jamie's American Road Trip</n><t>D</t>    <k>Just weeks after Hurricane Gustav wreaked havoc on Louisiana, Jamie Oliver visits the state, hoping to understand how food helps to maintain people's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 15:00:00" d="2021-07-14 15:30:00"><n>James Martin: Delicious</n><t>D</t>    <k>The chef visits a grower of asparagus, combines the vegetable with poached egg, chargrills it with red pepper and makes a tart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 15:30:00" d="2021-07-14 16:00:00"><n>James Martin: Delicious</n><t>D</t>    <k>The chef prepares chick pea and spinach tapas, charred tuna romesco and Iberian ham salad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 16:00:00" d="2021-07-14 17:00:00"><n>Paul Hollywood: City Bakes</n><t>D</t>    <k>In Iceland's capital city, Paul bakes using volcanic geothermal energy, meets food writer Eva Laufey, and creates two of his own bakes inspired by Icelandic cuisine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 17:00:00" d="2021-07-14 17:30:00"><n>Nigel Slater's Real Food Show</n><t>D</t>    <k>Recipes using cheese, including cauliflower and ricotta salad, New York cheesecake and poached pears with mascarpone and Gorgonzola</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 17:30:00" d="2021-07-14 18:00:00"><n>Nigel Slater's Real Food Show</n><t>D</t>    <k>Chocolate recipes, including chocolate espresso cake and white chocolate cardamom mousse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 18:00:00" d="2021-07-14 18:30:00"><n>The Pioneer Woman</n><t>D</t>    <k>Ree Drummond fills freezer with breakfast favourites, including freezer breakfast paninis, very berry croissants and frozen yoghurt bark</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 18:30:00" d="2021-07-14 19:00:00"><n>The Pioneer Woman</n><t>D</t>    <k>Ree makes a Mexican-inspired family dinner on the grill. On the menu are marinated carne asada with skewers of chipotle glazed shrimp and corn and squash salad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 19:00:00" d="2021-07-14 19:30:00"><n>The Pioneer Woman</n><t>D</t>    <k>Ree Drummond makes savoury breakfast kabobs, sweet breakfast kabobs, pancake pockets and an egg in a hole sandwich</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 19:30:00" d="2021-07-14 20:00:00"><n>The Pioneer Woman</n><t>D</t>    <k>Ree Drummond prepares for a party by making a tasty lineup of low-carb appetisers, including sausage stuffed mushrooms and courgette roll ups</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 20:00:00" d="2021-07-14 21:00:00"><n>The Great British Bake Off</n><t>D</t>    <k>As bread week arrives, the remaining home-bakers must face three tough tasks set by Paul Hollywood. For the signature bake, the contestants make a sweet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 21:00:00" d="2021-07-14 21:30:00"><n>Forever Summer with Nigella</n><t>D</t>    <k>Summer recipes, including sticky spare ribs containing fiery red chillies, Indonesian chicken, and ice-cream with a red-hot spicy syrup</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 21:30:00" d="2021-07-14 22:00:00"><n>Forever Summer with Nigella</n><t>D</t>    <k>Food writer Nigella Lawson prepares more summer recipes, taking her inspiration from around the world. She looks to the Middle East for za'tar chicken</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 22:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:00:00"><n>John Torode's Korean Food Tour</n><t>D</t>    <k>The masterful chef explores the wonders of Korean food. In Seoul, John discovers summer dishes and makes chicken ginseng soup and BBQ pork skewers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 23:00:00" d="2021-07-15 00:00:00"><n>Hairy Bikers' Best of British</n><t>D</t>    <k>Si King and Dave Myers explore the history behind some of the country's most popular spices and explore how they have been used to liven up meals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 00:00:00" d="2021-07-15 00:30:00"><n>Mystery Diners</n><t>D</t>    <k>A restaurant owner discovers that his manager brother is acting inappropriately with guests and asks the team to investigate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 00:30:00" d="2021-07-15 01:00:00"><n>Mystery Diners</n><t>D</t>    <k>Restaurant owners ask the team for help when two employees bring their personal life into the work place and begin to affect sales and disrupt morale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 01:00:00" d="2021-07-15 01:30:00"><n>Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives</n><t>D</t>    <k>Guy Fieri travels to Barcelona, and digs into everything from top-notch tapas, such as prawns and quail, to traditional Catalan specialties including</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 01:30:00" d="2021-07-15 02:00:00"><n>Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives</n><t>D</t>    <k>In Louisville, a funky seafood spot piles their specialties on top of waffles, and in Portland, a killer barbecue food truck stacks a fully-loaded 'shabamwich'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 02:00:00" d="2021-07-15 02:30:00"><n>Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives</n><t>D</t>    <k>Guy Fieri samples grilled cheese sandwiches with a twist, made-from-scratch sausages and specialties straight out of Switzerland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 02:30:00" d="2021-07-15 03:00:00"><n>Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives</n><t>D</t>    <k>Guy Fieri hunts down all kinds of meaty favourites, starting with an Irish pub's cottage pie in Louisville. Then he grabs burgers at two stops in North Carolina</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 03:00:00" d="2021-07-15 03:30:00"><n>Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives</n><t>D</t>    <k>Guy heads to Cancun, Mexico, to dig into cuisine at places like an authentic, family-owned spot where grandma is cooking up rellenos and killer chicharron gorditas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 03:30:00" d="2021-07-15 04:00:00"><n>Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives</n><t>D</t>    <k>In North Carolina, an eatery tucked inside a beer store slings crazy waffle creations, and in Texas, a not-your-everyday fusion joint mashes up barbecue with sushi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 04:00:00" d="2021-07-15 04:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 04:30:00" d="2021-07-15 05:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
</a>
