<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="42" t="2021-07-09 06:58:19"><p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 05:00:00" d="2021-07-15 05:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 05:30:00" d="2021-07-15 06:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 06:00:00" d="2021-07-15 06:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 06:30:00" d="2021-07-15 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 07:00:00" d="2021-07-15 08:00:00"><n>Jamie's American Road Trip</n><t>D</t>    <k>Having sampled some of America's most diverse dietary offerings, Jamie Oliver sets out in search of the country's cheapest culinary treats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 08:00:00" d="2021-07-15 08:30:00"><n>Valerie's Home Cooking</n><t>D</t>    <k>Valerie Bertinelli helps a friend cook a feast for her husband's birthday. The menu includes seared scallops, misticanza salad and strawberry icebox cake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 08:30:00" d="2021-07-15 09:00:00"><n>Valerie's Home Cooking</n><t>D</t>    <k>Valerie Bertinelli and her husband host a competitive game night at home with their friends. She serves up butter lettuce salad, part-cheesy twists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 09:00:00" d="2021-07-15 09:30:00"><n>Giada at Home</n><t>D</t>    <k>Giada hosts a fun kid's party featuring a secret treasure hunt and an imaginative menu. Dishes include carrot and courgette mini-muffins and colourful quesadillas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 09:30:00" d="2021-07-15 10:00:00"><n>Giada at Home</n><t>D</t>    <k>Giada plans a Father's Day meal. The menu features short rib lasagne rolls, crab and lemon bruschetta and raspberry-balsamic parfaits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 10:00:00" d="2021-07-15 10:30:00"><n>Forever Summer with Nigella</n><t>D</t>    <k>Summer recipes, including sticky spare ribs containing fiery red chillies, Indonesian chicken, and ice-cream with a red-hot spicy syrup</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 10:30:00" d="2021-07-15 11:00:00"><n>Forever Summer with Nigella</n><t>D</t>    <k>Food writer Nigella Lawson prepares more summer recipes, taking her inspiration from around the world. She looks to the Middle East for za'tar chicken</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 11:00:00" d="2021-07-15 11:30:00"><n>Farmhouse Rules</n><t>D</t>    <k>Chef Nancy Fuller gathers the best the land has to offer and feeds her friends and family classic, farm-fresh meals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 11:30:00" d="2021-07-15 12:00:00"><n>Farmhouse Rules</n><t>D</t>    <k>Chef Nancy Fuller gathers the best the land has to offer and feeds her friends and family classic, farm-fresh meals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 12:00:00" d="2021-07-15 12:30:00"><n>Girl Meets Farm</n><t>D</t>    <k>Molly Yeh's mother visits from Chicago for garden planting and a campfire supper, which includes breakfast tacos, charred sweet corn salsa and raspberry marshmallows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 12:30:00" d="2021-07-15 13:00:00"><n>Girl Meets Farm</n><t>D</t>    <k>Molly prepares a special menu to make ahead for her visiting friends. Dishes include sticky rhubarb short ribs and whipped cheesecakes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 13:00:00" d="2021-07-15 13:30:00"><n>Rachel Khoo: My Swedish Kitchen</n><t>D</t>    <k>Rachel Khoo embarks on a culinary journey through Sweden. This time, she samples falafel in Malmo, before preparing a vegetarian version of the traditional Swedish meatball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 13:30:00" d="2021-07-15 14:00:00"><n>Rachel Khoo: My Swedish Kitchen</n><t>D</t>    <k>Rachel Khoo embarks on a culinary journey through Sweden. She eats herring and prawns in Gothenburg, and then makes a canape version of traditional prawns on toast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 14:00:00" d="2021-07-15 15:00:00"><n>Jamie's American Road Trip</n><t>D</t>    <k>Having sampled some of America's most diverse dietary offerings, Jamie Oliver sets out in search of the country's cheapest culinary treats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 15:00:00" d="2021-07-15 15:30:00"><n>James Martin: Delicious</n><t>D</t>    <k>The chef prepares cheese with roast figs and prosciutto, and a classic Greek salad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 15:30:00" d="2021-07-15 16:00:00"><n>James Martin: Delicious</n><t>D</t>    <k>The chef prepares smoked trout salad and hot tea-smoked trout with celeriac remoulade. He also tries his hand at fly fishing for trout on the River Test in Hampshire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 16:00:00" d="2021-07-15 17:00:00"><n>Paul Hollywood: City Bakes</n><t>D</t>    <k>Paul visits San Francisco, home to one of America's most iconic bakes, the sourdough, where he creates savoury bread and butter pudding, and cheese and olive bread</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 17:00:00" d="2021-07-15 17:30:00"><n>Nigel Slater's Real Food Show</n><t>D</t>    <k>The food writer uses sausages as the basis for a pasta sauce, while Nigella Lawson creates a Spanish stew with chorizo and potatoes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 17:30:00" d="2021-07-15 18:00:00"><n>Nigel Slater's Real Food Show</n><t>D</t>    <k>The food writer demonstrates how to prepare an American club sandwich and a spicy chicken baguette</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 18:00:00" d="2021-07-15 18:30:00"><n>The Pioneer Woman</n><t>D</t>    <k>Ree Drummond demonstrates how to prepare her own take on comforting home cooking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 18:30:00" d="2021-07-15 19:00:00"><n>The Pioneer Woman</n><t>D</t>    <k>Ree makes dishes inspired by foreign countries. She celebrates exotic British food with a full English breakfast and makes a delicious chicken tagine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 19:00:00" d="2021-07-15 19:30:00"><n>The Pioneer Woman</n><t>D</t>    <k>Ree Drummond demonstrates how to prepare her own take on comforting home cooking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 19:30:00" d="2021-07-15 20:00:00"><n>The Pioneer Woman</n><t>D</t>    <k>Kids In The Kitchen . The Drummond children get creative in the kitchen, preparing dishes including a grilled fruit pizza and strawberry shortcake cake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 20:00:00" d="2021-07-15 21:00:00"><n>The Great British Bake Off</n><t>D</t>    <k>As bread week arrives, the remaining home-bakers must face three tough tasks set by Paul Hollywood. For the signature bake, the contestants make a sweet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 21:00:00" d="2021-07-15 21:30:00"><n>Forever Summer with Nigella</n><t>D</t>    <k>Food writer Nigella Lawson dips into family cookbooks and classic literature for some minty summer recipes, using the herb to add subtle flavour to a squid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 21:30:00" d="2021-07-15 22:00:00"><n>Forever Summer with Nigella</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cook Nigella Lawson adds a Mediterranean twist to familiar favourites, transforming the traditional Sunday lunch. Recipes include Moroccan roast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 22:00:00" d="2021-07-15 23:00:00"><n>Gok's Chinese Takeaway</n><t>D</t>    <k>Gok Wan embarks on a journey to visit Chinese communities around the globe to discover their take on Chinese food outside of China</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-15 23:00:00" d="2021-07-16 00:00:00"><n>Hairy Bikers' Best of British</n><t>D</t>    <k>Si King and Dave Myers brave the high seas to celebrate Britain's fishing industry, demonstrating a variety of dishes including sardines on toast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-16 00:00:00" d="2021-07-16 00:30:00"><n>Mystery Diners</n><t>D</t>    <k>The owner of a Brazilian restaurant is concerned that the meat sales are not being reflected in his profit, so asks the team to investigate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-16 00:30:00" d="2021-07-16 01:00:00"><n>Mystery Diners</n><t>D</t>    <k>A pub owner in Los Angeles uses undercover surveillance to spy on a worker who she suspects is over-pouring for customers and giving away too many free drinks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-16 01:00:00" d="2021-07-16 01:30:00"><n>Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives</n><t>D</t>    <k>Guy Fieri visits a burger joint in North Carolina, before sampling street tacos in Mexico</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-16 01:30:00" d="2021-07-16 02:00:00"><n>Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives</n><t>D</t>    <k>This trip, Guy Fieri grabs gangster global grub from a Jamaican joint in Houston and a 24-hour burrito hot spot in Cancun, Mexico</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-16 02:00:00" d="2021-07-16 02:30:00"><n>Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives</n><t>D</t>    <k>This trip, Guy Fieri visits an all-female lineup that's rockin' the house in Houston and Orlando, Florida</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-16 02:30:00" d="2021-07-16 03:00:00"><n>Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives</n><t>D</t>    <k>This trip, Guy Fieri digs into the traditions of many different cultures including a Mexican joint in Houston and a Jewish deli-on-wheels in Orlando, Florida</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-16 03:00:00" d="2021-07-16 03:30:00"><n>Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives</n><t>D</t>    <k>Guy digs into a righteous mashup of flavours across the country, including a restaurant dishing out hearty Brazilian specialties and a deli serving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-16 03:30:00" d="2021-07-16 04:00:00"><n>Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives</n><t>D</t>    <k>Guy dives into beef and barbecue in Florida and California, including an authentic Vietnamese spot serving up phenomenal pho</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-16 04:00:00" d="2021-07-16 04:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-16 04:30:00" d="2021-07-16 07:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
</a>
