<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="43" t="2021-07-08 05:01:00"><p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 05:00:00" d="2021-07-13 05:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 05:30:00" d="2021-07-13 06:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 06:00:00" d="2021-07-13 06:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 06:30:00" d="2021-07-13 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 07:00:00" d="2021-07-13 08:00:00"><n>Jamie's American Road Trip</n><t>D</t>    <k>The travelling chef heads for New York, shunning the glamour of Manhattan to discover an underground gastronomic subculture run by some of the Big Apple's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 08:00:00" d="2021-07-13 08:30:00"><n>Valerie's Home Cooking</n><t>D</t>    <k>Valerie Bertinelli rewards her hardworking crew by cooking up some tasty treats. On the menu are marinated lamb chops, zoodle panzanella and chocolate marble love cake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 08:30:00" d="2021-07-13 09:00:00"><n>Valerie's Home Cooking</n><t>D</t>    <k>Inspired by cooking classes she took in Italy, Valerie makes zucchini rollatini and homemade pici pasta, before serving a decadent tiramisu for dessert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 09:00:00" d="2021-07-13 09:30:00"><n>Giada at Home</n><t>D</t>    <k>Giada creates baked goodies for the school bake sale. She prepares chocolate-hazelnut drop cookies, berry ricotta tartlets and apricot and salami scones</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 09:30:00" d="2021-07-13 10:00:00"><n>Giada at Home</n><t>D</t>    <k>Giada prepares a Peruvian meal, inspired by a trip to Peru. She serves up chicken with Peruvian chile sauce, quinoa and purple potato salad and citrus parfait</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 10:00:00" d="2021-07-13 10:30:00"><n>Forever Summer with Nigella</n><t>D</t>    <k>Food writer Nigella Lawson focuses on Italian food, preparing pasta with mussels, and black rice with squid rings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 10:30:00" d="2021-07-13 11:00:00"><n>Forever Summer with Nigella</n><t>D</t>    <k>Food writer Nigella Lawson cooks irresistible summer recipes that can be eaten at any time of the year. The culinary delights on display range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 11:00:00" d="2021-07-13 11:30:00"><n>Farmhouse Rules</n><t>D</t>    <k>Chef Nancy Fuller gathers the best the land has to offer and feeds her friends and family classic, farm-fresh meals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 11:30:00" d="2021-07-13 12:00:00"><n>Farmhouse Rules</n><t>D</t>    <k>Chef Nancy Fuller gathers the best the land has to offer and feeds her friends and family classic, farm-fresh meals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 12:00:00" d="2021-07-13 12:30:00"><n>Girl Meets Farm</n><t>D</t>    <k>Molly makes a delicious buffet spread for her sister-in-law's baby shower. Her menu features meatless meatball sliders, 'walking' fish tacos and baked donuts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 12:30:00" d="2021-07-13 13:00:00"><n>Girl Meets Farm</n><t>D</t>    <k>Molly makes a range of family recipes to celebrate a visit from her father. Dishes include scallion pancakes with maple carrot slaw, and sprinkles cake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 13:00:00" d="2021-07-13 13:30:00"><n>Rachel Khoo: My Swedish Kitchen</n><t>D</t>    <k>Rachel Khoo embarks on a culinary journey through Sweden. She explores Sweden's balanced approach to food and celebrates the county's best-loved ingredients</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 13:30:00" d="2021-07-13 14:00:00"><n>Rachel Khoo: My Swedish Kitchen</n><t>D</t>    <k>Rachel Khoo embarks on a culinary journey through Sweden. She checks out Stockholm's street food scene and makes a Swedish-inspired smoked sausage dish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 14:00:00" d="2021-07-13 15:00:00"><n>Jamie's American Road Trip</n><t>D</t>    <k>The travelling chef heads for New York, shunning the glamour of Manhattan to discover an underground gastronomic subculture run by some of the Big Apple's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 15:00:00" d="2021-07-13 15:30:00"><n>James Martin: Delicious</n><t>D</t>    <k>The chef prepares chicken with flageolet beans and fennel, sea bass with summer herbs and basil oil tuna</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 15:30:00" d="2021-07-13 16:00:00"><n>James Martin: Delicious</n><t>D</t>    <k>The chef prepares a range of dishes using honey, including cod with honey onions and apple tart with honey and walnut ice-cream</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 16:00:00" d="2021-07-13 17:00:00"><n>Paul Hollywood: City Bakes</n><t>D</t>    <k>Paul returns to Cyprus, the island he called home for six years. He visits its capital city of Nicosia to show viewers the baking culture he loves dearly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 17:00:00" d="2021-07-13 17:30:00"><n>Nigel Slater's Real Food Show</n><t>D</t>    <k>The food writer rustles up an ice-cream sundae with chocolate sauce, along with a deep-fried ice-cream and mincemeat parcel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 17:30:00" d="2021-07-13 18:00:00"><n>Nigel Slater's Real Food Show</n><t>D</t>    <k>Chefs Alastair Little and Rowley Leigh prepare a roast chicken cooked with 40 cloves of garlic, while Nigella Lawson makes pea soup</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 18:00:00" d="2021-07-13 18:30:00"><n>The Pioneer Woman</n><t>D</t>    <k>It is a recipe showdown as Ree shares awesome football food inspired by her college rival daughters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 18:30:00" d="2021-07-13 19:00:00"><n>The Pioneer Woman</n><t>D</t>    <k>Ree prepares speedy seafood dishess. She makes coconut shrimp and mango dipping sauce, Greek grilled salmon with veggies, and a mixed seafood pasta</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 19:00:00" d="2021-07-13 19:30:00"><n>The Pioneer Woman</n><t>D</t>    <k>Ree Drummond's sharing recipes from her pizza place in town, as she makes foolproof pizza dough, garlic butter and a no-cook pizza sauce</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 19:30:00" d="2021-07-13 20:00:00"><n>The Pioneer Woman</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Drummond family throw a farewell dinner for college-bound cousins Paige and Caleb, and Ree prepares grilled rib eye steak and brown butter mashed potatoes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 20:00:00" d="2021-07-13 21:00:00"><n>The Great British Bake Off</n><t>D</t>    <k>Culinary competition in which amateur cooks compete in a variety of culinary challenges, hoping to be crowned Britain's best amateur baker. Contestants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 21:00:00" d="2021-07-13 21:30:00"><n>Forever Summer with Nigella</n><t>D</t>    <k>Nigella Lawson prepares spiced pink soup and black olive salad with feta</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 21:30:00" d="2021-07-13 22:00:00"><n>Forever Summer with Nigella</n><t>D</t>    <k>The food writer heads to the seaside for a weekend away in Whitstable, Kent, and rustles up ricotta hotcakes with strawberries, a golden coconut</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 22:00:00" d="2021-07-13 22:30:00"><n>John Torode's Asia</n><t>D</t>    <k>John's trip reaches the Maldives, where he explores local life and the glossy resorts, and cooks barbecued fish with coconut and chili salad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 22:30:00" d="2021-07-13 23:00:00"><n>John Torode's Asia</n><t>D</t>    <k>A look back at a series full of tantalising tastes and awe-inspiring vistas, and revisit some of the best chefs producing diverse and high-quality food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-13 23:00:00" d="2021-07-14 00:00:00"><n>Hairy Bikers' Best of British</n><t>D</t>    <k>Si King and Dave Myers explore the British tradition of cooking with food hunted from the land and prepare a selection of dishes using rabbit, grouse and venison</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 00:00:00" d="2021-07-14 00:30:00"><n>Mystery Diners</n><t>D</t>    <k>The owner of a Las Vegas restaurant suspects his wine sommelier is somehow negatively affecting spirit sales</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 00:30:00" d="2021-07-14 01:00:00"><n>Mystery Diners</n><t>D</t>    <k>A restaurant manager contacts the team for help after noticing unusually low sales during a late shift</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 01:00:00" d="2021-07-14 01:30:00"><n>Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives</n><t>D</t>    <k>Guy samples everything from burgers to buns to bagels, visiting a deli that serves up lamb burgers and righteous ribs in Portsmouth, New Hampshire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 01:30:00" d="2021-07-14 02:00:00"><n>Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives</n><t>D</t>    <k>Guy Fieri visits Raymond, New Hampshire, and samples scratch-made corn dogs before heading to Rocky Hill, New Jersey to a 1700s inn-turned-gastropub</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 02:00:00" d="2021-07-14 02:30:00"><n>Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives</n><t>D</t>    <k>Guy Fieri searches for food with flavour and has gingerbread pancakes in Austin, Chinese chicken wings in Minneapolis and duck enchiladas in Albuquerque</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 02:30:00" d="2021-07-14 03:00:00"><n>Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives</n><t>D</t>    <k>On this trip, Guy Fieri checks out fried bologna and veggie burgers in Louisville, and brunch staples at a diner-restaurant mash-up in Portland, Oregon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 03:00:00" d="2021-07-14 03:30:00"><n>Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives</n><t>D</t>    <k>Guy Fieri checks out some of the greatest carnivorous creations on the road, including a bomb butchery in Portland, Oregon, and a righteous barbecue joint in Kentucky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 03:30:00" d="2021-07-14 04:00:00"><n>Diners, Drive-Ins and Dives</n><t>D</t>    <k>Guy Fieri crosses the Atlantic to dive into the many different cuisines of Barcelona, sampling Galician-style octopus and soup, traditional sausage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 04:00:00" d="2021-07-14 04:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2021-07-14 04:30:00" d="2021-07-14 07:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
</a>
