<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="41" t="2019-08-15 22:42:06"><p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 05:00:00" d="2019-08-21 05:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 05:30:00" d="2019-08-21 06:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 06:00:00" d="2019-08-21 06:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 06:30:00" d="2019-08-21 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 07:00:00" d="2019-08-21 07:25:00"><n>Jamie's 30 Minute Meals</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jamie Oliver demonstrates how to make another quick and easy meal, preparing wonky summer pasta, herby salad and pear drop tartlets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 07:25:00" d="2019-08-21 07:50:00"><n>Giada at Home</n><t>D</t>    <k>Giada De Laurentiis and Todd host a twilight party in their Malibu backyard. The menu includes lamb sliders, penne with roasted vegetables, and white hot chocolate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 07:50:00" d="2019-08-21 08:15:00"><n>Giada at Home</n><t>D</t>    <k>Giada De Laurentiis hosts a cocktail party for her closest friends. She provides entertaining tips and creates easy dishes for an unforgettable evening</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 08:15:00" d="2019-08-21 08:40:00"><n>Giada at Home</n><t>D</t>    <k>Giada takes a gourmet approach to breakfast classics. She cooks up a creamy polenta with bacon, caramel-hazelnut rolls, sausage and egg bake, and a refreshing mimosa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 08:40:00" d="2019-08-21 09:05:00"><n>Giada at Home</n><t>D</t>    <k>Giada De Laurentiis prepares healthy recipes for her New Year's Resolution. The menu includes baked halibut, kale and brown rice soup, and blueberry frozen yogurt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 09:05:00" d="2019-08-21 09:35:00"><n>Giada at Home</n><t>D</t>    <k>Giada De Laurentiis prepares an affordable and delicious meal of strawberry cream parfaits, hearty meatball stew, and artichoke soup with fresh mint</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 09:35:00" d="2019-08-21 10:00:00"><n>Giada at Home</n><t>D</t>    <k>Giada cooks up some fabulous treats for a weekend of football. Dishes include Caprese burgers, artichoke and bacon dip and spicy cinnamon-chocolate brownies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 10:00:00" d="2019-08-21 10:30:00"><n>The Pioneer Woman</n><t>D</t>    <k>While the family works cattle, Ree Drummond fills the freezer with components ready to turn into meals at a moment's notice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 10:30:00" d="2019-08-21 11:00:00"><n>The Pioneer Woman</n><t>D</t>    <k>Ree Drummond confesses about her life on a plate, from beef stroganoff that she loved as a child of the 70s, to pasta ai quattro formaggi that defined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 11:00:00" d="2019-08-21 11:30:00"><n>The Pioneer Woman</n><t>D</t>    <k>Ree puts a breakfast spin on four dinners, starting with sausage kale strata. Wild rice pancakes get flipped to dinnertime for the girls, while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 11:30:00" d="2019-08-21 12:00:00"><n>The Pioneer Woman</n><t>D</t>    <k>While Ree Drummond's daughter Alex and her friends have a dorm room craft day at college, Ree makes green chili chicken, spicy taco potatoes, layered</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 12:00:00" d="2019-08-21 13:00:00"><n>The Great British Bake Off</n><t>D</t>    <k>The 10 remaining home-bakers must steel themselves to face the full force of Paul Hollywood's discerning eye as Bread week arrives. For the signature bake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 13:00:00" d="2019-08-21 14:00:00"><n>Rick Stein's Taste of Shanghai</n><t>D</t>    <k>Rick Stein finds out if Shanghai has hung on to its culinary roots and wants to add a few more dishes to his Chinese repertoire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 14:00:00" d="2019-08-21 15:00:00"><n>Hairy Bikers' Best of British</n><t>D</t>    <k>Si King and Dave Myers explore food-related customs associated with wedding ceremonies. The duo help prepare a Scottish breakfast fit for a bride</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 15:00:00" d="2019-08-21 16:00:00"><n>James Martin: Home Comforts</n><t>D</t>    <k>A glimpse of the chef off duty at home in his own kitchen in Hampshire, where he prepares a selection of warming winter dishes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 16:00:00" d="2019-08-21 16:30:00"><n>Jamie's 30 Minute Meals</n><t>D</t>    <k>Chef Jamie Oliver demonstrates how to prepare focaccia stuffed with prosciutto and celeriac remoulade, served with dressed mozzarella and fresh lemon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 16:30:00" d="2019-08-21 17:00:00"><n>30 Minute Meals</n><t>D</t>    <k>Rachael puts a spin on the classic carbonara dish. She adds crab meat and makes a rich and creamy sauce filled with celery, lemon, sherry and strong pancetta</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 17:00:00" d="2019-08-21 17:30:00"><n>The Pioneer Woman</n><t>D</t>    <k>It's dinner for two with Ree and her husband, Ladd. They whip up fried shrimp with cocktail sauce, spicy curly fries, grilled corn casserole and Mexican chocolate sundaes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 17:30:00" d="2019-08-21 18:00:00"><n>The Pioneer Woman</n><t>D</t>    <k>Ree Drummond demonstrates how to prepare her own take on comforting home cooking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 18:00:00" d="2019-08-21 18:30:00"><n>The Pioneer Woman</n><t>D</t>    <k>Ree Drummond demonstrates how to prepare her own take on comforting home cooking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 18:30:00" d="2019-08-21 19:00:00"><n>The Pioneer Woman</n><t>D</t>    <k>Ree and her son, Todd, make creamy chicken cacciatore soup, Parmesan herb drop biscuits and dark chocolate cheesecake for her father and stepmother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 19:00:00" d="2019-08-21 19:30:00"><n>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</n><t>D</t>    <k>American history is illustrious in Boston, Massachusetts, and here, Andrew explores its legendary cuisine; from New England clam chowder to the hotel where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 19:30:00" d="2019-08-21 20:00:00"><n>Bizarre Foods: Delicious Destinations</n><t>D</t>    <k>New York City is a melting pot of various ethnicities and culinary fusion. Andrew explores the iconic foods from the Big Apple like mile-high pastrami</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 20:00:00" d="2019-08-21 21:00:00"><n>The Great British Bake Off</n><t>D</t>    <k>The 10 remaining home-bakers must steel themselves to face the full force of Paul Hollywood's discerning eye as Bread week arrives. For the signature bake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 21:00:00" d="2019-08-21 21:30:00"><n>Diners, Drive-Ins, And Dives</n><t>D</t>    <k>Guy Fieri visits a Tuscan-style Italian restaurant in California, and also tries fish tacos in North Carolina and shepherd's pie in Honolulu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 21:30:00" d="2019-08-21 22:00:00"><n>Diners, Drive-Ins, And Dives</n><t>D</t>    <k>Guy Fieri visits a Tennessee restaurant that smokes whole hogs, heads to a sausage cafe in Kentucky and tries stuffed pork chops in California</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 22:00:00" d="2019-08-21 23:00:00"><n>Rick Stein's India</n><t>D</t>    <k>The chef begins an exploration of the country's food in the states of West Bengal and Tamil Nadu, where the influence of the British Empire on eating</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-21 23:00:00" d="2019-08-22 00:00:00"><n>Hairy Bikers' Best of British</n><t>D</t>    <k>Si King and Dave Myers explain how necessity often forced cooks to make the most of limited ingredients to create tasty dishes. They reveal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-22 00:00:00" d="2019-08-22 00:30:00"><n>Diners, Drive-Ins, And Dives</n><t>D</t>    <k>Guy Fieri visits a family-owned Italian restaurant in Carlsbad, California, to sample a traditional ravioli recipe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-22 00:30:00" d="2019-08-22 01:00:00"><n>Diners, Drive-Ins, And Dives</n><t>D</t>    <k>Guy Fieri visits a Venezuelan eatery in San Francisco to sample a gluten-free menu of authentic empanadas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-22 01:00:00" d="2019-08-22 01:30:00"><n>Mystery Diners</n><t>D</t>    <k>After purchasing Cafe Aldente in Studio City, the new owners believe their employees are still practising old policies, so the Mystery Diners see if anyone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-22 01:30:00" d="2019-08-22 02:00:00"><n>Mystery Diners</n><t>D</t>    <k>When Joe and Fran, owners of Geppino's Sicilian Kitchen, hear customer complaints about stolen items, Joe suspects their daughter's boyfriend is to blame</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-22 02:00:00" d="2019-08-22 03:00:00"><n>Restaurant: Impossible</n><t>D</t>    <k>Chef Robert Irvine travels to Baton Rouge where he meets the stubborn owner of Mama Della's New York City Pizzeria, who is the biggest obstacle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-22 03:00:00" d="2019-08-22 03:30:00"><n>Mystery Diners</n><t>D</t>    <k>Rick, owner of Weiland Brewery in Los Angeles, contacts Charles after noticing discrepancies in his beer supply. When mystery diners Brianna and Jamie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-22 03:30:00" d="2019-08-22 04:00:00"><n>Mystery Diners</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Mystery Diners discover the classroom at the The Real Food Academy in Miami Shores, Florida is being used for personal business by the instructors</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-22 04:00:00" d="2019-08-22 04:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="636" o="2019-08-22 04:30:00" d="2019-08-22 07:30:00"><n>Teleshopping</n><t>D</t>    <k>Buying goods from the comfort of home</k>  </p>
</a>
