<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="133" t="2019-08-11 01:29:37"><p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 05:01:00" d="2019-08-17 05:08:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy has prepared himself a TV dinner to eat in front of his favourite series. But his moment of pleasure is abruptly interrupted by unexplained static</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 05:08:00" d="2019-08-17 05:15:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings are having a rave party. When Grizzy throws their stereo into the river, he sparks a general power outage and is unable to watch his favourite shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 05:15:00" d="2019-08-17 05:25:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean is driven to distraction by diabolical decibels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 05:25:00" d="2019-08-17 05:35:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean finds himself with more than a spring in his step</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 05:35:00" d="2019-08-17 05:45:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>A puzzling puzzle has Mr Bean truly puzzled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 05:45:00" d="2019-08-17 06:00:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean needs to let a room but no one will let him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 06:00:00" d="2019-08-17 06:07:00"><n>Pink Panther and Pals - Elements</n>    <k>Pink Panther and pals Hoarse, Aardvark and Ant are up to their usual adventures. The coolest cat around, Pink Panther continues to run circles around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 06:07:00" d="2019-08-17 06:14:00"><n>Pink Panther and Pals - Elements</n>    <k>Pink Panther and pals Hoarse, Aardvark and Ant are up to their usual adventures. The coolest cat around, Pink Panther continues to run circles around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 06:14:00" d="2019-08-17 06:30:00"><n>Pink Panther and Pals - Elements</n>    <k>Pink Panther and pals Hoarse, Aardvark and Ant are up to their usual adventures. The coolest cat around, Pink Panther continues to run circles around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 06:30:00" d="2019-08-17 06:35:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Cal attempts to win gold in every Winter Olympic event</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 06:35:00" d="2019-08-17 06:40:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Tad Tucker is filming the last stages of his reality show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 06:40:00" d="2019-08-17 06:45:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Egotistical actor Elmer Fudd is doing his one man show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 06:45:00" d="2019-08-17 06:55:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Bugs accidentally buys an enchanted broom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 06:55:00" d="2019-08-17 07:00:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Bella attempts to stage a perfect performance are ruined, first by falling leaves, then by the robot hoover she uses to clear them up. But maybe there's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 07:00:00" d="2019-08-17 07:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a super-secret Canadian Army prototype which resembles a simple computer keyboard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 07:06:00" d="2019-08-17 07:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings are having a blast with a bowling game they found in the Ranger's storeroom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 07:13:00" d="2019-08-17 07:25:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>After the rains, to the great delight of the Lemmings, strange bouncing mushrooms have sprouted in the yard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 07:25:00" d="2019-08-17 07:31:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% A magical hat creates mayhem for Tom, Jerry, and Spike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 07:31:00" d="2019-08-17 07:38:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Hildie and Beatie return from the Ol’ Time Goblin Fair</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 07:38:00" d="2019-08-17 07:50:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Butch spots a dolled up Toodles heading his way!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 07:50:00" d="2019-08-17 07:56:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Ginger brings home a mynah bird, who can mimic anyone, and along with Jerry, brings mayhem to the whole house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 07:56:00" d="2019-08-17 08:03:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Ginger tries to make Tom get some exercise and makes Tom take an unwanted walk. Jerry and Tuffy take advantage of the empty house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 08:03:00" d="2019-08-17 08:20:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Butler Tom is in charge of a stinky cheese, and must work hard to get near enough to stop Jerry from eating it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 08:20:00" d="2019-08-17 08:30:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean inadvertently becomes a teacher. Can he control the unruly class?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 08:30:00" d="2019-08-17 08:45:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean finds out he is a Lord and visits his Scottish family home. But keeping a castle is a costly business</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 08:45:00" d="2019-08-17 08:52:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M meets a handsome trillionnaire… allergic to dogs!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 08:52:00" d="2019-08-17 08:58:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The pets team up to recreate Mrs M's wedding video</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 08:58:00" d="2019-08-17 09:15:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley has a secret admirer…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 09:15:00" d="2019-08-17 09:36:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>Scooby and his friends decide to go on a train trip. But they learn that pets are not allowed in the main carriages</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 09:36:00" d="2019-08-17 09:56:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>Just like every year for Halloween, Fred refuses to leave the house. He believes that no mysteries will be solved on that day and that nothing will go as planned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 09:56:00" d="2019-08-17 10:40:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>Scooby and the gang are in Japan where they find out that Velma is a real star. Everyone dresses up like her! But soon, Daphne steals the limelight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 10:40:00" d="2019-08-17 11:50:00"><n>Scooby-Doo! Mask of the Blue Falcon</n>    <k>When the Scooby gang visits a comic book convention, the monster from a classic television show appears</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 11:50:00" d="2019-08-17 11:55:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Space Adventurer Bugs Bunny and his crew face a battle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 11:55:00" d="2019-08-17 12:05:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Bella attempts to stage a perfect performance are ruined, first by falling leaves, then by the robot hoover she uses to clear them up. But maybe there's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 12:05:00" d="2019-08-17 12:15:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean finally has a showdown with the mysterious Reliant Robin. Who will be the victor?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 12:15:00" d="2019-08-17 12:30:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean has to get the bride to the church on time. nyway he can!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 12:30:00" d="2019-08-17 12:40:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>The pets must help Fluffy the Vampire Pointer as she faces off against a supernatural threat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 12:40:00" d="2019-08-17 12:49:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Bunnicula's spooky brand of fun comes to an abrupt end when he drains some blueberries. They turn him blue and make him super sad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 12:49:00" d="2019-08-17 12:59:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Bunnicula drains some spinach and turns to steel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 12:59:00" d="2019-08-17 13:10:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>A genie enjoys turning wishes into nightmares</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 13:10:00" d="2019-08-17 13:20:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>After getting magically awesome hairstyles, the pets realize there's a price for beauty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 13:20:00" d="2019-08-17 13:30:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>The pets use their detective skills to track down Mina's lost pony doll…in the underworld!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 13:30:00" d="2019-08-17 13:40:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Chester's perfect day isn't all it's cracked up to be</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 13:40:00" d="2019-08-17 13:50:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Bunnicula unwittingly clones himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 13:50:00" d="2019-08-17 14:00:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Bunnicula catches a fatal case of the hiccups</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 14:00:00" d="2019-08-17 14:10:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Chester's nine lives are running out, and his eight ghost lives come back to protect him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 14:10:00" d="2019-08-17 14:20:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Harold accidentally wins a dog race. The loser won't leave until he gets a rematch!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 14:20:00" d="2019-08-17 15:15:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Mina's friendly new neighbor has her eye on Bunnicula</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 15:15:00" d="2019-08-17 15:20:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Baby Happo wants the last fruit on a tree that’s just out of his reach. Star decides to help byusing her specialist acrobatic skills with hilarious consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 15:20:00" d="2019-08-17 15:30:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean discovers the great outdoors is not always so great</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 15:30:00" d="2019-08-17 15:45:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean’s hobby goes down in flames in his battle for air supremacy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 15:45:00" d="2019-08-17 15:55:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Patches the weredude enlists Chester to help him woo his girlfriend Elvira, but after Chester falls for the same girl, Bunnicula and Harold must diffuse the stuation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 15:55:00" d="2019-08-17 16:15:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>The pets are thrilled when a silver collar turns Bunnicula into a kindhearted, totally normal rabbit. That is, until a new threat arrives to terrorize</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 16:15:00" d="2019-08-17 16:22:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M meets a handsome trillionnaire… allergic to dogs!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 16:22:00" d="2019-08-17 16:28:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The pets team up to recreate Mrs M's wedding video</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 16:28:00" d="2019-08-17 16:40:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley has a secret admirer…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 16:40:00" d="2019-08-17 16:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 3</n>    <k>59% Angelo Rules follows twelve-year-old Angelo as he tries to control his life by using funny schemes - with a little help from his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 16:50:00" d="2019-08-17 17:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 3</n>    <k>59% Angelo Rules follows twelve-year-old Angelo as he tries to control his life by using funny schemes - with a little help from his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 17:10:00" d="2019-08-17 17:15:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Daffy Duck tries to help Settler Porky Pig fight Sam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 17:15:00" d="2019-08-17 17:20:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Bugs seeks revenge on Viktor the male model</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 17:20:00" d="2019-08-17 17:25:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Roughrider Yosemite Sam seeks glory in battle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 17:25:00" d="2019-08-17 17:35:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Daffy Ducks decides to help out Red Omaha mine for gold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 17:35:00" d="2019-08-17 17:41:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% When a tiny octopus accidentally arrives at the house, it's up to Jerry to make sure that Tom doesn't eat him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 17:41:00" d="2019-08-17 17:48:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% It's Tom versus Jerry on the manor's grounds, as Tom prepares the grounds for a croquet tournament</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 17:48:00" d="2019-08-17 18:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Rick buys a drone that Tom and Jerry immediately put to use for their own high-jinks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 18:00:00" d="2019-08-17 18:06:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom accidentally visits a bizarre twin version of his house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 18:06:00" d="2019-08-17 18:13:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Jerry dreams of a life where he is the lord of the manor, and Tom is the servant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 18:13:00" d="2019-08-17 18:30:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom is hypnotized by a television show and accidentally sold as a chew toy. Jerry works hard to get him back in one piece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 18:30:00" d="2019-08-17 18:55:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>Daphne brings the gang to a fancy Ice Hotel where a new exhibit of ice age artifacts is opening. Things heat up when a frozen Ice Man goes on a rampage inside the hotel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 18:55:00" d="2019-08-17 19:25:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>The gang heads to Shaggy’s beloved grandmother’s Florida retirement home, where they learn a crazed Ape Man has been frightening the elderly residents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 19:25:00" d="2019-08-17 19:35:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben stumbles into Dr. Animo’s secret lab – now ruled by his superior mutants, the Alphas – and must help the lesser animals escape – while stuck as Stinkfly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 19:35:00" d="2019-08-17 19:50:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben and Gwen’s camping trip is interrupted by the emotionless Weatherheads – Gust-o, Hail-o, &amp; Shock-o</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 19:50:00" d="2019-08-17 20:00:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 3</n>    <k>59% Angelo Rules follows twelve-year-old Angelo as he tries to control his life by using funny schemes - with a little help from his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 20:00:00" d="2019-08-17 20:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 3</n>    <k>59% Angelo Rules follows twelve-year-old Angelo as he tries to control his life by using funny schemes - with a little help from his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 20:20:00" d="2019-08-17 20:27:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M meets a handsome trillionnaire… allergic to dogs!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 20:27:00" d="2019-08-17 20:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The pets team up to recreate Mrs M's wedding video</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 20:33:00" d="2019-08-17 20:50:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley has a secret admirer…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 20:50:00" d="2019-08-17 20:56:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>When he realises that his beloved she-bear adores the smell of flowers, Grizzy decides to offer her the geraniums that decorate the window ledges of the ranger's cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 20:56:00" d="2019-08-17 21:03:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy can’t believe his eyes when he sees objects moving all by themselves. He soon realises it’s the Lemmings who are playing around with a magnet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 21:03:00" d="2019-08-17 21:15:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>This is not Grizzy's day: after making a fool of himself in front of the she-bear, he is ousted from the cabin by the Lemmings. But his luck is about to change</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 21:15:00" d="2019-08-17 21:21:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy is persuaded that the she-bear he's in love with has been turned into a frog. Whilst he looks through the ranger's books of fairytales, the Lemmings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 21:21:00" d="2019-08-17 21:28:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy discovers the pleasures of video games on the ranger’s console. The Lemmings want to try their hand at the joystick but Grizzy refuses to interrupt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 21:28:00" d="2019-08-17 21:40:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy discovers a baby raccoon not far from the log cabin. When he sees its big moist eyes, Grizzy melts and adopts the creature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 21:40:00" d="2019-08-17 21:50:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>After a foolhardy challenge causes Jimmy and Lance to be captured by Bad Jack, Henri and Wilfried must team up to save their squires</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 21:50:00" d="2019-08-17 22:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>After Jimmy and Cat stop thieves from robbing the Queen, Cat hides so her mother doesn’t find she's skipped school. But when the Queen celebrates Jimmy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 22:10:00" d="2019-08-17 22:20:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When the Black Rats are attacking all convoys supplying the kingdom, Henri is sent with a supercarriage to defeat the Rats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 22:20:00" d="2019-08-17 22:40:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy pushes his dad into “good-deed overdrive” to be First Knight, Henri goes too far and gets busted down to “Horse traffic duty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 22:40:00" d="2019-08-17 22:47:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is preparing a package to send to her Japanese pen pal. But the Guanos are watching and get the idea to sneak Hoodie inside the package and get rid of him forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 22:47:00" d="2019-08-17 22:53:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends must hand in a math assignment. Instead of doing his homework, Victor prefers to wait for the girls to finish the assignment, before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 22:53:00" d="2019-08-17 23:05:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Seeing how Pat and Tank have put on weight, Lola and Victor decide to put them both on fitness training program for dogs. Whoever loses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 23:05:00" d="2019-08-17 23:12:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola’s mother has installed a Geocaching application on her daughter’s phone. Lola is over the moon and heads outside to start playing. Victor also decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 23:12:00" d="2019-08-17 23:18:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Hoodie has an eye infection and has to wear a special protective bubble. Lola asks Pat to look after him. The Guanos naturally decide this is the perfect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 23:18:00" d="2019-08-17 23:30:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>In the garden, Lola is experimenting in how to plant watermelons. On one of the watermelons, she sprinkles a powerful fertilizer, which is also very dangerous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 23:30:00" d="2019-08-17 23:40:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean discovers the great outdoors is not always so great</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 23:40:00" d="2019-08-17 23:55:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean’s hobby goes down in flames in his battle for air supremacy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-17 23:55:00" d="2019-08-18 00:05:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>During a visit to Buckingham Palace, Mr Bean meets the lady of the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 00:05:00" d="2019-08-18 00:20:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean takes a trip down Memory Lane</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 00:20:00" d="2019-08-18 00:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy gleefully discovers that he can print images taken with the ranger's camera which is connected to a state-of-the-art printer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 00:26:00" d="2019-08-18 00:33:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>A van pulls up to the ranger's cabin to deliver a crate of jars of chocolate spread. While Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over a wrecking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 00:33:00" d="2019-08-18 00:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>As usual, Grizzy picks the door of the Ranger's log cabin to come in and make himself comfortable, but this time it's impossible to enter!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 00:39:00" d="2019-08-18 00:46:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings have got their hands on a pack of white beans which have very strange properties: when mixed with soda, anyone who eats them turns into a bouncing ball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 00:46:00" d="2019-08-18 00:50:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy wants to get rid of the old piano at any cost. But when he notices that the she-bear he's in love with likes the melody of &quot;Für Elise,&quot; he decides to learn the piece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 00:50:00" d="2019-08-18 00:55:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>When Bash whacks his ball high into the tree it lands in Napoleon’s nest, and Napoleon sits on it thinking it’s an egg. Bash has many failed attempts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 00:55:00" d="2019-08-18 01:05:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy and Lance’s bickering gets in the way of them serving Henri and Wilfried in battle, Colbert tells the squires they need to learn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 01:05:00" d="2019-08-18 01:20:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When the entire realm is blindly selling out and wearing Wilfried’s BWK (“Bright White Knight”) line of clothing, Jimmy refuses, determined stay true to his family color</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 01:20:00" d="2019-08-18 01:30:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy finds he’s too small to complete a squire competition in gym class, he sneaks a swig of Perlin's magic growing potion and soon realizes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 01:30:00" d="2019-08-18 01:40:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Jimmy gets a helmet that will make him a fearless super-warrior (and impress his dad), but the gear turns out to be a cursed “baddie magnet.”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 01:40:00" d="2019-08-18 01:47:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Pat goes to the vet with Lola and Hoodie to get his leg cast removed. But while waiting for their turn, Hoodie accidentally releases a little puppy from his cage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 01:47:00" d="2019-08-18 01:53:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>While surfing the internet, Lola finds the lamp her mother has been looking for. Now she must find an old toy of hers in exchange for the lamp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 01:53:00" d="2019-08-18 02:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>When Victor leaves for the weekend, Lola offers to petsit Tank. When Tank disappears, everyone is worried</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 02:00:00" d="2019-08-18 02:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is enjoying a quiet afternoon with her animals, when she hears Victor cursing a mole and trying to trap it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 02:07:00" d="2019-08-18 02:13:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola decides to hypnotise her dog with the help of her hypnotising book. But she’s disturbed by her father who’s preparing a surprise meal for his wife’ s birthday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 02:13:00" d="2019-08-18 02:25:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Pat is not feeling well today, he caught a cold and can’t smell anything. Too bad for his best friend who needs a favour: she needs his flare because Hoodie disappeared!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 02:25:00" d="2019-08-18 02:31:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy discovers that the frenzied &quot;break dance&quot; the Lemmings are doing is actually due to the fleas they are infested with</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 02:31:00" d="2019-08-18 02:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Another heat wave: even the riverbed is dried up. One very thirsty Grizzy discovers that the Lemmings have used the last remaining bottles of water</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 02:38:00" d="2019-08-18 02:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings have caught a little spider. Her sticky threads are perfect for bungee jumping. Grizzy, who has no intention of getting caught</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 02:45:00" d="2019-08-18 02:51:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over chocolate-spread jar lids, which they use as chips to win goodies. But more importantly, there's s grand prize: a giant jar of Yummy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 02:51:00" d="2019-08-18 02:58:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy has prepared himself a TV dinner to eat in front of his favourite series. But his moment of pleasure is abruptly interrupted by unexplained static</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 02:58:00" d="2019-08-18 03:05:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings are having a rave party. When Grizzy throws their stereo into the river, he sparks a general power outage and is unable to watch his favourite shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 03:05:00" d="2019-08-18 03:15:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>After a foolhardy challenge causes Jimmy and Lance to be captured by Bad Jack, Henri and Wilfried must team up to save their squires</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 03:15:00" d="2019-08-18 03:25:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>After Jimmy and Cat stop thieves from robbing the Queen, Cat hides so her mother doesn’t find she's skipped school. But when the Queen celebrates Jimmy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 03:25:00" d="2019-08-18 03:35:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When the Black Rats are attacking all convoys supplying the kingdom, Henri is sent with a supercarriage to defeat the Rats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 03:35:00" d="2019-08-18 03:50:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy pushes his dad into “good-deed overdrive” to be First Knight, Henri goes too far and gets busted down to “Horse traffic duty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 03:50:00" d="2019-08-18 03:57:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is preparing a package to send to her Japanese pen pal. But the Guanos are watching and get the idea to sneak Hoodie inside the package and get rid of him forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 03:57:00" d="2019-08-18 04:03:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Seeing how Pat and Tank have put on weight, Lola and Victor decide to put them both on fitness training program for dogs. Whoever loses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 04:03:00" d="2019-08-18 04:10:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends must hand in a math assignment. Instead of doing his homework, Victor prefers to wait for the girls to finish the assignment, before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 04:10:00" d="2019-08-18 04:17:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola’s mother has installed a Geocaching application on her daughter’s phone. Lola is over the moon and heads outside to start playing. Victor also decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 04:17:00" d="2019-08-18 04:23:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>In the garden, Lola is experimenting in how to plant watermelons. On one of the watermelons, she sprinkles a powerful fertilizer, which is also very dangerous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 04:23:00" d="2019-08-18 04:35:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Hoodie has an eye infection and has to wear a special protective bubble. Lola asks Pat to look after him. The Guanos naturally decide this is the perfect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 04:35:00" d="2019-08-18 04:41:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>When he realises that his beloved she-bear adores the smell of flowers, Grizzy decides to offer her the geraniums that decorate the window ledges of the ranger's cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 04:41:00" d="2019-08-18 04:48:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>This is not Grizzy's day: after making a fool of himself in front of the she-bear, he is ousted from the cabin by the Lemmings. But his luck is about to change</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 04:48:00" d="2019-08-18 04:55:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy can’t believe his eyes when he sees objects moving all by themselves. He soon realises it’s the Lemmings who are playing around with a magnet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 04:55:00" d="2019-08-18 05:01:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy is persuaded that the she-bear he's in love with has been turned into a frog. Whilst he looks through the ranger's books of fairytales, the Lemmings</k>  </p>
</a>
