<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="136" t="2020-04-10 04:28:08"><p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 05:00:00" d="2020-04-17 05:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% A newly unpacked UV tanning booth holds the place of honor in the middle of the cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 05:06:00" d="2020-04-17 05:12:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy wants to try out the brand new packaging format of chocolate spread that he discovers in the ranger's cupboard, a yummy-looking XXL jar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 05:12:00" d="2020-04-17 05:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy and the Lemmings discover the joys of photography with the ranger's instant print camera</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 05:19:00" d="2020-04-17 05:25:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The fridge in the cabin has changed: it's been replaced by a brand new state-of-the-art appliance which analyzes the body fat percentage of whoever wants to serve himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 05:25:00" d="2020-04-17 05:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy watches a demonstration of balloon modelling on TV. He decides to make a balloon poodle to offer the she-bear he's enamored with</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 05:32:00" d="2020-04-17 05:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy needs a nice nap. He can't find a pillow comfortable enough to his taste until he tests the pillow that the Lemmings use as a high-jump mat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 05:38:00" d="2020-04-17 05:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy is awakened from his nap by the unpleasant, ongoing sound of Velcro strips being ripped off</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 05:45:00" d="2020-04-17 05:51:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The she-bear Grizzy is enamored with has lost her favorite flower in an inaccessible spot under a giant boulder. Grizzy tries to lift it: impossible!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 05:51:00" d="2020-04-17 06:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings try to catch a bat to play rodeo, disturbing Grizzy as he plays his favorite game on the ranger's mobile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 06:00:00" d="2020-04-17 06:10:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% When Jerry ventures out of his hole for a late night snack Tom has a trap set for him./ Tom and Jerry are hired by Polly the Dog get back her collar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 06:10:00" d="2020-04-17 06:20:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% When Jerry ventures out of his hole for a late night snack Tom has a trap set for him./ Tom and Jerry are hired by Polly the Dog get back her collar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 06:20:00" d="2020-04-17 06:29:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% When Little Quacker finds that his favourite birdbath is cracked he enlists Jerry’s help./ It's the hottest day ever and Spike is building a swimming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 06:29:00" d="2020-04-17 06:40:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% When Little Quacker finds that his favourite birdbath is cracked he enlists Jerry’s help./ It's the hottest day ever and Spike is building a swimming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 06:40:00" d="2020-04-17 07:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% After working hard to get Tom to drift off to sleep Jerry heads for the coveted wedge of cheese in the kitchen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 07:00:00" d="2020-04-17 07:10:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean builds a supermarket super trolley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 07:10:00" d="2020-04-17 07:21:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean gets in a complete flap when he befriends a feathered theif</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 07:21:00" d="2020-04-17 07:31:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean is forced to look after his worst enemy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 07:31:00" d="2020-04-17 07:45:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean loses his bottle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 07:45:00" d="2020-04-17 08:00:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Bean is both cajoled by Irma and spurred by his own jealousy of the fund-raising super-star Declan into raising money for the local donkey sanctuary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 08:00:00" d="2020-04-17 08:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% How can one peacefully watch a documentary on salmon fish nice and comfy on the sofa when the Lemmings are playing chemistry novices with a fun experiment box?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 08:06:00" d="2020-04-17 08:12:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy's TV remote control is stolen by a partridge who collects high-tech objects in his nest perched high up in a tree. This is a case of absolute urgency!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 08:12:00" d="2020-04-17 08:18:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy has got it into his head to offer a butterfly to the she bear he's in love with. But the Lemmings fight with him over the rare specimens he's spotted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 08:18:00" d="2020-04-17 08:25:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have discovered an addictive new game based on the astonishing bouncing properties of the ranger's new running shoes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 08:25:00" d="2020-04-17 08:30:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy babysits for the she-bear he has a crush on. There's no question of Grizzy tripping up for he has no intention of taking any risks! But he hadn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 08:30:00" d="2020-04-17 08:37:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Unwilling to share the food both he and the Lemmings are wild about Grizzy locks it up inside the ranger's brand new and apparently burglar proof safe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 08:37:00" d="2020-04-17 08:50:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy is impressed by the TV show of a magician who transforms a partridge into a bouquet of flowers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 08:50:00" d="2020-04-17 09:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% To finally be on an equal footing with Grizzy's imposing build and throw their own weight around in the cabin the Lemmings decide to wear a blowup sumotori costume</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 09:00:00" d="2020-04-17 10:10:00"><n>Scooby-Doo! Moon Monster Madness</n>    <k>It's a giant leap for dog-kind as Scooby-Doo and the gang blast off for an epic, otherworldly adventure in this all-new original movie!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 10:10:00" d="2020-04-17 10:30:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>It's a classic haunted house caper when a rich man, whose life Scooby once saved, writes Scooby into his will!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 10:30:00" d="2020-04-17 11:00:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>Shaggy and Scooby discover their new favourite food as the gang investigates the mystery of a frightening Sorcerer that’s haunting a snack factory!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 11:00:00" d="2020-04-17 11:21:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>When a marble statue comes to life at a museum in Greece our gang is caught between a braying minotaur and a sword-wielding Wonder Woman!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 11:21:00" d="2020-04-17 12:00:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>Our mystery solving gang agrees to help Ricky Gervais with a haunted antique Egyptian statue of a cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 12:00:00" d="2020-04-17 12:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>In a peaceful coastal town, Ben must not only face the archaic antagonist Steam Smythe and his latest creation, the Clocktopus, but also his deepest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 12:10:00" d="2020-04-17 12:20:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben and Gwen are transformed into babies by nanny-gone-nuts Nanny Nightmare who will stop at nothing to reshape the world in the image of her day-care</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 12:20:00" d="2020-04-17 12:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben must go alien to save the Hoover Dam from disaster but when tough guy hero Tim Buktu swoops in to &quot;help&quot; Ben must figure out if Tim is friend… or foe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 12:30:00" d="2020-04-17 12:50:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben, Gwen and Max go on a tour of the impervious Fort Knox when Dr. Animo sicks a hungry ani-mutate on the Fort</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 12:50:00" d="2020-04-17 13:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben and Billy Billions go head to head over a Sumo Slammer Set sold exclusively inside the world's largest shopping centre, only to find six-year-old Simon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 13:00:00" d="2020-04-17 13:10:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% When Jerry ventures out of his hole for a late night snack Tom has a trap set for him./ Tom and Jerry are hired by Polly the Dog get back her collar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 13:10:00" d="2020-04-17 13:20:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% When Jerry ventures out of his hole for a late night snack Tom has a trap set for him./ Tom and Jerry are hired by Polly the Dog get back her collar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 13:20:00" d="2020-04-17 13:29:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% When Little Quacker finds that his favourite birdbath is cracked he enlists Jerry’s help./ It's the hottest day ever and Spike is building a swimming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 13:29:00" d="2020-04-17 13:40:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% When Little Quacker finds that his favourite birdbath is cracked he enlists Jerry’s help./ It's the hottest day ever and Spike is building a swimming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 13:40:00" d="2020-04-17 14:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% After working hard to get Tom to drift off to sleep Jerry heads for the coveted wedge of cheese in the kitchen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 14:00:00" d="2020-04-17 14:09:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean has a bad hair day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 14:09:00" d="2020-04-17 14:20:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Bean’s pursuit of a quiet life ends in a major row</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 14:20:00" d="2020-04-17 14:30:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean gets green eyes and green fingers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 14:30:00" d="2020-04-17 14:45:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean has to replace his landlady’s cat after an unfortunate ‘accident’</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 14:45:00" d="2020-04-17 15:00:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mrs. Wicket demands that Bean drives her and Miss Wince to their booked spa retreat; and wait outside in the car until they’re done</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 15:00:00" d="2020-04-17 15:09:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Sylvester is a bad dancer and finger painter so he believes he'll never be good at anything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 15:09:00" d="2020-04-17 15:19:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Daffy feels defeated whenever things aren't going his way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 15:19:00" d="2020-04-17 15:28:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Melissa brags about helping Petunia to the point of self-aggrandizement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 15:28:00" d="2020-04-17 15:45:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Petunia invents an imaginary friend to help her always get her way</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 15:45:00" d="2020-04-17 16:00:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Daffy thinks the Sandman is a monster that throws sand in children's eyes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 16:00:00" d="2020-04-17 16:10:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Chester steals Bunnicula's foot to improve his luck but, as a result, Bunnicula's luck gets worse and worse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 16:10:00" d="2020-04-17 16:20:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>When Mina runs into trouble in the kitchen, Bunnicula summons the ghost of her cooking idol to help out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 16:20:00" d="2020-04-17 16:30:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>After Bunnicula accidentally bites Chester, the cat is convinced that he's also becoming a creature of the night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 16:30:00" d="2020-04-17 16:45:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Mina is plagued by nightmares, so Bunnicula pulls Chester and Harold into her dreams to help solve the problem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 16:45:00" d="2020-04-17 17:00:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Harold accidentally wins a dog race. The loser won't leave until he gets a rematch!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 17:00:00" d="2020-04-17 17:10:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Ginger is in charge of taking care of her mother's bird./ Jerry pretends to be a vampire to scare Tom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 17:10:00" d="2020-04-17 17:20:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Ginger is in charge of taking care of her mother's bird./ Jerry pretends to be a vampire to scare Tom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 17:20:00" d="2020-04-17 17:30:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Rick leaves Spike in charge of protecting the house against burglars./ Dr Bigby creates a machine to turn back the hands of time for his belovedcat Wilson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 17:30:00" d="2020-04-17 17:40:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Rick leaves Spike in charge of protecting the house against burglars./ Dr Bigby creates a machine to turn back the hands of time for his belovedcat Wilson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 17:40:00" d="2020-04-17 18:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Feeling bad for giving Tom’s precious blanky to Badwill Jerry’s determined to get it back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 18:00:00" d="2020-04-17 18:10:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean builds a supermarket super trolley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 18:10:00" d="2020-04-17 18:21:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean gets in a complete flap when he befriends a feathered theif</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 18:21:00" d="2020-04-17 18:31:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean is forced to look after his worst enemy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 18:31:00" d="2020-04-17 18:45:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean loses his bottle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 18:45:00" d="2020-04-17 19:00:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Bean is both cajoled by Irma and spurred by his own jealousy of the fund-raising super-star Declan into raising money for the local donkey sanctuary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 19:00:00" d="2020-04-17 19:21:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>When a marble statue comes to life at a museum in Greece our gang is caught between a braying minotaur and a sword-wielding Wonder Woman!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 19:21:00" d="2020-04-17 20:00:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>Our mystery solving gang agrees to help Ricky Gervais with a haunted antique Egyptian statue of a cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 20:00:00" d="2020-04-17 20:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% When he brandishes an Indian scepter that the Lemmings brought home Grizzy sees the Lemmings bow low before him and behave like servants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 20:06:00" d="2020-04-17 20:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have got their hands on a pack of white beans which have very strange properties: when mixed with soda anyone who eats them turns into a bouncing ball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 20:13:00" d="2020-04-17 20:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy wants to get rid of the old piano at any cost. But when he notices that the she-bear he's in love with likes the melody of Für Elise he decides to learn the piece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 20:19:00" d="2020-04-17 20:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings inherit a crate that fell off a Canadian army convoy. Inside a case emits a sort of laser beam that divides objects into multiple miniaturized</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 20:26:00" d="2020-04-17 20:31:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Near the supermarket a machine hands out surprise eggs in exchange for a coin. Amongst the lots to be won there is a super firework rocket the Lemmings dream of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 20:31:00" d="2020-04-17 20:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% At the Ranger's home Grizzy finds a high-tech gadget that enables you to learn anything within seconds thanks to electrodes hooked to the brain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 20:38:00" d="2020-04-17 20:50:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy is disturbed in the middle of his TV-snack by a flow of incongruous objects that have been transformed into hot-air balloons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 20:50:00" d="2020-04-17 21:00:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Party wants to party. Problem is no-one’s really in the mood. Can Party change their minds? Or will he eventually have to give up on his dream</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 21:00:00" d="2020-04-17 21:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola wants to take part in an animal photography contest organized by the museum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 21:07:00" d="2020-04-17 21:14:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Bubbely encounters difficulties in his pond – the oxygen supply is running low</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 21:14:00" d="2020-04-17 21:19:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is rehearsing the flute recital she has to play this evening. A lady pigeon perches nearby to enjoy her playing and one of the Guanos falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 21:19:00" d="2020-04-17 21:26:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends are organizing a food drive for the city’s kennel. But the food supplies soon attract the attention of Tank and the Guanos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 21:26:00" d="2020-04-17 21:32:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is planning a surprise dinner for her parents' wedding anniversary so she settles into the kitchen to prepare a nice meal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 21:32:00" d="2020-04-17 21:39:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is due to be interviewed as Pet owner of the Week for a pet’s magazine. Victor is jealous. Surely he’s been the best pet owner this</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 21:39:00" d="2020-04-17 22:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and Victor are both fans of the game Galaktik dance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 22:00:00" d="2020-04-17 22:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy is disturbed in the middle of his TV-snack by a flow of incongruous objects that have been transformed into hot-air balloons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 22:06:00" d="2020-04-17 22:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy discovers with great delight that the ranger has purchased a brand new multi-function Stressless recliner. But the Lemmings transform</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 22:13:00" d="2020-04-17 22:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings play kite-surf with a homemade kite. Grizzy notices that the she-bear he's in love with watches the kite perform arabesques in the sky with admiration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 22:19:00" d="2020-04-17 22:25:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy snatches the last jar of chocolate spread out from under the noses of the Lemmings. In exchange he offers them the toy stuck inside the lid: a mini-flute</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 22:25:00" d="2020-04-17 22:31:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings play a new game floating like flags in the breeze from the fan set on maximum. But Grizzy quickly rids the living room of this interference</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 22:31:00" d="2020-04-17 22:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have fun tearing down their Kapla block buildings which they rebuild just as fast. Grizzy finds that the she-bear he's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 22:38:00" d="2020-04-17 23:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings draw inspiration from lessons they find in a martial arts book and start breaking every wooden object they can get their hands on into two</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 23:00:00" d="2020-04-17 23:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When an old cousin visits the Queen, Cat Jimmy and Henri are certain she’s a villain in disguise and Jimmy and Henri dress up as footmen to spy on her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 23:10:00" d="2020-04-17 23:21:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Jimmy, Cat and Bjorn set out to make Henri and Bad Jack become friends, so the kids can play Angry Knights without fear of being discovered by their enemy fathers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 23:21:00" d="2020-04-17 23:31:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy wakes up in his dream, and finds everyone else there, he discovers a coup has been made on Epic. Now, from the dream world they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 23:31:00" d="2020-04-18 00:00:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy shows off at an exercise about &quot;how to save a princess&quot; from a tower, Cat gets kidnapped by Bad Jack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 00:00:00" d="2020-04-18 00:06:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Can Taffy rescue the family without blowing his cover?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 00:06:00" d="2020-04-18 00:13:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs. M receives a visit from a famous raccoon trapper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 00:13:00" d="2020-04-18 00:19:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Exhausted, Forsythe tries to get rid of Bentley and Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 00:19:00" d="2020-04-18 00:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley and Taffy decide to order a robot to help Forsythe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 00:26:00" d="2020-04-18 00:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy is completely hulked out!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 00:33:00" d="2020-04-18 00:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy has a cavity and goes to the vet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 00:39:00" d="2020-04-18 00:46:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The vet comes for a stay at Muchmore Manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 00:46:00" d="2020-04-18 00:52:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>A new kitten is found into the mansion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 00:52:00" d="2020-04-18 01:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Fuffernin is looking for a star for his next movie!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 01:00:00" d="2020-04-18 01:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have a blast testing every app on the ranger's tablet one by one. Grizzy, who is starving, sees that the cupboards are bare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 01:06:00" d="2020-04-18 01:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy and the Lemmings discover the ranger's latest acquisition: a 3D printer that will duplicate anything at all in miniature form</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 01:13:00" d="2020-04-18 01:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a strange gateway to a parallel world. On the other side, there is the same cabin, only it doesn't belong to a ranger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 01:19:00" d="2020-04-18 01:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy and the Lemmings clumsily destroy the TV remote control while fighting over who gets to watch his favorite program</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 01:26:00" d="2020-04-18 01:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings discover that by changing the speed limit sign on the side of the road, they can create a huge draft that is just perfect for their extreme kiting game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 01:32:00" d="2020-04-18 01:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% While trying to stop the Lemmings, Grizzy slips on the canvas and unwittingly executes an amazing somersault in front of his beloved she-bear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 01:39:00" d="2020-04-18 01:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have hitched up a racoon with a sweet-tooth to their sled and get a ride by throwing cookies in front of the creature with a sling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 01:45:00" d="2020-04-18 01:52:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have unearthed a strange little gadget from amongst the Forest Ranger's belongings: a hand spinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 01:52:00" d="2020-04-18 02:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings play with figurines of wild Canadian animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 02:00:00" d="2020-04-18 02:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Tonight Lola and Pat are taking part in a huge flash mob event. They have rehearsed extensively and everything is set. Except that in the meantime Hoodie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 02:07:00" d="2020-04-18 02:14:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends are supposed to watch a performance at Moon Circus but unfortunately they miss it. No worries. Lola decides to put</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 02:14:00" d="2020-04-18 02:20:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>At the end of their tether with their sworn enemy Pat the Guanos decide to do away with him. With a little help from their bird friends they decide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 02:20:00" d="2020-04-18 02:27:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola enrolls Pat on a dog firefighter training program. But Victor is convinced that Tank is made for the job. An impromptu contest is held composed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 02:27:00" d="2020-04-18 02:33:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Victor tests his new remote-controlled car in the park with Lola and the dogs. But he loses control over the car and Tank is carried away by the car and hits his owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 02:33:00" d="2020-04-18 02:40:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola receives an invitation from the museum to attend the premiere of an exhibition about extinct species with one of her friends. She invites Victor who’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 02:40:00" d="2020-04-18 02:46:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is thrilled she just won the first prize in a contest and will get the visit of her favourite star! Unfortunately there’s a minor problem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 02:46:00" d="2020-04-18 02:53:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>The huge tree in the park is set to be cut down to make room for a new parking lot. Lola is outraged. They can't do this! It’s our special tree! With Victor's help Lola decides to protest against the plan while Pat forms an alliance with Tank and the Guanos to save the tree. But they have to use all their ingeniousness to outsmart the work-proud construction worker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 02:53:00" d="2020-04-18 03:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>To play an April fool’s trick on Lola Victor makes her believe that he has seen Hoodie in the subway whereas in fact Hoodie is actually locked in his room</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 03:00:00" d="2020-04-18 03:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When the entire realm is blindly selling out and wearing Wilfried’s BWK (“Bright White Knight”) line of clothing, Jimmy refuses, determined stay true to his family color</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 03:10:00" d="2020-04-18 03:21:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy finds he’s too small to complete a squire competition in gym class, he sneaks a swig of Perlin's magic growing potion and soon realizes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 03:21:00" d="2020-04-18 03:31:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Jimmy gets a helmet that will make him a fearless super-warrior (and impress his dad), but the gear turns out to be a cursed “baddie magnet.”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 03:31:00" d="2020-04-18 03:42:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>After a foolhardy challenge causes Jimmy and Lance to be captured by Bad Jack, Henri and Wilfried must team up to save their squires</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 03:42:00" d="2020-04-18 04:00:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>After Jimmy and Cat stop thieves from robbing the Queen, Cat hides so her mother doesn’t find she's skipped school. But when the Queen celebrates Jimmy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 04:00:00" d="2020-04-18 04:06:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Can Taffy rescue the family without blowing his cover?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 04:06:00" d="2020-04-18 04:13:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs. M receives a visit from a famous raccoon trapper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 04:13:00" d="2020-04-18 04:19:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Exhausted, Forsythe tries to get rid of Bentley and Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 04:19:00" d="2020-04-18 04:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley and Taffy decide to order a robot to help Forsythe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 04:26:00" d="2020-04-18 04:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy is completely hulked out!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 04:33:00" d="2020-04-18 04:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy has a cavity and goes to the vet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 04:39:00" d="2020-04-18 04:46:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The vet comes for a stay at Muchmore Manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 04:46:00" d="2020-04-18 04:52:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>A new kitten is found into the mansion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-18 04:52:00" d="2020-04-18 05:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Fuffernin is looking for a star for his next movie!</k>  </p>
</a>
