<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="135" t="2020-05-12 04:29:34"><p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 05:00:00" d="2020-05-19 05:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy is bothered by an object stuck in between the sofa cushions: a big fur lemming puppet glove</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 05:06:00" d="2020-05-19 05:12:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy discovers the leftovers of a Halloween party in the ranger's cabin which was entirely redecorated for the occasion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 05:12:00" d="2020-05-19 05:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy wants to give the she-bear he's in love with a plastic ring which he finds really swell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 05:19:00" d="2020-05-19 05:25:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy finds a strange figurine with the power to switch the spirits of two living beings and finds himself imprisoned in the body of a caribou</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 05:25:00" d="2020-05-19 05:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% While salmon fishing on the riverbank Grizzy hauls in an unusual catch: an old hand mirror straight out of a fairytale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 05:32:00" d="2020-05-19 05:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% In a casing that fell from a circus caravan the Lemmings find a magic stick that can enchant objects and make them come alive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 05:38:00" d="2020-05-19 05:44:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Whilst trying to stop the Lemmings from playing with a crate of firework rockets Grizzy is literally carried away with them when the largest specimen shoots off</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 05:44:00" d="2020-05-19 05:51:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% With their endless battles over the ranger's cabin, which they do not want to share, Grizzy and the Lemmings end up blowing the cabin up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 05:51:00" d="2020-05-19 06:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Inside a mysterious cave Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a magical Game of the Goose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 06:00:00" d="2020-05-19 06:11:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>Ted is accidentally thrust into outer space during a mission and Binky is determined to get him back!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 06:11:00" d="2020-05-19 06:21:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>When Gracie comes for a sleepover, the gang is excited for a party but she has other plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 06:21:00" d="2020-05-19 06:32:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>When Binky sees an alien changing from a caterpillar to a butterfly, it’s a race against time to defeat it before it changes into something even more powerful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 06:32:00" d="2020-05-19 07:00:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>When the Humans bring a new recliner chair home, Binky is sure it’s an alien robot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 07:00:00" d="2020-05-19 07:10:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean tries his hand as an international art sleuth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 07:10:00" d="2020-05-19 07:20:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>It's Nightmare on Bean Street!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 07:20:00" d="2020-05-19 07:31:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Romance is in the air and Bean's girlfriend is determined to have a piece of it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 07:31:00" d="2020-05-19 07:50:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>An escaped prisoner suffers hard labour under Mrs Wicket while Mr Bean puts his feet up in jail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 07:50:00" d="2020-05-19 08:00:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Handy has built a shiny new cannon as perfect for pirate adventures as it is for crazy stunts. But who deserves it more: Captain or Bash?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 08:00:00" d="2020-05-19 08:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings shiver with cold sneeze and are glassy-eyed: they have a big fat cold!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 08:06:00" d="2020-05-19 08:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings find a pack of icy mints that literally chill your breath. One blast from anyone who eats them freezes everything in sight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 08:13:00" d="2020-05-19 08:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy can't believe it: he has just swallowed a spoonful of his favorite food chocolate spread and he hates it!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 08:19:00" d="2020-05-19 08:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy discovers the fondness of his beloved she-bear for meditation. To seduce her he sets out to prove to her that he too can attain the Zen attitude</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 08:26:00" d="2020-05-19 08:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a super-secret Canadian Army prototype which resembles a simple computer keyboard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 08:32:00" d="2020-05-19 08:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings are having a blast with a bowling game they found in the Ranger's storeroom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 08:39:00" d="2020-05-19 09:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% After the rains to the great delight of the Lemmings strange bouncing mushrooms have sprouted in the yard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 09:00:00" d="2020-05-19 09:09:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean nearly gets fed to the fish!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 09:09:00" d="2020-05-19 09:20:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>A brand new lodger in the house could be a great new friend, or could be your worst enemy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 09:20:00" d="2020-05-19 09:31:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean takes to the air after being taken for a ride</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 09:31:00" d="2020-05-19 10:00:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean makes a meal out of his Birthday celebration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 10:00:00" d="2020-05-19 10:10:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Granny's sister's bakery, Cakery Bakery Dock, home of her wonderful cinnamon rolls, is being put out of business so her landlord can tear down the bakery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 10:10:00" d="2020-05-19 10:20:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Baby Bugs can't wait to see his favourite children's musical group, The Wormies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 10:20:00" d="2020-05-19 10:30:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% The Baby Looney Tunes are very eager to visit the local TV station, home of their favourite live children's show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 10:30:00" d="2020-05-19 11:00:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% The Baby Looney Tunes learn all about soccer from Floyd, who surprisingly is an enthused soccer expert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 11:00:00" d="2020-05-19 11:22:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>When Scooby and the gang are investigating one of the most haunted mansions in the historic Hollywood Hills they meet up with none-other than famous actor George Takei</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 11:22:00" d="2020-05-19 12:00:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>When the Mystery Inc. gang gets lost in the Pocono Mountains of Pennsylvania they stumble into Psychic University well off the beaten track</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 12:00:00" d="2020-05-19 12:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>After Ben gets too much publicity for his alien antics in Fort Knox a jealous Gwen feels unappreciated but she soon must prove she's a worthy member of Team Tennyson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 12:10:00" d="2020-05-19 12:20:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>After a lull in alien antics a restless Ben suggests to Max and Gwen that he might be a better hero if he went solo. Ben soon finds out he must rethink his strategy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 12:20:00" d="2020-05-19 12:31:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>The Weatherheads set their sights on Winter Wonderland as their next target and Ben must become one with his emotion if he is to save the town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 12:31:00" d="2020-05-19 13:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>When Ben and Max get into an argument, Ben goes Heatblast to blow off steam against Max's wishes; but Dr. Animo spots him and subsequently turns Max into a chicken</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 13:00:00" d="2020-05-19 13:07:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom is placed in charge of the preparations for the Duchess' surprise birthday party for nephew Rupert and Jerry is determined to make a mess of it all</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 13:07:00" d="2020-05-19 13:14:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry work together to save a live turkey from becoming the centerpiece of a holiday feast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 13:14:00" d="2020-05-19 13:20:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% A ghost in a painting casts an evil spell on Tom but it backfires when Tom can no longer get hurt chasing Jerry and Tuffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 13:20:00" d="2020-05-19 13:27:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Spike falls in love with a french poodle who is actually friends with Tom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 13:27:00" d="2020-05-19 13:34:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% A set of kittens inside a knight's armor create havoc for Tom and Jerry in a haunted castle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 13:34:00" d="2020-05-19 14:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% A lovely village mouse is stopped from her big stage debut, by the Phan-Tom of the Opera. Luckily Jerry is there to save the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 14:00:00" d="2020-05-19 14:09:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean nearly gets fed to the fish!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 14:09:00" d="2020-05-19 14:20:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>A brand new lodger in the house could be a great new friend, or could be your worst enemy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 14:20:00" d="2020-05-19 14:31:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean takes to the air after being taken for a ride</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 14:31:00" d="2020-05-19 15:00:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean makes a meal out of his Birthday celebration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 15:00:00" d="2020-05-19 15:11:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>When Gordon is taken over by aliens (code name: fleas), the PURST team has to help get rid of them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 15:11:00" d="2020-05-19 15:22:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>Binky’s favourite sweater is being eaten by aliens (code name: moths), and it’s up to the team to save to stop the aliens and save &quot;Fuzzy Wuzzy&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 15:22:00" d="2020-05-19 15:32:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>Ted is accidentally thrust into outer space during a mission and Binky is determined to get him back!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 15:32:00" d="2020-05-19 16:00:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>When Gracie comes for a sleepover, the gang is excited for a party but she has other plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 16:00:00" d="2020-05-19 16:10:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>When Bunnicula is kidnapped, Harold must teach Chester how to be a &quot;secret service&quot; animal to rescue their friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 16:10:00" d="2020-05-19 16:20:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>When torrential rain floods the basement, the pets find themselves hunted by the mysterious Cellarmander</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 16:20:00" d="2020-05-19 16:30:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>The pets must venture into the sewer and face sewer mermaids to get Bunnicula's eye back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 16:30:00" d="2020-05-19 17:00:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>After Mina gets her pets micro-chipped so she'll always know where they are, Harold and Chester set out to find out where Bunnicula's been going every night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 17:00:00" d="2020-05-19 17:07:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% The detectives across the hall are responsible for a series of high profile thefts and are framing innocent people for the crimes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 17:07:00" d="2020-05-19 17:14:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% It's a battle royale over the last box of donuts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 17:14:00" d="2020-05-19 17:20:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% A scheming ghost inside a mirror trades places with Tom and it's up to Jerry and Tuffy to stop him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 17:20:00" d="2020-05-19 17:27:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Overweight Jerry starts working out on a weight machine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 17:27:00" d="2020-05-19 17:34:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom's obsession with the sound his new crinkle ball drives the rest of the household crazy forcing them to take drastic measures to rid the house of the annoying toy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 17:34:00" d="2020-05-19 18:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Mice visitors from Mars force Tom to change the way he treats Jerry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 18:00:00" d="2020-05-19 18:10:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean tries his hand as an international art sleuth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 18:10:00" d="2020-05-19 18:20:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>It's Nightmare on Bean Street!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 18:20:00" d="2020-05-19 18:31:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Romance is in the air and Bean's girlfriend is determined to have a piece of it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 18:31:00" d="2020-05-19 19:00:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>An escaped prisoner suffers hard labour under Mrs Wicket while Mr Bean puts his feet up in jail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 19:00:00" d="2020-05-19 19:21:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>When Scooby and the Gang are in Sicily they're chasing a fire monster! But they are surprised to meet up with none other than famous actor Steve Buscemi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 19:21:00" d="2020-05-19 20:00:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>When Scooby and the gang are taking a tour of merry old London they run afoul of horrible screaming skulls of English legend!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 20:00:00" d="2020-05-19 20:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% When they find an old book on traditional Japanese origami, the Lemmings churn out paper birds to play gliding games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 20:06:00" d="2020-05-19 20:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings are all lined up on the couch to watch a cartoon film where a mouse plays nasty tricks on a cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 20:13:00" d="2020-05-19 20:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Once again Grizzy shows the Lemmings that they just don't measure up to him physically and that the last jar of chocolate spread is for the strongest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 20:19:00" d="2020-05-19 20:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings lay their hands on a full crate of chocolate spread which they hide somewhere behind Grizzy's back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 20:26:00" d="2020-05-19 20:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy is persuaded that he's discovered the ultimate gadget for good living</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 20:32:00" d="2020-05-19 20:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings clamor for their turn to play with the ranger's mobile phone but Grizzy isn't in the sharing mood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 20:39:00" d="2020-05-19 21:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy is captivated by a mime artist on TV who makes viewers believe in the presence of an invisible wall</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 21:00:00" d="2020-05-19 21:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Tonight Lola and Pat are taking part in a huge flash mob event. They have rehearsed extensively and everything is set. Except that in the meantime Hoodie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 21:07:00" d="2020-05-19 21:14:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends are supposed to watch a performance at Moon Circus but unfortunately they miss it. No worries. Lola decides to put</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 21:14:00" d="2020-05-19 21:20:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>At the end of their tether with their sworn enemy Pat the Guanos decide to do away with him. With a little help from their bird friends they decide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 21:20:00" d="2020-05-19 21:27:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola enrolls Pat on a dog firefighter training program. But Victor is convinced that Tank is made for the job. An impromptu contest is held composed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 21:27:00" d="2020-05-19 21:33:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Victor tests his new remote-controlled car in the park with Lola and the dogs. But he loses control over the car and Tank is carried away by the car and hits his owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 21:33:00" d="2020-05-19 21:40:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola receives an invitation from the museum to attend the premiere of an exhibition about extinct species with one of her friends. She invites Victor who’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 21:40:00" d="2020-05-19 22:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is thrilled she just won the first prize in a contest and will get the visit of her favourite star! Unfortunately there’s a minor problem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 22:00:00" d="2020-05-19 22:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings try to catch a bat to play rodeo, disturbing Grizzy as he plays his favorite game on the ranger's mobile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 22:06:00" d="2020-05-19 22:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings have a blast testing every app on the ranger's tablet one by one. Grizzy, who is starving, sees that the cupboards are bare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 22:13:00" d="2020-05-19 22:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy and the Lemmings discover the ranger's latest acquisition: a 3D printer that will duplicate anything at all in miniature form</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 22:19:00" d="2020-05-19 22:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a strange gateway to a parallel world. On the other side, there is the same cabin, only it doesn't belong to a ranger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 22:26:00" d="2020-05-19 22:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy and the Lemmings clumsily destroy the TV remote control while fighting over who gets to watch his favorite program</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 22:32:00" d="2020-05-19 22:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings discover that by changing the speed limit sign on the side of the road, they can create a huge draft that is just perfect for their extreme kiting game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 22:39:00" d="2020-05-19 23:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% While trying to stop the Lemmings, Grizzy slips on the canvas and unwittingly executes an amazing somersault in front of his beloved she-bear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 23:00:00" d="2020-05-19 23:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>After the queen eats a lollipop that makes her start to shrink, Jimmy and Henri must capture the Dark Forest Witch in order to get an antidote</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 23:10:00" d="2020-05-19 23:21:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy inadvertently convinces Ronny Flash to do an interview with a rock monster, Jimmy, Henri and Cat end up escorting Ronny into the Dark Lands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 23:21:00" d="2020-05-19 23:31:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>To show off, Jimmy arrives at the castle flying on Bjorn, and he pretends the dragon is his pet. But Wilfried captures the “monster,” and Bad Jack threatens to burn Epic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-19 23:31:00" d="2020-05-20 00:00:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When the Queen wishes she could give her knights a break during a particularly intense period of battles with the Villains, Jimmy suggests she call a truce</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 00:00:00" d="2020-05-20 00:06:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M is sick, everyone needs to be silent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 00:06:00" d="2020-05-20 00:13:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Scraggs a raccoon uses a cat disguise to enter Mrs M manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 00:13:00" d="2020-05-20 00:20:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy tries to get rid of Addie who knows he’s a raccoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 00:20:00" d="2020-05-20 00:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The pets help an unconscious Mrs M pass an inspection</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 00:26:00" d="2020-05-20 00:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M meets a handsome trillionnaire… allergic to dogs!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 00:33:00" d="2020-05-20 00:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The pets team up to recreate Mrs M's wedding video</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 00:39:00" d="2020-05-20 00:46:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley has a secret admirer…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 00:46:00" d="2020-05-20 00:52:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy gets scared as Mrs M tests him to discover his lineage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 00:52:00" d="2020-05-20 01:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Vacation's coming! But before the manor must be secured…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 01:00:00" d="2020-05-20 01:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy gets rid of the Lemmings by crushing them with one of the ranger's heavy trunks, which he immediately clears out of the cabin, his enemies stuck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 01:06:00" d="2020-05-20 01:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% A strange object is delivered to the Ranger's cabin: an over-board! It's a latest generation skateboard which levitates above the ground without wheels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 01:13:00" d="2020-05-20 01:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings encounter a white bear which has drifted all the way to them on a chunk of ice which is slowly melting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 01:19:00" d="2020-05-20 01:25:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% After studying a magazine advertisement with a couple standing in front of an SUV, Grizzy imagines that if only he had a nice car, his favorite she-bear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 01:25:00" d="2020-05-20 01:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings discover a strange pond in an American Indian grotto that has the power to rejuvenate anyone who dips in it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 01:32:00" d="2020-05-20 01:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% While chasing the Lemmings, Grizzy crashes into an arcade cabinet near the supermarket which displays a model fortuneteller and her crystal ball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 01:38:00" d="2020-05-20 01:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings have turned the entire cabin topsy-turvy to organize medieval jousts with the ranger's fencing gear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 01:45:00" d="2020-05-20 01:51:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy finds a bottle containing a love potion, anyone who drinks it immediately falls in love with the first creature he sees</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 01:51:00" d="2020-05-20 02:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Before taking a nap, Grizzy locks the food in a cupboard to prevent the Lemmings from getting into it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 02:00:00" d="2020-05-20 02:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>On their way back home Lola Lucie and Pat come across an old abandoned house. Lola is super excited and wants to explore the home but Lucie and Pat seem reluctant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 02:07:00" d="2020-05-20 02:14:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Today Lola and Lucie must give a presentation at school. But her mother embarks the girl’s presentation sheets to work thinking it’s her architectural designs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 02:14:00" d="2020-05-20 02:20:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola’s mom bought a 3D printer for work. The little girl is fascinated by the machine. Before leaving for school she promises Pat to 3D print a surprise for her parents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 02:20:00" d="2020-05-20 02:27:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>While playing a game with Hoodie and Lola Pat accidentally breaks the television. Lola says it was her fault to protect her faithful friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 02:27:00" d="2020-05-20 02:34:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Today Lola and her class are going to visit the museum. Before leaving to school her mother reminds her to behave and stay out of trouble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 02:34:00" d="2020-05-20 02:41:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and Pat are visiting one of her mom’s building sites for an article that she’s writing for school. But once there she discovers Hoodie inside her backpack!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 02:41:00" d="2020-05-20 02:47:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola decides to register Pat in a beauty contest. But for our hero Hoodie is the real star. Lola agrees on registering Hoodie instead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 02:47:00" d="2020-05-20 02:54:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola Hoodie and Paf are trick or treating on Halloween night. For Victor it’s the best opportunity to scare the little girl and her pets but his attempts fail miserably</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 02:54:00" d="2020-05-20 03:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola has won a prize to see one of her favorite singers Lady Kawai in concert. But Victor and the Guanos are determined to get hold of the ticket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 03:00:00" d="2020-05-20 03:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>After Jimmy and Cat stop thieves from robbing the Queen, Cat hides so her mother doesn’t find she's skipped school. But when the Queen celebrates Jimmy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 03:10:00" d="2020-05-20 03:21:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When the Black Rats are attacking all convoys supplying the kingdom, Henri is sent with a supercarriage to defeat the Rats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 03:21:00" d="2020-05-20 03:31:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy pushes his dad into “good-deed overdrive” to be First Knight, Henri goes too far and gets busted down to “Horse traffic duty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 03:31:00" d="2020-05-20 03:42:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy and Cat find a witch’s broom, they can’t resist taking it for a spin. But the fun quickly ends when their joyride inflames the rage of every</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 03:42:00" d="2020-05-20 04:00:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Epic, the Queen asks Henri to compose a song to lift the spirits of her beloved subjects for this year’s Harvest Festival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 04:00:00" d="2020-05-20 04:06:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M is sick, everyone needs to be silent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 04:06:00" d="2020-05-20 04:13:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Scraggs a raccoon uses a cat disguise to enter Mrs M manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 04:13:00" d="2020-05-20 04:20:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy tries to get rid of Addie who knows he’s a raccoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 04:20:00" d="2020-05-20 04:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The pets help an unconscious Mrs M pass an inspection</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 04:26:00" d="2020-05-20 04:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M meets a handsome trillionnaire… allergic to dogs!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 04:33:00" d="2020-05-20 04:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The pets team up to recreate Mrs M's wedding video</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 04:39:00" d="2020-05-20 04:46:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley has a secret admirer…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 04:46:00" d="2020-05-20 04:52:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy gets scared as Mrs M tests him to discover his lineage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-20 04:52:00" d="2020-05-20 05:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Vacation's coming! But before the manor must be secured…</k>  </p>
</a>
