<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="137" t="2021-07-09 06:35:38"><p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 05:00:00" d="2021-07-15 05:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Robo House
Mrs. Muchmore has equipped her home with a defense system. During his sleep, Taffy and Bentley use it against each other, in an escalation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 05:05:00" d="2021-07-15 05:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Whisperer to a Scream
Forsythe, fed up with cleaning up all the Taffy-Bentley destruction, urges Mrs. M to bring in a &quot;pet whisperer&quot; to improve their behaviour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 05:10:00" d="2021-07-15 05:20:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bentley Of The Jungle
Bentley gets a huge bang on his head and when he wakes up. Doesn't know who he is anymore! After thinking of another sneaky trap</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 05:20:00" d="2021-07-15 05:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Out Of The Woods
Mrs. M takes the family to a beautiful retreat in a pristine forest -- but they soon find themselves lost in the woods. When all their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 05:25:00" d="2021-07-15 05:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Reach Out and Touch Someone
Mrs. M receives a visit from her old friend Coonskin Carl, a famous trapper who holds the world record for most raccoons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 05:30:00" d="2021-07-15 05:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The White Gloves
Forsythe can not stand the battle between Taffy and Bentley anymore! He decides to get rid of the pets but that's without counting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 05:40:00" d="2021-07-15 05:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Machine Dreams
It's time for the annual International Butling Associate inspection. And each year Forsythe has received its highest honor the coveted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 05:45:00" d="2021-07-15 05:50:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Taffyzilla
Binikos is concerned about Mrs. M's lack of strength, so he orders a special muscle-building machine. But Taffy crashes into it during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 05:50:00" d="2021-07-15 06:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Laughy Taffy
Taffy has been eating too many sweets and has a cavity. He'll have to go to the vet and get a filling. Bentley tries to show to Dr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 06:00:00" d="2021-07-15 06:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Toes in the Sand
Magoo thinks he is on a beach and that sailors are emptying their oil tanker right into the ocean. Wanting to put a stop to the pollution</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 06:05:00" d="2021-07-15 06:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dinosaur Island
Fizz has reduced the size of the moon in order to model it in his own image. But Magoo thinks it’s a dinosaur egg ready to hatch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 06:15:00" d="2021-07-15 06:30:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Santa's Little Helper
Magoo a Christmas volunteer in a supermarket thinks a burglar is entering overnight and decides to stop him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 06:30:00" d="2021-07-15 06:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>At the Heart of the Crater
Magoo thinks that he is at the foot of a volcano but in fact he’s next to a huge soup vat. And he sets it all awry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 06:35:00" d="2021-07-15 06:45:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lost in the Subway
Magoo thinks he is in the subway but actually he’s in a cave. Running into Weasel he thinks he’s lost and decides to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 06:45:00" d="2021-07-15 07:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Baby Steps
Magoo is babysitting the Neighbors' toddler. The baby flees and kidnaps Fizz mistaking him for a plush toy. Thinking he’s playing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 07:00:00" d="2021-07-15 07:05:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Chew Toy
Tom is watching a hypnotist on TV, when the words &quot;you are asleep&quot; hit him hard. He becomes a virtual rag doll and ends up in a jumble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 07:05:00" d="2021-07-15 07:10:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Live and Let Diet
The Lady of the Manor's prize Pomeranian, Alfred, must get some pounds off before the big dog show. The butler suggests exercise—chasing a cat perhaps? Tom happily obliges, as Alfred's successful weight loss guarantees him a cushy spot upstairs. Meanwhi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 07:10:00" d="2021-07-15 07:25:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Auntie Social
When Rick and Ginger go to a couple's retreat, they leave Tom with Rick's Auntie Louella. Hearing that she's a whiz in the kitchen, Jerry comes along</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 07:25:00" d="2021-07-15 07:30:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% A Snootful
The Lady of the House's cousins, the Van der Snoots, visit with their prize-winning Persian cat, Prancy Van der Snoot. Tom is warned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 07:30:00" d="2021-07-15 07:40:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Lame Duck
Ginger and Rick have installed a new birdbath, and Little Quacker has taken up residence in it. Ginger forbids Tom from going</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 07:40:00" d="2021-07-15 07:46:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% It's All Relative
When Jerry's country cousins visit the Abbey, the cook is convinced Downton is in the midst of a vermin invasion! Cates (the butler)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 07:46:00" d="2021-07-15 07:47:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rock Concert
&quot;“Chasing Lamput” turns out to be the ultimate backstage pass; the Docs pursue the orange blob through the dressing room and directly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 07:47:00" d="2021-07-15 08:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Boss's Mom
Specs and Skinny get the day off from Lamput chasing, and receive a super important assignment: go to the train station, and pick up the Boss' beloved mom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 08:00:00" d="2021-07-15 08:10:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Grand Invitation
Mr Bean is all at sea with the landed gentry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 08:10:00" d="2021-07-15 08:30:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% A Royal Makeover
Mr Bean redecorates his room making it fit for a Queen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 08:30:00" d="2021-07-15 08:40:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Super Marrow
Mr Bean gets green eyes and green fingers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 08:40:00" d="2021-07-15 09:00:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Bean in Love
Mr Bean becomes smitten with a beautiful singer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 09:00:00" d="2021-07-15 09:30:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Where There's a Will, There's a Wraith
It's a classic haunted house caper when a rich man, whose life Scooby once saved, writes Scooby into his will! Now, to collect his share of the fortune, the gang must spend a night in a creepy mansion along with the rich man's kooky relative: a spooky pha</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 09:30:00" d="2021-07-15 10:00:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Sorcerer Snacks Scare
Shaggy and Scooby discover their new favorite food as the gang investigates the mystery of a frightening Sorcerer that’s haunting a snack factory!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 10:00:00" d="2021-07-15 11:00:00"><n u="The New Scooby-Doo Movies">The New Scooby-Doo Movies I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>76% The Haunted Horseman in Hagglethorn Hall
The Haunted Horseman in Hagglethorn Hall: The gang team up with singer Davey Jones to uncover the reason</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 11:00:00" d="2021-07-15 12:00:00"><n u="The New Scooby-Doo Movies">The New Scooby-Doo Movies I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>76% The Phantom of the Country Music Hall
The Phantom of the Country Music Hall: Scooby and the gang travel to Nashville to investigate the mysterious</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 12:00:00" d="2021-07-15 12:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Last Groundhog
Magoo mistakes Weasel (in an animal costume) for a groundhog being hunted and confiscates the hunter’s gun. In reality he steals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 12:05:00" d="2021-07-15 12:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Home Havoc
Magoo can't find the book that Linda lent him and he's ready to turn the house upside down to find it. The problem is that he</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 12:15:00" d="2021-07-15 12:30:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pinkbeard's Treasure
Magoo hunting for Pinkbeard’s treasure mistakes the park for an island. Fizz and Weasel are there selling ice cream that never falls on the ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 12:30:00" d="2021-07-15 12:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mistaken Identity
At the supermarket, Magoo mixes his shopping cart up with a baby stroller. Fizz decides to save the toddler and become a media star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 12:35:00" d="2021-07-15 12:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hamster Fishing
Fizz is at the municipal pool, he wants to revolution the world of sub-marine hairdressing!But Magoo, thinking that he is actually fishing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 12:40:00" d="2021-07-15 13:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Whiter Than White
Magoo thinking he’s at the laundromat wanders into a candy factory where Fizz and Weasel are creating a bubblegum that makes Fizz-shaped bubbles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 13:00:00" d="2021-07-15 13:10:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Pitcher Porky / Telephone Pole Gag: Cherry Picker / Duck Duck Boom
Benchwarmer Porky finally gets his chance to shine on the pitching mound</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 13:10:00" d="2021-07-15 13:30:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Postal Geist / Telephone Pole Gag: Anvil / Fudds Bunny
Porky and Daffy deliver packages to a haunted manor. / Sylvester tries to catch Tweety</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 13:30:00" d="2021-07-15 13:35:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% When Irish Eyes Are Swinin'
Shameless O'Scanty is out of luck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 13:35:00" d="2021-07-15 13:40:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Bunny Man
Trey Hugger is on a mission to protect rabbits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 13:40:00" d="2021-07-15 13:45:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Quagmire of Solace
Elmer Blofudd sets a trap for Pepe and Claudette</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 13:45:00" d="2021-07-15 14:00:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Coyote Under Construction
Wile E. Coyote drops everything to destroy the Roadrunner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 14:00:00" d="2021-07-15 14:10:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Double Trouble
Mr Bean meets a soul mate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 14:10:00" d="2021-07-15 14:25:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Home Movie
Mr Bean is unimpressed with a horror movie he sees at the cinema and reckons he can do much better. Bean sets out to create</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 14:25:00" d="2021-07-15 14:35:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Fish Sitting
Mr Bean has to look after Mrs Wicket’s pet goldfish while she is away. With a ravenous Scrapper sniffing around Bean ends up becoming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 14:35:00" d="2021-07-15 15:00:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% The Cruise
Mr Bean wins two tickets for an exotic cruise and naturally he takes Teddy along for the trip of a lifetime. Once aboard the huge ocean liner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 15:00:00" d="2021-07-15 15:30:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Saga of the Swamp. 
The gang’s trip to be bayou is ruined by a shambling Swamp Beast that’s scaring away anyone who dares to enter it’s soggy domain!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 15:30:00" d="2021-07-15 16:00:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Be Cold, Scooby-Doo!
The gang hits the ski slopes although Daphne’s more focused on nailing Fred with a revenge snowball. Their snowy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 16:00:00" d="2021-07-15 16:05:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Vegged Out
Jerry discovers the mysterious phobia cats have toward cucumbers and is inspired to try it out on Tom. After freaking Tom out repeatedly, Butch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 16:05:00" d="2021-07-15 16:10:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Lost Marbles
A dim-witted cat walks into the detective agency asking for help. It seems he has lost his marbles: He's the city's champion marble player</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 16:10:00" d="2021-07-15 16:25:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Frown and Country
Jerry is feeling lonely and wishes he had a girlfriend. Spike explains spring fever to Tom and they leave him be. Jerry's mood improves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 16:25:00" d="2021-07-15 16:30:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Vocal Yokel
Little Quacker develops the ability to sing like Pavarotti. But when Tom plots to use this to win a prize on the &quot;Pets With Talent&quot; TV show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 16:30:00" d="2021-07-15 16:40:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Hamster Hoopla
After Ginger keeps an abandoned pet hamster unbeknown to Rick, Jerry takes its place after the hamster scurries off. However, Jerry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 16:40:00" d="2021-07-15 16:45:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Tuff Shooting
Under-Butler Tom helps the Lord of the Manor have a trouble-free afternoon hunting with his guests shooting skeet, and Tom's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 16:45:00" d="2021-07-15 17:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Boss'stache
The Boss just happened to capture Lamput last night, so this morning he's on top of the world!! But disaster strikes; during his morning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 17:00:00" d="2021-07-15 17:10:00"><n u="Mush Mush And The Mushables">Mush Mush And The Mushables I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>My Muddy Buddy
When Lilit creates a &quot;friends tree&quot; mapping out who everyone is best friends with in Mushton, she realizes Muddler has no friends at all</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 17:10:00" d="2021-07-15 17:30:00"><n u="Mush Mush And The Mushables">Mush Mush And The Mushables I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mushlers To The Rescue
Having rescued a Mushlet, Mush-Mush, Chep and Lilit becomes heroes in Mushton, and they're loving it! So Mushlers create a rescue team</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 17:30:00" d="2021-07-15 17:40:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bodyguard
Lola is enjoying a quiet afternoon with her animals when she hears Victor berating a mole and trying to trap it. Lola wants Victor to leave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 17:40:00" d="2021-07-15 17:45:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hypno-Pat
Lola decides to use her hypnotizing book to hypnotize her dog. But she’s disturbed by her father who has been preparing a surprise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 17:45:00" d="2021-07-15 18:00:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pat's Cat Cold-Case
Pat is not feeling very well today. He has caught a cold and cannot smell anything. Which is too bad for his best friend who needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 18:00:00" d="2021-07-15 18:10:00"><n u="Kingdom Force">Kingdom Force I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Codes of Trouble
When the crystal-mining robots that Professor Dunbit creates out of old Sabre tech go haywire, Kingdom Force must shut them down before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 18:10:00" d="2021-07-15 18:30:00"><n u="Kingdom Force">Kingdom Force I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Chill or be Chilled
Kingdom Force 'defend' a Bear Village from an Ice Monster, but what if the newly discovered creature isn't the enemy they assume it is?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 18:30:00" d="2021-07-15 18:35:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lemming Beach
A newly unpacked UV tanning booth holds the place of honor in the middle of the cabin. Grizzy gets it into his head that a classy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 18:35:00" d="2021-07-15 18:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% No See No Do
Grizzy wants to try out the brand new packaging format of chocolate spread that he discovers in the ranger's cupboard: a yummy-looking XXL jar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 18:40:00" d="2021-07-15 19:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Animal Pics
Grizzy and the Lemmings discover the joys of photography with the ranger's instant print camera. Grizzy would like to make a beautiful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 19:00:00" d="2021-07-15 19:10:00"><n u="Alice &amp; Lewis">Alice &amp; Lewis I (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Play
Alice turns up in Wonderland super excited: she’s written a play and wants to stage it, with Lewis. Her Majesty loves the idea and demands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 19:10:00" d="2021-07-15 19:30:00"><n u="Alice &amp; Lewis">Alice &amp; Lewis I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Book-Wizard
Alice is not good at taking care of her books, much to her librarian mom’s dismay. The Queen of Wonderland is careless with books</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 19:30:00" d="2021-07-15 19:40:00"><n u="Baby Looney Tunes">Baby Looney Tunes I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Business as Unusual
Baby Looney Tunes introduces the world's most beloved cartoon characters as precocious preschoolers, discovering the world one baby-step at a time!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 19:40:00" d="2021-07-15 20:00:00"><n u="Baby Looney Tunes">Baby Looney Tunes I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Mr. McStuffles
Daffy doesn't want to give up his old toy even after he's outgrown it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 20:00:00" d="2021-07-15 20:10:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Pitcher Porky / Telephone Pole Gag: Cherry Picker / Duck Duck Boom
Benchwarmer Porky finally gets his chance to shine on the pitching mound</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 20:10:00" d="2021-07-15 20:30:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Postal Geist / Telephone Pole Gag: Anvil / Fudds Bunny
Porky and Daffy deliver packages to a haunted manor. / Sylvester tries to catch Tweety</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 20:30:00" d="2021-07-15 20:35:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% When Irish Eyes Are Swinin'
Shameless O'Scanty is out of luck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 20:35:00" d="2021-07-15 20:40:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Bunny Man
Trey Hugger is on a mission to protect rabbits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 20:40:00" d="2021-07-15 20:45:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Quagmire of Solace
Elmer Blofudd sets a trap for Pepe and Claudette</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 20:45:00" d="2021-07-15 21:00:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Coyote Under Construction
Wile E. Coyote drops everything to destroy the Roadrunner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 21:00:00" d="2021-07-15 21:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (168)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Twin Or Lose
Hector, Nestor's twin brother arrives at the Manor to attend a butler training. Unlike his brother, the latter is a calamity with regard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 21:05:00" d="2021-07-15 21:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (169)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Little Monster
Binikos, to keep Addie busy, offers her candies. Unfortunately by the action of sugar she turns into a terrifying and clumsy monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 21:10:00" d="2021-07-15 21:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (170)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Boot Camp Manor
While visiting her grandmother, Addie discovers the story of her ancestor, a legendary hero of garbage collection. Wanting to do the same</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 21:25:00" d="2021-07-15 21:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (171)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mirror Mansion
Mrs. Muchmore has found a rare object: a mirror of inestimable value. But when Taffy and Bentley fall against him, they pass through</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 21:30:00" d="2021-07-15 21:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (172)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Besties
A rebel punk raccoon moves into the back yard at Muchmore Manor. She gets all the scraps by being an unbelievable raccoon badass. Taffy, seeing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 21:40:00" d="2021-07-15 21:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (173)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>I Love Lamp
&quot; Bentley and Taffy discover in the cellar of the manor a magic lamp with a genius. Obviously, this is an opportunity for our two companions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 21:45:00" d="2021-07-15 22:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (174)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A Mouse in The House
Taffy is called into service to get rid of mice in the Manor. The problem is Taffy doesn't have the slightest idea how to do this</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 22:00:00" d="2021-07-15 22:05:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Kung Fu Lemmings
The Lemmings draw inspiration from lessons they find in a martial arts book and start breaking every wooden object they can get their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 22:05:00" d="2021-07-15 22:10:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Midsummer Bear's
Grizzy dreams that he's a valiant knight who has just delivered his beloved. As he is about to take her in his arms, he is woken</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 22:10:00" d="2021-07-15 22:25:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Manufacturing Secret
Grizzy stands in front of the pantry, desperate. The stock of chocolate spread is completely depleted. He realizes that the Lemmings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 22:25:00" d="2021-07-15 22:30:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bling Bling Bear
Inspired by a magazine with a jewelry ad showing a man offering a diamond to a woman, Grizzy imagines himself offering the ranger's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 22:30:00" d="2021-07-15 22:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Intellectual Bear
When he accidentally sticks a computer microprocessor to his temple, Grizzy is transformed into an exceptionally intelligent being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 22:40:00" d="2021-07-15 22:45:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Voodoo Blanket
The Lemmings prepare a dream afternoon snack with the last jar of chocolate spread in the cupboard. Tough luck, Grizzy is coming! Caught off guard, the Lemmings hide the jar in a teddy bear-pajama case to slip away without arousing suspicion. But Grizzy i</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 22:45:00" d="2021-07-15 23:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Prints
Grizzy gleefully discovers that he can print images taken with the ranger's camera which is connected to a state-of-the-art printer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 23:00:00" d="2021-07-15 23:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Free Weasel
Magoo atop an unfinished skyscraper thinks he’s at the beach. Fizz dressed as Santa in a sleigh pulled by Weasel is giving out gifts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 23:05:00" d="2021-07-15 23:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Magoo a Wrinkle in Time
Fizz has invented the hoverboard! After a slip-up from Weasel the board ends up in the hands of Magoo who thinks he has found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 23:15:00" d="2021-07-15 23:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Great Outdoors
In the forest Fizz and Weasel go in search of a legendary berry to make the best jam in the world. But Magoo out hiking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 23:25:00" d="2021-07-15 23:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Aerofizz!
Weasel tries for his AeroFizz pilot’s license again. Magoo throws a wrench in the works when convinced that he’s fixing his roof he pierces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 23:35:00" d="2021-07-15 23:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mountain Rescue
In the desert Fizz and Weasel plan a global fireworks display in Fizz’s honor. But Mountain Rescuer Magoo mistakes Weasel for a skier in distress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 23:40:00" d="2021-07-16 00:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Air Magoo
Run! Magoo’s going to miss his flight! Unfortunately he’s not at the airport but the supermarket precisely where Fizz and Weasel are hatching</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 00:00:00" d="2021-07-16 00:05:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Wacky Tacos
Mike's wants to impress Iris by preparing some yummy tacos, but Fluffy and the Turtles are making his life difficult by using the extractor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 00:05:00" d="2021-07-16 00:10:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Cone Of Shame
Mike is forced to live out a dog's worst nightmare. wearing a cone around his neck after a trip to the veterinarian! Oh, the humiliation! There's NO WAY he can let Iris see him like this. Mike refuses to leave the house and the raccoons take advantage o</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 00:10:00" d="2021-07-16 00:25:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Skate Pool
Mike's attempt to impress Iris with his diving skills backfires when he crashes into the bottom of an empty concrete swimming pool</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 00:25:00" d="2021-07-16 00:35:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Go Fetch
A gust of wind sends Iris's favourite hat up onto the Mikkelsen's roof and Mike sees the perfect chance to retrieve it and look like a hero</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 00:35:00" d="2021-07-16 00:40:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Robot-attack
Mike gets a stroke of artistic inspiration and decides to sculpt a life-sized statue of Iris. Meanwhile the raccoons decide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 00:40:00" d="2021-07-16 00:48:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Private Eye Mike
Stephan has lost his keys again but he doesn't think Mike is the right dog for the job to find them. Mike sets out to prove his owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 00:48:00" d="2021-07-16 00:50:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Water
Lamput faints of thirst on a desert highway, so already it’s not a great day for the little orange shape-shifter. Add to that the fact that Specs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 00:50:00" d="2021-07-16 01:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Future Tense
Skinny might be a man of science, but he’s more than happy to get his fortune told for a laugh. The palm-reader sees alarming visions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 01:00:00" d="2021-07-16 01:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bentley of the Jungle
Bentley gets a huge bang on his head and when he wakes up. Doesn't know who he is anymore! After thinking of another sneaky trap</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 01:05:00" d="2021-07-16 01:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Out Of The Woods
Mrs. M takes the family to a beautiful retreat in a pristine forest -- but they soon find themselves lost in the woods. When all their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 01:10:00" d="2021-07-16 01:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Reach Out and Touch Someone
Mrs. M receives a visit from her old friend Coonskin Carl, a famous trapper who holds the world record for most raccoons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 01:25:00" d="2021-07-16 01:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The White Gloves
Forsythe can not stand the battle between Taffy and Bentley anymore! He decides to get rid of the pets but that's without counting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 01:30:00" d="2021-07-16 01:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Machine Dreams
It's time for the annual International Butling Associate inspection. And each year Forsythe has received its highest honor the coveted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 01:40:00" d="2021-07-16 01:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Taffyzilla
Binikos is concerned about Mrs. M's lack of strength, so he orders a special muscle-building machine. But Taffy crashes into it during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 01:45:00" d="2021-07-16 02:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Laughy Taffy
Taffy has been eating too many sweets and has a cavity. He'll have to go to the vet and get a filling. Bentley tries to show to Dr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 02:00:00" d="2021-07-16 02:05:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% In the Service of His Majesty
When he brandishes an enchanted sceptre that the Lemmings brought home with other antique objects, Grizzy sees the Lemmings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 02:05:00" d="2021-07-16 02:10:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Art
Grizzy tries to impress the she-bear that he's in love with by making a sculpture of her from a piece of wood. But as soon as the artist's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 02:10:00" d="2021-07-16 02:20:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Happy Birthday Lemmings!
The Lemmings throw a surprise birthday party for one of the clan. When &quot;Happy Birthday&quot; rings out, the &quot;surpriiiiiise&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 02:20:00" d="2021-07-16 02:25:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Flower Power
A gust of wind sweeps away the flower that Grizzy's adored she-bear wears in her hair. Grizzy sees this as a golden opportunity to dazzle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 02:25:00" d="2021-07-16 02:30:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Teleportation's the Way to Go!
Grizzy finds two identical vases in a Native American chest. They are communicating vessels, so if he sticks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 02:30:00" d="2021-07-16 02:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Countdown
Grizzy finds a vintage stopwatch in the garage which lets him wind back the minute that has just passed by, and can</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 02:40:00" d="2021-07-16 02:45:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lemming Airlines
Grizzy is disturbed in the middle of his TV-snack by a flow of strange objects that have been transformed into hot-air balloons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 02:45:00" d="2021-07-16 02:50:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Relax Bear
Grizzy discovers with great delight that the ranger has purchased a brand new multifunction Stressless recliner. But even an armchair designed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 02:50:00" d="2021-07-16 03:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Gliding
The Lemmings play kite-surf with a homemade kite. Grizzy notices that the she-bear he's in love with watches the kite perform arabesques</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 03:00:00" d="2021-07-16 03:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (75)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Family Meal
Fizz wants to cure Magoo’s near-sightedness for good. He and Weasel go over to his house only to be taken for Magoo’s parents on a surprise visit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 03:05:00" d="2021-07-16 03:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (76)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Free the Rabbit!
As Fizz gets ready to travel to another dimension populated entirely by other Fizzes Magoo turns up and thinks that Weasel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 03:15:00" d="2021-07-16 03:20:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (77)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ratman
Magoo mistakes Fizz for billionaire Bruce Payne aka the superhero Ratman. When Ratman gets kidnapped by his mortal enemy Bozo (in reality Weasel)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 03:20:00" d="2021-07-16 03:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (78)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Here Kitty
Weasel tends to Fizz’s toothache but Magoo turns up thinking he’s busting into an animal-testing lab where cruel experiments are being carried</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 03:25:00" d="2021-07-16 03:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>They Are Among US
Busy observing the sky in search of UFOS Magoo accidentally finds himself wandering over to Fizz’s house. Thinking that the hamster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 03:35:00" d="2021-07-16 03:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Skyfall
When Magoo treats Mr Cat to a parachute jump the two friends land on the top of the AeroFizz. Convinced that they are marooned on a desert island</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 03:40:00" d="2021-07-16 03:50:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nice Little Doggy
Magoo is handing out food to the local neighborhood animals when he stumbles on a gigantic horrific hamster that Fizz has released</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 03:50:00" d="2021-07-16 04:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hats Off Magoo!!
Magoo thinks that Fizz is a hat he is going to wear for his romantic date with Marnie. The hamster is going to have</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 04:00:00" d="2021-07-16 04:05:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Martial Arts Mike
The raccoons break into the Mikkelsens house again and Mike is easily defeated during a fight against the determined crooks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 04:05:00" d="2021-07-16 04:10:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Ditzy Home
Stephan upgrades the house's security system and it looks like Mike might be able to take a break from playing guard dog. The new system</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 04:10:00" d="2021-07-16 04:20:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Well Trained
The raccoons stumble upon an old whistle in the trash. Mercury blows it like a madman and the raccoons discover that it has strange powers over Mike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 04:20:00" d="2021-07-16 04:25:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Guard Dog
Mike's got some company! A stray dog shows up at the Mikkelsens and the family is instantly impressed when he scares off the raccoons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 04:25:00" d="2021-07-16 04:30:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Who's The Boss?
Tom walks in and catches Mercury trying to break into in the garage. He thinks Mercury would make the cool, exciting pet he's always wanted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 04:30:00" d="2021-07-16 04:40:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (53)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Dog-Gone
Louise draws a bunch of hearts and flowers on Mike during a makeup game. Mike sees the results and he's absolutely horrified. When Iris shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 04:40:00" d="2021-07-16 04:45:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (54)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Fourth Turtle
Mike, Iris and the turtles are playing a game of ping pong when a mysterious aged turtle arrives on the patio and gets hit by the ball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 04:45:00" d="2021-07-16 04:50:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (55)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Trojan Racoons
The raccoons find a brilliant way of getting into the Mikkelsen's house without anyone noticing by getting mailed to the house inside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 04:50:00" d="2021-07-16 05:00:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (56)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Mike's Paws
Mike is running around like a headless chicken: saving Fluffy from danger, stopping the turtles from breaking everything in the house</k>  </p>
</a>
