<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="136" t="2020-04-09 04:27:41"><p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 05:00:00" d="2020-04-16 05:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have turned the entire cabin topsy-turvy to organize medieval jousts with the ranger's fencing gear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 05:06:00" d="2020-04-16 05:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy finds a bottle containing a love potion, anyone who drinks it immediately falls in love with the first creature he sees</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 05:13:00" d="2020-04-16 05:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Before taking a nap, Grizzy locks the food in a cupboard to prevent the Lemmings from getting into it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 05:19:00" d="2020-04-16 05:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% When Grizzy and the Lemmings accidentally activate a magic disk representing the earth, they are sent back in time to the prehistoric era</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 05:26:00" d="2020-04-16 05:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% While fighting over a jar of chocolate spread, Grizzy and the Lemmings set off a chain reaction which sends the jar flying into space, where it damages a space station</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 05:32:00" d="2020-04-16 05:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy discovers the ranger's collection of bird calls by chance. With a simple blow of the whistle, he can attract a flock of partridges that are at his beck and call</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 05:39:00" d="2020-04-16 05:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings notice that Grizzy moves away from the jar of chocolate spread whenever he chases the fly buzzing around him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 05:45:00" d="2020-04-16 05:52:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% A magic tomahawk divides Grizzy into two identical bears with diametrically opposite personalities, one short-tempered, the other super-sweet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 05:52:00" d="2020-04-16 06:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy finds a magician's hat that tosses out objects stored inside beforehand with the tap of a magic wand. He decides to impress his beloved she-bear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 06:00:00" d="2020-04-16 06:09:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% When Tom and Jerry accidentally ruin Spike's birthday party for Tyke he forces them to take over./Toodles hires Tom and Jerry to investigate and protect her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 06:09:00" d="2020-04-16 06:19:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% When Tom and Jerry accidentally ruin Spike's birthday party for Tyke he forces them to take over./Toodles hires Tom and Jerry to investigate and protect her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 06:19:00" d="2020-04-16 06:29:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry accidentally get locked out in the snow./Jerry causes Tom tolose 8 out of his 9 lives. Tom uses magic to bring them back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 06:29:00" d="2020-04-16 06:40:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry accidentally get locked out in the snow./Jerry causes Tom tolose 8 out of his 9 lives. Tom uses magic to bring them back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 06:40:00" d="2020-04-16 07:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry must work together to prove Bog is overkill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 07:00:00" d="2020-04-16 07:09:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean has a bad hair day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 07:09:00" d="2020-04-16 07:20:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Bean’s pursuit of a quiet life ends in a major row</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 07:20:00" d="2020-04-16 07:30:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean gets green eyes and green fingers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 07:30:00" d="2020-04-16 07:45:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean has to replace his landlady’s cat after an unfortunate ‘accident’</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 07:45:00" d="2020-04-16 08:00:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mrs. Wicket demands that Bean drives her and Miss Wince to their booked spa retreat; and wait outside in the car until they’re done</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 08:00:00" d="2020-04-16 08:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% As usual Grizzy picks the door of the Ranger's log cabin to come in and make himself comfortable but this time it's impossible to enter!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 08:06:00" d="2020-04-16 08:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have got their hands on a pack of white beans which have very strange properties: when mixed with soda anyone who eats them turns into a bouncing ball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 08:13:00" d="2020-04-16 08:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy wants to get rid of the old piano at any cost. But when he notices that the she-bear he's in love with likes the melody of Für Elise he decides to learn the piece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 08:19:00" d="2020-04-16 08:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings inherit a crate that fell off a Canadian army convoy. Inside a case emits a sort of laser beam that divides objects into multiple miniaturized</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 08:26:00" d="2020-04-16 08:31:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Near the supermarket a machine hands out surprise eggs in exchange for a coin. Amongst the lots to be won there is a super firework rocket the Lemmings dream of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 08:31:00" d="2020-04-16 08:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% At the Ranger's home Grizzy finds a high-tech gadget that enables you to learn anything within seconds thanks to electrodes hooked to the brain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 08:38:00" d="2020-04-16 08:50:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% An old metal box found by chance in a recess of a cliff brings back childhood memories for Grizzy and the Lemmings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 08:50:00" d="2020-04-16 09:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings are having a blast with the ranger's electric guitar and the cabin walls tremble with their experimental rock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 09:00:00" d="2020-04-16 10:10:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and the Samurai Sword</n>    <k>The Mystery Inc. crew travels the globe on a transcontinental treasure hunt to solve a series of ancient riddles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 10:10:00" d="2020-04-16 10:30:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>When an Artificial Intelligence takes over the building of a trendy tech company, the Gang has to solve the computerised mystery and learn a lesson about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 10:30:00" d="2020-04-16 11:00:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>The Gang has seats on the largest airplane ever to fly the open airways! Unfortunately the plane is also beset by a Gremlin bent on sabotaging the flight!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 11:00:00" d="2020-04-16 11:21:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>Scooby-Doo and the Mystery Inc. gang meet up with basketball legend and bowling aficionado Chris Paul at a golf tournament fundraiser held in Florida</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 11:21:00" d="2020-04-16 12:00:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>Scooby and the Mystery Inc. gang meet Wanda Sykes who is helping save a bunch of cute fuzzy animals up for adoption</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 12:00:00" d="2020-04-16 12:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>While trying to film his own indie film, Ben accidentally allows the Bug Gang to go free</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 12:10:00" d="2020-04-16 12:20:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>When Ben attempts to stay up all night for Adrenaland, he not only fails to utilize his alien powers to stay awake but his &quot;sleep-alien-ing&quot; causes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 12:20:00" d="2020-04-16 12:31:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>When Ben interferes with malicious magician Hex’s quest for the earth-moving Titan Gloves at a swap meet, he inadvertently switches bodies with Gwen!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 12:31:00" d="2020-04-16 12:50:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben finds a rare Sumo Slammers card during a tour of historic Oldeville. But when Billy Billions comes to claim the same card, Ben has to battle Billy’s high-tech drones</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 12:50:00" d="2020-04-16 13:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>After stumbling upon a cute cat-dog-rabbit creature hybrid or Cadobbit Ben ignores Grandpa Max's advice and sneaks the animal onto the Rust Bucket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 13:00:00" d="2020-04-16 13:09:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% When Tom and Jerry accidentally ruin Spike's birthday party for Tyke he forces them to take over./Toodles hires Tom and Jerry to investigate and protect her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 13:09:00" d="2020-04-16 13:19:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% When Tom and Jerry accidentally ruin Spike's birthday party for Tyke he forces them to take over./Toodles hires Tom and Jerry to investigate and protect her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 13:19:00" d="2020-04-16 13:29:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry accidentally get locked out in the snow./Jerry causes Tom tolose 8 out of his 9 lives. Tom uses magic to bring them back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 13:29:00" d="2020-04-16 13:40:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry accidentally get locked out in the snow./Jerry causes Tom tolose 8 out of his 9 lives. Tom uses magic to bring them back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 13:40:00" d="2020-04-16 14:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry must work together to prove Bog is overkill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 14:00:00" d="2020-04-16 14:10:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean, badgered by a strange pink animal, warms to the creature when it shows its true colours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 14:10:00" d="2020-04-16 14:20:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>When invited to dinner by Mr Bean, it’s probably best to take your own sandwiches</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 14:20:00" d="2020-04-16 14:30:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean makes it to the top of the ladder… and gets stuck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 14:30:00" d="2020-04-16 14:45:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean bites off more than he can chew when he attempts DIY dentistry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 14:45:00" d="2020-04-16 15:00:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr. Bean breaks his bed using it as a trampoline. He tries to fix it but he can’t. Next morning and after an awful night’s sleep he goes to buy a brand-new bed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 15:00:00" d="2020-04-16 15:09:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% When Granny gets sick, Lola tries to take over her responsibilities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 15:09:00" d="2020-04-16 15:18:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Lola begins tattling on the other babies until her friends no longer want to play with her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 15:18:00" d="2020-04-16 15:28:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Melissa spreads rumors about the babies, and Bugs goes undercover to find the truth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 15:28:00" d="2020-04-16 15:45:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Daffy and Melissa team up to play jokes on the other babies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 15:45:00" d="2020-04-16 16:00:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Petunia gets hooked on watching television and stops playing with her friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 16:00:00" d="2020-04-16 16:10:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>When a vampire hunting dog named Fluffy intends to destroy Bunnicula, she finds herself falling for one of Bunnicula's minions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 16:10:00" d="2020-04-16 16:20:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>When Bunnicula gets a visit from the guinea pig Lugosi, he doesn't realize that his old friend isn't exactly treating his new friend with respect…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 16:20:00" d="2020-04-16 16:30:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>After Chester decides to get rid of Bunnicula by passing him off to someone else at an all-night pet adoption fair, he soon begins to regret his decision</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 16:30:00" d="2020-04-16 16:45:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Mina leaves the pets out in the spooky old dog house in the Orlock courtyard overnight. Little does she realize, the doghouse is haunted by the ghost of a playful puppy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 16:45:00" d="2020-04-16 17:00:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Chester's nine lives are running out, and his eight ghost lives come back to protect him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 17:00:00" d="2020-04-16 17:10:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% When Jerry ventures out of his hole for a late night snack Tom has a trap set for him./ Tom and Jerry are hired by Polly the Dog get back her collar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 17:10:00" d="2020-04-16 17:20:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% When Jerry ventures out of his hole for a late night snack Tom has a trap set for him./ Tom and Jerry are hired by Polly the Dog get back her collar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 17:20:00" d="2020-04-16 17:29:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% When Little Quacker finds that his favourite birdbath is cracked he enlists Jerry’s help./ It's the hottest day ever and Spike is building a swimming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 17:29:00" d="2020-04-16 17:40:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% When Little Quacker finds that his favourite birdbath is cracked he enlists Jerry’s help./ It's the hottest day ever and Spike is building a swimming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 17:40:00" d="2020-04-16 18:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% After working hard to get Tom to drift off to sleep Jerry heads for the coveted wedge of cheese in the kitchen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 18:00:00" d="2020-04-16 18:09:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean has a bad hair day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 18:09:00" d="2020-04-16 18:20:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Bean’s pursuit of a quiet life ends in a major row</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 18:20:00" d="2020-04-16 18:30:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean gets green eyes and green fingers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 18:30:00" d="2020-04-16 18:45:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean has to replace his landlady’s cat after an unfortunate ‘accident’</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 18:45:00" d="2020-04-16 19:00:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mrs. Wicket demands that Bean drives her and Miss Wince to their booked spa retreat; and wait outside in the car until they’re done</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 19:00:00" d="2020-04-16 19:21:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>Scooby-Doo and the Mystery Inc. gang meet up with basketball legend and bowling aficionado Chris Paul at a golf tournament fundraiser held in Florida</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 19:21:00" d="2020-04-16 20:00:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>Scooby and the Mystery Inc. gang meet Wanda Sykes who is helping save a bunch of cute fuzzy animals up for adoption</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 20:00:00" d="2020-04-16 20:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy is persuaded that the she-bear he's in love with has been turned into a frog. Whilst he looks through the ranger's books of fairytales the Lemmings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 20:06:00" d="2020-04-16 20:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy stands in front of the pantry, desperate. The stock of chocolate spread is completely depleted. He realizes that the Lemmings are making some themselves!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 20:13:00" d="2020-04-16 20:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Inspired by a magazine with a jewellery ad showing a man offering a diamond to a woman Grizzy imagines himself offering the ranger's engagement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 20:19:00" d="2020-04-16 20:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% When he accidentally sticks a computer microprocessor to his temple Grizzy is transformed into an exceptionally intelligent being capable of predicting events to come</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 20:26:00" d="2020-04-16 20:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings prepare a dream afternoon snack with the last jar of chocolate spread in the cupboard. Tough luck Grizzy is coming!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 20:32:00" d="2020-04-16 20:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy gleefully discovers that he can print images taken with the ranger's camera which is connected to a state-of-the-art printer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 20:38:00" d="2020-04-16 20:50:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Under the wood floor of the log cabin Grizzy and the Lemmings discover the entrance to an underground gallery with an old treasure card that indicates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 20:50:00" d="2020-04-16 21:00:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Fixit tries to help Party Happo lay a fantastic new dance floor for his party but runs into a formidable adversary - a stubborn tree stump. The stakes are high</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 21:00:00" d="2020-04-16 21:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola enrolls Pat on a dog firefighter training program. But Victor is convinced that Tank is made for the job. An impromptu contest is held composed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 21:07:00" d="2020-04-16 21:13:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Victor tests his new remote-controlled car in the park with Lola and the dogs. But he loses control over the car and Tank is carried away by the car and hits his owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 21:13:00" d="2020-04-16 21:19:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola receives an invitation from the museum to attend the premiere of an exhibition about extinct species with one of her friends. She invites Victor who’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 21:19:00" d="2020-04-16 21:26:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is thrilled she just won the first prize in a contest and will get the visit of her favourite star! Unfortunately there’s a minor problem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 21:26:00" d="2020-04-16 21:33:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>The huge tree in the park is set to be cut down to make room for a new parking lot. Lola is outraged. They can't do this! It’s our special tree! With Victor's help Lola decides to protest against the plan while Pat forms an alliance with Tank and the Guanos to save the tree. But they have to use all their ingeniousness to outsmart the work-proud construction worker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 21:33:00" d="2020-04-16 21:39:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>To play an April fool’s trick on Lola Victor makes her believe that he has seen Hoodie in the subway whereas in fact Hoodie is actually locked in his room</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 21:39:00" d="2020-04-16 22:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>While playing with Pat and Hoodie Lola hears beautiful bird song. She looks in her dad’s ornithology book and finds out the bird is actually a parrot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 22:00:00" d="2020-04-16 22:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Under the wood floor of the log cabin Grizzy and the Lemmings discover the entrance to an underground gallery with an old treasure card that indicates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 22:06:00" d="2020-04-16 22:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% When he brandishes an Indian scepter that the Lemmings brought home Grizzy sees the Lemmings bow low before him and behave like servants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 22:13:00" d="2020-04-16 22:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy tries to impress the she-bear he's in love with by making a sculpture of her from a piece of wood. But the Lemmings gnaw at the</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 22:19:00" d="2020-04-16 22:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings throw a surprise birthday party for one of the clan. When Happy Birthday rings out the surpriiiiiise is as great for Grizzy as it is for the birthday Lemming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 22:26:00" d="2020-04-16 22:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% A gust of wind sweeps away the flower that Grizzy's adored she-bear wears in her hair. Grizzy sees this as a golden opportunity to dazzle her by bringing it back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 22:32:00" d="2020-04-16 22:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy finds communicating vessels. If he sticks his hand in one it comes out the other regardless of the distance between them. This should satisfy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 22:39:00" d="2020-04-16 23:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy finds a vintage stopwatch in the garage which lets you wind back the minute that has just passed by and it can even stop time and movement in one's surroundings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 23:00:00" d="2020-04-16 23:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Cat insists the Queen let her babysit for her cousin Louis, she discovers the 5-year-old is more of a rascal than she ever imagined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 23:10:00" d="2020-04-16 23:21:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Lady Fontaine leaves Princess High to dedicate herself to horse dance. But she’s a terrible horse rider and constantly risks her life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 23:21:00" d="2020-04-16 23:31:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Cat’s impulsiveness causes her, Jimmy and Henri to get captured by the Witch and the Black Rats, Cat is obliged to drive the Witch to Epic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-16 23:31:00" d="2020-04-17 00:00:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Cat has a school essay “your favourite legendary warrior” she eagerly talks about the Swan. But Lady Fontaine instantly rejects it, claiming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 00:00:00" d="2020-04-17 00:06:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Driiing! Taffy lives the same day for ever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 00:06:00" d="2020-04-17 00:13:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy becomes a huge star on internet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 00:13:00" d="2020-04-17 00:20:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley orders a bottle of caviar eau to trap Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 00:20:00" d="2020-04-17 00:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M registers Taffy in the biggest cat show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 00:26:00" d="2020-04-17 00:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy feels nostalgia for his former home – the dump</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 00:33:00" d="2020-04-17 00:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley sends Taffy to a factory on the other side of the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 00:39:00" d="2020-04-17 00:46:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs. Muchmore has equipped her home with a defense system</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 00:46:00" d="2020-04-17 00:52:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M calls a 'pet whisperer' to improve pets behaviour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 00:52:00" d="2020-04-17 01:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley doesn't know who he is and thinks he's a racoon!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 01:00:00" d="2020-04-17 01:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% A newly unpacked UV tanning booth holds the place of honor in the middle of the cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 01:06:00" d="2020-04-17 01:12:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy wants to try out the brand new packaging format of chocolate spread that he discovers in the ranger's cupboard, a yummy-looking XXL jar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 01:12:00" d="2020-04-17 01:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy and the Lemmings discover the joys of photography with the ranger's instant print camera</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 01:19:00" d="2020-04-17 01:25:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The fridge in the cabin has changed: it's been replaced by a brand new state-of-the-art appliance which analyzes the body fat percentage of whoever wants to serve himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 01:25:00" d="2020-04-17 01:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy watches a demonstration of balloon modelling on TV. He decides to make a balloon poodle to offer the she-bear he's enamored with</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 01:32:00" d="2020-04-17 01:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy needs a nice nap. He can't find a pillow comfortable enough to his taste until he tests the pillow that the Lemmings use as a high-jump mat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 01:38:00" d="2020-04-17 01:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy is awakened from his nap by the unpleasant, ongoing sound of Velcro strips being ripped off</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 01:45:00" d="2020-04-17 01:51:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The she-bear Grizzy is enamored with has lost her favorite flower in an inaccessible spot under a giant boulder. Grizzy tries to lift it: impossible!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 01:51:00" d="2020-04-17 02:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings try to catch a bat to play rodeo, disturbing Grizzy as he plays his favorite game on the ranger's mobile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 02:00:00" d="2020-04-17 02:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is enjoying a quiet afternoon with her animals when she hears Victor cursing a mole and trying to trap it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 02:07:00" d="2020-04-17 02:13:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola decides to hypnotise her dog with the help of her hypnotising book. But she’s disturbed by her father who’s preparing a surprise meal for his wife’ s birthday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 02:13:00" d="2020-04-17 02:20:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Pat is not feeling well today he caught a cold and can’t smell anything. Too bad for his best friend who needs a favour: she needs his flare because Hoodie disappeared!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 02:20:00" d="2020-04-17 02:27:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is preparing a package to send to her Japanese pen pal. But the Guanos are watching and get the idea to sneak Hoodie inside the package and get rid of him forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 02:27:00" d="2020-04-17 02:33:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Seeing how Pat and Tank have put on weight Lola and Victor decide to put them both on fitness training program for dogs. Whoever loses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 02:33:00" d="2020-04-17 02:40:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends must hand in a math assignment. Instead of doing his homework Victor prefers to wait for the girls to finish the assignment before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 02:40:00" d="2020-04-17 02:46:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola’s mother has installed a Geocaching application on her daughter’s phone. Lola is over the moon and heads outside to start playing. Victor also decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 02:46:00" d="2020-04-17 02:53:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>In the garden Lola is experimenting in how to plant watermelons. On one of the watermelons she sprinkles a powerful fertilizer which is also very dangerous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 02:53:00" d="2020-04-17 03:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Hoodie has an eye infection and has to wear a special protective bubble. Lola asks Pat to look after him. The Guanos naturally decide this is the perfect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 03:00:00" d="2020-04-17 03:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy shows off at an exercise about &quot;how to save a princess&quot; from a tower, Cat gets kidnapped by Bad Jack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 03:10:00" d="2020-04-17 03:21:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>To celebrate the Dragon New Year, Bad Jack plans to throw Henri and Jimmy into a bottomless pit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 03:21:00" d="2020-04-17 03:31:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When the evil witch turns all the knights into frogs but Henri, he's the only one who can save the kingdom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 03:31:00" d="2020-04-17 03:42:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy loses his dad’s prized mandolin, he makes a deal with a witch to replace it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 03:42:00" d="2020-04-17 04:00:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy and Lance’s bickering gets in the way of them serving Henri and Wilfried in battle, Colbert tells the squires they need to learn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 04:00:00" d="2020-04-17 04:06:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Driiing! Taffy lives the same day for ever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 04:06:00" d="2020-04-17 04:13:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy becomes a huge star on internet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 04:13:00" d="2020-04-17 04:20:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley orders a bottle of caviar eau to trap Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 04:20:00" d="2020-04-17 04:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M registers Taffy in the biggest cat show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 04:26:00" d="2020-04-17 04:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy feels nostalgia for his former home – the dump</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 04:33:00" d="2020-04-17 04:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley sends Taffy to a factory on the other side of the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 04:39:00" d="2020-04-17 04:46:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs. Muchmore has equipped her home with a defense system</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 04:46:00" d="2020-04-17 04:52:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M calls a 'pet whisperer' to improve pets behaviour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-17 04:52:00" d="2020-04-17 05:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley doesn't know who he is and thinks he's a racoon!</k>  </p>
</a>
