<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="138" t="2021-07-09 06:36:27"><p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 05:00:00" d="2021-07-16 05:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pet Therapist
The vet comes for a stay at Muchmore Manor. She immediately declares Taffy and Bentley have big issues. She knows because</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 05:05:00" d="2021-07-16 05:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>There Kitty Kitty
A new kitten is found into the mansion. Now Mrs. M is in love with the kitten and Taffy must try to do him in but something is weird</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 05:10:00" d="2021-07-16 05:20:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A Star is Born
Fuffernin is looking for a star for his next movie! Mrs M is in a hurry . But first and foremost, Bentley must succeed his casting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 05:20:00" d="2021-07-16 05:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Makeover Fakeover
Taffy must clear his jam-packed eating schedule to make Mish and Mash birthday party or risk losing their friendships for good! Unfortunately their party turns out to be at the exact same time Mrs. M is having a photographer over from a magazine to take p</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 05:25:00" d="2021-07-16 05:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Eye of the Racoon
Bentley is worried this disgusting fake cat but true racoon will bring shame on the Muchmore family with his disgusting manners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 05:30:00" d="2021-07-16 05:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Sweaters - Christmas
Christmas holidays are approaching, and Taffy thinks it would be hysterical if he could somehow get Mrs. Muchmore to buy Bentley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 05:40:00" d="2021-07-16 05:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>School's Fools
Mrs. Muchmore just finished an online course! Those online courses really work! Bentley gets a great idea…who says you can't teach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 05:45:00" d="2021-07-16 05:50:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Citizen Taffy
Bentley decide to make a newspaper and begins a real journalistic war. Taffy immediately recognizes his archrival alias and decide to get revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 05:50:00" d="2021-07-16 06:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Flowers For Bentley
Mrs M find an old special hypno-watch in the attic and gives her to Addie to play with it. Delightful! Taffy craftily swipes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 06:00:00" d="2021-07-16 06:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Golden Fizz
Fizz plans on replacing the statue from an Oscar-like award's ceremony, with a statue in his effigy. But Magoo grabs it, thinking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 06:05:00" d="2021-07-16 06:10:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Saving the Gnomes of Astroturf
Magoo mistakes some kids at the park for gnomes in a magic forest. Fizz uses a remote to immobilize them to win over their parents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 06:10:00" d="2021-07-16 06:30:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dusk of the Cucumber
Fizz invents a cucumber that turns whoever is holding it into an object of human worship. When Magoo sees hypnotized passers-by being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 06:30:00" d="2021-07-16 06:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Spinning Headlock Elbow Drop
Magoo thinks that he is auditioning for a circus troop but he is actually in a professional wrestling ring in the middle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 06:35:00" d="2021-07-16 06:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mega Magoo vs Dr. Fizz
Fizz controlling a robot distributes free ice cream to everyone in the city. When Magoo mistakes him for a destructive monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 06:40:00" d="2021-07-16 07:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ghost Hunt
Fizz has invented a machine which stops toast from landing butter-side down. Magoo paying his neighbor a visit sees some floating toast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 07:00:00" d="2021-07-16 07:05:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Vegged Out
Jerry discovers the mysterious phobia cats have toward cucumbers and is inspired to try it out on Tom. After freaking Tom out repeatedly, Butch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 07:05:00" d="2021-07-16 07:10:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Lost Marbles
A dim-witted cat walks into the detective agency asking for help. It seems he has lost his marbles: He's the city's champion marble player</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 07:10:00" d="2021-07-16 07:25:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Frown and Country
Jerry is feeling lonely and wishes he had a girlfriend. Spike explains spring fever to Tom and they leave him be. Jerry's mood improves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 07:25:00" d="2021-07-16 07:30:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Vocal Yokel
Little Quacker develops the ability to sing like Pavarotti. But when Tom plots to use this to win a prize on the &quot;Pets With Talent&quot; TV show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 07:30:00" d="2021-07-16 07:40:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Hamster Hoopla
After Ginger keeps an abandoned pet hamster unbeknown to Rick, Jerry takes its place after the hamster scurries off. However, Jerry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 07:40:00" d="2021-07-16 07:45:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Tuff Shooting
Under-Butler Tom helps the Lord of the Manor have a trouble-free afternoon hunting with his guests shooting skeet, and Tom's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 07:45:00" d="2021-07-16 08:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Boss'stache
The Boss just happened to capture Lamput last night, so this morning he's on top of the world!! But disaster strikes; during his morning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 08:00:00" d="2021-07-16 08:10:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Double Trouble
Mr Bean meets a soul mate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 08:10:00" d="2021-07-16 08:30:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Home Movie
Mr Bean is unimpressed with a horror movie he sees at the cinema and reckons he can do much better. Bean sets out to create</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 08:30:00" d="2021-07-16 08:40:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Fish Sitting
Mr Bean has to look after Mrs Wicket’s pet goldfish while she is away. With a ravenous Scrapper sniffing around Bean ends up becoming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 08:40:00" d="2021-07-16 09:00:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% The Cruise
Mr Bean wins two tickets for an exotic cruise and naturally he takes Teddy along for the trip of a lifetime. Once aboard the huge ocean liner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 09:00:00" d="2021-07-16 09:30:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Saga of the Swamp. 
The gang’s trip to be bayou is ruined by a shambling Swamp Beast that’s scaring away anyone who dares to enter it’s soggy domain!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 09:30:00" d="2021-07-16 10:00:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Be Cold, Scooby-Doo!
The gang hits the ski slopes although Daphne’s more focused on nailing Fred with a revenge snowball. Their snowy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 10:00:00" d="2021-07-16 11:15:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and the Legend of the Vampire</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Music, mystery and a legendary Australian vampire are all part of the mix when Scooby-Doo travels Down Under for a hair-raising adventure in this all-new Scooby-Doo movie!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 11:15:00" d="2021-07-16 11:35:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Me, Myself and A.I.
When an Artificial Intelligence takes over the building of a trendy tech company the Gang has to solve the computerised mystery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 11:35:00" d="2021-07-16 11:40:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show V (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Sock it to Me
There has been a wave of sock thefts from the local laundromat and the Cat and Mouse Detectives have been hired by Pontius Pig to solve</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 11:40:00" d="2021-07-16 12:00:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show V (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Pumpkin Punks
Maude tasks Tom with guarding her prize pumpkin until she enters it into competition at the county fair</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 12:00:00" d="2021-07-16 12:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Poolwatch!
Magoo thinks that the whole neighborhood has been flooded when in fact he is just at the local swimming pool. He starts trying to rescue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 12:05:00" d="2021-07-16 12:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hibernafizz
Magoo comes across Fizz encased in ice and thinks he has found a prehistoric man. He thaws him out and acts like a Cro-Magnon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 12:15:00" d="2021-07-16 12:30:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fizz Tower
Thinking he’s hunting down a rat in his attic Magoo finds himself on the theme park devoted to…the glory of Fizz. He decides to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 12:30:00" d="2021-07-16 12:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Magoo in Shining Armor
Magoo on a construction site thinks he’s been hired for a medieval theater show. Fizz and Weasel bump into Magoo at</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 12:35:00" d="2021-07-16 12:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Space Hamster
In order to make himself an object of worship Fizz makes people believe he’s an alien coming to share his wisdom. Magoo mistakes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 12:40:00" d="2021-07-16 13:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Doctor Magoo
Magoo thinks he’s helping out at an understaffed veterinary clinic. In fact he’s at the supermarket where Fizz is trying to gain popularity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 13:00:00" d="2021-07-16 13:10:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Shoe Shine-nanigans /…
Elmer visits Daffy for a quick shoe shine. / Wile E. Coyote clones himself to catch the Road Runner. / Porky is running</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 13:10:00" d="2021-07-16 13:30:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Shell-Shocked / Daffy Dentist
Bugs races against Cecil the Turtle for the title of &quot;fastest thing in New York City.&quot; / The only thing more painful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 13:30:00" d="2021-07-16 13:35:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% The Bunny and the Goon
Bugs is watching a hockey game and calls out cheating</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 13:35:00" d="2021-07-16 13:40:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Model T. Fudd
Bugs Bunny works on an assembly line in a car factory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 13:40:00" d="2021-07-16 13:45:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Victory Clasp
Bugs and the gang teach squeaks the Victory Clasp Song</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 13:45:00" d="2021-07-16 14:00:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Lola Rider
Rhoda Roundhouse tears up the forest with her muscle car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 14:00:00" d="2021-07-16 14:10:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Coconut Shy
Mr Bean goes to his favourite china shop to buy a new cup for Teddy but when he opens his wallet he doesn’t have enough money to pay for it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 14:10:00" d="2021-07-16 14:25:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Green Bean
Mr Bean’s electricity supply is cut off when Mrs Wicket sees the cost of her enormous electricity bill. As the snow falls outside Mr Bean’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 14:25:00" d="2021-07-16 14:35:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Cash Machine
Mr Bean goes to his local bakery to buy a cake but finds he doesn’t have any money. He goes to the bank to use the cash machine but he can’t</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 14:35:00" d="2021-07-16 15:00:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Litterbug
Mr Bean is furious with the untidy state of the streets and all the people who drop litter so he goes on a one-man mission to clean up the town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 15:00:00" d="2021-07-16 15:30:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Scary Christmas
It's Christmas Eve and Fred is ready to solve a Christmas mystery! Unfortunately the town the gang has arrived in is being attacked</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 15:30:00" d="2021-07-16 16:00:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Giant Problems
Daphne brings the gang to Ireland to visit an ancient Blake family castle. As the gang becomes enchanted by the magical Emerald</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 16:00:00" d="2021-07-16 16:05:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Anger Mismanagement
Inside the house, Tom and Jerry get into a full-on brawl. Steam comes out of their ears as they face off. Just then, Ginger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 16:05:00" d="2021-07-16 16:10:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Vampire State
On the edge of the village of Catsylvania, a bat snatches up Tom by his tail. He is carried off to a castle in the mountains and emerges</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 16:10:00" d="2021-07-16 16:25:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% It Ain't over Until the Cat Lady Sings
When Kitty Caterwaul goes missing the night before the opening of her new musical, &quot;Kitty Foiled,&quot; her agent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 16:25:00" d="2021-07-16 16:30:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Eggstra Credit
Tom and Jerry awake to the smell of eggs being cooked in the kitchen – Ginger and Rick are making breakfast courtesy of their neighbor's fresh eggs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 16:30:00" d="2021-07-16 16:40:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Costume Party. 
As Rick and Ginger prepare for a costume party, Tom tries to score some snacks. Jerry and Tuffy are out to do the same</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 16:40:00" d="2021-07-16 16:45:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Battle of the. 
Old Snelgrove, the senior butler, is retiring. There is an open backyard Olympics on the estate to see who will replace him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 16:45:00" d="2021-07-16 17:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Jamput
Pursuing Lamput is a dastardly career, but there's a right and a wrong way to go about it. Doc Specs cuts corners, showing up at</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 17:00:00" d="2021-07-16 17:10:00"><n u="Mush Mush And The Mushables">Mush Mush And The Mushables I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Shine, Lilit, Shine
The Beacon Mushroom that guides the Mushables back to Mushton in the dark has gone out. So Lilit lights up and stands in its place for the night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 17:10:00" d="2021-07-16 17:30:00"><n u="Mush Mush And The Mushables">Mush Mush And The Mushables I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Eyes On The Surprise
Every time Mush-Mush has tried to surprise his friend with a gift, Chep has always found out what it was. But Chep promises</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 17:30:00" d="2021-07-16 17:40:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Special Delivery
Lola is preparing a package to send to her Japanese pen pal. But the Guanos are watching and get an idea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 17:40:00" d="2021-07-16 17:45:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Marathon Pat
Seeing how Pat and Tank gained some weight, Lola and Victor decide to take them both for a training on a fitness path for dogs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 17:45:00" d="2021-07-16 18:00:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Worst Day Ever
Lola and her friends have to hand in a math assignment for the following day. Instead of doing his own homework Victor decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 18:00:00" d="2021-07-16 18:10:00"><n u="Kingdom Force">Kingdom Force I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Gimme a Break
Jalopi finally forms her own super-team. ull of Jalopi clones! Can Kingdom Force save the Jungle Kingdom before the well-intentioned Jalopi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 18:10:00" d="2021-07-16 18:30:00"><n u="Kingdom Force">Kingdom Force I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Under Pressure
Jabari resigns his Kingdom Force spot to legendary hero Mittens McGuirk, and it's a test of true teamwork to save the Plains Kingdom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 18:30:00" d="2021-07-16 18:35:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Diet
The fridge in the cabin has changed: it's been replaced by a brand new state-of-the-art appliance which analyzes the body fat percentage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 18:35:00" d="2021-07-16 18:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Balloon Bear
Grizzy watches a demonstration of balloon modelling on TV. He decides to make a balloon poodle to offer the she-bear he's enamored with</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 18:40:00" d="2021-07-16 19:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Pillow
Grizzy needs a nice nap. He can't find a pillow comfortable enough to his taste until he tests the pillow that the Lemmings use as a high-jump mat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 19:00:00" d="2021-07-16 19:10:00"><n u="Alice &amp; Lewis">Alice &amp; Lewis I (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Unforgettable Trip - Part 1
Alice has just moved into a new neighborhood but is nervous she might not be able to make new friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 19:10:00" d="2021-07-16 19:30:00"><n u="Alice &amp; Lewis">Alice &amp; Lewis I (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Unforgettable Trip - Part 2
Alice has just moved into a new neighborhood but is nervous she might not be able to make new friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 19:30:00" d="2021-07-16 19:40:00"><n u="Baby Looney Tunes">Baby Looney Tunes I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Picture This!
Baby Looney Tunes introduces the world's most beloved cartoon characters as precocious preschoolers, discovering the world one baby-step at a time!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 19:40:00" d="2021-07-16 20:00:00"><n u="Baby Looney Tunes">Baby Looney Tunes I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Hair Cut-Ups
Lola is afraid of getting her first haircut</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 20:00:00" d="2021-07-16 20:10:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Shoe Shine-nanigans /…
Elmer visits Daffy for a quick shoe shine. / Wile E. Coyote clones himself to catch the Road Runner. / Porky is running</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 20:10:00" d="2021-07-16 20:30:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Shell-Shocked / Daffy Dentist
Bugs races against Cecil the Turtle for the title of &quot;fastest thing in New York City.&quot; / The only thing more painful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 20:30:00" d="2021-07-16 20:35:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% The Bunny and the Goon
Bugs is watching a hockey game and calls out cheating</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 20:35:00" d="2021-07-16 20:40:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Model T. Fudd
Bugs Bunny works on an assembly line in a car factory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 20:40:00" d="2021-07-16 20:45:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Victory Clasp
Bugs and the gang teach squeaks the Victory Clasp Song</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 20:45:00" d="2021-07-16 21:00:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Lola Rider
Rhoda Roundhouse tears up the forest with her muscle car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 21:00:00" d="2021-07-16 21:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (175)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Phony Pony
When Mrs M welcomes a new resident to the Manor, Taffy and Bentley don't stand for this new pet that appeals all their mistress's attentions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 21:05:00" d="2021-07-16 21:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (176)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Squeakophobia
Bentley is about to unmask Taffy. But suddenly this one runs away totally horrified. Bentley would not have a 'squeakophobia' ?!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 21:10:00" d="2021-07-16 21:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (177)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Clone Sweet Clone
&quot; Mrs. M. decides to clone Taffy : here are 4 Taffy at the manor ! Even more worries for Bentley but also for Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 21:25:00" d="2021-07-16 21:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (178)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Silence of the Slams
Mrs. M is laid out. Her ears are sooooo sensitive that the slightest sound in the air makes her howl with pain. Anyone who makes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 21:30:00" d="2021-07-16 21:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Enter The Kitty
Scraggs the raccoon disguises himself as a cute cat to enter the luxurious Muchmore manor. Bentley, the dog of house, isn't fooled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 21:40:00" d="2021-07-16 21:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A Minor Problem
Addie comes to visit her grandmother, but Mrs Muchmore has to rush off and leaves the toddler with Forsythe and the pets. To Bentley's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 21:45:00" d="2021-07-16 22:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>No Strings Attached
Mrs Muchmore receives the great Mr Fuffernin for an inspection of the house. If anything goes wrong, Mrs Muchmore would</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 22:00:00" d="2021-07-16 22:05:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Inspector Grizzy
A van pulls up to the ranger's cabin to deliver a full crate of jars of chocolate spread. While Grizzy and the Lemmings fight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 22:05:00" d="2021-07-16 22:10:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% No Entrance!
Like usual, Grizzy picks the door of the Ranger's log cabin to come in and make himself comfortable, but this time it's impossible to enter! The Lemmings have requisitioned the cabin for a party and barricaded themselves inside. Grizzy has no intention of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 22:10:00" d="2021-07-16 22:25:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lemmings Indigestion
The Lemmings have got their hands on a pack of white beans which have very strange properties: when mixed with soda, anyone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 22:25:00" d="2021-07-16 22:30:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Sonata in Bear Major
Grizzy wants to get rid of the old piano in the garage at any cost, for the Lemmings love using it to make a dissonant racket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 22:30:00" d="2021-07-16 22:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Fractions
The Lemmings inherit a crate that fell off a Canadian army convoy transporting ultra-secret material. The case inside the crate emits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 22:40:00" d="2021-07-16 22:45:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (53)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The Bear That Laid Golden Eggs
Near the supermarket, a machine hands out surprise eggs in exchange for a coin. Amongst the lots to be won, there</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 22:45:00" d="2021-07-16 23:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (54)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Crash Training Course
At the Ranger's home, Grizzy finds a high-tech gadget that enables you to learn anything at all - sewing, origami, Kung Fu, etc</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 23:00:00" d="2021-07-16 23:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (53)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Nanogamba Tribe
When Fizz and Weasel shoot an ad for their special new fragrance “Fizz Scent” Fizz falls into the sewers only to bump into Magoo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 23:05:00" d="2021-07-16 23:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (54)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Kung Fizz
Fizz and Weasel are after the president’s jokebook! But Magoo thinking he’s in his dojo enters the high-security unit where it’s kept</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 23:15:00" d="2021-07-16 23:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (55)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Prophecy of the Goldensand's Dragon
Fizz is at the beach trying to build the most beautiful sandcastle in history. Magoo thinks he is in the legendary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 23:25:00" d="2021-07-16 23:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (56)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hornets Attack!
Volunteer firefighter Magoo patrols the park. Fizz and Weasel perched on a fake cloud like two Cupids shoot people with arrows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 23:35:00" d="2021-07-16 23:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (57)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Star Man
Fizz rehearses a dance number that’ll make him the world’s greatest star. But when Weasel catapults him next door onto the roof Magoo thinks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-16 23:40:00" d="2021-07-17 00:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (58)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Last Oak Tree Standing
Fizz and Weasel have set up their super-antenna in the middle of the desert. Magoo thinking he’s walking in the forest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 00:00:00" d="2021-07-17 00:05:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Chickie's Return
Mike's worst nightmare comes true when Louise digs out her old toy Chikie from her trunk. Chikie is a horrifying squeaky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 00:05:00" d="2021-07-17 00:10:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Feline A Little Racoon
Mike's yoga session is rudely interrupted when Fluffy comes to annoy him. Mike pushes him away and Fluffy ends up landing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 00:10:00" d="2021-07-17 00:25:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Electric Turtles
The turtles are struck by lightning during a storm, turning them into positively charged projectiles zapping everything they touch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 00:25:00" d="2021-07-17 00:35:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Rescuing Roxanne
Playing with Louise and her doll gives Mike an idea. He decides to stage a rescue mission with the doll from the roof of the Mikkelson's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 00:35:00" d="2021-07-17 00:40:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% A Sick Trick
The racoons watch Mike enviously as he makes himself comfortable in his living room. If only they could get a piece of that sweet action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 00:40:00" d="2021-07-17 00:48:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Aye Aye Aye Phone
Laura leaves her cell phone at home and Mike discovers a hilarious video of Fluffy on it that he absolutely has to show Iris</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 00:48:00" d="2021-07-17 00:50:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Skinny At The Pool
When Lamput masquerades as a swimming trophy at the local pool, Skinny finds himself in his red trunks, warming up for the big race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 00:50:00" d="2021-07-17 01:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Date Night
It’s Specs’ big date! He looks sharp. His beloved is enjoying herself. Life’s good. Things hit a snag when the annoying customer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 01:00:00" d="2021-07-17 01:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pet Therapist
The vet comes for a stay at Muchmore Manor. She immediately declares Taffy and Bentley have big issues. She knows because</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 01:05:00" d="2021-07-17 01:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>There Kitty Kitty
A new kitten is found into the mansion. Now Mrs. M is in love with the kitten and Taffy must try to do him in but something is weird</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 01:10:00" d="2021-07-17 01:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A Star is Born
Fuffernin is looking for a star for his next movie! Mrs M is in a hurry . But first and foremost, Bentley must succeed his casting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 01:25:00" d="2021-07-17 01:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Makeover Fakeover
Taffy must clear his jam-packed eating schedule to make Mish and Mash birthday party or risk losing their friendships for good! Unfortunately their party turns out to be at the exact same time Mrs. M is having a photographer over from a magazine to take p</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 01:30:00" d="2021-07-17 01:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Eye of the Racoon
Bentley is worried this disgusting fake cat but true racoon will bring shame on the Muchmore family with his disgusting manners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 01:40:00" d="2021-07-17 01:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Sweaters - Christmas
Christmas holidays are approaching, and Taffy thinks it would be hysterical if he could somehow get Mrs. Muchmore to buy Bentley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 01:45:00" d="2021-07-17 02:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>School's Fools
Mrs. Muchmore just finished an online course! Those online courses really work! Bentley gets a great idea…who says you can't teach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 02:00:00" d="2021-07-17 02:05:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The Sound of a Lemming
Grizzy snatches the last jar of chocolate spread out from under the noses of the Lemmings. In exchange, he offers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 02:05:00" d="2021-07-17 02:10:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear in the Wind
The Lemmings play a new game, floating like flags in the breeze from the fan which is set at maximum. Grizzy, who has decided to watch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 02:10:00" d="2021-07-17 02:20:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Construction Bear
The Lemmings have a grand old time tearing down their Kapla block buildings, which they rebuild just as fast. Grizzy remarks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 02:20:00" d="2021-07-17 02:25:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Kung Fu Lemmings
The Lemmings draw inspiration from lessons they find in a martial arts book and start breaking every wooden object they can get their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 02:25:00" d="2021-07-17 02:30:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Midsummer Bear's
Grizzy dreams that he's a valiant knight who has just delivered his beloved. As he is about to take her in his arms, he is woken</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 02:30:00" d="2021-07-17 02:35:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Manufacturing Secret
Grizzy stands in front of the pantry, desperate. The stock of chocolate spread is completely depleted. He realizes that the Lemmings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 02:35:00" d="2021-07-17 02:45:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bling Bling Bear
Inspired by a magazine with a jewelry ad showing a man offering a diamond to a woman, Grizzy imagines himself offering the ranger's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 02:45:00" d="2021-07-17 02:50:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Intellectual Bear
When he accidentally sticks a computer microprocessor to his temple, Grizzy is transformed into an exceptionally intelligent being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 02:50:00" d="2021-07-17 03:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Voodoo Blanket
The Lemmings prepare a dream afternoon snack with the last jar of chocolate spread in the cupboard. Tough luck, Grizzy is coming! Caught off guard, the Lemmings hide the jar in a teddy bear-pajama case to slip away without arousing suspicion. But Grizzy i</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 03:00:00" d="2021-07-17 03:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Firefighter for a Day
Magoo is a part-time firefighter reservist whose rescue mission for the day is to save a cat in a tree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 03:05:00" d="2021-07-17 03:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lend Me Your Earpiece
Magoo finds himself shrunk and then dragged inside the President’s head along with Fizz. He thinks the hamster is a little</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 03:15:00" d="2021-07-17 03:20:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Wallpapering Magoo
Magoo thinks that he is peeling off old wallpaper on Linda’s walls but he is actually destroying Fizz’ hypnotic posters In order</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 03:20:00" d="2021-07-17 03:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A Mountaineer Like No Other
Magoo has decided to go mountain climbing but in reality, he is climbing up a skyscraper! He mixes Fizz up with a wounded</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 03:25:00" d="2021-07-17 03:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Legs of Steel
Thinking he is in the middle of a work-out at his local gym Magoo inadvertently climbs onto a delivery boy’s bicycle. It just so happens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 03:35:00" d="2021-07-17 03:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A Recipe for Success
Magoo thinks Weasel has opened a restaurant and wants to help him improve it. He mistakes the FizzLab for a kitchen and prevents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 03:40:00" d="2021-07-17 03:50:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Honey Bear
Magoo thinks that he is on a camping trip but he is actually just in the city park. When he sees Weasel wearing a suit that allows him to stock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 03:50:00" d="2021-07-17 04:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Halloween Hold-up
Magoo is thinks is out trick-or-treating for Halloween. But he unwittingly robs a bank instead of Weasel. Fizz, whose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 04:00:00" d="2021-07-17 04:05:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (57)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Sauna
It's cold and grey outside. Mike invites Iris over to warm up over a hot chocolate. The raccoons sneak into the house and damage the Mikkelsen's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 04:05:00" d="2021-07-17 04:10:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (58)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Wrong Mike
The raccoons steal Iris's favorite toy but accidentally drop it on the terrace during their escape. Mike picks it up while cleaning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 04:10:00" d="2021-07-17 04:20:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (59)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Rival
Mike's plans to hang out with Iris are cruelly dashed when he trots out onto the patio to find her playing with a hunky other dog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 04:20:00" d="2021-07-17 04:25:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (60)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Prank
It's April Fool's Day. Mike has invited Iris over for a romantic dinner but instead of romance, Iris is more interested in pranking Mike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 04:25:00" d="2021-07-17 04:30:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (61)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% White Cat
A cute white cat turns up on the Mikkelsen's patio. Everyone thinks it's super-duper adorable, especially Iris. It looks like Fluffy has found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 04:30:00" d="2021-07-17 04:40:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (62)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Party
It's Mike's birthday and he's excited to be spending the day with Iris. But instead of a private party - Iris has invited the entire neighbourhood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 04:40:00" d="2021-07-17 04:45:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (63)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Best in Show
When Tom suggests to his mom that Mike could be a show dog, she bursts out laughing. Mike is hurt and sets out to prove</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 04:45:00" d="2021-07-17 04:50:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (64)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Stuck On You
Mike accidentally gets handcuffed to Freddy while attempting to eject the raccoons from the house. The two enemies have to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 04:50:00" d="2021-07-17 05:00:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (65)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Hoverboard
Mike is impressed with Tom's hoverboard tricks and decides to try to master them to impress Iris. As soon as Tom steps out, Mike tries</k>  </p>
</a>
