<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="138" t="2019-08-15 22:28:15"><p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 05:01:00" d="2019-08-22 05:08:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy gleefully discovers that he can print images taken with the ranger's camera which is connected to a state-of-the-art printer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 05:08:00" d="2019-08-22 05:15:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>A van pulls up to the ranger's cabin to deliver a crate of jars of chocolate spread. While Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over a wrecking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 05:15:00" d="2019-08-22 05:24:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean nearly gets fed to the fish!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 05:24:00" d="2019-08-22 05:35:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>A brand new lodger in the house could be a great new friend, or could be your worst enemy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 05:35:00" d="2019-08-22 05:45:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean takes to the air after being taken for a ride</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 05:45:00" d="2019-08-22 06:00:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean makes a meal out of his Birthday celebration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 06:00:00" d="2019-08-22 06:11:00"><n>The Zoo</n>    <k>Mysterious monsters are rumoured to be lurking in Flamingo Lagoon and keeper Pete is on a mission to prove to the zoo that the rumours are true</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 06:11:00" d="2019-08-22 06:30:00"><n>The Zoo</n>    <k>A mystery illness leaves Topaz the kangaroo without a hop. Gorilla Jürgen also comes down with ‘attention-seeker-itis’ and wants treatment too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 06:30:00" d="2019-08-22 06:35:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Angelo the Flea is told that he's too small to wrestle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 06:35:00" d="2019-08-22 06:40:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Bugs Bunny returns to his summer home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 06:40:00" d="2019-08-22 06:45:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Famous inventor Thomas Fuddison needs a lab assistant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 06:45:00" d="2019-08-22 06:55:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Bugs' hole, Witch Hazel's home, Count Bloodcount's castle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 06:55:00" d="2019-08-22 07:00:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Doc invents a cloning machine so Striker can play a game of 5 aside footie but how will he cope with loads of identical ball hogging versions of himself?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 07:00:00" d="2019-08-22 07:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy discovers that the frenzied &quot;break dance&quot; the Lemmings are doing is actually due to the fleas they are infested with</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 07:06:00" d="2019-08-22 07:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Another heat wave: even the riverbed is dried up. One very thirsty Grizzy discovers that the Lemmings have used the last remaining bottles of water</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 07:13:00" d="2019-08-22 07:25:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings have caught a little spider. Her sticky threads are perfect for bungee jumping. Grizzy, who has no intention of getting caught</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 07:25:00" d="2019-08-22 07:31:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry must investigate a missing cake that has a giant diamond ring inside, before a tough customer finds out it went missing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 07:31:00" d="2019-08-22 07:38:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry must solve the case of why Red Herring keeps hearing people laughing at him when there's no one around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 07:38:00" d="2019-08-22 07:50:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom lands in a haunted castle, where Jerry, Tuffy and he must outrun an invisible cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 07:50:00" d="2019-08-22 07:56:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry work together to protect a family of baby eagles from a mountain lion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 07:56:00" d="2019-08-22 08:03:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% When Butch breaks up with his girlfriend, Tom, Jerry, and Tuffy work to bring them back together so Butch won't go after Toodles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 08:03:00" d="2019-08-22 08:20:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom accidentally eats Spikes food and starts acting like a dog, soon the whole gang starts eating food that causes them to act crazy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 08:20:00" d="2019-08-22 08:30:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean tries to get some muscles, but attempts a shortcut to physical perfection</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 08:30:00" d="2019-08-22 08:45:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean has a new friend - a Seagull, but sometimes friends can overstay their welcome</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 08:45:00" d="2019-08-22 08:52:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy feels nostalgia for his former home – the dump</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 08:52:00" d="2019-08-22 08:58:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley sends Taffy to a factory on the other side of the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 08:58:00" d="2019-08-22 09:15:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs. Muchmore has equipped her home with a defense system</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 09:15:00" d="2019-08-22 09:36:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>Scooby Doo runs into an old kennel mate from the rescue shelter, Axel, who is now a state-of-the–art, highly trained K-9 police dog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 09:36:00" d="2019-08-22 09:57:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>When a successful video game company tries to convince Velma to work for them in San Francisco, the gang becomes embroiled in the mystery of a video game villain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 09:57:00" d="2019-08-22 10:40:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>The gang goes to Salem, Massachusetts for the historical festival, only to discover a demon has been set loose on the town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 10:40:00" d="2019-08-22 11:25:00"><n>The New Scooby-Doo Movies</n>    <k>77% Ghastly Ghost Town: Scooby and the gang team up with the Three Stooges when the Mystery Machine crashes into a giant sand pit by a vampire bat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 11:25:00" d="2019-08-22 11:55:00"><n>Scooby-Doo! And the Spooky Scarecrow</n>    <k>Scooby-Doo and the rest of the ghost-busting gang visit a quiet farm town where everyone is preparing for the annual Halloween harvest celebration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 11:55:00" d="2019-08-22 12:05:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean redecorates his room, making it fit for a Queen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 12:05:00" d="2019-08-22 12:15:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean is stuck in a lift and starts to annoy the other passengers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 12:15:00" d="2019-08-22 12:30:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean digs a hole in his garden… and finds a bomb!!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 12:30:00" d="2019-08-22 12:36:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Hildie and Beatie bring home a magic ogre's tooth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 12:36:00" d="2019-08-22 12:43:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Rick accidentally locks Tom and Jerry in the garage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 12:43:00" d="2019-08-22 12:55:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Hildie's received another dozen roses from her admirer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 12:55:00" d="2019-08-22 13:01:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Rick's installed a state-of-the-art home automation system</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 13:01:00" d="2019-08-22 13:08:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom takes a shot to the kisser that knocks the cat out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 13:08:00" d="2019-08-22 13:25:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% A travelling cat “salesman” sells Tom just what he needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 13:25:00" d="2019-08-22 13:32:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The pets help an unconscious Mrs M pass an inspection</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 13:32:00" d="2019-08-22 13:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M meets a handsome trillionnaire… allergic to dogs!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 13:39:00" d="2019-08-22 13:46:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The pets team up to recreate Mrs M's wedding video</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 13:46:00" d="2019-08-22 13:53:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley has a secret admirer…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 13:53:00" d="2019-08-22 14:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy gets scared as Mrs M tests him to discover his lineage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 14:00:00" d="2019-08-22 14:07:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Vacation's coming! But before the manor must be secured…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 14:07:00" d="2019-08-22 14:14:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy’s friends from the dump discover Mrs M manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 14:14:00" d="2019-08-22 14:21:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>It's Christmas Eve. Some ghosts come to haunt Bentley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 14:21:00" d="2019-08-22 14:28:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>A freak accident leads Bentley and Taffy to switch bodies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 14:28:00" d="2019-08-22 14:35:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M discovers a new social network app for pet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 14:35:00" d="2019-08-22 14:42:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The entire mansion is on a kale diet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 14:42:00" d="2019-08-22 15:10:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley helps a cat burglar stealing Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 15:10:00" d="2019-08-22 15:20:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>When Doc creates some invisible paint Party thinks he will borrow it and have some fun.Slapping on the paint, and turning himself invisible, means Party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 15:20:00" d="2019-08-22 15:31:00"><n>The Zoo</n>    <k>Mysterious monsters are rumoured to be lurking in Flamingo Lagoon and keeper Pete is on a mission to prove to the zoo that the rumours are true</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 15:31:00" d="2019-08-22 15:45:00"><n>The Zoo</n>    <k>A mystery illness leaves Topaz the kangaroo without a hop. Gorilla Jürgen also comes down with ‘attention-seeker-itis’ and wants treatment too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 15:45:00" d="2019-08-22 15:54:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>When tiny troll has its sights set on eating Mina and Becky for dinner, Bunnicula must save the day! There’s just one problem: he’s never been invited</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 15:54:00" d="2019-08-22 16:15:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Bunnicula drains an old yam and turns invisible</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 16:15:00" d="2019-08-22 16:22:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy feels nostalgia for his former home – the dump</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 16:22:00" d="2019-08-22 16:28:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley sends Taffy to a factory on the other side of the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 16:28:00" d="2019-08-22 16:40:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs. Muchmore has equipped her home with a defense system</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 16:40:00" d="2019-08-22 16:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 3</n>    <k>59% Angelo Rules follows twelve-year-old Angelo as he tries to control his life by using funny schemes - with a little help from his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 16:50:00" d="2019-08-22 17:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 3</n>    <k>59% Angelo Rules follows twelve-year-old Angelo as he tries to control his life by using funny schemes - with a little help from his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 17:10:00" d="2019-08-22 17:15:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Foghorn Leghorn opens a high-end grocery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 17:15:00" d="2019-08-22 17:20:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Bugs Bunny competes with Cecil the Turtle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 17:20:00" d="2019-08-22 17:25:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% The Bugs Bunny you love is back!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 17:25:00" d="2019-08-22 17:35:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Architect Daffy Duck is building his next “world famous” home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 17:35:00" d="2019-08-22 17:41:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% When Tom accidentally loses Tyke, he must distract Spike from looking for him. Jerry must try to find Tyke from a litter of identical looking puppies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 17:41:00" d="2019-08-22 17:48:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry go to a pool party at Toodle's house and compete against Meathead and Butch in various pool games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 17:48:00" d="2019-08-22 18:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom switches heads with a nine foot monster but he still wants to chase Jerry instead of villagers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 18:00:00" d="2019-08-22 18:06:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom gets a can of Cat Cop, a spray that creates a tiny cop that chases Jerry around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 18:06:00" d="2019-08-22 18:13:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry investigate why Spike keeps getting mistaken for another dog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 18:13:00" d="2019-08-22 18:30:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% When the gang find an air hockey table in the garage, it's cats versus mice in an epic game of hockey!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 18:30:00" d="2019-08-22 18:55:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>It's Scooby's dream come true as the gang visits the set of his favourite TV show and he meets the star, his celebrity crush, a dog actress who plays</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 18:55:00" d="2019-08-22 19:25:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>The Gang venture in an intricate labyrinth of crystal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 19:25:00" d="2019-08-22 19:35:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>No one believes Ben when he insists that one of the other patrons waiting on line at the World of Wet Water Park, is the nefarious Frightwig disguised as a common girl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 19:35:00" d="2019-08-22 19:50:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>During a book signing at a medieval castle, Ben must stop Hex from getting his hands on a grimoire that can fuse its user with mythical beasts – creating monstrous hybrids!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 19:50:00" d="2019-08-22 20:01:00"><n>The Zoo</n>    <k>A group of tiny frogs escape during the Zoo stock take. As rumours spread that these miniscule amphibians may actually be deadly, panic breaks out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 20:01:00" d="2019-08-22 20:20:00"><n>The Zoo</n>    <k>Under pressure to ‘man up’ and ‘get buff’, wimpy lion Neil takes takes diet advice from vegetarian gorilla Jürgen - with disastrous consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 20:20:00" d="2019-08-22 20:27:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy feels nostalgia for his former home – the dump</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 20:27:00" d="2019-08-22 20:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley sends Taffy to a factory on the other side of the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 20:33:00" d="2019-08-22 20:50:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs. Muchmore has equipped her home with a defense system</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 20:50:00" d="2019-08-22 20:56:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>As usual, Grizzy picks the door of the Ranger's log cabin to come in and make himself comfortable, but this time it's impossible to enter!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 20:56:00" d="2019-08-22 21:03:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy wants to get rid of the old piano at any cost. But when he notices that the she-bear he's in love with likes the melody of &quot;Für Elise,&quot; he decides to learn the piece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 21:03:00" d="2019-08-22 21:15:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings have got their hands on a pack of white beans which have very strange properties: when mixed with soda, anyone who eats them turns into a bouncing ball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 21:15:00" d="2019-08-22 21:21:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings inherit a crate that fell off a Canadian army convoy. Inside, a case emits a sort of laser beam that divides objects into multiple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 21:21:00" d="2019-08-22 21:28:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>At the Ranger's home, Grizzy finds a high-tech gadget that enables you to learn anything within seconds thanks to electrodes hooked to the brain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 21:28:00" d="2019-08-22 21:40:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Near the supermarket, a machine hands out surprise eggs in exchange for a coin. Amongst the lots to be won, there is a super firework rocket the Lemmings dream of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 21:40:00" d="2019-08-22 21:50:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Colbert catches Jimmy and the knights trading their assignments to get the mission worth the most victory points, Colbert assigns the knights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 21:50:00" d="2019-08-22 22:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When our trio lets success get to their heads, they boast about their team and inadvertently inspire the Cursed Forest Witch and Bad Jack to create their own deadly duo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 22:10:00" d="2019-08-22 22:20:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy complains that Henri treats him like a baby, Henri lets him do “grownup” things for himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 22:20:00" d="2019-08-22 22:40:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Jimmy, Cat and Henri have to organise a fake kidnapping of Lance by Bjorn, in order to retrieve Lance’s smart-mirror, which contains films of Cat, Henri</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 22:40:00" d="2019-08-22 22:47:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola’s mother has just received the latest prototype for a food processor to test. Even though Lola promises to wait till evening before trying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 22:47:00" d="2019-08-22 22:53:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Today is the big Robot Battle day! Lola’s robot, which looks like Pat, has to face down Victor’s. But the boy cheats and breaks RoboPat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 22:53:00" d="2019-08-22 23:05:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>A renowned pastry chef has organized a pie tasting contest. The winner will get to present a TV show with him. Lola is naturally taking part in the contest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 23:05:00" d="2019-08-22 23:12:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola has found herself a fun activity for the afternoon: to break a Guinness World record. To do so, she intends to build the biggest cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 23:12:00" d="2019-08-22 23:19:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola leaves the supermarket with all the ingredients for a super smoothie party. But disaster! She realizes she has forgotten the milk. She entrusts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 23:19:00" d="2019-08-22 23:30:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola has to write an essay on the theme &quot;My Hero Pet.&quot; It's not easiest task in the world for her, she explains to Victor, for while Pat is the loveliest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 23:30:00" d="2019-08-22 23:40:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean tries his hand as an international art sleuth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 23:40:00" d="2019-08-22 23:55:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>It's Nightmare on Bean Street!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 23:55:00" d="2019-08-23 00:05:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Romance is in the air and Bean's girlfriend is determined to have a piece of it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 00:05:00" d="2019-08-23 00:20:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>An escaped prisoner suffers hard labour under Mrs Wicket while Mr Bean puts his feet up in jail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 00:20:00" d="2019-08-23 00:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy is bothered by an object stuck in between the sofa cushions: a big fur lemming puppet glove</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 00:26:00" d="2019-08-23 00:33:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy discovers the leftovers of a Halloween party in the ranger's cabin, which was entirely redecorated for the occasion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 00:33:00" d="2019-08-23 00:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy wants to give the she-bear he's in love with a plastic ring which he finds really swell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 00:39:00" d="2019-08-23 00:46:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy finds a strange figurine with the power to switch the spirits of two living beings and finds himself imprisoned in the body of a caribou</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 00:46:00" d="2019-08-23 00:50:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>While salmon fishing on the riverbank, Grizzy hauls in an unusual catch: an old hand mirror straight out of a fairytale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 00:50:00" d="2019-08-23 00:55:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Star sleepwalks through her routine, ever-changing music keeping her safe through a numberof dangerous obstacles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 00:55:00" d="2019-08-23 01:05:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When the Queen wishes she could give her knights a break during a particularly intense period of battles with the Villains, Jimmy suggests she call a truce</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 01:05:00" d="2019-08-23 01:20:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy and Cat use science to help them win the school Sorcery Faire, their classmates think they’re masters of the Dark Arts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 01:20:00" d="2019-08-23 01:30:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>As Jimmy tells Cat and Bjorn about yet another cool day he had with Henri, his two friends sigh their own parents aren’t as cool</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 01:30:00" d="2019-08-23 01:40:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Henri is convinced that he wins his fights because he’s got a (ridiculous) ritual with a lucky charm. Wilfried steals it, which makes Henri completely lose his confidence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 01:40:00" d="2019-08-23 01:47:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Tonight, Lola is determined to spy a shooting star so that she can make a wish. When the Guanos meanwhile are set on making their wish come true: to get rid of Hoodie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 01:47:00" d="2019-08-23 01:54:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola finds Victor, sad and alone, in his garden. Tomorrow is his birthday and nothing has been planned for the special day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 01:54:00" d="2019-08-23 02:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends are in the middle of a medieval role playing game and there is treasure hidden in the bouncy castle: candies and cookies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 02:00:00" d="2019-08-23 02:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Today Lola is spending the afternoon in the company of her former neighbor, Honorine. On the menu: games and homemade pies. At least that’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 02:07:00" d="2019-08-23 02:14:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola looks on as an old lady throws seed to the birds and observes how the Guanos use their brute force to push other birds out of the way to hog the food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 02:14:00" d="2019-08-23 02:25:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola has to play a violin solo during the big show tonight. When she is on stage, Victor creates an accident as a pretext to make Lola believe the place is haunted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 02:25:00" d="2019-08-23 02:31:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy stands in front of the pantry, desperate. The stock of chocolate spread is completely depleted. He realizes that the Lemmings are making some themselves!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 02:31:00" d="2019-08-23 02:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Inspired by a magazine with a jewellery ad showing a man offering a diamond to a woman, Grizzy imagines himself offering the ranger's engagement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 02:38:00" d="2019-08-23 02:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>When he accidentally sticks a computer microprocessor to his temple, Grizzy is transformed into an exceptionally intelligent being capable of predicting events to come</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 02:45:00" d="2019-08-23 02:51:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings prepare a dream afternoon snack with the last jar of chocolate spread in the cupboard. Tough luck, Grizzy is coming!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 02:51:00" d="2019-08-23 02:58:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy gleefully discovers that he can print images taken with the ranger's camera which is connected to a state-of-the-art printer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 02:58:00" d="2019-08-23 03:05:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>A van pulls up to the ranger's cabin to deliver a crate of jars of chocolate spread. While Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over a wrecking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 03:05:00" d="2019-08-23 03:15:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Colbert catches Jimmy and the knights trading their assignments to get the mission worth the most victory points, Colbert assigns the knights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 03:15:00" d="2019-08-23 03:25:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When our trio lets success get to their heads, they boast about their team and inadvertently inspire the Cursed Forest Witch and Bad Jack to create their own deadly duo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 03:25:00" d="2019-08-23 03:35:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy complains that Henri treats him like a baby, Henri lets him do “grownup” things for himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 03:35:00" d="2019-08-23 03:50:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Jimmy, Cat and Henri have to organise a fake kidnapping of Lance by Bjorn, in order to retrieve Lance’s smart-mirror, which contains films of Cat, Henri</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 03:50:00" d="2019-08-23 03:57:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola’s mother has just received the latest prototype for a food processor to test. Even though Lola promises to wait till evening before trying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 03:57:00" d="2019-08-23 04:04:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>A renowned pastry chef has organized a pie tasting contest. The winner will get to present a TV show with him. Lola is naturally taking part in the contest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 04:04:00" d="2019-08-23 04:10:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Today is the big Robot Battle day! Lola’s robot, which looks like Pat, has to face down Victor’s. But the boy cheats and breaks RoboPat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 04:10:00" d="2019-08-23 04:17:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola has found herself a fun activity for the afternoon: to break a Guinness World record. To do so, she intends to build the biggest cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 04:17:00" d="2019-08-23 04:24:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola has to write an essay on the theme &quot;My Hero Pet.&quot; It's not easiest task in the world for her, she explains to Victor, for while Pat is the loveliest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 04:24:00" d="2019-08-23 04:35:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola leaves the supermarket with all the ingredients for a super smoothie party. But disaster! She realizes she has forgotten the milk. She entrusts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 04:35:00" d="2019-08-23 04:41:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>As usual, Grizzy picks the door of the Ranger's log cabin to come in and make himself comfortable, but this time it's impossible to enter!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 04:41:00" d="2019-08-23 04:48:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings have got their hands on a pack of white beans which have very strange properties: when mixed with soda, anyone who eats them turns into a bouncing ball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 04:48:00" d="2019-08-23 04:55:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy wants to get rid of the old piano at any cost. But when he notices that the she-bear he's in love with likes the melody of &quot;Für Elise,&quot; he decides to learn the piece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-23 04:55:00" d="2019-08-23 05:01:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings inherit a crate that fell off a Canadian army convoy. Inside, a case emits a sort of laser beam that divides objects into multiple</k>  </p>
</a>
