<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="138" t="2019-08-15 22:27:40"><p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 05:01:00" d="2019-08-21 05:08:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings draw inspiration from lessons they find in a martial arts book and start breaking every wooden object they can get their hands on into two</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 05:08:00" d="2019-08-21 05:15:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy dreams that he's a valiant knight who has delivered his beloved. As he is about to take her in his arms, he is woken by the Lemmings who have chosen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 05:15:00" d="2019-08-21 05:25:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean builds a supermarket super trolley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 05:25:00" d="2019-08-21 05:35:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean gets in a complete flap when he befriends a feathered theif</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 05:35:00" d="2019-08-21 05:45:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean is forced to look after his worst enemy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 05:45:00" d="2019-08-21 06:00:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean loses his bottle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 06:00:00" d="2019-08-21 06:11:00"><n>The Zoo</n>    <k>Under pressure to ‘man up’ and ‘get buff’, wimpy lion Neil takes takes diet advice from vegetarian gorilla Jürgen - with disastrous consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 06:11:00" d="2019-08-21 06:30:00"><n>The Zoo</n>    <k>It’s the Zoo’s annual inspection day and evil-genius monkey Brutus hatches an explosive plan to get Jürgen kicked out of the zoo, forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 06:30:00" d="2019-08-21 06:35:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Cal-umbus discovers the new world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 06:35:00" d="2019-08-21 06:40:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Porky wants to live his dream and play football</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 06:40:00" d="2019-08-21 06:45:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Bugs and his small boat are run over by a giant Riverboat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 06:45:00" d="2019-08-21 06:55:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% A theft occurs at the local art museum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 06:55:00" d="2019-08-21 07:00:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Captain discovers an ancient looking map from a message in a bottle bobbing in the lagoon.He thinks it will lead him a chest full of gold coins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 07:00:00" d="2019-08-21 07:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy wants to learn to dance the mambo to please his lovely she-bear. He finds a learning kit at the ranger’s home which has a dance carpet with footprints</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 07:06:00" d="2019-08-21 07:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>After receiving a terrible blow over the head, Grizzy is no longer the same: he thinks he's a rodent! He tries to get the gang to adopt him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 07:13:00" d="2019-08-21 07:25:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy is exhausted and the couch has never seemed so enticing! He goes to fetch a pillow and a sleeping mask, but the Lemmings have entirely different</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 07:25:00" d="2019-08-21 07:31:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom works with a vampire to collect mice to eat. Luckily, Jerry Van Mouseling is on the case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 07:31:00" d="2019-08-21 07:38:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% In a musical detective episode, Tom and Jerry must figure out the disappearance of famed stage actress Kitty Caterwaul before the opening night of her new musical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 07:38:00" d="2019-08-21 07:50:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry try to break in to a chicken coop to steal eggs and end up defending the chickens from unknown intruders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 07:50:00" d="2019-08-21 07:56:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% A Halloween party turns the house upside down, as Tom and Jerry try to raid the party food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 07:56:00" d="2019-08-21 08:03:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom is trained by Jerry to compete in a butler competition for the glory of the manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 08:03:00" d="2019-08-21 08:20:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom uses a baby goat to mow the manor's lawn, but it turns out the baby goat wants to eat everything in the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 08:20:00" d="2019-08-21 08:30:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean ends up on stage at the opera house. n a dress!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 08:30:00" d="2019-08-21 08:45:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean becomes a taxi driver after being locked in a taxi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 08:45:00" d="2019-08-21 08:51:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy becomes a huge star on internet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 08:51:00" d="2019-08-21 08:58:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley orders a bottle of caviar eau to trap Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 08:58:00" d="2019-08-21 09:15:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M registers Taffy in the biggest cat show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 09:15:00" d="2019-08-21 09:35:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>Fred’s worst nightmare comes true when an evil spirit possesses the Mystery Machine and turns his beloved van into an unrelenting monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 09:35:00" d="2019-08-21 09:57:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>Daphne brings the gang to a fancy Ice Hotel where a new exhibit of ice age artifacts is opening. Things heat up when a frozen Ice Man goes on a rampage inside the hotel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 09:57:00" d="2019-08-21 10:40:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>The gang heads to Shaggy’s beloved grandmother’s Florida retirement home, where they learn a crazed Ape Man has been frightening the elderly residents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 10:40:00" d="2019-08-21 11:25:00"><n>The New Scooby-Doo Movies</n>    <k>77% Scooby Doo Meets Dick Van Dyke: Scooby and the gang are asked by actor Dick Van Dyke to uncover the truth behind the haunting of his new fairground attraction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 11:25:00" d="2019-08-21 11:50:00"><n>Scooby Doo! Ghastly Goals</n>    <k>Scooby and the gang are in Rio, Brazil enjoying a parade celebrating the beginning of the International Soccer Cup</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 11:50:00" d="2019-08-21 12:05:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>A puzzling puzzle has Mr Bean truly puzzled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 12:05:00" d="2019-08-21 12:15:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean tries to get some muscles, but attempts a shortcut to physical perfection</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 12:15:00" d="2019-08-21 12:30:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean has a new friend - a Seagull, but sometimes friends can overstay their welcome</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 12:30:00" d="2019-08-21 12:36:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Ginger notices a visitor has taken roots in the backyard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 12:36:00" d="2019-08-21 12:43:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry get into a garden growing contest that turns out badly for Tom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 12:43:00" d="2019-08-21 12:55:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% An overly ambitious young house sitter ruins Tom’s plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 12:55:00" d="2019-08-21 13:01:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom is stranded on a deserted island</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 13:01:00" d="2019-08-21 13:08:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom’s tried everything to get rid of his hiccups</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 13:08:00" d="2019-08-21 13:25:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% After a particularly rough cat and mouse, Jerry quits!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 13:25:00" d="2019-08-21 13:32:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The vet comes for a stay at Muchmore Manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 13:32:00" d="2019-08-21 13:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>A new kitten is found into the mansion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 13:39:00" d="2019-08-21 13:46:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Fuffernin is looking for a star for his next movie!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 13:46:00" d="2019-08-21 13:53:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy has a birthday party and a makeover at the same time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 13:53:00" d="2019-08-21 14:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley is provoked in a duel against a corgi!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 14:00:00" d="2019-08-21 14:07:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs. Muchmore buys Bentley a godawful holiday doggy sweater</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 14:07:00" d="2019-08-21 14:14:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Who says you can’t teach an old dog new tricks?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 14:14:00" d="2019-08-21 14:21:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley starts an escalating journalistic war</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 14:21:00" d="2019-08-21 14:28:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy hypnotizes Bentley to get rid of him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 14:28:00" d="2019-08-21 14:35:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Tonight it's a super rare occurrence of a ‘raccoon moon’</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 14:35:00" d="2019-08-21 14:42:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley creates a fake Taffy or Mrs M will be devastated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 14:42:00" d="2019-08-21 15:10:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Scraggs a raccoon uses a cat disguise to enter Mrs M manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 15:10:00" d="2019-08-21 15:20:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Doc invents a cloning machine so Striker can play a game of 5 aside footie but how will he cope with loads of identical ball hogging versions of himself?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 15:20:00" d="2019-08-21 15:31:00"><n>The Zoo</n>    <k>Under pressure to ‘man up’ and ‘get buff’, wimpy lion Neil takes takes diet advice from vegetarian gorilla Jürgen - with disastrous consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 15:31:00" d="2019-08-21 15:45:00"><n>The Zoo</n>    <k>It’s the Zoo’s annual inspection day and evil-genius monkey Brutus hatches an explosive plan to get Jürgen kicked out of the zoo, forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 15:45:00" d="2019-08-21 15:55:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>After Mina's imaginary friend returns to her life, Bunnicula is set on a collision course with a type of supernatural creature he has never had to deal with</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 15:55:00" d="2019-08-21 16:15:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>After Chester feeds mixed vegetable juices to Bunnicula to get him to clean the house, the results are so amazing that the cat keeps on feeding the juice to the rabbit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 16:15:00" d="2019-08-21 16:21:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy becomes a huge star on internet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 16:21:00" d="2019-08-21 16:28:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley orders a bottle of caviar eau to trap Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 16:28:00" d="2019-08-21 16:40:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M registers Taffy in the biggest cat show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 16:40:00" d="2019-08-21 16:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 3</n>    <k>59% Angelo Rules follows twelve-year-old Angelo as he tries to control his life by using funny schemes - with a little help from his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 16:50:00" d="2019-08-21 17:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 3</n>    <k>59% Angelo Rules follows twelve-year-old Angelo as he tries to control his life by using funny schemes - with a little help from his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 17:10:00" d="2019-08-21 17:15:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Angelo the Flea is told that he's too small to wrestle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 17:15:00" d="2019-08-21 17:20:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Bugs Bunny returns to his summer home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 17:20:00" d="2019-08-21 17:25:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Famous inventor Thomas Fuddison needs a lab assistant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 17:25:00" d="2019-08-21 17:35:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Bugs' hole, Witch Hazel's home, Count Bloodcount's castle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 17:35:00" d="2019-08-21 17:41:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry must investigate a missing cake that has a giant diamond ring inside, before a tough customer finds out it went missing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 17:41:00" d="2019-08-21 17:48:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry must solve the case of why Red Herring keeps hearing people laughing at him when there's no one around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 17:48:00" d="2019-08-21 18:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom lands in a haunted castle, where Jerry, Tuffy and he must outrun an invisible cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 18:00:00" d="2019-08-21 18:06:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry work together to protect a family of baby eagles from a mountain lion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 18:06:00" d="2019-08-21 18:13:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% When Butch breaks up with his girlfriend, Tom, Jerry, and Tuffy work to bring them back together so Butch won't go after Toodles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 18:13:00" d="2019-08-21 18:30:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom accidentally eats Spikes food and starts acting like a dog, soon the whole gang starts eating food that causes them to act crazy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 18:30:00" d="2019-08-21 18:55:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>63% The Scooby gang need to figure out why the ghost of Elias Kingston, the founder of Kingston University, is haunting the school halls!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 18:55:00" d="2019-08-21 19:25:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>63% Daphne brings the Gang to a Victorian murder mystery party, so they can dress up and solve a fake mystery for once</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 19:25:00" d="2019-08-21 19:35:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>In the heart of Silicon Valley, Ben has to stop Victorian villain Steam Smythe from securing an epic power source sealed in a Tesla time capsule</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 19:35:00" d="2019-08-21 19:50:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>During Chefapalooza in the Rocky Montains, three famous chefs and infamous bad-guys, The Tri-Chefta, hunt down Wildvine in hopes of creating their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 19:50:00" d="2019-08-21 20:01:00"><n>The Zoo</n>    <k>Mysterious monsters are rumoured to be lurking in Flamingo Lagoon and keeper Pete is on a mission to prove to the zoo that the rumours are true</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 20:01:00" d="2019-08-21 20:20:00"><n>The Zoo</n>    <k>A mystery illness leaves Topaz the kangaroo without a hop. Gorilla Jürgen also comes down with ‘attention-seeker-itis’ and wants treatment too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 20:20:00" d="2019-08-21 20:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy becomes a huge star on internet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 20:26:00" d="2019-08-21 20:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley orders a bottle of caviar eau to trap Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 20:33:00" d="2019-08-21 20:50:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M registers Taffy in the biggest cat show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 20:50:00" d="2019-08-21 20:56:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy stands in front of the pantry, desperate. The stock of chocolate spread is completely depleted. He realizes that the Lemmings are making some themselves!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 20:56:00" d="2019-08-21 21:03:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>When he accidentally sticks a computer microprocessor to his temple, Grizzy is transformed into an exceptionally intelligent being capable of predicting events to come</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 21:03:00" d="2019-08-21 21:15:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Inspired by a magazine with a jewellery ad showing a man offering a diamond to a woman, Grizzy imagines himself offering the ranger's engagement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 21:15:00" d="2019-08-21 21:21:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings prepare a dream afternoon snack with the last jar of chocolate spread in the cupboard. Tough luck, Grizzy is coming!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 21:21:00" d="2019-08-21 21:28:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>A van pulls up to the ranger's cabin to deliver a crate of jars of chocolate spread. While Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over a wrecking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 21:28:00" d="2019-08-21 21:40:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy gleefully discovers that he can print images taken with the ranger's camera which is connected to a state-of-the-art printer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 21:40:00" d="2019-08-21 21:50:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When the Queen wishes she could give her knights a break during a particularly intense period of battles with the Villains, Jimmy suggests she call a truce</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 21:50:00" d="2019-08-21 22:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy and Cat use science to help them win the school Sorcery Faire, their classmates think they’re masters of the Dark Arts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 22:10:00" d="2019-08-21 22:20:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>As Jimmy tells Cat and Bjorn about yet another cool day he had with Henri, his two friends sigh their own parents aren’t as cool</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 22:20:00" d="2019-08-21 22:40:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Henri is convinced that he wins his fights because he’s got a (ridiculous) ritual with a lucky charm. Wilfried steals it, which makes Henri completely lose his confidence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 22:40:00" d="2019-08-21 22:47:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Tonight, Lola is determined to spy a shooting star so that she can make a wish. When the Guanos meanwhile are set on making their wish come true: to get rid of Hoodie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 22:47:00" d="2019-08-21 22:54:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends are in the middle of a medieval role playing game and there is treasure hidden in the bouncy castle: candies and cookies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 22:54:00" d="2019-08-21 23:05:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola finds Victor, sad and alone, in his garden. Tomorrow is his birthday and nothing has been planned for the special day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 23:05:00" d="2019-08-21 23:12:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Today Lola is spending the afternoon in the company of her former neighbor, Honorine. On the menu: games and homemade pies. At least that’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 23:12:00" d="2019-08-21 23:19:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola has to play a violin solo during the big show tonight. When she is on stage, Victor creates an accident as a pretext to make Lola believe the place is haunted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 23:19:00" d="2019-08-21 23:30:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola looks on as an old lady throws seed to the birds and observes how the Guanos use their brute force to push other birds out of the way to hog the food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 23:30:00" d="2019-08-21 23:39:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean nearly gets fed to the fish!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 23:39:00" d="2019-08-21 23:55:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>A brand new lodger in the house could be a great new friend, or could be your worst enemy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 23:55:00" d="2019-08-22 00:05:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean takes to the air after being taken for a ride</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 00:05:00" d="2019-08-22 00:20:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean makes a meal out of his Birthday celebration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 00:20:00" d="2019-08-22 00:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy's last jar of chocolate spread was pinched by the Lemmings, who are savoring it in secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 00:26:00" d="2019-08-22 00:33:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Wedged in his sofa to relieve his aching back, Grizzy balks at getting up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 00:33:00" d="2019-08-22 00:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The vibrations created by Grizzy's snoring during his nap give the Lemmings an idea for a bouncing game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 00:39:00" d="2019-08-22 00:46:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy finds a birthday pinata in the ranger's living room. The idea of bursting open a papier-mâché statue with a bat like it says in the instructions pleases him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 00:46:00" d="2019-08-22 00:50:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Inside a mysterious cave, Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a magical Game of the Goose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 00:50:00" d="2019-08-22 00:55:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Luna thinks she's a shoo-in for a gold medal at the Happo Sports Day, if only shecan overcome Super, Star, Bash. nd her misbehaving jet pack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 00:55:00" d="2019-08-22 01:05:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy enables the Witch of the Cursed Forest to kidnap the Queen, Wilfried becomes the regent’s realm. Wilfried immediately decrees foolish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 01:05:00" d="2019-08-22 01:20:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>After the queen eats a lollipop that makes her start to shrink, Jimmy and Henri must capture the Dark Forest Witch in order to get an antidote</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 01:20:00" d="2019-08-22 01:30:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy inadvertently convinces Ronny Flash to do an interview with a rock monster, Jimmy, Henri and Cat end up escorting Ronny into the Dark Lands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 01:30:00" d="2019-08-22 01:40:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>To show off, Jimmy arrives at the castle flying on Bjorn, and he pretends the dragon is his pet. But Wilfried captures the “monster,” and Bad Jack threatens to burn Epic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 01:40:00" d="2019-08-22 01:45:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is rehearsing the flute recital she has to play this evening. A lady pigeon perches nearby to enjoy her playing and one of the Guanos falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 01:45:00" d="2019-08-22 01:52:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends are organizing a food drive for the city’s kennel. But the food supplies soon attract the attention of Tank and the Guanos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 01:52:00" d="2019-08-22 02:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is planning a surprise dinner for her parents' wedding anniversary so she settles into the kitchen to prepare a nice meal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 02:00:00" d="2019-08-22 02:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is due to be interviewed as Pet owner of the Week for a pet’s magazine. Victor is jealous. Surely he’s been the best pet owner this week</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 02:07:00" d="2019-08-22 02:13:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and Victor are both fans of the game Galaktik dance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 02:13:00" d="2019-08-22 02:25:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>This morning Lola is feeling very anxious. She has a big test coming up at school and she’s not at all confident</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 02:25:00" d="2019-08-22 02:31:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings play kite-surf with a homemade kite. Grizzy notices that the she-bear he's in love with watches the kite perform arabesques in the sky with admiration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 02:31:00" d="2019-08-22 02:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy snatches the last jar of chocolate spread out from under the noses of the Lemmings. In exchange, he offers them the toy stuck inside the lid: a mini-flute</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 02:38:00" d="2019-08-22 02:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings play a new game, floating like flags in the breeze from the fan set on maximum. But Grizzy quickly rids the living room of this interference</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 02:45:00" d="2019-08-22 02:51:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings have fun tearing down their Kapla block buildings, which they rebuild just as fast. Grizzy finds that the she-bear he's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 02:51:00" d="2019-08-22 02:58:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings draw inspiration from lessons they find in a martial arts book and start breaking every wooden object they can get their hands on into two</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 02:58:00" d="2019-08-22 03:05:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy dreams that he's a valiant knight who has delivered his beloved. As he is about to take her in his arms, he is woken by the Lemmings who have chosen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 03:05:00" d="2019-08-22 03:15:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When the Queen wishes she could give her knights a break during a particularly intense period of battles with the Villains, Jimmy suggests she call a truce</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 03:15:00" d="2019-08-22 03:25:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy and Cat use science to help them win the school Sorcery Faire, their classmates think they’re masters of the Dark Arts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 03:25:00" d="2019-08-22 03:35:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>As Jimmy tells Cat and Bjorn about yet another cool day he had with Henri, his two friends sigh their own parents aren’t as cool</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 03:35:00" d="2019-08-22 03:50:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Henri is convinced that he wins his fights because he’s got a (ridiculous) ritual with a lucky charm. Wilfried steals it, which makes Henri completely lose his confidence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 03:50:00" d="2019-08-22 03:57:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Tonight, Lola is determined to spy a shooting star so that she can make a wish. When the Guanos meanwhile are set on making their wish come true: to get rid of Hoodie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 03:57:00" d="2019-08-22 04:04:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola finds Victor, sad and alone, in his garden. Tomorrow is his birthday and nothing has been planned for the special day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 04:04:00" d="2019-08-22 04:10:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends are in the middle of a medieval role playing game and there is treasure hidden in the bouncy castle: candies and cookies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 04:10:00" d="2019-08-22 04:17:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Today Lola is spending the afternoon in the company of her former neighbor, Honorine. On the menu: games and homemade pies. At least that’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 04:17:00" d="2019-08-22 04:24:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola looks on as an old lady throws seed to the birds and observes how the Guanos use their brute force to push other birds out of the way to hog the food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 04:24:00" d="2019-08-22 04:35:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola has to play a violin solo during the big show tonight. When she is on stage, Victor creates an accident as a pretext to make Lola believe the place is haunted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 04:35:00" d="2019-08-22 04:41:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy stands in front of the pantry, desperate. The stock of chocolate spread is completely depleted. He realizes that the Lemmings are making some themselves!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 04:41:00" d="2019-08-22 04:48:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Inspired by a magazine with a jewellery ad showing a man offering a diamond to a woman, Grizzy imagines himself offering the ranger's engagement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 04:48:00" d="2019-08-22 04:55:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>When he accidentally sticks a computer microprocessor to his temple, Grizzy is transformed into an exceptionally intelligent being capable of predicting events to come</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-22 04:55:00" d="2019-08-22 05:01:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings prepare a dream afternoon snack with the last jar of chocolate spread in the cupboard. Tough luck, Grizzy is coming!</k>  </p>
</a>
