<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="135" t="2021-07-10 04:55:07"><p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 05:00:00" d="2021-07-17 05:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Raccoon Moon
Taffy is watching TV with Mrs. M: tonight it's a super rare occurrence of a &quot;raccoon moon&quot;. Legend has it, he says, that during its presence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 05:05:00" d="2021-07-17 05:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Love of Loaf
Bentley takes advantage of Mrs. Muchmore's spa treatment, with slices of cucumber on her eyes, to get rid of Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 05:10:00" d="2021-07-17 05:20:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Climate Control Freaks
Mrs. M installs a hi-tech AC and Heating Unit capable of creating different temperature in the mansion. When Mrs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 05:20:00" d="2021-07-17 05:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Cone Heads
After another rambunctious fight, one that doesn't end well for Taffy, the Vet prescribes him a high-tech cone to stop any unsavory wound-licking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 05:25:00" d="2021-07-17 05:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (141)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Time out of Taffy
Taffy and Bentley are in the middle of a tense ceasefire when two strange, metal-clad raccoons appear in a flash of light</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 05:30:00" d="2021-07-17 05:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Racoon In A Guilted Cage
Taffy is the winner of another cruel prank war: this time he put Bentley in a box and sent him to the Antarctic. Taffy celebrates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 05:40:00" d="2021-07-17 05:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Flea Party
Taffy is scratching himself when Mrs. Muchmore says: &quot;If you got fleas, I'll have to take your bow off and put you a flea collar&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 05:45:00" d="2021-07-17 05:50:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Guard Dog
Taffy accidentally saves the bear! The bear instantly vows its loyalty - he's like a huge puppy dog following him around. Taffy's freaked</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 05:50:00" d="2021-07-17 06:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Cat's Pajamas
It's sooooo cold outside. Problem for Taffy is - extreme cold triggers hibernation in raccoons! If he's out for two weeks - he'll</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 06:00:00" d="2021-07-17 06:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Love Thy Neighbour
Magoo thinks he is housesitting for Weasel while the latter is on vacation. When he sees him returning from the grocery store</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 06:05:00" d="2021-07-17 06:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dances with Walruses
Magoo thinks he’s herding cattle through the desert but is in fact on an ice floe with walruses. He takes Fizz and Weasel for cattle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 06:15:00" d="2021-07-17 06:30:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Bodyguard
Fizz has dressed Weasel up as a supervillain in order to pretend to save the city. Magoo mistakes his disguised neighbor for an actress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 06:30:00" d="2021-07-17 06:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Not Without My Hamster
Fizz and Weasel are at the supermarket buying ingredients to make the world’s best cake. They bump into Magoo who thinks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 06:35:00" d="2021-07-17 06:45:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Curse of the Pyramid
Magoo thinks that he is lost in a pyramid but he is in fact in a big conference room where Fizz is about to perform a stand-up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 06:45:00" d="2021-07-17 07:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Deep Sea Diving
Magoo thinks he’s underwater scooting and has discovered Atlantis. In fact he’s in New York riding Fizz’s latest invention:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 07:00:00" d="2021-07-17 07:05:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Anger Mismanagement
Inside the house, Tom and Jerry get into a full-on brawl. Steam comes out of their ears as they face off. Just then, Ginger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 07:05:00" d="2021-07-17 07:10:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Vampire State
On the edge of the village of Catsylvania, a bat snatches up Tom by his tail. He is carried off to a castle in the mountains and emerges</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 07:10:00" d="2021-07-17 07:25:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% It Ain't Over Until the Cat Lady Sings
When Kitty Caterwaul goes missing the night before the opening of her new musical, &quot;Kitty Foiled,&quot; her agent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 07:25:00" d="2021-07-17 07:30:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Eggstra Credit
Tom and Jerry awake to the smell of eggs being cooked in the kitchen – Ginger and Rick are making breakfast courtesy of their neighbor's fresh eggs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 07:30:00" d="2021-07-17 07:40:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Costume Party. 
As Rick and Ginger prepare for a costume party, Tom tries to score some snacks. Jerry and Tuffy are out to do the same</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 07:40:00" d="2021-07-17 07:45:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Battle of the. 
Old Snelgrove, the senior butler, is retiring. There is an open backyard Olympics on the estate to see who will replace him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 07:45:00" d="2021-07-17 08:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Jamput
Pursuing Lamput is a dastardly career, but there's a right and a wrong way to go about it. Doc Specs cuts corners, showing up at</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 08:00:00" d="2021-07-17 08:10:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Coconut Shy
Mr Bean goes to his favourite china shop to buy a new cup for Teddy but when he opens his wallet he doesn’t have enough money to pay for it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 08:10:00" d="2021-07-17 08:30:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Green Bean
Mr Bean’s electricity supply is cut off when Mrs Wicket sees the cost of her enormous electricity bill. As the snow falls outside Mr Bean’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 08:30:00" d="2021-07-17 08:40:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Cash Machine
Mr Bean goes to his local bakery to buy a cake but finds he doesn’t have any money. He goes to the bank to use the cash machine but he can’t</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 08:40:00" d="2021-07-17 09:00:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Litterbug
Mr Bean is furious with the untidy state of the streets and all the people who drop litter so he goes on a one-man mission to clean up the town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 09:00:00" d="2021-07-17 09:30:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Scary Christmas
It's Christmas Eve and Fred is ready to solve a Christmas mystery! Unfortunately the town the gang has arrived in is being attacked</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 09:30:00" d="2021-07-17 10:00:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Giant Problems
Daphne brings the gang to Ireland to visit an ancient Blake family castle. As the gang becomes enchanted by the magical Emerald</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 10:00:00" d="2021-07-17 11:15:00"><n>Scooby-Doo! Wrestlemania Mystery</n><t>Q</t>    <k>62% This original Scooby-Doo mystery features some of the biggest names in the WWE! When Shaggy and Scooby win tickets to WrestleMania by getting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 11:15:00" d="2021-07-17 11:35:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Gremlin on a Plane
The gang has seats on the largest airplane ever to fly the open skies! Unfortunately the plane is also beset by a Gremlin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 11:35:00" d="2021-07-17 11:45:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show V (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Para-Abnormal Activities
Jerry pretends to be a ghost to terrorize Tom until he gets a fright of his own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 11:45:00" d="2021-07-17 12:00:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show V (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% I Dream of Jerry
A battle ensues over who will control the Genie that emerges from an antic lamp Genger brings home from a yard sale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 12:00:00" d="2021-07-17 12:10:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series III (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Scrapper Cleans Up
Irma wants a romantic break; Bean doesn’t. It’s too expensive. Irma kidnaps Teddy and refuses to give him back unless Bean promises</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 12:10:00" d="2021-07-17 12:25:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series III (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Coach Trip
Bean wants to avoid lunch with Irma’s Mum at all costs. He persuades Mrs. Wicket to let him join her on a coach trip to a concert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 12:25:00" d="2021-07-17 12:35:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series III (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Save That Tree
Bean is showing Irma his favourite tree in the park one day when he discovers a tree surgeon getting ready to cut it down</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 12:35:00" d="2021-07-17 13:00:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series III (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% For Sale
Mrs. Wicket is persuaded by a jaunty estate agent to put her house up for sale. Bean is distraught – where will he live? Not Mrs. Wicket’s problem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 13:00:00" d="2021-07-17 13:10:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series III (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Jumping Bean
Mr. Bean wants to learn skateboarding but hurts himself on his first try. Meanwhile Miss Wince is showing off her new mobility scooter at Mrs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 13:10:00" d="2021-07-17 13:25:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series III (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Cat Chaos
Mrs. Wicket becomes annoyingly inconsolable when Scrapper goes missing – calling for him at all hours of the day and night. Bean can’t get any sleep! He decides that the only way to restore peace in the household is to go out and find Scrapper himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 13:25:00" d="2021-07-17 13:40:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series III (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Stick It
Bean discovers Mrs. Wicket’s nephew and Bruiser Jnr swapping football stickers and decides that he wants to fill up a sticker album too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 13:40:00" d="2021-07-17 14:00:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series III (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Bean at the Museum
Mr. Bean thinks he’s just dug up a valuable coin in the back-garden and goes rushing off to the Museum to have it valued little knowing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 14:00:00" d="2021-07-17 14:10:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Rat Trap
Mr Bean is very scared on a stormy night and even more so when he hears Mrs Wicket screaming from downstairs. Mr Bean investigates and finds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 14:10:00" d="2021-07-17 14:25:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Valentine's Bean
Mr Bean decides to do something romantic on Valentine’s Day for his long-suffering girlfriend Irma. But while he is secretly delivering</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 14:25:00" d="2021-07-17 14:35:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% All You Can Eat
Mr Bean has forgotten he's supposed to be cooking dinner for his long-suffering girlfriend Irma. He dashes to the supermarket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 14:35:00" d="2021-07-17 15:00:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Flat Pack
Mr Bean is in need of a sturdy new bookcase and sets off to visit a furniture warehouse. He finds one that’s perfect but is outraged</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 15:00:00" d="2021-07-17 15:30:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Eating Crow
The gang visits a farm that’s being haunted by a creepy Scarecrow Ghost. Fred wants to impress the farmer’s daughter with his mystery solving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 15:30:00" d="2021-07-17 16:00:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% I Scooby Dooby Do
The gang is honoured to take part in the wedding of two close friends. But can Best Man, Shaggy, and Maid of Honor, Daphne, save their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 16:00:00" d="2021-07-17 16:05:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Kid Stuff
A little baby goat butts his head through a distant wall of the estate and starts nibbling the grass. At first, he helps Tom with the yardwork</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 16:05:00" d="2021-07-17 16:10:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Stolen Heart
When a gorgeous feline walks into the Cat and Mouse Detective Agency, Tom is immediately smitten. But someone has already stolen her heart—a</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 16:10:00" d="2021-07-17 16:25:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% The Last Laugh
Red Herring complains to Tom and Jerry that he keeps hearing laughter everywhere he goes. Tom and Jerry bodyguard Red to prevent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 16:25:00" d="2021-07-17 16:30:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% The Invisible Cat
On another scary night in the castle, The Invisible Cat wants nothing more than to catch mice. After it picks up and carries Jerry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 16:30:00" d="2021-07-17 16:40:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Eagle Eye Jerry
While Rick and Ginger take a mountain hike, Tom and Jerry befriend three cute baby eaglets and help them learn to fly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 16:40:00" d="2021-07-17 16:46:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Frenemies
When Rick and Ginger argue on their anniversary, Cupid decides to get involved. However, he gets a head injury in a chase between Tom and Jerry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 16:46:00" d="2021-07-17 16:50:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Alien Again
Lamput likes nothing more than a pleasant evening watching the night sky for UFOs. The peaceful night is ruined, of course, by those pesky Docs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 16:50:00" d="2021-07-17 17:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Opera
Specs and Skinny spruce themselves up and head out to a piano concerto in the royal concert hall. They're on their best behavior, until</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 17:00:00" d="2021-07-17 17:10:00"><n u="Mush Mush And The Mushables">Mush Mush And The Mushables I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Show Mush Go On
Mushpie loves to sing. Only problem she is terrible at it! But Lilit, who has never heard her sing before, wants to make Mushpie happy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 17:10:00" d="2021-07-17 17:30:00"><n u="Mush Mush And The Mushables">Mush Mush And The Mushables I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mushpot's Treasure
When Mushpot wishes he could roll back the seasons and relive being a Mushler, our friends get him to hang out doing cool Mushler stuff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 17:30:00" d="2021-07-17 17:40:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Geocaching
Lola’s mother has installed a Geocaching application on her daughter’s phone. Lola is over the moon and heads outside to start playing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 17:40:00" d="2021-07-17 17:45:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Monster Melon
In the garden Lola is experimenting in how to plant watermelons. On one of the watermelons she sprinkles a powerful fertilizer which</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 17:45:00" d="2021-07-17 18:00:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Eyes Wide Open
Hoodie has an eye disease and must be contained inside a special bubble for his owns protection. Lola asks Pat to keep a close eye on him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 18:00:00" d="2021-07-17 18:10:00"><n u="Kingdom Force">Kingdom Force I (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>License to Drill
TJ is irked when he's told to train the other Kingdom Force members how to use his vehicle, but it's nothing to how he feels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 18:10:00" d="2021-07-17 18:30:00"><n u="Kingdom Force">Kingdom Force I (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Norvyn Not-So-Big
Big problems follow the team after a shrink ray zaps everything in sight. ncluding Kingdom Force themselves! Will the tiny heroes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 18:30:00" d="2021-07-17 18:35:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Hooks and Loops Bear
Grizzy is awakened from his nap by the unpleasant, ongoing sound of Velcro strips being ripped off. The Lemmings have covered their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 18:35:00" d="2021-07-17 18:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Fast Workout
The she-bear Grizzy is enamored with has lost her favorite flower in an inaccessible spot under a giant boulder. Grizzy tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 18:40:00" d="2021-07-17 19:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bat-Grizzy
The Lemmings try to catch a bat to play rodeo, disturbing Grizzy as he plays his favorite game on the ranger's mobile. But when the phone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 19:00:00" d="2021-07-17 19:10:00"><n u="Alice &amp; Lewis">Alice &amp; Lewis I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Teatime, Again and Again
Wonderland is stuck in a time loop and only Alice and Lewis are aware of it! Teatime is a sacred moment, so having to repeat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 19:10:00" d="2021-07-17 19:30:00"><n u="Alice &amp; Lewis">Alice &amp; Lewis I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bubble Mania
Alice comes bursting into Wonderland, eager to get Lewis to try out her new chewing-gums. But the rabbit swallows one sideways and now, every</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 19:30:00" d="2021-07-17 19:40:00"><n u="Baby Looney Tunes">Baby Looney Tunes I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% A Clean Sweep
Baby Looney Tunes introduces the world's most beloved cartoon characters as precocious preschoolers, discovering the world one baby-step at a time!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 19:40:00" d="2021-07-17 20:00:00"><n u="Baby Looney Tunes">Baby Looney Tunes I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Daffy Did It!
Tweety blames Daffy for his mistake and then has trouble living with the guilt of lying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 20:00:00" d="2021-07-17 20:10:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Curse of the Monkeybird / Marvin Flag Gag: Deflating Planet / Harm Wrestling
In the series premiere episode, Daffy and Porky Pig ride through the jungle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 20:10:00" d="2021-07-17 20:30:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Big League Beast / Hole Gag: Mini Elmer / Firehouse Frenzy
When the lights go out in Bugs Bunny's home, he decides to visit the only neighborhood house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 20:30:00" d="2021-07-17 20:35:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Daredevil Duck
Daredevil Daffy attempts to jump his motorcycle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 20:35:00" d="2021-07-17 20:40:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Planet of the Bigfoots - Part 1
Space Adventurer Bugs Bunny and his crew face a battle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 20:40:00" d="2021-07-17 20:45:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Planet of the Bigfoots - Part 2
Space Adventurer Bugs Bunny and his crew face a battle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 20:45:00" d="2021-07-17 21:00:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Cold Medal Wabbit
Cal attempts to win gold in every Winter Olympic event</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 21:00:00" d="2021-07-17 21:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Highest Bidder
At a luxurious auction, Mrs. Muchmore enters a bidding war with a charming young man to acquire a priceless ruby brooch. She invites</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 21:05:00" d="2021-07-17 21:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>I Now Pronounce You Dog And Cat
It's movie night! Mrs. M screens her old wedding video for her pets. As she steps away, the pets get in one of their usual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 21:10:00" d="2021-07-17 21:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bentley'S Girlfriend
Taffy witnesses Bentley and Mrs Muchmore sobbing in front of a romance scene on television. What would happen to Bentley if he met his true love?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 21:25:00" d="2021-07-17 21:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dna
Mrs. Muchmore wants to find out her pet's lineage so she send Taffy and Bentley's hair to be tested. Taffy, anxious that she finds out he's a raccoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 21:30:00" d="2021-07-17 21:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Staycation
When Forsythe loads the limo up for Mrs Muchmore and the pets' vacation, Taffy and Bentley get accidentally locked in the basement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 21:40:00" d="2021-07-17 21:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mission Mish Mash
Taffy's raccoon friends come to the Mansion, hoping to take advantage of Mrs. Muchmore's largesse. But the red bow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 21:45:00" d="2021-07-17 22:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A Bentley Carol - Christmas
It's Christmas Eve and Bentley finally succeeds -- he has removed Taffy's ribbon and the raccoon is tossed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 22:00:00" d="2021-07-17 22:05:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (55)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% As Far as Bear Can Remember
An old metal box found by chance in a recess of a cliff brings back childhood memories for Grizzy and the Lemmings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 22:05:00" d="2021-07-17 22:10:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (56)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Chemical Lemmings
How can one peacefully watch a documentary on salmon fish, nice and comfy on the sofa, when the Lemmings are playing chemistry novices</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 22:10:00" d="2021-07-17 22:25:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (57)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Remote Control
Grizzy's TV remote control is stolen by a partridge who collects high-tech objects in his nest perched high up in a tree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 22:25:00" d="2021-07-17 22:30:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (58)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The Bear and the Butterfly
Grizzy has got it into his head to offer a butterfly to the she-bear he's in love with. But the Lemmings fight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 22:30:00" d="2021-07-17 22:35:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (59)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Get off My. 
The Lemmings have discovered an addictive new game based on the astonishing bouncing properties of the ranger's new running shoes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 22:35:00" d="2021-07-17 22:45:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (60)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Babysitting
Grizzy babysits for the she-bear he has a crush on, who has entrusted him with the care of her cub. There's no question of Grizzy tripping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 22:45:00" d="2021-07-17 23:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (61)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Under Lock and Key
Unwilling to share the food both he and the Lemmings are wild about Grizzy locks it up inside the ranger's brand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 23:00:00" d="2021-07-17 23:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (59)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Super Duper Sale
Hidden inside a robot Fizz and Weasel hack the world’s Internet server but Magoo shopping the sales mistakes it for a shopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 23:05:00" d="2021-07-17 23:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (60)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Chill Out
Fizz is recording a chill CD to de-stress the world so he needs peace and quiet. Unlucky for him: Magoo’s come over to borrow a wrench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 23:15:00" d="2021-07-17 23:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (61)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Man of Steel
Magoo thinks he’s in a triathlon and takes Fizz’s superhuman strength headband. The latter had been planning to use it to beat the President</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 23:25:00" d="2021-07-17 23:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (62)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vanilla Strawberry Meltdown
Thinking he’s on an Artic expedition (actually at the beach) Magoo mistakes Fizz for an Amazonian marmoset monkey definitive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 23:35:00" d="2021-07-17 23:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (63)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Sweet Dreams Mr Cat
Fizz beams himself into Weasel’s brain in order to control his useless sidekick and take out Magoo with tranquilizer darts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-17 23:40:00" d="2021-07-18 00:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (64)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fizz FM
Today's the big day! Magoo is recording a hit single! Thinking he's in a music studio, he goes next door and mistakes Fizz for famous producer, Phil Dustspeck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 00:00:00" d="2021-07-18 00:05:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Agent 000
Wanting to impress Iris, Mike slips his bowtie on and does his best James Bond impression. What a stud! Meanwhile the turtles are using</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 00:05:00" d="2021-07-18 00:10:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% What A Circus
Mike tries to brighten Iris's day by putting together an impromptu circus on the patio. Mike plays ringmaster as Fluffy pretends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 00:10:00" d="2021-07-18 00:25:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Double Dog
When Stephan brings a new robot into the house that looks exactly like Mike - he gets an idea. He can use the robot as his stunt double</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 00:25:00" d="2021-07-18 00:35:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Ice Rink
It's sweltering outside and Mike has invited Iris onto the terrace for a cooling cocktail. But the raccoons steal the ice maker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 00:35:00" d="2021-07-18 00:40:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Amnesia
Mercury suffers a huge blow to the head while trying to break into the Mikkelsen's house. When he wakes up, to Mike's great surprise, he seems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 00:40:00" d="2021-07-18 00:48:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Mike Unchained
Tom leaves his beautiful train set out in the house and the raccoons see it as a fantastic way to ship their loot back to their den</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 00:48:00" d="2021-07-18 00:50:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lamput and the Spider
For a blob of goo, Lamput sure has a big heart; the orange softie really can’t sleep until the little spider nearby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 00:50:00" d="2021-07-18 01:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pup Mix
There’s a mixup at the market involving Lamput and a guide-dog, and the Docs find themselves in the unenviable position of having to sneak</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 01:00:00" d="2021-07-18 01:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Citizen Taffy
Bentley decide to make a newspaper and begins a real journalistic war. Taffy immediately recognizes his archrival alias and decide to get revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 01:05:00" d="2021-07-18 01:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Flowers for Bentley
Mrs M find an old special hypno-watch in the attic and gives her to Addie to play with it. Delightful! Taffy craftily swipes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 01:10:00" d="2021-07-18 01:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Raccoon Moon
Taffy is watching TV with Mrs. M: tonight it's a super rare occurrence of a &quot;raccoon moon&quot;. Legend has it, he says, that during its presence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 01:25:00" d="2021-07-18 01:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Love of Loaf
Bentley takes advantage of Mrs. Muchmore's spa treatment, with slices of cucumber on her eyes, to get rid of Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 01:30:00" d="2021-07-18 01:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Climate Control Freaks
Mrs. M installs a hi-tech AC and Heating Unit capable of creating different temperature in the mansion. When Mrs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 01:40:00" d="2021-07-18 01:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Cone Heads
After another rambunctious fight, one that doesn't end well for Taffy, the Vet prescribes him a high-tech cone to stop any unsavory wound-licking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 01:45:00" d="2021-07-18 02:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (141)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Time Out Of Taffy
Taffy and Bentley are in the middle of a tense ceasefire when two strange, metal-clad raccoons appear in a flash of light</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 02:00:00" d="2021-07-18 02:05:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Prints
Grizzy gleefully discovers that he can print images taken with the ranger's camera which is connected to a state-of-the-art printer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 02:05:00" d="2021-07-18 02:10:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Inspector Grizzy
A van pulls up to the ranger's cabin to deliver a full crate of jars of chocolate spread. While Grizzy and the Lemmings fight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 02:10:00" d="2021-07-18 02:20:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% No Entrance!
Like usual, Grizzy picks the door of the Ranger's log cabin to come in and make himself comfortable, but this time it's impossible to enter! The Lemmings have requisitioned the cabin for a party and barricaded themselves inside. Grizzy has no intention of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 02:20:00" d="2021-07-18 02:25:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lemmings Indigestion
The Lemmings have got their hands on a pack of white beans which have very strange properties: when mixed with soda, anyone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 02:25:00" d="2021-07-18 02:30:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Sonata in Bear Major
Grizzy wants to get rid of the old piano in the garage at any cost, for the Lemmings love using it to make a dissonant racket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 02:30:00" d="2021-07-18 02:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Fractions
The Lemmings inherit a crate that fell off a Canadian army convoy transporting ultra-secret material. The case inside the crate emits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 02:40:00" d="2021-07-18 02:45:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (53)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The Bear That Laid Golden Eggs
Near the supermarket, a machine hands out surprise eggs in exchange for a coin. Amongst the lots to be won, there</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 02:45:00" d="2021-07-18 02:50:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (54)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Crash Training Course
At the Ranger's home, Grizzy finds a high-tech gadget that enables you to learn anything at all - sewing, origami, Kung Fu, etc</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 02:50:00" d="2021-07-18 03:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (55)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% As Far as Bear Can Remember
An old metal box found by chance in a recess of a cliff brings back childhood memories for Grizzy and the Lemmings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 03:00:00" d="2021-07-18 03:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Last Groundhog
Magoo mistakes Weasel (in an animal costume) for a groundhog being hunted and confiscates the hunter’s gun. In reality he steals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 03:05:00" d="2021-07-18 03:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Home Havoc
Magoo can't find the book that Linda lent him and he's ready to turn the house upside down to find it. The problem is that he</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 03:15:00" d="2021-07-18 03:20:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pinkbeard's Treasure
Magoo hunting for Pinkbeard’s treasure mistakes the park for an island. Fizz and Weasel are there selling ice cream that never falls on the ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 03:20:00" d="2021-07-18 03:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mistaken Identity
At the supermarket, Magoo mixes his shopping cart up with a baby stroller. Fizz decides to save the toddler and become a media star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 03:25:00" d="2021-07-18 03:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hamster Fishing
Fizz is at the municipal pool, he wants to revolution the world of sub-marine hairdressing!But Magoo, thinking that he is actually fishing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 03:35:00" d="2021-07-18 03:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Whiter Than White
Magoo thinking he’s at the laundromat wanders into a candy factory where Fizz and Weasel are creating a bubblegum that makes Fizz-shaped bubbles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 03:40:00" d="2021-07-18 03:50:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Poolwatch!
Magoo thinks that the whole neighborhood has been flooded when in fact he is just at the local swimming pool. He starts trying to rescue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 03:50:00" d="2021-07-18 04:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hibernafizz
Magoo comes across Fizz encased in ice and thinks he has found a prehistoric man. He thaws him out and acts like a Cro-Magnon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 04:00:00" d="2021-07-18 04:05:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (66)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Duchess in charge
Mike has a visitor for the afternoon - Duchess - and she's still hopelessly infatuated with Mike. She's so in</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 04:05:00" d="2021-07-18 04:10:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (67)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gone to Pot
It's a beautiful summer day and Mike decides to woo Iris with a refreshing pineapple cocktail. But the pot he needs to make the drink</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 04:10:00" d="2021-07-18 04:20:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (68)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Animal Magnetism
Mike decides to try to impress Iris by pretending to be a superhero. With the help of a huge fridge magnet, Mike intends to attract</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 04:20:00" d="2021-07-18 04:25:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (69)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Hypnosis
Mike wakes up in the bathtub, huh? The house has been turned upside down and the other animals are being weird. They're acting like zombies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 04:25:00" d="2021-07-18 04:30:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (70)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Mike Impounded
The raccoons finally get the better of Mike while he tries to retrieve an object in their lair. They lock him in a cage and Freddy rushes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 04:30:00" d="2021-07-18 04:40:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (71)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Lights, Camera. Inaction!
Mike is inspired by a movie he sees on TV and decides to direct his own film. He enlists the help of Iris, Fluffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 04:40:00" d="2021-07-18 04:45:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (72)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Freddy's Blues
Mercury's clumsiness leads to his brother Freddy being locked in the safe in their den. Now Mercury has to break into the Mikkelsens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 04:45:00" d="2021-07-18 04:50:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (73)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Dognapped
The raccoons resort to kidnapping Iris in order to create a diversion so Freddy can rob the Mikkelsens' house. Back in the lair, Mercury</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 04:50:00" d="2021-07-18 05:00:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (74)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Fluffy the Fugitive
Mike rescues Fluffy from the raccoon's lair but he doesn't notice that the kitty has pocketed one the racoon's favourite toys</k>  </p>
</a>
