<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="133" t="2019-08-13 01:56:43"><p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 05:01:00" d="2019-08-18 05:08:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy discovers a baby raccoon not far from the log cabin. When he sees its big moist eyes, Grizzy melts and adopts the creature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 05:08:00" d="2019-08-18 05:15:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy discovers the pleasures of video games on the ranger’s console. The Lemmings want to try their hand at the joystick but Grizzy refuses to interrupt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 05:15:00" d="2019-08-18 05:25:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean discovers the great outdoors is not always so great</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 05:25:00" d="2019-08-18 05:35:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean’s hobby goes down in flames in his battle for air supremacy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 05:35:00" d="2019-08-18 05:45:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>During a visit to Buckingham Palace, Mr Bean meets the lady of the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 05:45:00" d="2019-08-18 06:00:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean takes a trip down Memory Lane</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 06:00:00" d="2019-08-18 06:07:00"><n>Pink Panther and Pals - Elements</n>    <k>Pink Panther and pals Hoarse, Aardvark and Ant are up to their usual adventures. The coolest cat around, Pink Panther continues to run circles around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 06:07:00" d="2019-08-18 06:14:00"><n>Pink Panther and Pals - Elements</n>    <k>Pink Panther and pals Hoarse, Aardvark and Ant are up to their usual adventures. The coolest cat around, Pink Panther continues to run circles around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 06:14:00" d="2019-08-18 06:30:00"><n>Pink Panther and Pals - Elements</n>    <k>Pink Panther and pals Hoarse, Aardvark and Ant are up to their usual adventures. The coolest cat around, Pink Panther continues to run circles around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 06:30:00" d="2019-08-18 06:35:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Daffy Duck tries to help Settler Porky Pig fight Sam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 06:35:00" d="2019-08-18 06:40:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Bugs seeks revenge on Viktor the male model</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 06:40:00" d="2019-08-18 06:45:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Roughrider Yosemite Sam seeks glory in battle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 06:45:00" d="2019-08-18 06:55:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Daffy Ducks decides to help out Red Omaha mine for gold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 06:55:00" d="2019-08-18 07:00:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Baby Happo wants the last fruit on a tree that’s just out of his reach. Star decides to help byusing her specialist acrobatic skills with hilarious consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 07:00:00" d="2019-08-18 07:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Nutty Hill is suffering from a stifling heat wave. Grizzy decides to get into the fridge, where the temperature will be more bearable, but the shelves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 07:06:00" d="2019-08-18 07:12:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy is frustrated: just as he was about to coat a nice big fresh salmon with chocolate spread and snuggle up in front of the TV, he discovers that the pantry is empty!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 07:12:00" d="2019-08-18 07:25:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy's nap is interrupted by an annoying vibration. He sees the forest ranger's cell phone on the couch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 07:25:00" d="2019-08-18 07:31:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% When a tiny octopus accidentally arrives at the house, it's up to Jerry to make sure that Tom doesn't eat him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 07:31:00" d="2019-08-18 07:38:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% It's Tom versus Jerry on the manor's grounds, as Tom prepares the grounds for a croquet tournament</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 07:38:00" d="2019-08-18 07:50:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Rick buys a drone that Tom and Jerry immediately put to use for their own high-jinks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 07:50:00" d="2019-08-18 07:56:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom accidentally visits a bizarre twin version of his house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 07:56:00" d="2019-08-18 08:03:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Jerry dreams of a life where he is the lord of the manor, and Tom is the servant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 08:03:00" d="2019-08-18 08:20:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom is hypnotized by a television show and accidentally sold as a chew toy. Jerry works hard to get him back in one piece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 08:20:00" d="2019-08-18 08:30:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean finally has a showdown with the mysterious Reliant Robin. Who will be the victor?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 08:30:00" d="2019-08-18 08:45:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean has to get the bride to the church on time. nyway he can!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 08:45:00" d="2019-08-18 08:51:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy gets scared as Mrs M tests him to discover his lineage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 08:51:00" d="2019-08-18 08:58:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Vacation's coming! But before the manor must be secured…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 08:58:00" d="2019-08-18 09:15:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy’s friends from the dump discover Mrs M manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 09:15:00" d="2019-08-18 09:36:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>When the ghost of a small town's founder returns to scare off mayoral candidates, the gang decides to run Velma as mayor to bait the ghost</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 09:36:00" d="2019-08-18 09:57:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>The Scooby Gang enter Dickens' classic &quot;A Christmas Carol&quot; as they try to get to the bottom of the mysterious ghost tormenting Scrooge in 1843 England</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 09:57:00" d="2019-08-18 10:40:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>A very bad parking choice on Fred’s part leads the gang to an asteroid mining base in outer space where an alien virus appears to be turning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 10:40:00" d="2019-08-18 11:50:00"><n>Scooby-Doo! Frankencreepy</n>    <k>Velma discovers she's inherited her great-great-uncle Dr. Von Dinkenstein's cursed castle in the terrifying town of Transylvania, Pennsylvania</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 11:50:00" d="2019-08-18 11:55:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Space Adventurer Bugs Bunny and his crew face a battle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 11:55:00" d="2019-08-18 12:05:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Baby Happo wants the last fruit on a tree that’s just out of his reach. Star decides to help byusing her specialist acrobatic skills with hilarious consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 12:05:00" d="2019-08-18 12:15:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean wants a smart phone but they’re too expensive especially when you can build your own!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 12:15:00" d="2019-08-18 12:30:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean has some unexpected guests who think he runs a hotel!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 12:30:00" d="2019-08-18 12:40:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Bunnicula and his gang, &quot;The Bunny Boys,&quot; go through New Orleans to retrieve his stolen ears</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 12:40:00" d="2019-08-18 12:50:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>The pets must figure out the cure for Bunnicula's supernatural flu before it's too late!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 12:50:00" d="2019-08-18 13:00:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>The pets encounter a strange creature on a camping trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 13:00:00" d="2019-08-18 13:10:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Harold's tail decides who's boss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 13:10:00" d="2019-08-18 13:20:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Bunnicula goes back in time to prevent a bad day from happening</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 13:20:00" d="2019-08-18 13:29:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Bunnicula gives Chester a magical hat of bravery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 13:29:00" d="2019-08-18 13:39:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Bunnicula and Chester use enchanted dolls against each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 13:39:00" d="2019-08-18 13:49:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Bunnicula enlists the help of a party expert to loosen Chester up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 13:49:00" d="2019-08-18 13:59:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>The pets pay a high price for good luck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 13:59:00" d="2019-08-18 14:09:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>The pets go to a monster convention and realize Bunnicula is famous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 14:09:00" d="2019-08-18 14:19:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>The pets get stuck in each other's skins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 14:19:00" d="2019-08-18 15:15:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>A doppelganger has been set loose in the Orlock Apartments!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 15:15:00" d="2019-08-18 15:20:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>When Super Happo catches a cold, his super sized sneezes threaten to reveal his secret heroidentity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 15:20:00" d="2019-08-18 15:30:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>During a visit to Buckingham Palace, Mr Bean meets the lady of the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 15:30:00" d="2019-08-18 15:45:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean takes a trip down Memory Lane</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 15:45:00" d="2019-08-18 15:55:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Chester and Harold try to stop a pet calendar photo shoot that threatens to expose Bunnicula’s vampire secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 15:55:00" d="2019-08-18 16:15:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Mina's new friend Russel has a dark secret. e's slowly turning into a Brussels sprout! Can Bunnicula help the poor lad, or will he simply eat him?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 16:15:00" d="2019-08-18 16:21:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy gets scared as Mrs M tests him to discover his lineage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 16:21:00" d="2019-08-18 16:28:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Vacation's coming! But before the manor must be secured…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 16:28:00" d="2019-08-18 16:40:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy’s friends from the dump discover Mrs M manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 16:40:00" d="2019-08-18 16:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 3</n>    <k>59% Angelo Rules follows twelve-year-old Angelo as he tries to control his life by using funny schemes - with a little help from his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 16:50:00" d="2019-08-18 17:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 3</n>    <k>59% Angelo Rules follows twelve-year-old Angelo as he tries to control his life by using funny schemes - with a little help from his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 17:10:00" d="2019-08-18 17:15:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Darkbat seeks vengeance against Blacque Jacque Shellacque</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 17:15:00" d="2019-08-18 17:20:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Police Officers Horace and Porky go undercover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 17:20:00" d="2019-08-18 17:25:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Porky falls in love with Petunia, queen of the land</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 17:25:00" d="2019-08-18 17:35:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Porky falls in love with Petunia, queen of the land</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 17:35:00" d="2019-08-18 17:41:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom is put in charge of getting the manor's dog into showdog shape, unfortunately Jerry will try to sabotage him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 17:41:00" d="2019-08-18 17:48:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry are left with Aunt Loella, a kindly woman who accidentally mistakes them for a dog and cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 17:48:00" d="2019-08-18 18:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom is in charge of keeping a snobby cat, Prancy Van der Snoot, clean and out of trouble. Unfortunately, she has her eye on Jerry who leads her on a manic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 18:00:00" d="2019-08-18 18:06:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Ginger loves that Little Quacker visits her new birdbath. Unfortunately, Tom and Spike try their hardest to get him to move out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 18:06:00" d="2019-08-18 18:13:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Jerry's cousins come for a visit to the manor, but turn out to bring more trouble than they're worth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 18:13:00" d="2019-08-18 18:30:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Jerry uses Tom's fear of cucumbers to startle him at every turn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 18:30:00" d="2019-08-18 18:55:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>Scooby Doo runs into an old kennel mate from the rescue shelter, Axel, who is now a state-of-the–art, highly trained K-9 police dog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 18:55:00" d="2019-08-18 19:25:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>When a successful video game company tries to convince Velma to work for them in San Francisco, the gang becomes embroiled in the mystery of a video game villain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 19:25:00" d="2019-08-18 19:35:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Touring Yellowstone, Ben uncovers a plot by the fast &amp; furious LaGrange to find treasure buried below the national park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 19:35:00" d="2019-08-18 19:50:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>When a wizard cosplayer gets his hands on a real, magical wand at Comic Con, Ben enlists Gwen to help stop Hex from retrieving it by tricking the wicked warlock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 19:50:00" d="2019-08-18 20:00:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 3</n>    <k>59% Angelo Rules follows twelve-year-old Angelo as he tries to control his life by using funny schemes - with a little help from his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 20:00:00" d="2019-08-18 20:20:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 3</n>    <k>59% Angelo Rules follows twelve-year-old Angelo as he tries to control his life by using funny schemes - with a little help from his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 20:20:00" d="2019-08-18 20:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy gets scared as Mrs M tests him to discover his lineage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 20:26:00" d="2019-08-18 20:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Vacation's coming! But before the manor must be secured…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 20:33:00" d="2019-08-18 20:50:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy’s friends from the dump discover Mrs M manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 20:50:00" d="2019-08-18 20:56:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy builds a look-alike robot to keep the Lemmings away while he prepares a party for his beloved she-bear. But his double's artificial intelligence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 20:56:00" d="2019-08-18 21:03:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>When a meteorite falls not far from the log cabin, strange berries start to grow. One of their properties is that they make anyone who</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 21:03:00" d="2019-08-18 21:15:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>When she is accidentally hit over the head, the she-bear Grizzy's in love with thinks she's a Lemming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 21:15:00" d="2019-08-18 21:21:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Under the wood floor of the log cabin, Grizzy and the Lemmings discover the entrance to an underground gallery with an old treasure card that indicates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 21:21:00" d="2019-08-18 21:28:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy tries to impress the she-bear he's in love with by making a sculpture of her from a piece of wood. But the Lemmings gnaw at the</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 21:28:00" d="2019-08-18 21:40:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>When he brandishes an Indian scepter that the Lemmings brought home, Grizzy sees the Lemmings bow low before him and behave like servants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 21:40:00" d="2019-08-18 21:50:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy and Cat find a witch’s broom, they can’t resist taking it for a spin. But the fun quickly ends when their joyride inflames the rage of every</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 21:50:00" d="2019-08-18 22:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Epic, the Queen asks Henri to compose a song to lift the spirits of her beloved subjects for this year’s Harvest Festival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 22:10:00" d="2019-08-18 22:20:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>As Henri and Bad Jack go head-to-head in a race to find an extremely rare treasure, Jimmy lies to Bjorn and then has to try to repair their friendship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 22:20:00" d="2019-08-18 22:40:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Heart of gold Henri and Jimmy host the bad Witch, who has been kicked out of her house by her sister Stinky Swamp Witch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 22:40:00" d="2019-08-18 22:47:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Tonight, Lola and Pat are taking part in a huge flash mob event. They have rehearsed extensively and everything is set. Except that in the meantime Hoodie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 22:47:00" d="2019-08-18 22:54:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>At the end of their tether with their sworn enemy Pat, the Guanos decide to do away with him. With a little help from their bird friends, they decide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 22:54:00" d="2019-08-18 23:05:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends are supposed to watch a performance at Moon Circus, but unfortunately they miss it. No worries. Lola decides to put</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 23:05:00" d="2019-08-18 23:12:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola enrolls Pat on a dog firefighter training program. But Victor is convinced that Tank is made for the job. An impromptu contest is held composed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 23:12:00" d="2019-08-18 23:19:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola receives an invitation from the museum to attend the premiere of an exhibition about extinct species with one of her friends. She invites Victor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 23:19:00" d="2019-08-18 23:30:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Victor tests his new remote-controlled car in the park with Lola and the dogs. But he loses control over the car, and Tank is carried away by the car and hits his owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 23:30:00" d="2019-08-18 23:40:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean, badgered by a strange pink animal, warms to the creature when it shows its true colours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 23:40:00" d="2019-08-18 23:55:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>When invited to dinner by Mr Bean, it’s probably best to take your own sandwiches</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-18 23:55:00" d="2019-08-19 00:05:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean makes it to the top of the ladder… and gets stuck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 00:05:00" d="2019-08-19 00:20:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean bites off more than he can chew when he attempts DIY dentistry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 00:20:00" d="2019-08-19 00:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings inherit a crate that fell off a Canadian army convoy. Inside, a case emits a sort of laser beam that divides objects into multiple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 00:26:00" d="2019-08-19 00:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Near the supermarket, a machine hands out surprise eggs in exchange for a coin. Amongst the lots to be won, there is a super firework rocket the Lemmings dream of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 00:32:00" d="2019-08-19 00:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>At the Ranger's home, Grizzy finds a high-tech gadget that enables you to learn anything within seconds thanks to electrodes hooked to the brain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 00:38:00" d="2019-08-19 00:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>An old metal box found by chance in a recess of a cliff brings back childhood memories for Grizzy and the Lemmings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 00:45:00" d="2019-08-19 00:50:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>How can one peacefully watch a documentary on salmon fish, nice and comfy on the sofa, when the Lemmings are playing chemistry novices with a fun experiment box?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 00:50:00" d="2019-08-19 00:55:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Fixit finds a magic lamp containing a genie and makes a wish. But Captain has moreambitious ideas and wants to make his own magic. With two keen Happos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 00:55:00" d="2019-08-19 01:05:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>After a foolhardy challenge causes Jimmy and Lance to be captured by Bad Jack, Henri and Wilfried must team up to save their squires</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 01:05:00" d="2019-08-19 01:20:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>After Jimmy and Cat stop thieves from robbing the Queen, Cat hides so her mother doesn’t find she's skipped school. But when the Queen celebrates Jimmy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 01:20:00" d="2019-08-19 01:30:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When the Black Rats are attacking all convoys supplying the kingdom, Henri is sent with a supercarriage to defeat the Rats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 01:30:00" d="2019-08-19 01:40:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy pushes his dad into “good-deed overdrive” to be First Knight, Henri goes too far and gets busted down to “Horse traffic duty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 01:40:00" d="2019-08-19 01:47:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is preparing a package to send to her Japanese pen pal. But the Guanos are watching and get the idea to sneak Hoodie inside the package and get rid of him forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 01:47:00" d="2019-08-19 01:53:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Seeing how Pat and Tank have put on weight, Lola and Victor decide to put them both on fitness training program for dogs. Whoever loses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 01:53:00" d="2019-08-19 02:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends must hand in a math assignment. Instead of doing his homework, Victor prefers to wait for the girls to finish the assignment, before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 02:00:00" d="2019-08-19 02:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola’s mother has installed a Geocaching application on her daughter’s phone. Lola is over the moon and heads outside to start playing. Victor also decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 02:07:00" d="2019-08-19 02:13:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>In the garden, Lola is experimenting in how to plant watermelons. On one of the watermelons, she sprinkles a powerful fertilizer, which is also very dangerous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 02:13:00" d="2019-08-19 02:25:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Hoodie has an eye infection and has to wear a special protective bubble. Lola asks Pat to look after him. The Guanos naturally decide this is the perfect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 02:25:00" d="2019-08-19 02:31:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>When he realises that his beloved she-bear adores the smell of flowers, Grizzy decides to offer her the geraniums that decorate the window ledges of the ranger's cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 02:31:00" d="2019-08-19 02:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>This is not Grizzy's day: after making a fool of himself in front of the she-bear, he is ousted from the cabin by the Lemmings. But his luck is about to change</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 02:38:00" d="2019-08-19 02:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy can’t believe his eyes when he sees objects moving all by themselves. He soon realises it’s the Lemmings who are playing around with a magnet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 02:45:00" d="2019-08-19 02:51:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy is persuaded that the she-bear he's in love with has been turned into a frog. Whilst he looks through the ranger's books of fairytales, the Lemmings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 02:51:00" d="2019-08-19 02:58:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy discovers a baby raccoon not far from the log cabin. When he sees its big moist eyes, Grizzy melts and adopts the creature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 02:58:00" d="2019-08-19 03:05:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy discovers the pleasures of video games on the ranger’s console. The Lemmings want to try their hand at the joystick but Grizzy refuses to interrupt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 03:05:00" d="2019-08-19 03:15:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy and Cat find a witch’s broom, they can’t resist taking it for a spin. But the fun quickly ends when their joyride inflames the rage of every</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 03:15:00" d="2019-08-19 03:25:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Epic, the Queen asks Henri to compose a song to lift the spirits of her beloved subjects for this year’s Harvest Festival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 03:25:00" d="2019-08-19 03:35:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>As Henri and Bad Jack go head-to-head in a race to find an extremely rare treasure, Jimmy lies to Bjorn and then has to try to repair their friendship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 03:35:00" d="2019-08-19 03:50:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Heart of gold Henri and Jimmy host the bad Witch, who has been kicked out of her house by her sister Stinky Swamp Witch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 03:50:00" d="2019-08-19 03:57:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Tonight, Lola and Pat are taking part in a huge flash mob event. They have rehearsed extensively and everything is set. Except that in the meantime Hoodie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 03:57:00" d="2019-08-19 04:04:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends are supposed to watch a performance at Moon Circus, but unfortunately they miss it. No worries. Lola decides to put</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 04:04:00" d="2019-08-19 04:10:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>At the end of their tether with their sworn enemy Pat, the Guanos decide to do away with him. With a little help from their bird friends, they decide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 04:10:00" d="2019-08-19 04:17:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola enrolls Pat on a dog firefighter training program. But Victor is convinced that Tank is made for the job. An impromptu contest is held composed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 04:17:00" d="2019-08-19 04:23:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Victor tests his new remote-controlled car in the park with Lola and the dogs. But he loses control over the car, and Tank is carried away by the car and hits his owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 04:23:00" d="2019-08-19 04:35:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola receives an invitation from the museum to attend the premiere of an exhibition about extinct species with one of her friends. She invites Victor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 04:35:00" d="2019-08-19 04:41:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy builds a look-alike robot to keep the Lemmings away while he prepares a party for his beloved she-bear. But his double's artificial intelligence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 04:41:00" d="2019-08-19 04:48:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>When she is accidentally hit over the head, the she-bear Grizzy's in love with thinks she's a Lemming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 04:48:00" d="2019-08-19 04:55:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>When a meteorite falls not far from the log cabin, strange berries start to grow. One of their properties is that they make anyone who</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 04:55:00" d="2019-08-19 05:01:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Under the wood floor of the log cabin, Grizzy and the Lemmings discover the entrance to an underground gallery with an old treasure card that indicates</k>  </p>
</a>
