<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="138" t="2019-08-15 22:27:05"><p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 05:01:00" d="2019-08-20 05:08:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy is disturbed in the middle of his TV-snack by a flow of incongruous objects that have been transformed into hot-air balloons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 05:08:00" d="2019-08-20 05:15:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy discovers with great delight that the ranger has purchased a brand new multi-function Stressless recliner. But the Lemmings transform</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 05:15:00" d="2019-08-20 05:24:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean has a bad hair day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 05:24:00" d="2019-08-20 05:35:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Bean’s pursuit of a quiet life ends in a major row</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 05:35:00" d="2019-08-20 05:45:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean discovers being in hospital isn't always a bed of roses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 05:45:00" d="2019-08-20 06:00:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean has to replace his landlady’s cat after an unfortunate ‘accident’</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 06:00:00" d="2019-08-20 06:11:00"><n>The Zoo</n>    <k>It’s the Zoo’s annual inspection day and evil-genius monkey Brutus hatches an explosive plan to get Jürgen kicked out of the zoo, forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 06:11:00" d="2019-08-20 06:30:00"><n>The Zoo</n>    <k>A mystery illness leaves Topaz the kangaroo without a hop. Gorilla Jürgen also comes down with ‘attention-seeker-itis’ and wants treatment too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 06:30:00" d="2019-08-20 06:35:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Daffy Duck crashes a music festival and wreaks havoc</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 06:35:00" d="2019-08-20 06:40:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Blacque Jacque Shellacque kidnaps Santa Clause</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 06:40:00" d="2019-08-20 06:45:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% The Mice have their juice stand destroyed by Yosemite Sam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 06:45:00" d="2019-08-20 06:55:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Bugs eats at Slugsworthy's gaudy restaurant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 06:55:00" d="2019-08-20 07:00:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Striker is not having much luck getting other Happos to be goalie so he can practice awesome penalty shots. Until Super flies in and uses all his powers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 07:00:00" d="2019-08-20 07:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy discovers a gadget that controls various functions in the cabin. He will finally be able to rid of the Lemmings, without even leaving the couch!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 07:06:00" d="2019-08-20 07:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>To make sure that the Lemmings don’t snatch his chocolate spread, Grizzy turns the fridge into a safe. But the Lemmings see Grizzy open the door while sleepwalking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 07:13:00" d="2019-08-20 07:25:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings have invented a new popcorn game which consists of throwing popcorn and catching it with their mouths</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 07:25:00" d="2019-08-20 07:31:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Meathead has lost his marbles- really! Tom and Jerry visit the place where he last saw them, so he can compete in the marble championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 07:31:00" d="2019-08-20 07:38:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Jerry goes out on a blind date set up by his cousin Muscles with a feisty girl mouse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 07:38:00" d="2019-08-20 07:50:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Little Quacker develops a rich operatic voice, and competes in a television pet contest, while Tom tries to make him stop singing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 07:50:00" d="2019-08-20 07:56:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Jerry impersonates a missing hamster, while Tom tries to hide her rapidly multiplying babies from Rick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 07:56:00" d="2019-08-20 08:03:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom is in charge of the manor's clay shooting machine, but Jerry and Tuffy interfere with the afternoon's events</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 08:03:00" d="2019-08-20 08:20:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Jerry's cousin Muscles tries to teach Tom and Spike his anger management tools to no avail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 08:20:00" d="2019-08-20 08:30:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean goes in search of wildlife, but he isn’t expecting to see anything prehistoric!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 08:30:00" d="2019-08-20 08:45:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean has to look after an injured Mrs Wicket, whose demands start to become a pain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 08:45:00" d="2019-08-20 08:51:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The entire mansion is on a kale diet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 08:51:00" d="2019-08-20 08:58:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley helps a cat burglar stealing Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 08:58:00" d="2019-08-20 09:15:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Driiing! Taffy lives the same day for ever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 09:15:00" d="2019-08-20 09:35:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>We travel back to Ancient Greece, where the gang plays unique roles in a Greek Mystery involving the mythological spider woman and her attempts to disrupt a royal wedding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 09:35:00" d="2019-08-20 09:56:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>Shaggy is surprised to see his old childhood first crush has become a goth. Embarrassed that he hasn’t changed at all, Shaggy attends a goth party with the gang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 09:56:00" d="2019-08-20 10:40:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>The gang gets caught up in international espionage when they cross paths with British secret agent, Jenny Vex, and must help her complete her dangerous mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 10:40:00" d="2019-08-20 11:25:00"><n>Scooby-Doo! Adventures: The Mystery Map!</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 11:25:00" d="2019-08-20 11:50:00"><n>Scooby-Doo! Spooky Games</n>    <k>Scooby and the gang get a chance to compete at then world games in London, but when an ancient statue comes to life, it could be game over</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 11:50:00" d="2019-08-20 12:05:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean finds himself with more than a spring in his step</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 12:05:00" d="2019-08-20 12:15:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean ends up on stage at the opera house. n a dress!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 12:15:00" d="2019-08-20 12:30:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean becomes a taxi driver after being locked in a taxi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 12:30:00" d="2019-08-20 12:36:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Trouble ensues when Tom is separated from his own shadow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 12:36:00" d="2019-08-20 12:43:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Jerry leads an accident-prone scouting troop, earning badges and creating mayhem for Tom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 12:43:00" d="2019-08-20 12:55:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Rick has taken up painting to help him relax</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 12:55:00" d="2019-08-20 13:01:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% The witch sisters are brewing their latest concoction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 13:01:00" d="2019-08-20 13:08:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom has planned an afternoon rendezvous with Toodles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 13:08:00" d="2019-08-20 13:25:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% A magical hat creates mayhem for Tom, Jerry, and Spike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 13:25:00" d="2019-08-20 13:32:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley orders a bottle of caviar eau to trap Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 13:32:00" d="2019-08-20 13:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M registers Taffy in the biggest cat show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 13:39:00" d="2019-08-20 13:46:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy feels nostalgia for his former home – the dump</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 13:46:00" d="2019-08-20 13:53:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley sends Taffy to a factory on the other side of the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 13:53:00" d="2019-08-20 14:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs. Muchmore has equipped her home with a defense system</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 14:00:00" d="2019-08-20 14:07:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M calls a 'pet whisperer' to improve pets behaviour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 14:07:00" d="2019-08-20 14:14:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley doesn't know who he is and thinks he's a racoon!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 14:14:00" d="2019-08-20 14:21:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Can Taffy rescue the family without blowing his cover?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 14:21:00" d="2019-08-20 14:28:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs. M receives a visit from a famous raccoon trapper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 14:28:00" d="2019-08-20 14:35:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Exhausted, Forsythe tries to get rid of Bentley and Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 14:35:00" d="2019-08-20 14:42:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley and Taffy decide to order a robot to help Forsythe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 14:42:00" d="2019-08-20 15:10:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy is completely hulked out!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 15:10:00" d="2019-08-20 15:20:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Captain discovers an ancient looking map from a message in a bottle bobbing in the lagoon.He thinks it will lead him a chest full of gold coins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 15:20:00" d="2019-08-20 15:31:00"><n>The Zoo</n>    <k>It’s the Zoo’s annual inspection day and evil-genius monkey Brutus hatches an explosive plan to get Jürgen kicked out of the zoo, forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 15:31:00" d="2019-08-20 15:45:00"><n>The Zoo</n>    <k>A mystery illness leaves Topaz the kangaroo without a hop. Gorilla Jürgen also comes down with ‘attention-seeker-itis’ and wants treatment too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 15:45:00" d="2019-08-20 15:55:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Mina wants to see a real ghost so her pets hire one to give her a little bit of a scare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 15:55:00" d="2019-08-20 16:15:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>After an evil portrait swallows up Mina and her dad, the pets must find a way to break the spell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 16:15:00" d="2019-08-20 16:21:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The entire mansion is on a kale diet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 16:21:00" d="2019-08-20 16:28:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley helps a cat burglar stealing Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 16:28:00" d="2019-08-20 16:40:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Driiing! Taffy lives the same day for ever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 16:40:00" d="2019-08-20 16:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 3</n>    <k>59% Angelo Rules follows twelve-year-old Angelo as he tries to control his life by using funny schemes - with a little help from his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 16:50:00" d="2019-08-20 17:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 3</n>    <k>59% Angelo Rules follows twelve-year-old Angelo as he tries to control his life by using funny schemes - with a little help from his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 17:10:00" d="2019-08-20 17:15:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Cal-umbus discovers the new world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 17:15:00" d="2019-08-20 17:20:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Porky wants to live his dream and play football</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 17:20:00" d="2019-08-20 17:25:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Bugs and his small boat are run over by a giant Riverboat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 17:25:00" d="2019-08-20 17:35:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% A theft occurs at the local art museum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 17:35:00" d="2019-08-20 17:41:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom works with a vampire to collect mice to eat. Luckily, Jerry Van Mouseling is on the case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 17:41:00" d="2019-08-20 17:48:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% In a musical detective episode, Tom and Jerry must figure out the disappearance of famed stage actress Kitty Caterwaul before the opening night of her new musical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 17:48:00" d="2019-08-20 18:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry try to break in to a chicken coop to steal eggs and end up defending the chickens from unknown intruders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 18:00:00" d="2019-08-20 18:06:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% A Halloween party turns the house upside down, as Tom and Jerry try to raid the party food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 18:06:00" d="2019-08-20 18:13:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom is trained by Jerry to compete in a butler competition for the glory of the manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 18:13:00" d="2019-08-20 18:30:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom uses a baby goat to mow the manor's lawn, but it turns out the baby goat wants to eat everything in the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 18:30:00" d="2019-08-20 18:55:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>Fred and the gang help with a mystery involving a figure from Fred's past. Fred discovers his old childhood friend has also arrived with her gang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 18:55:00" d="2019-08-20 19:25:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>Shaggy drags the gang to a childhood arcade where he's determined to finally collect enough tickets to win the prize he's wanted since he was a boy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 19:25:00" d="2019-08-20 19:35:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben, Gwen, and Max stop by the graveyard set of Gwen’s favorite TV show, The Unalivers, but when Ben discovers its lead, Michael Morningstar, is an energy vampire!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 19:35:00" d="2019-08-20 19:50:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben, Gwen, and Max meet a family that appears to be a mirror image of them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 19:50:00" d="2019-08-20 20:01:00"><n>The Zoo</n>    <k>Under pressure to ‘man up’ and ‘get buff’, wimpy lion Neil takes takes diet advice from vegetarian gorilla Jürgen - with disastrous consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 20:01:00" d="2019-08-20 20:20:00"><n>The Zoo</n>    <k>It’s the Zoo’s annual inspection day and evil-genius monkey Brutus hatches an explosive plan to get Jürgen kicked out of the zoo, forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 20:20:00" d="2019-08-20 20:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The entire mansion is on a kale diet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 20:26:00" d="2019-08-20 20:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley helps a cat burglar stealing Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 20:33:00" d="2019-08-20 20:50:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Driiing! Taffy lives the same day for ever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 20:50:00" d="2019-08-20 20:56:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings play kite-surf with a homemade kite. Grizzy notices that the she-bear he's in love with watches the kite perform arabesques in the sky with admiration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 20:56:00" d="2019-08-20 21:03:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings play a new game, floating like flags in the breeze from the fan set on maximum. But Grizzy quickly rids the living room of this interference</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 21:03:00" d="2019-08-20 21:15:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy snatches the last jar of chocolate spread out from under the noses of the Lemmings. In exchange, he offers them the toy stuck inside the lid: a mini-flute</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 21:15:00" d="2019-08-20 21:21:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings have fun tearing down their Kapla block buildings, which they rebuild just as fast. Grizzy finds that the she-bear he's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 21:21:00" d="2019-08-20 21:28:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy dreams that he's a valiant knight who has delivered his beloved. As he is about to take her in his arms, he is woken by the Lemmings who have chosen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 21:28:00" d="2019-08-20 21:40:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings draw inspiration from lessons they find in a martial arts book and start breaking every wooden object they can get their hands on into two</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 21:40:00" d="2019-08-20 21:50:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy enables the Witch of the Cursed Forest to kidnap the Queen, Wilfried becomes the regent’s realm. Wilfried immediately decrees foolish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 21:50:00" d="2019-08-20 22:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>After the queen eats a lollipop that makes her start to shrink, Jimmy and Henri must capture the Dark Forest Witch in order to get an antidote</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 22:10:00" d="2019-08-20 22:20:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy inadvertently convinces Ronny Flash to do an interview with a rock monster, Jimmy, Henri and Cat end up escorting Ronny into the Dark Lands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 22:20:00" d="2019-08-20 22:40:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>To show off, Jimmy arrives at the castle flying on Bjorn, and he pretends the dragon is his pet. But Wilfried captures the “monster,” and Bad Jack threatens to burn Epic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 22:40:00" d="2019-08-20 22:45:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is rehearsing the flute recital she has to play this evening. A lady pigeon perches nearby to enjoy her playing and one of the Guanos falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 22:45:00" d="2019-08-20 22:52:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is planning a surprise dinner for her parents' wedding anniversary so she settles into the kitchen to prepare a nice meal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 22:52:00" d="2019-08-20 23:05:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends are organizing a food drive for the city’s kennel. But the food supplies soon attract the attention of Tank and the Guanos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 23:05:00" d="2019-08-20 23:12:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is due to be interviewed as Pet owner of the Week for a pet’s magazine. Victor is jealous. Surely he’s been the best pet owner this week</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 23:12:00" d="2019-08-20 23:18:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>This morning Lola is feeling very anxious. She has a big test coming up at school and she’s not at all confident</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 23:18:00" d="2019-08-20 23:30:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and Victor are both fans of the game Galaktik dance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 23:30:00" d="2019-08-20 23:40:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean builds a supermarket super trolley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 23:40:00" d="2019-08-20 23:55:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean gets in a complete flap when he befriends a feathered theif</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 23:55:00" d="2019-08-21 00:05:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean is forced to look after his worst enemy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 00:05:00" d="2019-08-21 00:20:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean loses his bottle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 00:20:00" d="2019-08-21 00:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy is impressed by the TV show of a magician who transforms a partridge into a bouquet of flowers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 00:26:00" d="2019-08-21 00:33:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>On a very hot day, an ice cream commercial awakes the desire of Grizzy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 00:33:00" d="2019-08-21 00:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings have discovered a truly wild new game: an augmented reality program on the ranger's digital tablet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 00:39:00" d="2019-08-21 00:46:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The only edible food item left in the ranger's cabin is a gorgeous salmon, which is stuck inside a block of ice at the back of the freezer compartment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 00:46:00" d="2019-08-21 00:50:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings have unearthed a box filled with birthday fountains of light that spit forth giant bursts of sparks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 00:50:00" d="2019-08-21 00:55:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Bella tries to set up her deck chair but, in the struggle, she gets trapped between its struts. Can Fixit save the day or will he make things a whole lot worse?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 00:55:00" d="2019-08-21 01:05:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy and Cat discover Colbert never completed his officiant exam, he has to go on a &quot;field mission&quot; with Henri to keep his job</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 01:05:00" d="2019-08-21 01:20:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Cat’s morale is low about ever becoming a knight, Henri tries to save her with a song and inadvertently sends her on a dangerous solo quest into the dark lands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 01:20:00" d="2019-08-21 01:30:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Henri offers to help Jimmy win the school talent show, he mentors his son in the “Zen of mandolin.” But one of the judges of the show turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 01:30:00" d="2019-08-21 01:40:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy makes a bargain with Bad Jack’s family-outcast brother Jeff, he gets Bad Jack banished from the kingdom. But Jeff turns out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 01:40:00" d="2019-08-21 01:47:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is thrilled, she just won the first prize in a contest, and will get the visit of her favourite star! Unfortunately, there’s a minor problem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 01:47:00" d="2019-08-21 01:54:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>The huge tree in the park is set to be cut down to make room for a new parking lot. Lola is outraged. They can't do this! It’s our special tree! With Victor's help, Lola decides to protest against the plan, while Pat forms an alliance with Tank and the Guanos to save the tree. But they have to use all their ingeniousness to outsmart the work-proud construction worker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 01:54:00" d="2019-08-21 02:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>To play an April fool’s trick on Lola, Victor makes her believe that he has seen Hoodie in the subway, whereas in fact, Hoodie is actually locked in his room</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 02:00:00" d="2019-08-21 02:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>While playing with Pat and Hoodie, Lola hears beautiful bird song. She looks in her dad’s ornithology book and finds out the bird is actually a parrot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 02:07:00" d="2019-08-21 02:14:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola wants to take part in an animal photography contest organized by the museum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 02:14:00" d="2019-08-21 02:25:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Bubbely encounters difficulties in his pond – the oxygen supply is running low</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 02:25:00" d="2019-08-21 02:31:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings throw a surprise birthday party for one of the clan. When &quot;Happy Birthday&quot; rings out, the &quot;surpriiiiiise&quot; is as great for Grizzy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 02:31:00" d="2019-08-21 02:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>A gust of wind sweeps away the flower that Grizzy's adored she-bear wears in her hair. Grizzy sees this as a golden opportunity to dazzle her by bringing it back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 02:38:00" d="2019-08-21 02:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy finds communicating vessels. If he sticks his hand in one, it comes out the other, regardless of the distance between them. This should satisfy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 02:45:00" d="2019-08-21 02:51:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy finds a vintage stopwatch in the garage which lets you wind back the minute that has just passed by and it can even stop time and movement in one's surroundings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 02:51:00" d="2019-08-21 02:58:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy is disturbed in the middle of his TV-snack by a flow of incongruous objects that have been transformed into hot-air balloons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 02:58:00" d="2019-08-21 03:05:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy discovers with great delight that the ranger has purchased a brand new multi-function Stressless recliner. But the Lemmings transform</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 03:05:00" d="2019-08-21 03:15:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy enables the Witch of the Cursed Forest to kidnap the Queen, Wilfried becomes the regent’s realm. Wilfried immediately decrees foolish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 03:15:00" d="2019-08-21 03:25:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>After the queen eats a lollipop that makes her start to shrink, Jimmy and Henri must capture the Dark Forest Witch in order to get an antidote</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 03:25:00" d="2019-08-21 03:35:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy inadvertently convinces Ronny Flash to do an interview with a rock monster, Jimmy, Henri and Cat end up escorting Ronny into the Dark Lands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 03:35:00" d="2019-08-21 03:50:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>To show off, Jimmy arrives at the castle flying on Bjorn, and he pretends the dragon is his pet. But Wilfried captures the “monster,” and Bad Jack threatens to burn Epic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 03:50:00" d="2019-08-21 03:55:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is rehearsing the flute recital she has to play this evening. A lady pigeon perches nearby to enjoy her playing and one of the Guanos falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 03:55:00" d="2019-08-21 04:02:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends are organizing a food drive for the city’s kennel. But the food supplies soon attract the attention of Tank and the Guanos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 04:02:00" d="2019-08-21 04:10:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is planning a surprise dinner for her parents' wedding anniversary so she settles into the kitchen to prepare a nice meal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 04:10:00" d="2019-08-21 04:17:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is due to be interviewed as Pet owner of the Week for a pet’s magazine. Victor is jealous. Surely he’s been the best pet owner this week</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 04:17:00" d="2019-08-21 04:23:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and Victor are both fans of the game Galaktik dance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 04:23:00" d="2019-08-21 04:35:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>This morning Lola is feeling very anxious. She has a big test coming up at school and she’s not at all confident</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 04:35:00" d="2019-08-21 04:41:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings play kite-surf with a homemade kite. Grizzy notices that the she-bear he's in love with watches the kite perform arabesques in the sky with admiration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 04:41:00" d="2019-08-21 04:48:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy snatches the last jar of chocolate spread out from under the noses of the Lemmings. In exchange, he offers them the toy stuck inside the lid: a mini-flute</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 04:48:00" d="2019-08-21 04:55:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings play a new game, floating like flags in the breeze from the fan set on maximum. But Grizzy quickly rids the living room of this interference</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-21 04:55:00" d="2019-08-21 05:01:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings have fun tearing down their Kapla block buildings, which they rebuild just as fast. Grizzy finds that the she-bear he's</k>  </p>
</a>
