<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="134" t="2021-07-11 04:53:33"><p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 05:00:00" d="2021-07-18 05:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Happy Home
In one of their most ruthless fights, Taffy and Bentley both bonk heads and lose their memories. Seeing nothing but the cuddly pet pictures Mrs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 05:05:00" d="2021-07-18 05:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Burried Treasure
Taffy discovers that Mrs. M's great-great-great-great-great-great uncle was the infamous Pirate Moistbeard Muchmore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 05:10:00" d="2021-07-18 05:20:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Fortune 500
Bentley realizes that Mrs. M will do anything a fortune cookie tells her to, and immediately gets to work writing a fortune that tells</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 05:20:00" d="2021-07-18 05:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (151)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Jitter Fever
The town is gripped by the fear of jitter fever, a nasty malady that affects house pets. The only way to cure it is to send the affected</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 05:25:00" d="2021-07-18 05:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Recall
Mrs. M gets an alarming notice in the mail: there's been a recall of fancy cat bows, which look a lot like the one Taffy wears</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 05:30:00" d="2021-07-18 05:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (53)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>New Leaf Taffy
Taffy has a near-death experience, where a raccoon tells him he has to turn his life around, and be kind to Bentley in every</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 05:40:00" d="2021-07-18 05:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (54)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The New Mrs M
During a particularly epic chase, Taffy and Bentley collide with Mrs. Muchmore. She suddenly looses her mind and adores raccoons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 05:45:00" d="2021-07-18 05:50:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (55)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Upgrade
Taffy orders a new bow. But not just any bow: this is the Extra-Strength Non-Tear Accept-No-Substitutes Guaranteed-Unsnatchable Maxwell Deluxe 3000! When it arrives, Taffy gleefully puts it on and throws the old one away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 05:50:00" d="2021-07-18 06:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (156)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Honey I Shrunk the Raccoon
It's Spring Cleaning day and everyone is throwing out old useless junk. Suddenly, Taffy and Bentley have shrunk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 06:00:00" d="2021-07-18 06:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Shaaaaaark!
Magoo thinks he’s a beach lifeguard but is actually on an ice floe and the swimmers are penguins! When Fizz shows up in a submarine to kidnap</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 06:05:00" d="2021-07-18 06:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Magoo the Sorcerer
Fizz and Weasel are trying to steal the president’s jokebook. Magoo thinking he is visiting a museum of sorcery mistakes Weasel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 06:15:00" d="2021-07-18 06:30:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Concrete Jungle
Fizz has invented a machine which turns spoiled brats into perfect children. Weasel accidentally launches Fizz next to Magoo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 06:30:00" d="2021-07-18 06:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Letter to Santa Claus
Magoo forgets to include a gift for Mr Cat in his letter to Santa! Trying to make amends he follows Weasel disguised</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 06:35:00" d="2021-07-18 06:45:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Free Weasel
Magoo atop an unfinished skyscraper thinks he’s at the beach. Fizz dressed as Santa in a sleigh pulled by Weasel is giving out gifts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 06:45:00" d="2021-07-18 07:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Magoo a Wrinkle in Time
Fizz has invented the hoverboard! After a slip-up from Weasel the board ends up in the hands of Magoo who thinks he has found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 07:00:00" d="2021-07-18 07:05:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Kid Stuff
A little baby goat butts his head through a distant wall of the estate and starts nibbling the grass. At first, he helps Tom with the yardwork</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 07:05:00" d="2021-07-18 07:10:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Stolen Heart
When a gorgeous feline walks into the Cat and Mouse Detective Agency, Tom is immediately smitten. But someone has already stolen her heart—a</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 07:10:00" d="2021-07-18 07:25:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% The Last Laugh
Red Herring complains to Tom and Jerry that he keeps hearing laughter everywhere he goes. Tom and Jerry bodyguard Red to prevent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 07:25:00" d="2021-07-18 07:30:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% The Invisible Cat
On another scary night in the castle, The Invisible Cat wants nothing more than to catch mice. After it picks up and carries Jerry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 07:30:00" d="2021-07-18 07:40:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Eagle Eye Jerry
While Rick and Ginger take a mountain hike, Tom and Jerry befriend three cute baby eaglets and help them learn to fly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 07:40:00" d="2021-07-18 07:45:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Frenemies
When Rick and Ginger argue on their anniversary, Cupid decides to get involved. However, he gets a head injury in a chase between Tom and Jerry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 07:45:00" d="2021-07-18 07:50:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Alien Again
Lamput likes nothing more than a pleasant evening watching the night sky for UFOs. The peaceful night is ruined, of course, by those pesky Docs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 07:50:00" d="2021-07-18 08:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Opera
Specs and Skinny spruce themselves up and head out to a piano concerto in the royal concert hall. They're on their best behavior, until</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 08:00:00" d="2021-07-18 08:10:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Rat Trap
Mr Bean is very scared on a stormy night and even more so when he hears Mrs Wicket screaming from downstairs. Mr Bean investigates and finds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 08:10:00" d="2021-07-18 08:30:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Valentine's Bean
Mr Bean decides to do something romantic on Valentine’s Day for his long-suffering girlfriend Irma. But while he is secretly delivering</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 08:30:00" d="2021-07-18 08:35:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% All You Can Eat
Mr Bean has forgotten he's supposed to be cooking dinner for his long-suffering girlfriend Irma. He dashes to the supermarket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 08:35:00" d="2021-07-18 09:00:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Flat Pack
Mr Bean is in need of a sturdy new bookcase and sets off to visit a furniture warehouse. He finds one that’s perfect but is outraged</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 09:00:00" d="2021-07-18 09:30:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Eating Crow
The gang visits a farm that’s being haunted by a creepy Scarecrow Ghost. Fred wants to impress the farmer’s daughter with his mystery solving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 09:30:00" d="2021-07-18 10:00:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% I Scooby Dooby Do
The gang is honoured to take part in the wedding of two close friends. But can Best Man, Shaggy, and Maid of Honor, Daphne, save their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 10:00:00" d="2021-07-18 11:20:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and the Monster of Mexico</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Scooby-Doo and the Mystery, Inc. gang are in for a creepy encounter with a monster from Mexico in the mucho spooky, all-new Scooby-Doo movie. The sleuths</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 11:20:00" d="2021-07-18 11:40:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Where There's a Will, There's a Wraith
It's a classic haunted house caper when a rich man, whose life Scooby once saved, writes Scooby into his will! Now, to collect his share of the fortune, the gang must spend a night in a creepy mansion along with the rich man's kooky relative: a spooky pha</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 11:40:00" d="2021-07-18 12:00:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Sleuth or Consequences
Butch and a squirrel detective have set up shop across the street from Tom and Jerry and are stealing all their customers by using</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 12:00:00" d="2021-07-18 12:10:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series III (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% A Car for Irma
Bean discovers Declan giving Irma a lift in his swanky new SUV. Bean is unimpressed until Declan shows off all the car’s features</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 12:10:00" d="2021-07-18 12:25:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series III (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Trophy Bean
Mrs. Wicket’s Nephew is staying with her when he wins two tickets to an Outward Bound course. She refuses to go but then ropes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 12:25:00" d="2021-07-18 12:35:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% In the Wild
Whilst out snapping nature with his camera Mr Bean gets angry when nature snaps back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 12:35:00" d="2021-07-18 13:00:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Missing Teddy
Bean discovers that in the world of organised crime a teddy isn’t always a teddy. Sometimes it’s a rabbit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 13:00:00" d="2021-07-18 13:10:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% No Parking
Mr Bean can't find a parking space so he makes one of his own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 13:10:00" d="2021-07-18 13:25:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Bean's Bounty
Whilst digging for buried treasure Mr Bean digs himself a hole too deep to get out of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 13:25:00" d="2021-07-18 13:40:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Artful Bean
Mr Bean gets a real bug for painting. Then several bugs… and flies and slugs and mice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 13:40:00" d="2021-07-18 14:00:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% The Fly
Bean fights a losing battle with a winged beast from Hell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 14:00:00" d="2021-07-18 14:10:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Holiday Teddy
Mr Bean decides to take Teddy on holiday to the seaside. But when he arrives at his hotel a spoilt little girl wants Teddy all for herself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 14:10:00" d="2021-07-18 14:25:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% The Newspaper
Mr Bean is left in peace when Mrs Wicket goes off on her holidays. This means Mr Bean has free access to her daily newspaper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 14:25:00" d="2021-07-18 14:40:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Viral Bean
Mr Bean is trying to find a nice quiet place to read his book so he sets off for the Library. But instead of reading he becomes distracted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 14:40:00" d="2021-07-18 15:00:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Super Spy
Mr Bean is obsessed by his favourite TV hero ‘Super Spy’ and is excited when his very own Super-Spy spy kit arrives in the post</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 15:00:00" d="2021-07-18 15:30:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% El Bandito
The gang heads out to a Day of the Dead festival. There, they learn that the spirit of the old, legendary criminal, El Bandito, has returned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 15:30:00" d="2021-07-18 16:00:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Into the Mouth of Madcap
Daphne agrees to watch her friend’s kid Wayne and convinces Fred to take a night off from mysteries to go to the boardwalk amusement park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 16:00:00" d="2021-07-18 16:05:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% You Are What You Eat
Rick and Ginger wake up late and, in their hurry, they accidentally put dog food in Tom's bowl and cat food in Spike's. This causes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 16:05:00" d="2021-07-18 16:10:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Not My Tyke
Spike orders Tom and Jerry to watch Tyke while he's away, but instead Tom takes the opportunity to chase Jerry in the backyard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 16:10:00" d="2021-07-18 16:25:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show V (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Tom Thumblestein
Papa tells his fractured version of the Tom Thumb story to the Bavarian mouse trio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 16:25:00" d="2021-07-18 16:30:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Everyone Into the Pool
When Tom and Jerry go to a pool party at Toodles's place, Tom shows off in the pool with ridiculous stunts. Butch and Meathead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 16:30:00" d="2021-07-18 16:40:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% A Head For Science
On the edge of the village of Catsylvania, Tom is carried off to Dr. Frankenstein's castle lab. Several lightning bolts later</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 16:40:00" d="2021-07-18 16:45:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Cat Cop
Ginger brings home an aerosol can of Rat Cop, rat and mouse repellent, to help Tom do his job. And it's not your typical rodent repellent! When the spray makes a human-shaped cop appear, it yells at Jerry and starts pursuit, along with Tom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 16:45:00" d="2021-07-18 17:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Wig
To escape the clutches of his dastardly pursuers, Lamput leaps onto Skinny's head and poses as a luscious mane of auburn hair. Shouldn't work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 17:00:00" d="2021-07-18 17:10:00"><n u="Mush Mush And The Mushables">Mush Mush And The Mushables I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mush-Mush The Predictor
Mush-Mush can't figure out why his sense foot keeps buzzing like crazy. until an earthquake shakes the forest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 17:10:00" d="2021-07-18 17:30:00"><n u="Mush Mush And The Mushables">Mush Mush And The Mushables I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Who's Eating Mushton
Everyone in Mushton is finding that their precious wooden things are being munched and destroyed by someone or something</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 17:30:00" d="2021-07-18 17:40:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dances with Fleas
Tonight Lola and Pat are taking part in a huge flash mob event. They have rehearsed extensively and everything is set</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 17:40:00" d="2021-07-18 17:45:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Circus Chaos
Lola and her friends were supposed to assist to a performance at the Moon Circus, but they missed it. No problem, she decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 17:45:00" d="2021-07-18 18:00:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Guanos
This time, the Guanos are more than fed up with their sworn enemy Pat. With a little help from their bird friends, they are determined</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 18:00:00" d="2021-07-18 18:10:00"><n u="Kingdom Force">Kingdom Force I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Skate Expectations
Luka is too embarrassed to admit that he doesn't know how to skateboard, but he'll have to own up to the truth and try</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 18:10:00" d="2021-07-18 18:30:00"><n u="Kingdom Force">Kingdom Force I (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Moustivus
When Jabari takes a practical joke too far and pranks Dr. Sabre on TV, it's the Plains Kingdom who'll end up paying the price! Can the team stop Dr. Sabre's misdirected revenge before it's too late?When Jabari takes a practical joke too far and pranks Dr.</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 18:30:00" d="2021-07-18 18:35:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Moveable Apps
The Lemmings have a blast testing every app on the ranger's tablet one by one. Grizzy, who is starving, sees that the cupboards are bare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 18:35:00" d="2021-07-18 18:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Wild Modeling
Grizzy and the Lemmings discover the ranger's latest acquisition: a 3D printer that will duplicate anything at all in miniature format</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 18:40:00" d="2021-07-18 19:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The Bear Next Door
Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a strange gateway to a parallel world. On the other side, there is the same cabin, only it doesn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 19:00:00" d="2021-07-18 19:10:00"><n u="Alice &amp; Lewis">Alice &amp; Lewis I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fighting Back
Alice loathes injustice and never hesitates to call someone out on it. But while defending the Cards against the Queen, she finds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 19:10:00" d="2021-07-18 19:30:00"><n u="Alice &amp; Lewis">Alice &amp; Lewis I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Cutie-Twee Safari
Alice loves adventures in the wilderness. So imagine her joy at having the opportunity to accompany her friends on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 19:30:00" d="2021-07-18 19:40:00"><n u="Baby Looney Tunes">Baby Looney Tunes I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Pig Who Cried Woof
Petunia fakes emergencies. But when a real one arises no one believes her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 19:40:00" d="2021-07-18 20:00:00"><n u="Baby Looney Tunes">Baby Looney Tunes I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% New Cat in Town
Baby Looney Tunes introduces the world's most beloved cartoon characters as precocious preschoolers, discovering the world one baby-step at a time!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 20:00:00" d="2021-07-18 20:10:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Boo! Appetweet / Hole Gag: Plunger / Bubble Dum
Sylvester thinks he's being haunted ty the ghost of Tweety Bird. / In the second of a series of shorts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 20:10:00" d="2021-07-18 20:30:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Pain in the Ice / Tunnel Vision /…
While Tweety skates outside Granny's cabin, Sylvester keeps trying to catch and eat Tweety, only to be stopped by the ice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 20:30:00" d="2021-07-18 20:35:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% No Duck is an Island
Tad Tucker is filming the last stages of his reality show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 20:35:00" d="2021-07-18 20:40:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% My Kingdom for a Duck
Egotistical actor Elmer Fudd is doing his one man show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 20:40:00" d="2021-07-18 20:45:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Finders Keepers Losers Sweepers
Bugs accidentally buys an enchanted broom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 20:45:00" d="2021-07-18 21:00:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Daffy Crockpot
Daffy Duck tries to help Settler Porky Pig fight Sam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 21:00:00" d="2021-07-18 21:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Switch
A freak accident leads Bentley and Taffy to switch bodies, allowing each one to live in the other's shoes for a day. Taffy (as Bentley)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 21:05:00" d="2021-07-18 21:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Cute Or Boot
Mrs. M comes home from the club all aflutter. Her ladies who lunch are all raving about the new social network app that allows everyone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 21:10:00" d="2021-07-18 21:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>License To Kale
Mrs. Muchmore is in good shape but still wants to improve her health. Binikos immediately puts the entire mansion on kale diet. Taffy goes crazyy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 21:25:00" d="2021-07-18 21:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Cat Burglar
Bentley learns about a cat burglar in the neighborhood. That night, Bentley lures the cat burglar into the mansion and tries to help him steal Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 21:30:00" d="2021-07-18 21:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Racoon's Day
Driiing ! The beautiful sound of the alarm clock awakes Taffy for another beautiful day in the beautiful and comfy Muchmore Manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 21:40:00" d="2021-07-18 21:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Logging Off
Taffy becomes a real star on internet! Everybody thinks he is a real cute lolcat. Bentley gets angry and jealous. But, maybe internet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 21:45:00" d="2021-07-18 22:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Smell of the Chase
Bentley comes up with a fool-proof way to get rid of Taffy: he'll order a bottle of caviar eau online, then simply pour a trail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 22:00:00" d="2021-07-18 22:05:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (62)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lemming Blues
Grizzy is impressed by the TV show of a magician who transforms a partridge into a bouquet of flowers. To get rid of the Lemmings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 22:05:00" d="2021-07-18 22:10:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (63)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Snow Lemmings
It's hot out and when Grizzy sees an ice cream commercial on TV, he has a sudden craving. Unfortunately, the Lemmings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 22:10:00" d="2021-07-18 22:25:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (64)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Augmented Bear
The Lemmings have discovered a truly wild new game: an augmented reality program on the ranger's digital tablet. They move around the cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 22:25:00" d="2021-07-18 22:30:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (65)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lemmings Under Pressure
The only edible food item left in the ranger's cabin is a gorgeous salmon. which is stuck inside a block of ice at</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 22:30:00" d="2021-07-18 22:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (66)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lemmings in Space
The Lemmings have unearthed a box filled with birthday fountains of light that spit forth giant bursts of sparks. They have a blast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 22:40:00" d="2021-07-18 22:45:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (67)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Sniffer Sniffler Raccoon
Grizzy's last jar of chocolate spread was pinched by the Lemmings, who are savoring it in secret. To localize the Lemmings'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 22:45:00" d="2021-07-18 23:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (68)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Transformational Bear
Wedged in his sofa to relieve his aching back, Grizzy balks at getting up. He designs clever strategies to do everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 23:00:00" d="2021-07-18 23:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (65)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Magoo 2.0
Fizz tests his FizzoJam a ray that makes people dance in his honor. Magoo wearing a snorkeling mask that he’s convinced is a virtual reality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 23:05:00" d="2021-07-18 23:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (66)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mr Fixit
Thinking he’s fixing Weasel’s coffee maker Magoo tweaks Fizz’s teleporter the invention that the hamster plans to exhibit at the innovation tradeshow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 23:15:00" d="2021-07-18 23:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (67)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Gluttons for Punishment
Fizz and Weasel plan to enter Fizz’s revolutionary new condiment in an international culinary contest. Magoo mistakes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 23:25:00" d="2021-07-18 23:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (68)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Brain Washed
While helping Linda clean her attic Magoo gets shrunken and teleported into Fizz’s brain. Fizz himself had intended for his brain to become</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 23:35:00" d="2021-07-18 23:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (69)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>MAG007
Magoo takes Fizz for a toy containing top secret information which he steals from a secret agent (in reality Weasel). Hell-bent on destroying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-18 23:40:00" d="2021-07-19 00:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (70)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Maggie Magoo
A bear has escaped from the zoo and Fizz is hell-bent on making it his pet. Magoo mistakes the bear for his niece who’s come to spend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 00:00:00" d="2021-07-19 00:05:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Petal To The Metal
Mike comes up with new plan to win Iris's affection by showering her with a cascade of rose petals. To do it, he needs to borrow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 00:05:00" d="2021-07-19 00:10:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Abraca-Disaster!
There's nothing better than a little magic trick to impress your crush. Iris isn't the only one impressed when Mike puts on a magic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 00:10:00" d="2021-07-19 00:25:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Itchy Frenzy
The racoons have fleas! They head over to Mike's to find something they can use to relieve the itch and pass the fleas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 00:25:00" d="2021-07-19 00:35:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Handcuffed
The crafty racoons manage to handcuff Mike's back legs together. The raccoons are convinced that with Mike incapacitated, they're finally going</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 00:35:00" d="2021-07-19 00:40:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Sleepy Head
Mike hasn't sleep at all. He can barely keep his eyes open and all he wants is nice long nap, but the raccoons are in top form, wreaking havoc</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 00:40:00" d="2021-07-19 00:48:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Diamond Dogs
Mike gets himself into a tough situation when Fluffy takes a necklace belonging to his owner into Iris's yard. Iris thinks the necklace</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 00:48:00" d="2021-07-19 00:50:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Age Remote
The Docs prove their inventing skills by coming up with an age-altering time-ray. This breakthrough could change the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 00:50:00" d="2021-07-19 01:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Sunday Holiday
It might be Sunday, but Specs just won’t let up: his obsession with Lamput knows no weekends. Skinny, on the other hand, knows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 01:00:00" d="2021-07-19 01:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Racoon in a Guilted Cage
Taffy is the winner of another cruel prank war: this time he put Bentley in a box and sent him to the Antarctic. Taffy celebrates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 01:05:00" d="2021-07-19 01:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Flea Party
Taffy is scratching himself when Mrs. Muchmore says: &quot;If you got fleas, I'll have to take your bow off and put you a flea collar&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 01:10:00" d="2021-07-19 01:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Guard Dog
Taffy accidentally saves the bear! The bear instantly vows its loyalty - he's like a huge puppy dog following him around. Taffy's freaked</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 01:25:00" d="2021-07-19 01:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Cat's Pajamas
It's sooooo cold outside. Problem for Taffy is - extreme cold triggers hibernation in raccoons! If he's out for two weeks - he'll</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 01:30:00" d="2021-07-19 01:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Happy Home
In one of their most ruthless fights, Taffy and Bentley both bonk heads and lose their memories. Seeing nothing but the cuddly pet pictures Mrs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 01:40:00" d="2021-07-19 01:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Burried Treasure
Taffy discovers that Mrs. M's great-great-great-great-great-great uncle was the infamous Pirate Moistbeard Muchmore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 01:45:00" d="2021-07-19 02:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Fortune 500
Bentley realizes that Mrs. M will do anything a fortune cookie tells her to, and immediately gets to work writing a fortune that tells</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 02:00:00" d="2021-07-19 02:05:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (56)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Chemical Lemmings
How can one peacefully watch a documentary on salmon fish, nice and comfy on the sofa, when the Lemmings are playing chemistry novices</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 02:05:00" d="2021-07-19 02:10:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (57)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Remote Control
Grizzy's TV remote control is stolen by a partridge who collects high-tech objects in his nest perched high up in a tree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 02:10:00" d="2021-07-19 02:15:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (58)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The Bear and the Butterfly
Grizzy has got it into his head to offer a butterfly to the she-bear he's in love with. But the Lemmings fight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 02:15:00" d="2021-07-19 02:25:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (59)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Get off My. 
The Lemmings have discovered an addictive new game based on the astonishing bouncing properties of the ranger's new running shoes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 02:25:00" d="2021-07-19 02:30:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (60)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Babysitting
Grizzy babysits for the she-bear he has a crush on, who has entrusted him with the care of her cub. There's no question of Grizzy tripping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 02:30:00" d="2021-07-19 02:35:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (61)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Under Lock and Key
Unwilling to share the food both he and the Lemmings are wild about Grizzy locks it up inside the ranger's brand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 02:35:00" d="2021-07-19 02:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (62)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lemming Blues
Grizzy is impressed by the TV show of a magician who transforms a partridge into a bouquet of flowers. To get rid of the Lemmings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 02:40:00" d="2021-07-19 02:50:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (63)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Snow Lemmings
It's hot out and when Grizzy sees an ice cream commercial on TV, he has a sudden craving. Unfortunately, the Lemmings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 02:50:00" d="2021-07-19 03:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (64)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Augmented Bear
The Lemmings have discovered a truly wild new game: an augmented reality program on the ranger's digital tablet. They move around the cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 03:00:00" d="2021-07-19 03:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fizz Tower
Thinking he’s hunting down a rat in his attic Magoo finds himself on the theme park devoted to…the glory of Fizz. He decides to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 03:05:00" d="2021-07-19 03:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Magoo in Shining Armor
Magoo on a construction site thinks he’s been hired for a medieval theater show. Fizz and Weasel bump into Magoo at</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 03:15:00" d="2021-07-19 03:20:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Space Hamster
In order to make himself an object of worship Fizz makes people believe he’s an alien coming to share his wisdom. Magoo mistakes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 03:20:00" d="2021-07-19 03:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Doctor Magoo
Magoo thinks he’s helping out at an understaffed veterinary clinic. In fact he’s at the supermarket where Fizz is trying to gain popularity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 03:25:00" d="2021-07-19 03:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Toes in the Sand
Magoo thinks he is on a beach and that sailors are emptying their oil tanker right into the ocean. Wanting to put a stop to the pollution</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 03:35:00" d="2021-07-19 03:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dinosaur Island
Fizz has reduced the size of the moon in order to model it in his own image. But Magoo thinks it’s a dinosaur egg ready to hatch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 03:40:00" d="2021-07-19 03:50:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Santa's Little Helper
Magoo a Christmas volunteer in a supermarket thinks a burglar is entering overnight and decides to stop him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 03:50:00" d="2021-07-19 04:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>At the Heart of the Crater
Magoo thinks that he is at the foot of a volcano but in fact he’s next to a huge soup vat. And he sets it all awry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 04:00:00" d="2021-07-19 04:05:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (75)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% And then there were none
Mike is forced into action when the raccoons steal the turtles to help Freddy hold up his newly made throne. The crazy raccoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 04:05:00" d="2021-07-19 04:10:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (77)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% In the Doghouse
Mike is forced to spend the day outside in his doghouse due to Grandma Mikkelsen's fur allergy. Mike makes the best of being exiled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 04:10:00" d="2021-07-19 04:20:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (78)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Slippery When Wet
The Mikkelsen's house has been cleaned and the floor has been polished to a deep sheen. Mike has been told to keep his paws off it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 04:20:00" d="2021-07-19 04:25:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Wacky Tacos
Mike's wants to impress Iris by preparing some yummy tacos, but Fluffy and the Turtles are making his life difficult by using the extractor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 04:25:00" d="2021-07-19 04:30:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Cone of Shame
Mike is forced to live out a dog's worst nightmare. wearing a cone around his neck after a trip to the veterinarian! Oh, the humiliation! There's NO WAY he can let Iris see him like this. Mike refuses to leave the house and the raccoons take advantage o</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 04:30:00" d="2021-07-19 04:40:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Skate Pool
Mike's attempt to impress Iris with his diving skills backfires when he crashes into the bottom of an empty concrete swimming pool</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 04:40:00" d="2021-07-19 04:45:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Go Fetch
A gust of wind sends Iris's favourite hat up onto the Mikkelsen's roof and Mike sees the perfect chance to retrieve it and look like a hero</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 04:45:00" d="2021-07-19 04:50:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Robot-Attack
Mike gets a stroke of artistic inspiration and decides to sculpt a life-sized statue of Iris. Meanwhile the raccoons decide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 04:50:00" d="2021-07-19 05:00:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Private Eye Mike
Stephan has lost his keys again but he doesn't think Mike is the right dog for the job to find them. Mike sets out to prove his owner</k>  </p>
</a>
