<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="135" t="2020-05-14 04:44:32"><p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 05:00:00" d="2020-05-21 05:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% While fighting over a jar of chocolate spread, Grizzy and the Lemmings set off a chain reaction which sends the jar flying into space, where it damages a space station</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 05:06:00" d="2020-05-21 05:12:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy discovers the ranger's collection of bird calls by chance. With a simple blow of the whistle, he can attract a flock of partridges that are at his beck and call</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 05:12:00" d="2020-05-21 05:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings notice that Grizzy moves away from the jar of chocolate spread whenever he chases the fly buzzing around him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 05:19:00" d="2020-05-21 05:25:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% A magic tomahawk divides Grizzy into two identical bears with diametrically opposite personalities, one short-tempered, the other super-sweet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 05:25:00" d="2020-05-21 05:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy finds a magician's hat that tosses out objects stored inside beforehand with the tap of a magic wand. He decides to impress his beloved she-bear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 05:32:00" d="2020-05-21 05:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% A newly unpacked UV tanning booth holds the place of honor in the middle of the cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 05:38:00" d="2020-05-21 05:44:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy wants to try out the brand new packaging format of chocolate spread that he discovers in the ranger's cupboard, a yummy-looking XXL jar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 05:44:00" d="2020-05-21 05:51:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy and the Lemmings discover the joys of photography with the ranger's instant print camera</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 05:51:00" d="2020-05-21 06:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% When Grizzy and the Lemmings accidentally activate a magic disk representing the earth, they are sent back in time to the prehistoric era</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 06:00:00" d="2020-05-21 06:11:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>Ted is the test pilot of a space roamer when the remote control is taken over by an alien (code name: snail)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 06:11:00" d="2020-05-21 06:22:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>When aliens (code name: ants) take a piece of fruit that belongs to Small Human, it’s up to the team to get it back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 06:22:00" d="2020-05-21 06:33:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>When Binky sees an alien changing from a caterpillar to a butterfly, it’s a race against time to defeat it before it changes into something even more powerful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 06:33:00" d="2020-05-21 07:00:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>When the Humans bring a new recliner chair home, Binky is sure it’s an alien robot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 07:00:00" d="2020-05-21 07:10:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean runs rings around the town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 07:10:00" d="2020-05-21 07:21:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean is 'storked' by an unwelcome visitor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 07:21:00" d="2020-05-21 07:31:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean finds that tons of toads weigh loads and loads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 07:31:00" d="2020-05-21 07:50:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean is all at sea with the landed gentry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 07:50:00" d="2020-05-21 08:00:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Party hears a fabulous tune but can’t work out where it’s coming from not realising thesound is actually a ring tone caused by the happos phoning each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 08:00:00" d="2020-05-21 08:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings have unearthed a crate of competition boomerangs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 08:06:00" d="2020-05-21 08:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Exasperated by the Lemmings who prevent him from watching his favorite TV show in peace Grizzy catapults them out of the cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 08:13:00" d="2020-05-21 08:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% A strange new object figures prominently in the cabin: a big wall clock that resembles a Swiss cuckoo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 08:19:00" d="2020-05-21 08:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Woken with a start by a nightmare filled with Lemmings Grizzy stumbles on the Ranger's dream machine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 08:26:00" d="2020-05-21 08:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy happens onto an old American India medallion bearing the symbol of the wind. He who wears it has the power to command air streams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 08:32:00" d="2020-05-21 08:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% A magic Amerindian top modifies the mental age of anyone who watches it spin. From now on, Grizzy has the mind of a 10-month old baby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 08:39:00" d="2020-05-21 09:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% A magic horn lands on the muzzle of a moose endowing it with grace and the ability to fly. It soars off leaving a rainbow-colored streak in its wake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 09:00:00" d="2020-05-21 09:10:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>High-tech wizardry and low-tech cunning get Mr Bean out of a jam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 09:10:00" d="2020-05-21 09:21:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean learns that generosity can be an effective weapon against greed, gluttony and getting your hands back on your own TV remote control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 09:21:00" d="2020-05-21 09:32:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean goes to buy the biggest TV in the world only to find that it has a price- tag to match</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 09:32:00" d="2020-05-21 10:00:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Determined to play the piano, Mr Bean finds a tune in his heart and sausages for fingers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 10:00:00" d="2020-05-21 10:09:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% A trip to the seashore brings the Baby Looney Tunes into contact with a just-hatched turtle that Melissa names Myrtle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 10:09:00" d="2020-05-21 10:20:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% On an overnight train trip to visit Floyd at college, Lola's doll vanishes. Baby Bugs acts as a detective as he tries to solve the missing Edna mystery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 10:20:00" d="2020-05-21 10:30:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% The Baby Looney Tunes tour the local fire station, learning fire prevention tips. Later, Baby Daffy displays the most fire-fighting knowledge when he is suddenly tested</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 10:30:00" d="2020-05-21 11:00:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% The Baby Looney Tunes explore a world of botanic wonder as they search for just the right spot to plant a young lemon tree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 11:00:00" d="2020-05-21 11:21:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>When Scooby and the Gang are in Sicily they're chasing a fire monster! But they are surprised to meet up with none other than famous actor Steve Buscemi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 11:21:00" d="2020-05-21 12:00:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>When Scooby and the gang are taking a tour of merry old London they run afoul of horrible screaming skulls of English legend!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 12:00:00" d="2020-05-21 12:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben accidentally creates a giant sink hole and frees King Koil and his Kimodo Dragon from below</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 12:10:00" d="2020-05-21 12:20:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>After a series of reoccurring nightmares affect his sleep, Ben refuses to open up to Max and Gwen about what's bothering him. But they realize Zombozo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 12:20:00" d="2020-05-21 12:31:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Gwen drags Ben along on a hike in search of the legendary Forgeti, a yeti that makes people forget they ever saw it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 12:31:00" d="2020-05-21 13:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben has to clean the Rust Bucket but when he is tricked into letting the vile Fly Guys steal it he must chase them down before they create an unstoppable maggot monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 13:00:00" d="2020-05-21 13:07:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% When Tuffy shows an interest in soccer Jerry decides to be the little guys coach and show him how the game is really played by beating Tom in a one-on-one match</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 13:07:00" d="2020-05-21 13:14:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% The gang do battle with a magical broom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 13:14:00" d="2020-05-21 13:20:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom enlists the help of the lake monster to terrorize the mouse village forcing Jerry Van Mouseling to intervene and save the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 13:20:00" d="2020-05-21 13:27:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% A werewolf terrorizes Tom and the inhabitants of the Catsylvania village</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 13:27:00" d="2020-05-21 13:34:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom must compete with his American cousin for the right to remain a Butler at Postlewaite manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 13:34:00" d="2020-05-21 14:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry are forced to go back to Detective School in order to renew their detective licenses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 14:00:00" d="2020-05-21 14:10:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>High-tech wizardry and low-tech cunning get Mr Bean out of a jam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 14:10:00" d="2020-05-21 14:21:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean learns that generosity can be an effective weapon against greed, gluttony and getting your hands back on your own TV remote control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 14:21:00" d="2020-05-21 14:32:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean goes to buy the biggest TV in the world only to find that it has a price- tag to match</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 14:32:00" d="2020-05-21 15:00:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Determined to play the piano, Mr Bean finds a tune in his heart and sausages for fingers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 15:00:00" d="2020-05-21 15:11:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>The team discovers Gracie’s whistle was taken by an alien (code name: cockroach) in Small Human’s messy room</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 15:11:00" d="2020-05-21 15:22:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>An Alien Rover (automated vacuum cleaner) is on the loose in the space station and it’s up to the PURST team to put it out of commission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 15:22:00" d="2020-05-21 15:33:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>When Gordon is taken over by aliens (code name: fleas), the PURST team has to help get rid of them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 15:33:00" d="2020-05-21 16:00:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>Binky’s favourite sweater is being eaten by aliens (code name: moths), and it’s up to the team to save to stop the aliens and save &quot;Fuzzy Wuzzy&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 16:00:00" d="2020-05-21 16:10:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>After Bunnicula accidentally mesmerizes Scott Dingleman, he wipes the poor kid's mind completely. Now it's up to the pets to teach him how to be the best Scott he can be</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 16:10:00" d="2020-05-21 16:20:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>A mystical locket gives the pets a glimpse into the future</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 16:20:00" d="2020-05-21 16:29:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>If Agent 51 can prove that the vampire rabbits are real, he can save his job at the Supernatural Task Force</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 16:29:00" d="2020-05-21 17:00:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Bunnicula faces off against an ancient threat at 40,000 feet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 17:00:00" d="2020-05-21 17:07:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% An over protected Spike goes to extreme lengths to keep his precious pup safe from harm</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 17:07:00" d="2020-05-21 17:14:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Spikes bones are missing and Frankie the Rat is the culprit. Now all they have to do is catch in the dirty rat in the act</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 17:14:00" d="2020-05-21 17:20:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom serves an evil pirate determined to steal treasure belonging to the village mice until Jerry Van Mouseling foils his plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 17:20:00" d="2020-05-21 17:27:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom turns into a Blob monster and proceeds to eat everything in sight including the village mice! Jerry Van Mouseling to the rescue!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 17:27:00" d="2020-05-21 17:33:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Rick and Ginger leave town with instructions for Tom to keep the house in order but Jerry's got other ideas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 17:33:00" d="2020-05-21 18:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom is tricked into helping an evil magician capture all of the mice in the village but Jerry Van Mouseling foils the magician's plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 18:00:00" d="2020-05-21 18:10:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean runs rings around the town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 18:10:00" d="2020-05-21 18:21:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean is 'storked' by an unwelcome visitor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 18:21:00" d="2020-05-21 18:31:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean finds that tons of toads weigh loads and loads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 18:31:00" d="2020-05-21 19:00:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean is all at sea with the landed gentry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 19:00:00" d="2020-05-21 19:22:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>Famous dancer Maddie Ziegler wins an old, haunted dance studio in a competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 19:22:00" d="2020-05-21 20:00:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>Scooby-Doo and the Mystery Inc. gang meet up with basketball legend and bowling aficionado Chris Paul at a golf tournament fundraiser held in Florida</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 20:00:00" d="2020-05-21 20:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings have laid hand on special magnets which turn any object they are stuck to into flying objects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 20:06:00" d="2020-05-21 20:12:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% With a lion-tamer's whip a sugar bowl and lots of work the Lemmings have successfully trained a caribou to go through their obstacle course</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 20:12:00" d="2020-05-21 20:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy happens onto the electronic version of the Ranger Lemming toy which is capable of reproducing the movements one teaches it like a smart robot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 20:19:00" d="2020-05-21 20:25:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Ranger's cabin is equipped with an ultra-effective pest detector capable of sensing the presence of an intruder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 20:25:00" d="2020-05-21 20:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy finds himself unwillingly caught up in a race between two teams of Lemmings. When he understands the stakes he tries to win but loses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 20:32:00" d="2020-05-21 20:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings have placed giant remote-controlled hydraulic jacks under the cabin to transform it into a life-sized rolling ball game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 20:38:00" d="2020-05-21 21:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy is disturbed during his nap by a few uncatchable flies which buzz incessantly around his head</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 21:00:00" d="2020-05-21 21:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is planning a surprise dinner for her parents' wedding anniversary so she settles into the kitchen to prepare a nice meal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 21:07:00" d="2020-05-21 21:13:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is due to be interviewed as Pet owner of the Week for a pet’s magazine. Victor is jealous. Surely he’s been the best pet owner this</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 21:13:00" d="2020-05-21 21:19:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and Victor are both fans of the game Galaktik dance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 21:19:00" d="2020-05-21 21:25:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>This morning Lola is feeling very anxious. She has a big test coming up at school and she’s not at all confident</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 21:25:00" d="2020-05-21 21:32:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Tonight Lola is determined to spy a shooting star so that she can make a wish. When the Guanos meanwhile are set on making their wish come true: to get rid of Hoodie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 21:32:00" d="2020-05-21 21:39:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola finds Victor sad and alone in his garden. Tomorrow is his birthday and nothing has been planned for the special day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 21:39:00" d="2020-05-21 22:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends are in the middle of a medieval role playing game and there is treasure hidden in the bouncy castle: candies and cookies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 22:00:00" d="2020-05-21 22:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% When they find an old book on traditional Japanese origami, the Lemmings churn out paper birds to play gliding games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 22:06:00" d="2020-05-21 22:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings are all lined up on the couch to watch a cartoon film where a mouse plays nasty tricks on a cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 22:13:00" d="2020-05-21 22:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Once again Grizzy shows the Lemmings that they just don't measure up to him physically and that the last jar of chocolate spread is for the strongest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 22:19:00" d="2020-05-21 22:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings lay their hands on a full crate of chocolate spread which they hide somewhere behind Grizzy's back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 22:26:00" d="2020-05-21 22:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy is persuaded that he's discovered the ultimate gadget for good living</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 22:32:00" d="2020-05-21 22:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings clamor for their turn to play with the ranger's mobile phone but Grizzy isn't in the sharing mood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 22:39:00" d="2020-05-21 23:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy is captivated by a mime artist on TV who makes viewers believe in the presence of an invisible wall</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 23:00:00" d="2020-05-21 23:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When our trio lets success get to their heads, they boast about their team and inadvertently inspire the Cursed Forest Witch and Bad Jack to create their own deadly duo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 23:10:00" d="2020-05-21 23:21:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy complains that Henri treats him like a baby, Henri lets him do “grownup” things for himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 23:21:00" d="2020-05-21 23:31:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Jimmy, Cat and Henri have to organise a fake kidnapping of Lance by Bjorn, in order to retrieve Lance’s smart-mirror, which contains films of Cat, Henri</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-21 23:31:00" d="2020-05-22 00:00:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Jimmy squires for the Red Knight, and his insistence on showing Red he’s a great squire causes Red to get captured by the Black Sorcerer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 00:00:00" d="2020-05-22 00:06:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M registers Taffy in the biggest cat show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 00:06:00" d="2020-05-22 00:13:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy feels nostalgia for his former home – the dump</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 00:13:00" d="2020-05-22 00:20:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley sends Taffy to a factory on the other side of the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 00:20:00" d="2020-05-22 00:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs. Muchmore has equipped her home with a defense system</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 00:26:00" d="2020-05-22 00:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M calls a 'pet whisperer' to improve pets behaviour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 00:33:00" d="2020-05-22 00:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley doesn't know who he is and thinks he's a racoon!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 00:39:00" d="2020-05-22 00:46:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Can Taffy rescue the family without blowing his cover?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 00:46:00" d="2020-05-22 00:52:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs. M receives a visit from a famous raccoon trapper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 00:52:00" d="2020-05-22 01:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Exhausted, Forsythe tries to get rid of Bentley and Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 01:00:00" d="2020-05-22 01:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The fridge in the cabin has changed: it's been replaced by a brand new state-of-the-art appliance which analyzes the body fat percentage of whoever wants to serve himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 01:06:00" d="2020-05-22 01:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy watches a demonstration of balloon modelling on TV. He decides to make a balloon poodle to offer the she-bear he's enamored with</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 01:13:00" d="2020-05-22 01:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy needs a nice nap. He can't find a pillow comfortable enough to his taste until he tests the pillow that the Lemmings use as a high-jump mat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 01:19:00" d="2020-05-22 01:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy is awakened from his nap by the unpleasant, ongoing sound of Velcro strips being ripped off</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 01:26:00" d="2020-05-22 01:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The she-bear Grizzy is enamored with has lost her favorite flower in an inaccessible spot under a giant boulder. Grizzy tries to lift it: impossible!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 01:32:00" d="2020-05-22 01:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings try to catch a bat to play rodeo, disturbing Grizzy as he plays his favorite game on the ranger's mobile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 01:39:00" d="2020-05-22 01:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings have a blast testing every app on the ranger's tablet one by one. Grizzy, who is starving, sees that the cupboards are bare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 01:45:00" d="2020-05-22 01:52:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy and the Lemmings discover the ranger's latest acquisition: a 3D printer that will duplicate anything at all in miniature form</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 01:52:00" d="2020-05-22 02:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a strange gateway to a parallel world. On the other side, there is the same cabin, only it doesn't belong to a ranger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 02:00:00" d="2020-05-22 02:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is preparing a package to send to her Japanese pen pal. But the Guanos are watching and get the idea to sneak Hoodie inside the package and get rid of him forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 02:07:00" d="2020-05-22 02:13:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Seeing how Pat and Tank have put on weight Lola and Victor decide to put them both on fitness training program for dogs. Whoever loses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 02:13:00" d="2020-05-22 02:20:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends must hand in a math assignment. Instead of doing his homework Victor prefers to wait for the girls to finish the assignment before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 02:20:00" d="2020-05-22 02:26:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola’s mother has installed a Geocaching application on her daughter’s phone. Lola is over the moon and heads outside to start playing. Victor also decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 02:26:00" d="2020-05-22 02:33:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>In the garden Lola is experimenting in how to plant watermelons. On one of the watermelons she sprinkles a powerful fertilizer which is also very dangerous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 02:33:00" d="2020-05-22 02:39:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Hoodie has an eye infection and has to wear a special protective bubble. Lola asks Pat to look after him. The Guanos naturally decide this is the perfect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 02:39:00" d="2020-05-22 02:46:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Tonight Lola and Pat are taking part in a huge flash mob event. They have rehearsed extensively and everything is set. Except that in the meantime Hoodie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 02:46:00" d="2020-05-22 02:53:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends are supposed to watch a performance at Moon Circus but unfortunately they miss it. No worries. Lola decides to put</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 02:53:00" d="2020-05-22 03:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>At the end of their tether with their sworn enemy Pat the Guanos decide to do away with him. With a little help from their bird friends they decide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 03:00:00" d="2020-05-22 03:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy makes a bargain with Bad Jack’s family-outcast brother Jeff, he gets Bad Jack banished from the kingdom. But Jeff turns out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 03:10:00" d="2020-05-22 03:21:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy enables the Witch of the Cursed Forest to kidnap the Queen, Wilfried becomes the regent’s realm. Wilfried immediately decrees foolish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 03:21:00" d="2020-05-22 03:31:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>After the queen eats a lollipop that makes her start to shrink, Jimmy and Henri must capture the Dark Forest Witch in order to get an antidote</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 03:31:00" d="2020-05-22 03:42:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy inadvertently convinces Ronny Flash to do an interview with a rock monster, Jimmy, Henri and Cat end up escorting Ronny into the Dark Lands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 03:42:00" d="2020-05-22 04:00:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>To show off, Jimmy arrives at the castle flying on Bjorn, and he pretends the dragon is his pet. But Wilfried captures the “monster,” and Bad Jack threatens to burn Epic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 04:00:00" d="2020-05-22 04:06:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M registers Taffy in the biggest cat show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 04:06:00" d="2020-05-22 04:13:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy feels nostalgia for his former home – the dump</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 04:13:00" d="2020-05-22 04:20:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley sends Taffy to a factory on the other side of the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 04:20:00" d="2020-05-22 04:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs. Muchmore has equipped her home with a defense system</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 04:26:00" d="2020-05-22 04:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M calls a 'pet whisperer' to improve pets behaviour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 04:33:00" d="2020-05-22 04:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley doesn't know who he is and thinks he's a racoon!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 04:39:00" d="2020-05-22 04:46:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Can Taffy rescue the family without blowing his cover?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 04:46:00" d="2020-05-22 04:52:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs. M receives a visit from a famous raccoon trapper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 04:52:00" d="2020-05-22 05:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Exhausted, Forsythe tries to get rid of Bentley and Taffy</k>  </p>
</a>
