<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="133" t="2020-05-16 04:43:02"><p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 05:00:00" d="2020-05-23 05:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings discover that by changing the speed limit sign on the side of the road, they can create a huge draft that is just perfect for their extreme kiting game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 05:06:00" d="2020-05-23 05:12:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% While trying to stop the Lemmings, Grizzy slips on the canvas and unwittingly executes an amazing somersault in front of his beloved she-bear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 05:12:00" d="2020-05-23 05:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings have hitched up a racoon with a sweet-tooth to their sled and get a ride by throwing cookies in front of the creature with a sling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 05:19:00" d="2020-05-23 05:25:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings have unearthed a strange little gadget from amongst the Forest Ranger's belongings: a hand spinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 05:25:00" d="2020-05-23 05:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings play with figurines of wild Canadian animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 05:32:00" d="2020-05-23 05:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy discovers a new generation Tamagotchi game on the Ranger's tablet: the camera scans the player and gives him a virtual avatar of himself to take care of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 05:38:00" d="2020-05-23 05:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy and the Lemmings find a vase with a genie inside that will make anyone's dreams come true, if they only let him out by rubbing the vase</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 05:45:00" d="2020-05-23 05:51:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings get their hands on a secret weapon that belongs to the Canadian Army: anyone hit with it becomes non-violent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 05:51:00" d="2020-05-23 06:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy and the Lemmings clumsily destroy the TV remote control while fighting over who gets to watch his favorite program</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 06:00:00" d="2020-05-23 06:11:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>Ted is the test pilot of a space roamer when the remote control is taken over by an alien (code name: snail)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 06:11:00" d="2020-05-23 06:22:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>When aliens (code name: ants) take a piece of fruit that belongs to Small Human, it’s up to the team to get it back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 06:22:00" d="2020-05-23 06:33:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>When Binky sees an alien changing from a caterpillar to a butterfly, it’s a race against time to defeat it before it changes into something even more powerful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 06:33:00" d="2020-05-23 07:00:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>When the Humans bring a new recliner chair home, Binky is sure it’s an alien robot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 07:00:00" d="2020-05-23 07:10:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean makes his own horror movie and ropes in Mrs Wicket as the star!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 07:10:00" d="2020-05-23 07:20:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean has to look after Mrs Wicket’s goldfish, but Scrapper the cat is keen to ‘help’</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 07:20:00" d="2020-05-23 07:30:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean wins tickets for a Cruise, but if only he could stay on it!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 07:30:00" d="2020-05-23 07:50:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean hopes to win some cash prizes at the funfair, but it’s not as easy as it seems!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 07:50:00" d="2020-05-23 08:00:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Fixit has made a beautiful smooth path in the enclosure but will he be able to stop the Happos from stepping on the wet cement?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 08:00:00" d="2020-05-23 08:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings have found an Amerindian eagle amulet that endows he who wears it with the powers of a bird of prey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 08:06:00" d="2020-05-23 08:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings are having a blast with the ranger's electric guitar and the cabin walls tremble with their experimental rock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 08:13:00" d="2020-05-23 08:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% To finally be on an equal footing with Grizzy's imposing build and throw their own weight around in the cabin the Lemmings decide to wear a blowup sumotori costume</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 08:19:00" d="2020-05-23 08:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy and the Lemmings discover an ancient Amerindian table with the power to show you past events</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 08:26:00" d="2020-05-23 08:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings discover an old book of magic spells with a formula that enables one to take on the appearance of any other creature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 08:32:00" d="2020-05-23 08:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Nutty Hill is suffering from a stifling heat wave. Grizzy decides to get into the fridge, where the temperature will be more bearable, but the shelves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 08:38:00" d="2020-05-23 09:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy is frustrated: just as he was about to coat a nice big fresh salmon with chocolate spread and snuggle up in front of the TV he discovers that the pantry is empty!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 09:00:00" d="2020-05-23 09:10:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean redecorates his room, making it fit for a Queen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 09:10:00" d="2020-05-23 09:21:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean gets green eyes and green fingers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 09:21:00" d="2020-05-23 09:31:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean becomes smitten with a beautiful singer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 09:31:00" d="2020-05-23 10:00:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean meets a soul mate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 10:00:00" d="2020-05-23 10:09:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% The babies play pretend school in preparation for the real thing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 10:09:00" d="2020-05-23 10:19:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Bugs must find the courage to discover what's making scary noises outside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 10:19:00" d="2020-05-23 10:28:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Faced with nothing to do, the babies use a cardboard box and their imaginations to make playtime fun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 10:28:00" d="2020-05-23 11:00:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Sylvester eats all of Granny's cookies then makes up a cookie monster to blame</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 11:00:00" d="2020-05-23 11:22:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>Famous dancer Maddie Ziegler wins an old, haunted dance studio in a competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 11:22:00" d="2020-05-23 12:00:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>Scooby-Doo and the Mystery Inc. gang meet up with basketball legend and bowling aficionado Chris Paul at a golf tournament fundraiser held in Florida</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 12:00:00" d="2020-05-23 12:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>When Ben interferes with malicious magician Hex’s quest for the earth-moving Titan Gloves at a swap meet, he inadvertently switches bodies with Gwen!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 12:10:00" d="2020-05-23 12:20:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben finds a rare Sumo Slammers card during a tour of historic Oldeville. But when Billy Billions comes to claim the same card, Ben has to battle Billy’s high-tech drones</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 12:20:00" d="2020-05-23 12:31:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>In a peaceful coastal town, Ben must not only face the archaic antagonist Steam Smythe and his latest creation, the Clocktopus, but also his deepest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 12:31:00" d="2020-05-23 13:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben and Gwen are transformed into babies by nanny-gone-nuts Nanny Nightmare who will stop at nothing to reshape the world in the image of her day-care</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 13:00:00" d="2020-05-23 13:10:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>On a fishing trip to Crags Lake, Pebbles and Bamm-Bamm get pulled into the middle of an age-old feud between two rival species of dinosaurs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 13:10:00" d="2020-05-23 13:20:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>Bamm-Bamm brings home a rare plant from the Crags as a last-minute birthday gift for his mom, but he starts to suspect that the plant may want something</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 13:20:00" d="2020-05-23 13:31:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>Pebbles accidentally leads a shape-shifting dinosaur from the Crags back to Bedrock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 13:31:00" d="2020-05-23 14:00:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>A friendly but obnoxiously noisy dinosaur moves in next to the treehouse and Pebbles and Bamm-Bamm would rather build a whole new clubhouse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 14:00:00" d="2020-05-23 14:10:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>Pebbles and Bamm-Bamm are grounded after leading a Beeasaurus from the Crags to Fred's work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 14:10:00" d="2020-05-23 14:20:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>A mysterious otherworldly hunter is kidnapping dinosaurs from the Crags and Pebbles will do anything to chase it down and stop it, even if she loses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 14:20:00" d="2020-05-23 14:31:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>Pebbles makes a dinosaur's dream of flying come true, but the dinosaur uses her new power to wreak havoc and revenge on all those who used to mock her dreams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 14:31:00" d="2020-05-23 15:00:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>Bamm-Bamm runs off to the Crags to get out of doing work around the house. Pebbles offers to help a dinosaur in need</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 15:00:00" d="2020-05-23 15:10:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>On Halloween night, a weird new health food turns all of Bedrock's garbage disposals into starving zombies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 15:10:00" d="2020-05-23 15:20:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>Pebbles and Bamm-Bamm take a shortcut through a mysterious part of the Crags, rumored to be home to terrifying and dangerous dinosaurs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 15:20:00" d="2020-05-23 15:31:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>When some other dinosaurs make fun of Dino for being a pampered pet, Pebbles tries to prove them all wrong by entering him into a contest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 15:31:00" d="2020-05-23 16:00:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>When the dinosaurs of the Crags see signs that the first frost of the year is coming, they all set out to celebrate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 16:00:00" d="2020-05-23 16:10:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>The epic bromance between Bunnicula and Patches is put to the test when Patches' old roommate Steve comes back into town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 16:10:00" d="2020-05-23 16:20:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>The pets visit a magical world where Harold is king</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 16:20:00" d="2020-05-23 16:30:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>The pets visit the beach for the first time in ages and thanks to an ancient formula discovered by Lugosi, Bunnicula gets to spend some time in the sun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 16:30:00" d="2020-05-23 17:00:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>When Mina accidentally hits &quot;send&quot; on an embarrassing text message, Bunnicula must race the emoji itself before it reaches Scott's phone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 17:00:00" d="2020-05-23 17:07:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom and Spike get glued together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 17:07:00" d="2020-05-23 17:14:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Jerry's cousins pay a return visit to the Manor eager to create mayhem for Tom things get crazier than ever when the cousins wives show up as well</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 17:14:00" d="2020-05-23 17:20:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% A guilty conscience causes Butch to change his ways. But Tom Jerry Spike and Tuffy quickly decide they like the old Butch better</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 17:20:00" d="2020-05-23 17:27:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry are hired by Dixie Wolf to find all the sheep that have gone missing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 17:27:00" d="2020-05-23 17:34:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Spike needs convinced he's still the alpha dog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 17:34:00" d="2020-05-23 18:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom's assigned laundry duty at the estate and Jerry's determined to soil the job</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 18:00:00" d="2020-05-23 18:10:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean makes his own horror movie and ropes in Mrs Wicket as the star!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 18:10:00" d="2020-05-23 18:20:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean has to look after Mrs Wicket’s goldfish, but Scrapper the cat is keen to ‘help’</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 18:20:00" d="2020-05-23 18:30:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean wins tickets for a Cruise, but if only he could stay on it!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 18:30:00" d="2020-05-23 19:00:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean hopes to win some cash prizes at the funfair, but it’s not as easy as it seems!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 19:00:00" d="2020-05-23 19:22:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>When Scooby and the gang accept an invitation from famous actor Malcolm McDowell to take an exploratory trip through time, they find themselves actually</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 19:22:00" d="2020-05-23 20:00:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>When a marble statue comes to life at a museum in Greece our gang is caught between a braying minotaur and a sword-wielding Wonder Woman!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 20:00:00" d="2020-05-23 20:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% While looking for the TV remote-control device Grizzy happens onto a box that can localize a bunch of keys thanks to its key ring which is equipped with a tracker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 20:06:00" d="2020-05-23 20:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings have turned the cabin topsy-turvy and created an obstacle course to race through in a hamster ball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 20:13:00" d="2020-05-23 20:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings create a customized hang-glider using a supermarket shopping cart for the nacelle and a ventilator as an engine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 20:19:00" d="2020-05-23 20:25:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings scribble all over the book Snow White on the living room sofa. Grizzy throws them off with scant ceremony and they crash to the floor with their book</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 20:25:00" d="2020-05-23 20:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy and the Lemmings' favorite chocolate spread brand is organizing a big competition where the prize is a giant jar of spread</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 20:32:00" d="2020-05-23 20:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Freed from the ice which had preserved him for millions of years a saber-toothed bear bursts into the cabin starving to death</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 20:38:00" d="2020-05-23 21:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings discover a top-secret Canadian Army prototype that allows you to pass through solid surfaces for a window of several seconds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 21:00:00" d="2020-05-23 21:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola has to write an essay on the theme My Hero Pet. It's not easiest task in the world for her she explains to Victor for while Pat is the loveliest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 21:07:00" d="2020-05-23 21:14:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola leaves the supermarket with all the ingredients for a super smoothie party. But disaster! She realizes she has forgotten the milk. She entrusts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 21:14:00" d="2020-05-23 21:20:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola decides to post a video of Pat and Hoodie. She prepares a script and decides to fix a camera on Pat’s head. But the shooting quickly goes down the drain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 21:20:00" d="2020-05-23 21:25:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Hoodie falls into the sewers with Lola’s precious scrapbook. Victor pretends he has the book and has Lola work in his garden to recover it. But Pat witnessed everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 21:25:00" d="2020-05-23 21:32:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>At the yard sale Lola decides to sell Pat’s old puppy bed making our hero feel nostalgic. But the bed attracts Tank’s attention who's had</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 21:32:00" d="2020-05-23 21:39:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola must take care of an extremely rare caterpillar as a school assignment. But the little caterpillar attracts the Guanos’ appetite who imagine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 21:39:00" d="2020-05-23 22:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and Pat have a garden where they grow a strawberry. But this splendid strawberry attracts Tank and the Guanos curiosity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 22:00:00" d="2020-05-23 22:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings have laid hand on special magnets which turn any object they are stuck to into flying objects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 22:06:00" d="2020-05-23 22:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% With a lion-tamer's whip a sugar bowl and lots of work the Lemmings have successfully trained a caribou to go through their obstacle course</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 22:13:00" d="2020-05-23 22:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy happens onto the electronic version of the Ranger Lemming toy which is capable of reproducing the movements one teaches it like a smart robot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 22:19:00" d="2020-05-23 22:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Ranger's cabin is equipped with an ultra-effective pest detector capable of sensing the presence of an intruder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 22:26:00" d="2020-05-23 22:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy finds himself unwillingly caught up in a race between two teams of Lemmings. When he understands the stakes he tries to win but loses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 22:32:00" d="2020-05-23 22:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings have placed giant remote-controlled hydraulic jacks under the cabin to transform it into a life-sized rolling ball game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 22:39:00" d="2020-05-23 23:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy is disturbed during his nap by a few uncatchable flies which buzz incessantly around his head</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 23:00:00" d="2020-05-23 23:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Jimmy fears that being a “shrimp” will prevent him from getting knight missions when he grows up and decides to become a gym rat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 23:10:00" d="2020-05-23 23:21:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>While Bad Jack gets some sleep, he leaves Bjorn to guard his treasure. Bjorn enlists help from Jimmy and Cat who make a silly suggestion to keep thieves away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 23:21:00" d="2020-05-23 23:31:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Cynthia makes everybody believe she's the legendary Swan, Cat and Jimmy must find a way to make her confess the truth before she (and Epic) gets into real danger…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 23:31:00" d="2020-05-24 00:00:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Jimmy convinces Henri to repair a leak in Lady Fontaine's classroom. Henri ends up being appointed as the castle's Maintenance Official</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 00:00:00" d="2020-05-24 00:06:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Who says you can’t teach an old dog new tricks?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 00:06:00" d="2020-05-24 00:13:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley starts an escalating journalistic war</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 00:13:00" d="2020-05-24 00:20:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy hypnotizes Bentley to get rid of him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 00:20:00" d="2020-05-24 00:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Tonight it's a super rare occurrence of a ‘raccoon moon’</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 00:26:00" d="2020-05-24 00:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley creates a fake Taffy or Mrs M will be devastated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 00:33:00" d="2020-05-24 00:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley and Taffy use the AC to get rid of one another</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 00:39:00" d="2020-05-24 00:45:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy is injured and must wear a cone head</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 00:45:00" d="2020-05-24 00:52:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Strangers have travelled back in time with a warning…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 00:52:00" d="2020-05-24 01:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy gets rid of Bentley. Victory!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 01:00:00" d="2020-05-24 01:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a super fun app that allows you to see yourself as a rabbit or a robot or else decked out with lots of animated accessories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 01:06:00" d="2020-05-24 01:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% When they find an old book on traditional Japanese origami, the Lemmings churn out paper birds to play gliding games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 01:13:00" d="2020-05-24 01:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings are all lined up on the couch to watch a cartoon film where a mouse plays nasty tricks on a cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 01:19:00" d="2020-05-24 01:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Once again Grizzy shows the Lemmings that they just don't measure up to him physically and that the last jar of chocolate spread is for the strongest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 01:26:00" d="2020-05-24 01:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings lay their hands on a full crate of chocolate spread which they hide somewhere behind Grizzy's back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 01:32:00" d="2020-05-24 01:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy is persuaded that he's discovered the ultimate gadget for good living</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 01:39:00" d="2020-05-24 01:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings clamor for their turn to play with the ranger's mobile phone but Grizzy isn't in the sharing mood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 01:45:00" d="2020-05-24 01:52:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy is captivated by a mime artist on TV who makes viewers believe in the presence of an invisible wall</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 01:52:00" d="2020-05-24 02:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings shiver with cold sneeze and are glassy-eyed: they have a big fat cold!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 02:00:00" d="2020-05-24 02:05:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is rehearsing the flute recital she has to play this evening. A lady pigeon perches nearby to enjoy her playing and one of the Guanos falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 02:05:00" d="2020-05-24 02:12:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends are organizing a food drive for the city’s kennel. But the food supplies soon attract the attention of Tank and the Guanos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 02:12:00" d="2020-05-24 02:19:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is planning a surprise dinner for her parents' wedding anniversary so she settles into the kitchen to prepare a nice meal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 02:19:00" d="2020-05-24 02:25:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is due to be interviewed as Pet owner of the Week for a pet’s magazine. Victor is jealous. Surely he’s been the best pet owner this</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 02:25:00" d="2020-05-24 02:31:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and Victor are both fans of the game Galaktik dance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 02:31:00" d="2020-05-24 02:37:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>This morning Lola is feeling very anxious. She has a big test coming up at school and she’s not at all confident</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 02:37:00" d="2020-05-24 02:44:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Tonight Lola is determined to spy a shooting star so that she can make a wish. When the Guanos meanwhile are set on making their wish come true: to get rid of Hoodie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 02:44:00" d="2020-05-24 02:51:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola finds Victor sad and alone in his garden. Tomorrow is his birthday and nothing has been planned for the special day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 02:51:00" d="2020-05-24 03:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends are in the middle of a medieval role playing game and there is treasure hidden in the bouncy castle: candies and cookies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 03:00:00" d="2020-05-24 03:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When our trio lets success get to their heads, they boast about their team and inadvertently inspire the Cursed Forest Witch and Bad Jack to create their own deadly duo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 03:10:00" d="2020-05-24 03:21:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy complains that Henri treats him like a baby, Henri lets him do “grownup” things for himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 03:21:00" d="2020-05-24 03:31:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Jimmy, Cat and Henri have to organise a fake kidnapping of Lance by Bjorn, in order to retrieve Lance’s smart-mirror, which contains films of Cat, Henri</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 03:31:00" d="2020-05-24 03:42:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Jimmy squires for the Red Knight, and his insistence on showing Red he’s a great squire causes Red to get captured by the Black Sorcerer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 03:42:00" d="2020-05-24 04:00:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy loses Torpedo in a bet with Lance, Lance trades Henri’s horse to the Black Rats. It’s not a good time, as Henri has to deliver a peace agreement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 04:00:00" d="2020-05-24 04:06:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Who says you can’t teach an old dog new tricks?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 04:06:00" d="2020-05-24 04:13:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley starts an escalating journalistic war</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 04:13:00" d="2020-05-24 04:20:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy hypnotizes Bentley to get rid of him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 04:20:00" d="2020-05-24 04:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Tonight it's a super rare occurrence of a ‘raccoon moon’</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 04:26:00" d="2020-05-24 04:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley creates a fake Taffy or Mrs M will be devastated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 04:33:00" d="2020-05-24 04:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley and Taffy use the AC to get rid of one another</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 04:39:00" d="2020-05-24 04:45:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy is injured and must wear a cone head</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 04:45:00" d="2020-05-24 04:52:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Strangers have travelled back in time with a warning…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 04:52:00" d="2020-05-24 05:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy gets rid of Bentley. Victory!</k>  </p>
</a>
