<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="135" t="2020-04-16 04:27:58"><p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 05:00:00" d="2020-04-23 05:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings scribble all over the book Snow White on the living room sofa. Grizzy throws them off with scant ceremony and they crash to the floor with their book</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 05:06:00" d="2020-04-23 05:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy and the Lemmings' favorite chocolate spread brand is organizing a big competition where the prize is a giant jar of spread</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 05:13:00" d="2020-04-23 05:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Freed from the ice which had preserved him for millions of years a saber-toothed bear bursts into the cabin starving to death</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 05:19:00" d="2020-04-23 05:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings discover a top-secret Canadian Army prototype that allows you to pass through solid surfaces for a window of several seconds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 05:26:00" d="2020-04-23 05:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have found an Amerindian eagle amulet that endows he who wears it with the powers of a bird of prey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 05:32:00" d="2020-04-23 05:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings are having a blast with the ranger's electric guitar and the cabin walls tremble with their experimental rock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 05:39:00" d="2020-04-23 05:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% To finally be on an equal footing with Grizzy's imposing build and throw their own weight around in the cabin the Lemmings decide to wear a blowup sumotori costume</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 05:45:00" d="2020-04-23 05:52:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy and the Lemmings discover an ancient Amerindian table with the power to show you past events</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 05:52:00" d="2020-04-23 06:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings discover an old book of magic spells with a formula that enables one to take on the appearance of any other creature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 06:00:00" d="2020-04-23 06:09:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Tom stars in a documentary that mischaracterises his daily activities./ Dr. Bigby latest invention transports Tom and Jerry to Paris where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 06:09:00" d="2020-04-23 06:19:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Tom stars in a documentary that mischaracterises his daily activities./ Dr. Bigby latest invention transports Tom and Jerry to Paris where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 06:19:00" d="2020-04-23 06:29:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Rick and Ginger are going on a vacation and bringing Tom and Spike aboard the plane./Rick and Ginger sneak Tom and Spike into a hotel where pets are not allowed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 06:29:00" d="2020-04-23 06:39:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Rick and Ginger are going on a vacation and bringing Tom and Spike aboard the plane./Rick and Ginger sneak Tom and Spike into a hotel where pets are not allowed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 06:39:00" d="2020-04-23 07:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Jerry leads an accident-prone scouting troop earning badges and creating mayhem for Tom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 07:00:00" d="2020-04-23 07:10:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean makes his own horror movie and ropes in Mrs Wicket as the star!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 07:10:00" d="2020-04-23 07:20:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean has to look after Mrs Wicket’s goldfish, but Scrapper the cat is keen to ‘help’</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 07:20:00" d="2020-04-23 07:30:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean wins tickets for a Cruise, but if only he could stay on it!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 07:30:00" d="2020-04-23 07:45:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean hopes to win some cash prizes at the funfair, but it’s not as easy as it seems!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 07:45:00" d="2020-04-23 08:00:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr. Bean becomes obsessed with gaming after being introduced by Mrs. Wicket’s nephew</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 08:00:00" d="2020-04-23 08:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The fridge in the cabin has changed: it's been replaced by a brand new state-of-the-art appliance which analyzes the body fat percentage of whoever wants to serve himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 08:06:00" d="2020-04-23 08:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy watches a demonstration of balloon modelling on TV. He decides to make a balloon poodle to offer the she-bear he's enamored with</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 08:13:00" d="2020-04-23 08:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy needs a nice nap. He can't find a pillow comfortable enough to his taste until he tests the pillow that the Lemmings use as a high-jump mat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 08:19:00" d="2020-04-23 08:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy is awakened from his nap by the unpleasant, ongoing sound of Velcro strips being ripped off</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 08:26:00" d="2020-04-23 08:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The she-bear Grizzy is enamored with has lost her favorite flower in an inaccessible spot under a giant boulder. Grizzy tries to lift it: impossible!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 08:32:00" d="2020-04-23 08:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings try to catch a bat to play rodeo, disturbing Grizzy as he plays his favorite game on the ranger's mobile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 08:39:00" d="2020-04-23 08:50:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have a blast testing every app on the ranger's tablet one by one. Grizzy, who is starving, sees that the cupboards are bare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 08:50:00" d="2020-04-23 09:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings are having a blast with the ranger's electric guitar and the cabin walls tremble with their experimental rock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 09:00:00" d="2020-04-23 10:25:00"><n>Scooby-Doo! Curse of the Lake Monster</n>    <k>School is out and the familiar Scooby gang are looking to enjoy a long vacation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 10:25:00" d="2020-04-23 11:00:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>Daphne agrees to watch her friend’s kid, Wayne, and convinces Fred to take a night off from mysteries to go to the boardwalk amusement park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 11:00:00" d="2020-04-23 11:22:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>When our mystery solving gang is driving in Japan they are stopped by none-other than famous actor Mark Hamill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 11:22:00" d="2020-04-23 12:00:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>When the Mystery Inc. gang gets lost in the Pocono Mountains of Pennsylvania they stumble into Psychic University well off the beaten track</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 12:00:00" d="2020-04-23 12:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben is at the annual Big Bacon Pig Parade but childhood friend Penny Heaven has met the family to ruin Ben's fun with her safety-obsessed self</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 12:10:00" d="2020-04-23 12:20:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>While Ben, Gwen and Max hike to a waterfall, the Bug Brothers are back with a plan to duplicate Diamondhead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 12:20:00" d="2020-04-23 12:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben, Gwen and Max revisit their favourite amusement park – renovated and rebranded as AdrenaWORLD! Unfortunately, the new management is Zombozo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 12:30:00" d="2020-04-23 12:50:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben and Billy Billions clash in a duel for supremacy at the Laser Tag Park. But when Billy inadvertently ignites a robot rebellion their game escalates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 12:50:00" d="2020-04-23 13:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Gwen drags Ben along on a hike in search of the legendary Forgeti, a yeti that makes people forget they ever saw it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 13:00:00" d="2020-04-23 13:09:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Tom stars in a documentary that mischaracterises his daily activities./ Dr. Bigby latest invention transports Tom and Jerry to Paris where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 13:09:00" d="2020-04-23 13:19:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Tom stars in a documentary that mischaracterises his daily activities./ Dr. Bigby latest invention transports Tom and Jerry to Paris where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 13:19:00" d="2020-04-23 13:29:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Rick and Ginger are going on a vacation and bringing Tom and Spike aboard the plane./Rick and Ginger sneak Tom and Spike into a hotel where pets are not allowed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 13:29:00" d="2020-04-23 13:39:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Rick and Ginger are going on a vacation and bringing Tom and Spike aboard the plane./Rick and Ginger sneak Tom and Spike into a hotel where pets are not allowed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 13:39:00" d="2020-04-23 14:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Jerry leads an accident-prone scouting troop earning badges and creating mayhem for Tom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 14:00:00" d="2020-04-23 14:10:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean redecorates his room, making it fit for a Queen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 14:10:00" d="2020-04-23 14:21:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean gets green eyes and green fingers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 14:21:00" d="2020-04-23 14:31:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean becomes smitten with a beautiful singer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 14:31:00" d="2020-04-23 14:45:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean meets a soul mate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 14:45:00" d="2020-04-23 15:00:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean is on his way to the seaside when the mini runs out of petrol</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 15:00:00" d="2020-04-23 15:10:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% During a trip, Floyd, obsessed with taking the Baby Looney Tunes to visit the distant Acme Garlic Festival, endures countless variants of the kid question</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 15:10:00" d="2020-04-23 15:20:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Granny's sister's bakery, Cakery Bakery Dock, home of her wonderful cinnamon rolls, is being put out of business so her landlord can tear down the bakery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 15:20:00" d="2020-04-23 15:30:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Baby Bugs can't wait to see his favourite children's musical group, The Wormies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 15:30:00" d="2020-04-23 15:45:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% The Baby Looney Tunes are very eager to visit the local TV station, home of their favourite live children's show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 15:45:00" d="2020-04-23 16:00:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Taz discovers pratfalls get him laughs and attention</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 16:00:00" d="2020-04-23 16:10:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Bunnicula and Chester are trapped in an ever-escalating prank war</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 16:10:00" d="2020-04-23 16:20:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Patches the Weredude is back -- this time to help Mina's dad as a &quot;pet psychologist.&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 16:20:00" d="2020-04-23 16:30:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>When Bunnicula is kidnapped, Harold must teach Chester how to be a &quot;secret service&quot; animal to rescue their friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 16:30:00" d="2020-04-23 16:45:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>When torrential rain floods the basement, the pets find themselves hunted by the mysterious Cellarmander</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 16:45:00" d="2020-04-23 17:00:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Harold's tail decides who's boss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 17:00:00" d="2020-04-23 17:10:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Rick and Ginger take Tom and Butch on a cruise ship./Rick and Ginger take Tom and Spike on a road trip to Ginger's aunt's house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 17:10:00" d="2020-04-23 17:19:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Rick and Ginger take Tom and Butch on a cruise ship./Rick and Ginger take Tom and Spike on a road trip to Ginger's aunt's house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 17:19:00" d="2020-04-23 17:29:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Hildie and Beatie bring home a fortune telling magic mirror./Spike comes to Tom and Jerry for help finding his missing bones</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 17:29:00" d="2020-04-23 17:39:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Hildie and Beatie bring home a fortune telling magic mirror./Spike comes to Tom and Jerry for help finding his missing bones</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 17:39:00" d="2020-04-23 18:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Rick has taken up painting to help him relax</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 18:00:00" d="2020-04-23 18:10:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean makes his own horror movie and ropes in Mrs Wicket as the star!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 18:10:00" d="2020-04-23 18:20:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean has to look after Mrs Wicket’s goldfish, but Scrapper the cat is keen to ‘help’</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 18:20:00" d="2020-04-23 18:30:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean wins tickets for a Cruise, but if only he could stay on it!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 18:30:00" d="2020-04-23 18:45:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean hopes to win some cash prizes at the funfair, but it’s not as easy as it seems!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 18:45:00" d="2020-04-23 19:00:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr. Bean becomes obsessed with gaming after being introduced by Mrs. Wicket’s nephew</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 19:00:00" d="2020-04-23 19:22:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>When Scooby and the gang are investigating one of the most haunted mansions in the historic Hollywood Hills they meet up with none-other than famous actor George Takei</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 19:22:00" d="2020-04-23 20:00:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>When Scooby and the gang are taking a tour of merry old London they run afoul of horrible screaming skulls of English legend!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 20:00:00" d="2020-04-23 20:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Inside a mysterious cave Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a magical Game of the Goose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 20:06:00" d="2020-04-23 20:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings notice that Grizzy moves away from the jar of chocolate spread whenever he chases the fly buzzing around him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 20:13:00" d="2020-04-23 20:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% A magic tomahawk divides Grizzy into two identical bears with diametrically opposite personalities, one short-tempered, the other super-sweet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 20:19:00" d="2020-04-23 20:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy finds a magician's hat that tosses out objects stored inside beforehand with the tap of a magic wand. He decides to impress his beloved she-bear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 20:26:00" d="2020-04-23 20:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% A newly unpacked UV tanning booth holds the place of honor in the middle of the cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 20:32:00" d="2020-04-23 20:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy wants to try out the brand new packaging format of chocolate spread that he discovers in the ranger's cupboard, a yummy-looking XXL jar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 20:38:00" d="2020-04-23 20:50:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% In a casing that fell from a circus caravan the Lemmings find a magic stick that can enchant objects and make them come alive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 20:50:00" d="2020-04-23 21:00:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Bella attempts to stage a perfect performance are ruined first by falling leaves then by the robot hoover she uses to clear them up. But maybe there's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 21:00:00" d="2020-04-23 21:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola has to keep a little puppy for the day but he turns out to be a real fury. Pat will have to do everything in his power to keep him from turning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 21:07:00" d="2020-04-23 21:13:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola agrees on pet-sitting the goldfish belonging to Honorine her former neighbor. Of course the Guanos have set their sights on the poor creature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 21:13:00" d="2020-04-23 21:20:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>On their way back home Lola Lucie and Pat come across an old abandoned house. Lola is super excited and wants to explore the home but Lucie and Pat seem reluctant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 21:20:00" d="2020-04-23 21:27:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Today Lola and Lucie must give a presentation at school. But her mother embarks the girl’s presentation sheets to work thinking it’s her architectural designs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 21:27:00" d="2020-04-23 21:34:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola’s mom bought a 3D printer for work. The little girl is fascinated by the machine. Before leaving for school she promises Pat to 3D print a surprise for her parents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 21:34:00" d="2020-04-23 21:40:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>While playing a game with Hoodie and Lola Pat accidentally breaks the television. Lola says it was her fault to protect her faithful friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 21:40:00" d="2020-04-23 22:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Today Lola and her class are going to visit the museum. Before leaving to school her mother reminds her to behave and stay out of trouble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 22:00:00" d="2020-04-23 22:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% In a casing that fell from a circus caravan the Lemmings find a magic stick that can enchant objects and make them come alive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 22:06:00" d="2020-04-23 22:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Whilst trying to stop the Lemmings from playing with a crate of firework rockets Grizzy is literally carried away with them when the largest specimen shoots off</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 22:13:00" d="2020-04-23 22:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% With their endless battles over the ranger's cabin, which they do not want to share, Grizzy and the Lemmings end up blowing the cabin up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 22:19:00" d="2020-04-23 22:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy gets rid of the Lemmings by crushing them with one of the ranger's heavy trunks, which he immediately clears out of the cabin, his enemies stuck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 22:26:00" d="2020-04-23 22:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% A strange object is delivered to the Ranger's cabin: an over-board! It's a latest generation skateboard which levitates above the ground without wheels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 22:32:00" d="2020-04-23 22:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings encounter a white bear which has drifted all the way to them on a chunk of ice which is slowly melting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 22:39:00" d="2020-04-23 23:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% After studying a magazine advertisement with a couple standing in front of an SUV, Grizzy imagines that if only he had a nice car, his favorite she-bear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 23:00:00" d="2020-04-23 23:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>After the queen eats a lollipop that makes her start to shrink, Jimmy and Henri must capture the Dark Forest Witch in order to get an antidote</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 23:10:00" d="2020-04-23 23:21:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy inadvertently convinces Ronny Flash to do an interview with a rock monster, Jimmy, Henri and Cat end up escorting Ronny into the Dark Lands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 23:21:00" d="2020-04-23 23:31:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>To show off, Jimmy arrives at the castle flying on Bjorn, and he pretends the dragon is his pet. But Wilfried captures the “monster,” and Bad Jack threatens to burn Epic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 23:31:00" d="2020-04-24 00:00:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When the Queen wishes she could give her knights a break during a particularly intense period of battles with the Villains, Jimmy suggests she call a truce</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 00:00:00" d="2020-04-24 00:06:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M is sick, everyone needs to be silent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 00:06:00" d="2020-04-24 00:13:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Scraggs a raccoon uses a cat disguise to enter Mrs M manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 00:13:00" d="2020-04-24 00:20:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy tries to get rid of Addie who knows he’s a raccoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 00:20:00" d="2020-04-24 00:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The pets help an unconscious Mrs M pass an inspection</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 00:26:00" d="2020-04-24 00:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M meets a handsome trillionnaire… allergic to dogs!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 00:33:00" d="2020-04-24 00:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The pets team up to recreate Mrs M's wedding video</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 00:39:00" d="2020-04-24 00:46:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley has a secret admirer…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 00:46:00" d="2020-04-24 00:52:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy gets scared as Mrs M tests him to discover his lineage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 00:52:00" d="2020-04-24 01:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Vacation's coming! But before the manor must be secured…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 01:00:00" d="2020-04-24 01:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Nutty Hill is suffering from a stifling heat wave. Grizzy decides to get into the fridge, where the temperature will be more bearable, but the shelves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 01:06:00" d="2020-04-24 01:12:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy is frustrated: just as he was about to coat a nice big fresh salmon with chocolate spread and snuggle up in front of the TV he discovers that the pantry is empty!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 01:12:00" d="2020-04-24 01:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy's nap is interrupted by an annoying vibration. He sees the forest ranger's cell phone on the couch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 01:19:00" d="2020-04-24 01:25:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Freed by the thawing ice a mysterious giant egg slides up to the front door of the log cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 01:25:00" d="2020-04-24 01:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% In order to seduce the she-bear he's infatuated with Grizzy decides to take things in hand and slim down with the ranger's bodybuilding equipment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 01:32:00" d="2020-04-24 01:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% By chance Grizzy discovers that the ranger's new robot vacuum cleaner also gives very pleasant back massages. But the Lemmings see the new gadget</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 01:38:00" d="2020-04-24 01:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy discovers a gadget that controls various functions in the cabin. He will finally be able to rid of the Lemmings without even leaving the couch!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 01:45:00" d="2020-04-24 01:51:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% To make sure that the Lemmings don’t snatch his chocolate spread Grizzy turns the fridge into a safe. But the Lemmings see Grizzy open the door while sleepwalking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 01:51:00" d="2020-04-24 02:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have invented a new popcorn game which consists of throwing popcorn and catching it with their mouths</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 02:00:00" d="2020-04-24 02:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>On their way back home Lola Lucie and Pat come across an old abandoned house. Lola is super excited and wants to explore the home but Lucie and Pat seem reluctant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 02:07:00" d="2020-04-24 02:14:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Today Lola and Lucie must give a presentation at school. But her mother embarks the girl’s presentation sheets to work thinking it’s her architectural designs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 02:14:00" d="2020-04-24 02:20:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola’s mom bought a 3D printer for work. The little girl is fascinated by the machine. Before leaving for school she promises Pat to 3D print a surprise for her parents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 02:20:00" d="2020-04-24 02:27:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>While playing a game with Hoodie and Lola Pat accidentally breaks the television. Lola says it was her fault to protect her faithful friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 02:27:00" d="2020-04-24 02:34:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Today Lola and her class are going to visit the museum. Before leaving to school her mother reminds her to behave and stay out of trouble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 02:34:00" d="2020-04-24 02:41:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and Pat are visiting one of her mom’s building sites for an article that she’s writing for school. But once there she discovers Hoodie inside her backpack!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 02:41:00" d="2020-04-24 02:47:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola decides to register Pat in a beauty contest. But for our hero Hoodie is the real star. Lola agrees on registering Hoodie instead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 02:47:00" d="2020-04-24 02:54:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola Hoodie and Paf are trick or treating on Halloween night. For Victor it’s the best opportunity to scare the little girl and her pets but his attempts fail miserably</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 02:54:00" d="2020-04-24 03:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola has won a prize to see one of her favorite singers Lady Kawai in concert. But Victor and the Guanos are determined to get hold of the ticket</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 03:00:00" d="2020-04-24 03:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Jimmy wants to make a squire out of the school’s doormat, Kurt, and teach him how to stand up for himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 03:10:00" d="2020-04-24 03:21:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy accidentally spills the beans to the Red Knight’s visiting father that Red is a gym teacher and not First Knight, Grandpa Red expresses his disapproval</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 03:21:00" d="2020-04-24 03:31:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Jimmy fears that being a “shrimp” will prevent him from getting knight missions when he grows up and decides to become a gym rat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 03:31:00" d="2020-04-24 03:42:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>While Bad Jack gets some sleep, he leaves Bjorn to guard his treasure. Bjorn enlists help from Jimmy and Cat who make a silly suggestion to keep thieves away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 03:42:00" d="2020-04-24 04:00:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Cynthia makes everybody believe she's the legendary Swan, Cat and Jimmy must find a way to make her confess the truth before she (and Epic) gets into real danger…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 04:00:00" d="2020-04-24 04:06:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M is sick, everyone needs to be silent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 04:06:00" d="2020-04-24 04:13:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Scraggs a raccoon uses a cat disguise to enter Mrs M manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 04:13:00" d="2020-04-24 04:20:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy tries to get rid of Addie who knows he’s a raccoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 04:20:00" d="2020-04-24 04:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The pets help an unconscious Mrs M pass an inspection</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 04:26:00" d="2020-04-24 04:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M meets a handsome trillionnaire… allergic to dogs!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 04:33:00" d="2020-04-24 04:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The pets team up to recreate Mrs M's wedding video</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 04:39:00" d="2020-04-24 04:46:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley has a secret admirer…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 04:46:00" d="2020-04-24 04:52:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy gets scared as Mrs M tests him to discover his lineage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-24 04:52:00" d="2020-04-24 05:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Vacation's coming! But before the manor must be secured…</k>  </p>
</a>
