<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="137" t="2021-07-08 04:55:46"><p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 05:00:00" d="2021-07-13 05:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>No Strings Attached
Mrs Muchmore receives the great Mr Fuffernin for an inspection of the house. If anything goes wrong, Mrs Muchmore would</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 05:05:00" d="2021-07-13 05:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Highest Bidder
At a luxurious auction, Mrs. Muchmore enters a bidding war with a charming young man to acquire a priceless ruby brooch. She invites</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 05:10:00" d="2021-07-13 05:20:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>I Now Pronounce You Dog and Cat
It's movie night! Mrs. M screens her old wedding video for her pets. As she steps away, the pets get in one of their usual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 05:20:00" d="2021-07-13 05:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bentley's Girlfriend
Taffy witnesses Bentley and Mrs Muchmore sobbing in front of a romance scene on television. What would happen to Bentley if he met his true love?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 05:25:00" d="2021-07-13 05:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dna
Mrs. Muchmore wants to find out her pet's lineage so she send Taffy and Bentley's hair to be tested. Taffy, anxious that she finds out he's a raccoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 05:30:00" d="2021-07-13 05:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Staycation
When Forsythe loads the limo up for Mrs Muchmore and the pets' vacation, Taffy and Bentley get accidentally locked in the basement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 05:40:00" d="2021-07-13 05:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mission Mish Mash
Taffy's raccoon friends come to the Mansion, hoping to take advantage of Mrs. Muchmore's largesse. But the red bow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 05:45:00" d="2021-07-13 05:50:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A Bentley Carol - Christmas
It's Christmas Eve and Bentley finally succeeds -- he has removed Taffy's ribbon and the raccoon is tossed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 05:50:00" d="2021-07-13 06:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Switch
A freak accident leads Bentley and Taffy to switch bodies, allowing each one to live in the other's shoes for a day. Taffy (as Bentley)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 06:00:00" d="2021-07-13 06:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Last Groundhog
Magoo mistakes Weasel (in an animal costume) for a groundhog being hunted and confiscates the hunter’s gun. In reality he steals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 06:05:00" d="2021-07-13 06:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Home Havoc
Magoo can't find the book that Linda lent him and he's ready to turn the house upside down to find it. The problem is that he</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 06:15:00" d="2021-07-13 06:30:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pinkbeard's Treasure
Magoo hunting for Pinkbeard’s treasure mistakes the park for an island. Fizz and Weasel are there selling ice cream that never falls on the ground</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 06:30:00" d="2021-07-13 06:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mistaken Identity
At the supermarket, Magoo mixes his shopping cart up with a baby stroller. Fizz decides to save the toddler and become a media star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 06:35:00" d="2021-07-13 06:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hamster Fishing
Fizz is at the municipal pool, he wants to revolution the world of sub-marine hairdressing!But Magoo, thinking that he is actually fishing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 06:40:00" d="2021-07-13 07:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Whiter Than White
Magoo thinking he’s at the laundromat wanders into a candy factory where Fizz and Weasel are creating a bubblegum that makes Fizz-shaped bubbles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 07:00:00" d="2021-07-13 07:05:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show II (72)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Wish Bone
Butch finds a wishbone in the rubbish and dupes Tom into believing it will make his wishes come true. Butch trades Tom the bone for a dozen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 07:05:00" d="2021-07-13 07:10:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show II (78)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Novel Idea
An overflowing trash bin filled with crumpled paper can mean only one thing…Tom is writing a novel - it's a mystery novel, of course! Tom soon realizes his book is playing out in real life (including the femme fatale who has taken an interest in the fel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 07:10:00" d="2021-07-13 07:25:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show II (76)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Cat Match Fever
Butch is bobbing for apple cores when he spots a dolled up Toodles heading his way! Butch slicks back his hair with some lard and strikes a pose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 07:25:00" d="2021-07-13 07:30:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show II (75)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Fish Out of Water
Hildie and Beatie return from the Ol' Time Goblin Fair with kettle corn, a giant stuffed warlock, and a piranha they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 07:30:00" d="2021-07-13 07:40:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Someone's in the Kitchen with Mynah
Ginger brings home a new pet—a mynah bird who can mimic anyone and anything. Rick complains about the money</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 07:40:00" d="2021-07-13 07:45:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% When You Leash Expect It
Ginger decides she wants to teach Tom to walk on a leash to ensure he gets much-needed exercise. Tom hates the leash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 07:45:00" d="2021-07-13 07:50:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Thief In The Museum
The orange blob is down at the Museum, nerding out about ancient Egypt, when the Docs show up and ruin Lamput’s day. Darn science geeks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 07:50:00" d="2021-07-13 08:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Evolution
Lamput spends the day at the beach, and, in a pair of swimming trunks, cuts a fine figure indeed. That is to say; a small, round and blobby figure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 08:00:00" d="2021-07-13 08:10:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Wanted
An escaped prisoner suffers hard labour under Mrs Wicket while Mr Bean puts his feet up in jail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 08:10:00" d="2021-07-13 08:30:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Gadget Kid
High-tech wizardry and low-tech cunning get Mr Bean out of a jam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 08:30:00" d="2021-07-13 08:40:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% The Visitor
Mr Bean learns that generosity can be an effective weapon against greed gluttony and getting your hands back on your own TV remote control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 08:40:00" d="2021-07-13 09:00:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Big TV
Mr Bean goes to buy the biggest TV in the world only to find that it has a price- tag to match</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 09:00:00" d="2021-07-13 09:30:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Area 51 Adjacent
Daphne always dreamed of meeting extra-terrestrial life but that dream becomes a nightmare when the gang gets caught up in the mystery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 09:30:00" d="2021-07-13 10:00:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Grand Scam
Shaggy takes the gang to the Minor League Baseball stadium of his youth only to learn that it's about to be shut down because a Ghostly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 10:00:00" d="2021-07-13 11:15:00"><n>Scooby-Doo! And The Goblin King</n><t>Q</t>    <k>63% Shaggy, Scooby and the gang visit an eerie carnival on Halloween night, but all is not as it seems when the evil Goblin King makes an appearance!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 11:15:00" d="2021-07-13 11:40:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Area 51 Adjacent
Daphne always dreamed of meeting extra-terrestrial life but that dream becomes a nightmare when the gang gets caught up in the mystery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 11:40:00" d="2021-07-13 12:00:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% For the Love of Ruggles
Tom impulsively kicks Spike's beloved chew toy Ruggles over the fence and has to go get it back when he sees how heartbroken Spike becomes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 12:00:00" d="2021-07-13 12:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>They Are Among US
Busy observing the sky in search of UFOS Magoo accidentally finds himself wandering over to Fizz’s house. Thinking that the hamster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 12:05:00" d="2021-07-13 12:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Skyfall
When Magoo treats Mr Cat to a parachute jump the two friends land on the top of the AeroFizz. Convinced that they are marooned on a desert island</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 12:15:00" d="2021-07-13 12:30:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nice Little Doggy
Magoo is handing out food to the local neighborhood animals when he stumbles on a gigantic horrific hamster that Fizz has released</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 12:30:00" d="2021-07-13 12:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hats Off Magoo!!
Magoo thinks that Fizz is a hat he is going to wear for his romantic date with Marnie. The hamster is going to have</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 12:35:00" d="2021-07-13 12:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Firefighter for a Day
Magoo is a part-time firefighter reservist whose rescue mission for the day is to save a cat in a tree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 12:40:00" d="2021-07-13 13:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lend Me Your Earpiece
Magoo finds himself shrunk and then dragged inside the President’s head along with Fizz. He thinks the hamster is a little</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 13:00:00" d="2021-07-13 13:10:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Taziator / Marvin Flag Gag: Little Martian / Climate Control
Bugs tunnels up into an ancient Roman gladiator arena, and must fight the Tasmanian Devil</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 13:10:00" d="2021-07-13 13:30:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Lepreconned / Marvin Flag Gag: Flag Won't Stay Straight / Brave New Home
While looking for Hawaii, Bugs Bunny accidentally finds himself in Ireland, where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 13:30:00" d="2021-07-13 13:35:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Cal the Viking
Cal the Viking attempts to conquer Bugs' Bunny's Home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 13:35:00" d="2021-07-13 13:40:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Rhoda's Road House
Bugs and Squeaks go to Rhoda Roundhouse's Restaurant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 13:40:00" d="2021-07-13 13:45:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Claire de Loon
Phoebe and Justin are forced to go to sleep by their Mom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 13:45:00" d="2021-07-13 14:00:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Daffy Duck: Motivational Guru
Elmer takes a Tony Robbins-type self confidence course</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 14:00:00" d="2021-07-13 14:10:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Keyboard Capers
Determined to play the piano Mr Bean finds a tune in his heart and sausages for fingers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 14:10:00" d="2021-07-13 14:25:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% A Running Battle
Mr Bean runs rings around the town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 14:25:00" d="2021-07-13 14:40:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Egg and Bean
Mr Bean is 'storked' by an unwelcome visitor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 14:40:00" d="2021-07-13 15:00:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Hopping Mad!
Mr Bean finds that tons of toads weigh loads and loads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 15:00:00" d="2021-07-13 15:30:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Me, Myself and A.I.
When an Artificial Intelligence takes over the building of a trendy tech company the Gang has to solve the computerised mystery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 15:30:00" d="2021-07-13 16:00:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Gremlin on a Plane
The gang has seats on the largest airplane ever to fly the open skies! Unfortunately the plane is also beset by a Gremlin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 16:00:00" d="2021-07-13 16:05:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Don't Cut the Cheese
It's that special time of year when the Lady of the House's rare, exotic (and very stinky) cheese gets delivered to the manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 16:05:00" d="2021-07-13 16:10:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Calamari Jerry
Ginger leaves some frozen fish on the kitchen counter to thaw. Ginger and Rick warn Tom to keep his paws away, or he will not get anything to eat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 16:10:00" d="2021-07-13 16:25:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Cattyshack
It's time for the annual croquet tournament at the Manor. The butler tells Tom how important it is to the Lady of the Manor to always win…no matter what! The last thing they need is any pesky rodents interfering with the game. Knowing any sighting of Je</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 16:25:00" d="2021-07-13 16:30:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Drone Sweet Drone
Up to their usual antics, Tom, Jerry and Spike get into monkey business with a drone at Rick and Ginger's house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 16:30:00" d="2021-07-13 16:40:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% Home Away from Home
Tom falls asleep inside a rolled-up carpet left out on the curb by Rick with a &quot;free&quot; sign attached. When the new owners unload their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 16:40:00" d="2021-07-13 16:45:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>70% From Riches to Rags
After a series of beatings from Tom, Jerry storms off into his mouse hole. Soon he falls asleep and dreams himself to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 16:45:00" d="2021-07-13 17:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Shrunk Docs
Safety standards at the Docs' Lab remain shockingly low. Once, just once, it would be nice to invent something that doesn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 17:00:00" d="2021-07-13 17:10:00"><n u="Mush Mush And The Mushables">Mush Mush And The Mushables I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Let It Bee
Wanting to rush off to climb Mush Mountain, Mush-Mush is in a hurry checking nectar level in flowers. a job that takes time and care</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 17:10:00" d="2021-07-13 17:30:00"><n u="Mush Mush And The Mushables">Mush Mush And The Mushables I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Staff Of Wisdom
Mush-Mush is amazed by the way Mushpot uses his staff of wisdom and how awesome it makes him look. Mush-Mush wants to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 17:30:00" d="2021-07-13 17:40:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Real Pat
While Lola is preparing her birthday party the Guanos discover a stray dog that looks exactly like Pat. This gives them a great idea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 17:40:00" d="2021-07-13 17:45:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Easter Eggs
Lola is organizing an Easter egg hunt and with Pat she is hiding eggs in the garden. But seized by some maternal instinct the Guanos decide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 17:45:00" d="2021-07-13 18:00:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Inspector Pat
On her way back from school, Lola makes a stop to buy a cereal bar. But when leaving the store, the manager holds her back and accuses her of theft</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 18:00:00" d="2021-07-13 18:10:00"><n u="Kingdom Force">Kingdom Force I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Cat Me If You Can
Jabari's solo-mission is thwarted after Mittens McGuirk intervenes and accidentally lets the Gunter &amp; Gustav steal Jabari's crystal cargo! Will Kingdom Force and Mittens be able to reclaim the crystals before the Henchbears gets away?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 18:10:00" d="2021-07-13 18:30:00"><n u="Kingdom Force">Kingdom Force I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ready, Set, Slow!
After Envie Fernandez is quick to steal Professor Dunbit's slo-mo ray, it's up to Kingdom Force to hurry up and get it back before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 18:30:00" d="2021-07-13 18:35:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Timeless Bear
When Grizzy and the Lemmings accidentally activate a magic disk representing the earth they are sent back in time to the prehistoric era</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 18:35:00" d="2021-07-13 18:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Weightless Bear
While fighting over a jar of chocolate spread, Grizzy and the Lemmings set off a chain reaction which sends the jar flying into space</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 18:40:00" d="2021-07-13 19:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Call of the Bear
Grizzy discovers the ranger's collection of bird calls by chance. With a simple blow of the whistle, he can attract a flock of partridges</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 19:00:00" d="2021-07-13 19:10:00"><n u="Alice &amp; Lewis">Alice &amp; Lewis I (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Travelling Dodo
Dodson the dodo wants to get to the top of the cliff to enjoy the sunset with Junior. When he spots the caravan, nearby, he realizes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 19:10:00" d="2021-07-13 19:30:00"><n u="Alice &amp; Lewis">Alice &amp; Lewis I (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>How to Train Your Cat
Alice has been trying to train Echo, to no avail. So she heads off to Wonderland to try her method out on Chester. But she invites</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 19:30:00" d="2021-07-13 19:40:00"><n u="Baby Looney Tunes">Baby Looney Tunes I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Tea and Basketball
ylvester wants to play tea with the girls while Lola wants to play basketball with the boys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 19:40:00" d="2021-07-13 20:00:00"><n u="Baby Looney Tunes">Baby Looney Tunes I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Band Together
The babies learn about music and improvise their own orchestra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 20:00:00" d="2021-07-13 20:10:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Taziator / Marvin Flag Gag: Little Martian / Climate Control
Bugs tunnels up into an ancient Roman gladiator arena, and must fight the Tasmanian Devil</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 20:10:00" d="2021-07-13 20:30:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Lepreconned / Marvin Flag Gag: Flag Won't Stay Straight / Brave New Home
While looking for Hawaii, Bugs Bunny accidentally finds himself in Ireland, where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 20:30:00" d="2021-07-13 20:35:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Cal the Viking
Cal the Viking attempts to conquer Bugs' Bunny's Home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 20:35:00" d="2021-07-13 20:40:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Rhoda's Road House
Bugs and Squeaks go to Rhoda Roundhouse's Restaurant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 20:40:00" d="2021-07-13 20:45:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Claire de Loon
Phoebe and Justin are forced to go to sleep by their Mom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 20:45:00" d="2021-07-13 21:00:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Daffy Duck: Motivational Guru
Elmer takes a Tony Robbins-type self confidence course</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 21:00:00" d="2021-07-13 21:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (53)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>New Leaf Taffy
Taffy has a near-death experience, where a raccoon tells him he has to turn his life around, and be kind to Bentley in every</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 21:05:00" d="2021-07-13 21:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (54)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The New Mrs M
During a particularly epic chase, Taffy and Bentley collide with Mrs. Muchmore. She suddenly looses her mind and adores raccoons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 21:10:00" d="2021-07-13 21:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (55)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Upgrade
Taffy orders a new bow. But not just any bow: this is the Extra-Strength Non-Tear Accept-No-Substitutes Guaranteed-Unsnatchable Maxwell Deluxe 3000! When it arrives, Taffy gleefully puts it on and throws the old one away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 21:25:00" d="2021-07-13 21:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (156)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Honey I Shrunk The Raccoon
It's Spring Cleaning day and everyone is throwing out old useless junk. Suddenly, Taffy and Bentley have shrunk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 21:30:00" d="2021-07-13 21:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (57)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Caged
Forsythe has caught vermin on the property using a cage. Unfortunately for Taffy, the vermin are Mish and Mash! Forsythe entrusts Bentley to guard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 21:40:00" d="2021-07-13 21:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (158)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Scare Tactics
Overhearing Mrs. M's passion for ghosts and other supernatural things, Bentley at last hits on the perfect solution to get rid of Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 21:45:00" d="2021-07-13 22:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (59)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Petty Shack
Today it's the world's only golf tourney where the pets caddy for their owners. This year's grand prize is an all-expenses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 22:00:00" d="2021-07-13 22:05:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% A Sizeable Problem
When a meteorite falls not far from the log cabin, strange berries start to grow. One of their properties is that they make any animal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 22:05:00" d="2021-07-13 22:10:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Treasure Bear
Under the wood floor of the log cabin, Grizzy and the Lemmings discover the entrance to an underground gallery with an old treasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 22:10:00" d="2021-07-13 22:25:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% In the Service of His Majesty
When he brandishes an enchanted sceptre that the Lemmings brought home with other antique objects, Grizzy sees the Lemmings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 22:25:00" d="2021-07-13 22:30:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Art
Grizzy tries to impress the she-bear that he's in love with by making a sculpture of her from a piece of wood. But as soon as the artist's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 22:30:00" d="2021-07-13 22:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Happy Birthday Lemmings!
The Lemmings throw a surprise birthday party for one of the clan. When &quot;Happy Birthday&quot; rings out, the &quot;surpriiiiiise&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 22:40:00" d="2021-07-13 22:45:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Flower Power
A gust of wind sweeps away the flower that Grizzy's adored she-bear wears in her hair. Grizzy sees this as a golden opportunity to dazzle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 22:45:00" d="2021-07-13 23:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Teleportation's the Way to Go!
Grizzy finds two identical vases in a Native American chest. They are communicating vessels, so if he sticks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 23:00:00" d="2021-07-13 23:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mega Magoo vs Dr. Fizz
Fizz controlling a robot distributes free ice cream to everyone in the city. When Magoo mistakes him for a destructive monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 23:05:00" d="2021-07-13 23:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ghost Hunt
Fizz has invented a machine which stops toast from landing butter-side down. Magoo paying his neighbor a visit sees some floating toast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 23:15:00" d="2021-07-13 23:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Love Thy Neighbour
Magoo thinks he is housesitting for Weasel while the latter is on vacation. When he sees him returning from the grocery store</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 23:25:00" d="2021-07-13 23:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dances with Walruses
Magoo thinks he’s herding cattle through the desert but is in fact on an ice floe with walruses. He takes Fizz and Weasel for cattle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 23:35:00" d="2021-07-13 23:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Bodyguard
Fizz has dressed Weasel up as a supervillain in order to pretend to save the city. Magoo mistakes his disguised neighbor for an actress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-13 23:40:00" d="2021-07-14 00:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Not Without My Hamster
Fizz and Weasel are at the supermarket buying ingredients to make the world’s best cake. They bump into Magoo who thinks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 00:00:00" d="2021-07-14 00:05:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (66)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Duchess In Charge
Mike has a visitor for the afternoon - Duchess - and she's still hopelessly infatuated with Mike. She's so in</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 00:05:00" d="2021-07-14 00:10:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (67)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Gone To Pot
It's a beautiful summer day and Mike decides to woo Iris with a refreshing pineapple cocktail. But the pot he needs to make the drink</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 00:10:00" d="2021-07-14 00:25:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (68)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Animal Magnetism
Mike decides to try to impress Iris by pretending to be a superhero. With the help of a huge fridge magnet, Mike intends to attract</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 00:25:00" d="2021-07-14 00:35:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (69)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Hypnosis
Mike wakes up in the bathtub, huh? The house has been turned upside down and the other animals are being weird. They're acting like zombies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 00:35:00" d="2021-07-14 00:40:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (70)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Mike Impounded
The raccoons finally get the better of Mike while he tries to retrieve an object in their lair. They lock him in a cage and Freddy rushes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 00:40:00" d="2021-07-14 00:45:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (71)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Lights, Camera. Inaction!
Mike is inspired by a movie he sees on TV and decides to direct his own film. He enlists the help of Iris, Fluffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 00:45:00" d="2021-07-14 01:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Doc And The Thief
Specs and the jewel thief have a lot in common. They are both round and blue. Also they both like accelerating into blind corners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 01:00:00" d="2021-07-14 01:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mission Mish Mash
Taffy's raccoon friends come to the Mansion, hoping to take advantage of Mrs. Muchmore's largesse. But the red bow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 01:05:00" d="2021-07-14 01:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A Bentley Carol - Christmas
It's Christmas Eve and Bentley finally succeeds -- he has removed Taffy's ribbon and the raccoon is tossed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 01:10:00" d="2021-07-14 01:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Switch
A freak accident leads Bentley and Taffy to switch bodies, allowing each one to live in the other's shoes for a day. Taffy (as Bentley)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 01:25:00" d="2021-07-14 01:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Cute or Boot
Mrs. M comes home from the club all aflutter. Her ladies who lunch are all raving about the new social network app that allows everyone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 01:30:00" d="2021-07-14 01:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>License To Kale
Mrs. Muchmore is in good shape but still wants to improve her health. Binikos immediately puts the entire mansion on kale diet. Taffy goes crazyy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 01:40:00" d="2021-07-14 01:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Cat Burglar
Bentley learns about a cat burglar in the neighborhood. That night, Bentley lures the cat burglar into the mansion and tries to help him steal Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 01:45:00" d="2021-07-14 02:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Racoon's Day
Driiing ! The beautiful sound of the alarm clock awakes Taffy for another beautiful day in the beautiful and comfy Muchmore Manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 02:00:00" d="2021-07-14 02:05:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Role Change
After receiving a terrible blow over the head, Grizzy is no longer the same: he thinks he's a rodent! He tries to get the gang to adopt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 02:05:00" d="2021-07-14 02:10:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lemming Tonic
Grizzy is exhausted and the couch has never seemed so enticing! He goes to fetch a pillow and a sleeping mask, but the Lemmings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 02:10:00" d="2021-07-14 02:20:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Itch
Grizzy discovers that the frenzied &quot;break dance&quot; the Lemmings are doing is actually due to the fleas they are infested with. When Grizzy catches</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 02:20:00" d="2021-07-14 02:25:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Thirst Quencher
Another heat wave: even the riverbed is dried up. One very thirsty Grizzy discovers that the Lemmings have used the last remaining bottles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 02:25:00" d="2021-07-14 02:30:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Spider Lemmings
The Lemmings have caught a little spider. Her sticky, elastic threads are absolutely perfect for bungee jumping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 02:30:00" d="2021-07-14 02:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Random Bear
Grizzy and the Lemmings fight over chocolate-spread jar lids, which they use as chips in a competition to win goodies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 02:40:00" d="2021-07-14 02:45:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lemming Interference
Grizzy has prepared himself a TV dinner to eat in front of his favorite series. But his moment of pleasure is abruptly interrupted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 02:45:00" d="2021-07-14 02:50:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% High Voltage Bear Attack
The Lemmings are having a rave party. When Grizzy throws their ghetto blaster into the river, he sparks a general power outage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 02:50:00" d="2021-07-14 03:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Scents
When he realises his beloved she-bear adores the smell of flowers, Grizzy decides to offer her the geraniums that decorate the window ledges</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 03:00:00" d="2021-07-14 03:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (59)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Super Duper Sale
Hidden inside a robot Fizz and Weasel hack the world’s Internet server but Magoo shopping the sales mistakes it for a shopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 03:05:00" d="2021-07-14 03:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (60)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Chill Out
Fizz is recording a chill CD to de-stress the world so he needs peace and quiet. Unlucky for him: Magoo’s come over to borrow a wrench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 03:15:00" d="2021-07-14 03:20:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (61)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Man of Steel
Magoo thinks he’s in a triathlon and takes Fizz’s superhuman strength headband. The latter had been planning to use it to beat the President</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 03:20:00" d="2021-07-14 03:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (62)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Vanilla Strawberry Meltdown
Thinking he’s on an Artic expedition (actually at the beach) Magoo mistakes Fizz for an Amazonian marmoset monkey definitive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 03:25:00" d="2021-07-14 03:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (63)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Sweet Dreams Mr Cat
Fizz beams himself into Weasel’s brain in order to control his useless sidekick and take out Magoo with tranquilizer darts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 03:35:00" d="2021-07-14 03:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (64)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fizz FM
Today's the big day! Magoo is recording a hit single! Thinking he's in a music studio, he goes next door and mistakes Fizz for famous producer, Phil Dustspeck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 03:40:00" d="2021-07-14 03:50:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (65)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Magoo 2.0
Fizz tests his FizzoJam a ray that makes people dance in his honor. Magoo wearing a snorkeling mask that he’s convinced is a virtual reality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 03:50:00" d="2021-07-14 04:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (66)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mr Fixit
Thinking he’s fixing Weasel’s coffee maker Magoo tweaks Fizz’s teleporter the invention that the hamster plans to exhibit at the innovation tradeshow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 04:00:00" d="2021-07-14 04:05:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Garden Games
The turtles organize a sports contest and whoever wins gets a special trophy. Iris volunteers a reluctant Mike to take part in the games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 04:05:00" d="2021-07-14 04:10:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Vampire Attack
The weather is miserable so Mike decides to stay in and catch up on his reading. However the book he's reading on Vampires is scarier</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 04:10:00" d="2021-07-14 04:20:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% In the Box
Mike has his work cut out for him when Stephan leaves a beautiful gift for his wife on the counter and goes to work for the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 04:20:00" d="2021-07-14 04:25:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% That Magnificent Mike!
It's Iris's birthday and Mike wants to surprise her with a special party. Balloons, gifts, Pinata - the works! Everything has been perfectly planned but the relentless raccoons decide to crash the party and steal all the candy. The racoons discover the h</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 04:25:00" d="2021-07-14 04:30:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Mikeyzushi
While Mike prepares a special sushi dinner to win Iris's heart, the racoons break into the garage intent on creating some mischief</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 04:30:00" d="2021-07-14 04:40:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Sneezed To Meet You!
Mike has the perfect gift idea for Iris, flowers! The only snag is that Mike discovers he's horribly allergic and the raccoons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 04:40:00" d="2021-07-14 04:45:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Mike Crooner
Mike decides to try to win Iris's affection by singing her a romantic musical number. As Mike has zero musical ability he uses Stephan's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 04:45:00" d="2021-07-14 04:50:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Duchess
Mike's over the moon! He's going to spend the afternoon with the neighbor's dog. Except that it's not Iris, it's Ginette, a pug</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 04:50:00" d="2021-07-14 05:00:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Fun Fur
Mike recreates a fun fair on the patio as a great way to impress Iris. He decorates the terrace and invites her over. However, there's</k>  </p>
</a>
