<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="135" t="2020-05-15 04:34:46"><p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 05:00:00" d="2020-05-22 05:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy watches a demonstration of balloon modelling on TV. He decides to make a balloon poodle to offer the she-bear he's enamored with</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 05:06:00" d="2020-05-22 05:12:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy needs a nice nap. He can't find a pillow comfortable enough to his taste until he tests the pillow that the Lemmings use as a high-jump mat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 05:12:00" d="2020-05-22 05:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy is awakened from his nap by the unpleasant, ongoing sound of Velcro strips being ripped off</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 05:19:00" d="2020-05-22 05:25:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The she-bear Grizzy is enamored with has lost her favorite flower in an inaccessible spot under a giant boulder. Grizzy tries to lift it: impossible!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 05:25:00" d="2020-05-22 05:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings try to catch a bat to play rodeo, disturbing Grizzy as he plays his favorite game on the ranger's mobile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 05:32:00" d="2020-05-22 05:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings have a blast testing every app on the ranger's tablet one by one. Grizzy, who is starving, sees that the cupboards are bare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 05:38:00" d="2020-05-22 05:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy and the Lemmings discover the ranger's latest acquisition: a 3D printer that will duplicate anything at all in miniature form</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 05:45:00" d="2020-05-22 05:51:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a strange gateway to a parallel world. On the other side, there is the same cabin, only it doesn't belong to a ranger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 05:51:00" d="2020-05-22 06:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The fridge in the cabin has changed: it's been replaced by a brand new state-of-the-art appliance which analyzes the body fat percentage of whoever wants to serve himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 06:00:00" d="2020-05-22 06:11:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>The team discovers Gracie’s whistle was taken by an alien (code name: cockroach) in Small Human’s messy room</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 06:11:00" d="2020-05-22 06:22:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>An Alien Rover (automated vacuum cleaner) is on the loose in the space station and it’s up to the PURST team to put it out of commission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 06:22:00" d="2020-05-22 06:33:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>When Gordon is taken over by aliens (code name: fleas), the PURST team has to help get rid of them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 06:33:00" d="2020-05-22 07:00:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>Binky’s favourite sweater is being eaten by aliens (code name: moths), and it’s up to the team to save to stop the aliens and save &quot;Fuzzy Wuzzy&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 07:00:00" d="2020-05-22 07:10:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean redecorates his room, making it fit for a Queen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 07:10:00" d="2020-05-22 07:21:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean gets green eyes and green fingers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 07:21:00" d="2020-05-22 07:31:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean becomes smitten with a beautiful singer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 07:31:00" d="2020-05-22 07:50:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean meets a soul mate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 07:50:00" d="2020-05-22 08:00:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>When Star stumbles across a vacuum cleaner she thinks it’ll be just the thing to get rid of all the litter in the enclosure but on full power it sucks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 08:00:00" d="2020-05-22 08:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% While looking for the TV remote-control device Grizzy happens onto a box that can localize a bunch of keys thanks to its key ring which is equipped with a tracker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 08:06:00" d="2020-05-22 08:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings have turned the cabin topsy-turvy and created an obstacle course to race through in a hamster ball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 08:13:00" d="2020-05-22 08:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings create a customized hang-glider using a supermarket shopping cart for the nacelle and a ventilator as an engine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 08:19:00" d="2020-05-22 08:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings scribble all over the book Snow White on the living room sofa. Grizzy throws them off with scant ceremony and they crash to the floor with their book</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 08:26:00" d="2020-05-22 08:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy and the Lemmings' favorite chocolate spread brand is organizing a big competition where the prize is a giant jar of spread</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 08:32:00" d="2020-05-22 08:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Freed from the ice which had preserved him for millions of years a saber-toothed bear bursts into the cabin starving to death</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 08:39:00" d="2020-05-22 09:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings discover a top-secret Canadian Army prototype that allows you to pass through solid surfaces for a window of several seconds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 09:00:00" d="2020-05-22 09:10:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean runs rings around the town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 09:10:00" d="2020-05-22 09:21:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean is 'storked' by an unwelcome visitor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 09:21:00" d="2020-05-22 09:31:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean finds that tons of toads weigh loads and loads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 09:31:00" d="2020-05-22 10:00:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean is all at sea with the landed gentry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 10:00:00" d="2020-05-22 10:09:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% After Taz breaks all of his toys, Granny gives him one last chance to care for something</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 10:09:00" d="2020-05-22 10:19:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% The babies plan a surprise birthday party for Tweety</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 10:19:00" d="2020-05-22 10:28:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Sylvester learns to live without his blankey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 10:28:00" d="2020-05-22 11:00:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Daffy overcomes his fear of the swimming pool</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 11:00:00" d="2020-05-22 11:22:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>When Scooby and the gang are hired to escort a supposedly possessed ventriloquist dummy to the annual Ventriloquist Talent Competition</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 11:22:00" d="2020-05-22 12:00:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>Scooby-Doo and the gang travel to Chambersburg a battlefield near Gettysburg to investigate the mysterious appearance of ghost zombie Civil War soldiers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 12:00:00" d="2020-05-22 12:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>While tailgating at a homecoming football game, Ben teams up with Grandpa Max’s old college buddies to keep the crazy clown Zombozo from robbing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 12:10:00" d="2020-05-22 12:20:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>While winning big on a Sumo Slammers video game, Ben gets the idea to win a wrestling match for real until an intimidating wrestler Kyle decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 12:20:00" d="2020-05-22 12:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>While trying to film his own indie film, Ben accidentally allows the Bug Gang to go free</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 12:30:00" d="2020-05-22 13:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>When Ben attempts to stay up all night for Adrenaland, he not only fails to utilize his alien powers to stay awake but his &quot;sleep-alien-ing&quot; causes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 13:00:00" d="2020-05-22 13:07:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% An over protected Spike goes to extreme lengths to keep his precious pup safe from harm</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 13:07:00" d="2020-05-22 13:14:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Spikes bones are missing and Frankie the Rat is the culprit. Now all they have to do is catch in the dirty rat in the act</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 13:14:00" d="2020-05-22 13:20:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom serves an evil pirate determined to steal treasure belonging to the village mice until Jerry Van Mouseling foils his plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 13:20:00" d="2020-05-22 13:27:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom turns into a Blob monster and proceeds to eat everything in sight including the village mice! Jerry Van Mouseling to the rescue!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 13:27:00" d="2020-05-22 13:33:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Rick and Ginger leave town with instructions for Tom to keep the house in order but Jerry's got other ideas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 13:33:00" d="2020-05-22 14:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom is tricked into helping an evil magician capture all of the mice in the village but Jerry Van Mouseling foils the magician's plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 14:00:00" d="2020-05-22 14:10:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean runs rings around the town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 14:10:00" d="2020-05-22 14:21:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean is 'storked' by an unwelcome visitor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 14:21:00" d="2020-05-22 14:31:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean finds that tons of toads weigh loads and loads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 14:31:00" d="2020-05-22 15:00:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean is all at sea with the landed gentry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 15:00:00" d="2020-05-22 15:11:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>When Small Human gets a cold, Binky and the team decide to do what humans do and make him some &quot;sooouup&quot; to help cure him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 15:11:00" d="2020-05-22 15:22:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>When Binky gets back from the vet completely shaved, the team thinks he’s an alien and he must prove he’s Binky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 15:22:00" d="2020-05-22 15:33:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>Ted is the test pilot of a space roamer when the remote control is taken over by an alien (code name: snail)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 15:33:00" d="2020-05-22 16:00:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>When aliens (code name: ants) take a piece of fruit that belongs to Small Human, it’s up to the team to get it back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 16:00:00" d="2020-05-22 16:09:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Bunnicula drains some cat nip and turns into a cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 16:09:00" d="2020-05-22 16:19:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>When Mina and her dad bring the pets on an island vacation, draining some seaweed turns Bunnicula into one very angry kaiju</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 16:19:00" d="2020-05-22 16:29:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>After draining a cocoa bean, Bunnicula turns to chocolate and is hunted by every candy craving maniac child in New Orleans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 16:29:00" d="2020-05-22 17:00:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>The lucky locket's back, and the pets must find a way to help Mina's future self</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 17:00:00" d="2020-05-22 17:07:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Things get crazy down on the farm when a cat and mouse pursuit leads Jerry to hide his turtle egg in a hen's nest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 17:07:00" d="2020-05-22 17:14:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% The Cat and Mouse are hired to find out who absconded with Hoops McJumpalot's lucky high top sneakers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 17:14:00" d="2020-05-22 17:20:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% The neighbor's cat turns out to be a hipster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 17:20:00" d="2020-05-22 17:27:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom falls into a manhole and finds a magic cloak that turns him into King of the Catacombs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 17:27:00" d="2020-05-22 17:34:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Spike leaves Tom in charge of his boy Tyke only to discover upon his return that Tyke now behaves more like a cat than a dog</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 17:34:00" d="2020-05-22 18:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Fed up Tom decides to go home to his birth family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 18:00:00" d="2020-05-22 18:10:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean redecorates his room, making it fit for a Queen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 18:10:00" d="2020-05-22 18:21:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean gets green eyes and green fingers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 18:21:00" d="2020-05-22 18:31:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean becomes smitten with a beautiful singer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 18:31:00" d="2020-05-22 19:00:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean meets a soul mate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 19:00:00" d="2020-05-22 19:22:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>Scooby and our gang of mystery solving teens have been invited by famous comedian Jeff Foxworthy to help him move an old mansion that he's just purchased</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 19:22:00" d="2020-05-22 20:00:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>Scooby and the Mystery Inc. gang meet Wanda Sykes who is helping save a bunch of cute fuzzy animals up for adoption</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 20:00:00" d="2020-05-22 20:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings have unearthed a crate of competition boomerangs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 20:06:00" d="2020-05-22 20:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Exasperated by the Lemmings who prevent him from watching his favorite TV show in peace Grizzy catapults them out of the cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 20:13:00" d="2020-05-22 20:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% A strange new object figures prominently in the cabin: a big wall clock that resembles a Swiss cuckoo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 20:19:00" d="2020-05-22 20:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Woken with a start by a nightmare filled with Lemmings Grizzy stumbles on the Ranger's dream machine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 20:26:00" d="2020-05-22 20:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy happens onto an old American India medallion bearing the symbol of the wind. He who wears it has the power to command air streams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 20:32:00" d="2020-05-22 20:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% A magic Amerindian top modifies the mental age of anyone who watches it spin. From now on, Grizzy has the mind of a 10-month old baby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 20:38:00" d="2020-05-22 21:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% A magic horn lands on the muzzle of a moose endowing it with grace and the ability to fly. It soars off leaving a rainbow-colored streak in its wake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 21:00:00" d="2020-05-22 21:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Today Lola is spending the afternoon in the company of her former neighbor Honorine. On the menu: games and homemade pies. At least that’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 21:07:00" d="2020-05-22 21:14:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola looks on as an old lady throws seed to the birds and observes how the Guanos use their brute force to push other birds out of the way to hog the food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 21:14:00" d="2020-05-22 21:20:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola has to play a violin solo during the big show tonight. When she is on stage Victor creates an accident as a pretext to make Lola believe the place is haunted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 21:20:00" d="2020-05-22 21:27:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola’s mother has just received the latest prototype for a food processor to test. Even though Lola promises to wait till evening before trying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 21:27:00" d="2020-05-22 21:34:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>A renowned pastry chef has organized a pie tasting contest. The winner will get to present a TV show with him. Lola is naturally taking part in the contest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 21:34:00" d="2020-05-22 21:40:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Today is the big Robot Battle day! Lola’s robot which looks like Pat has to face down Victor’s. But the boy cheats and breaks RoboPat. However Pat decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 21:40:00" d="2020-05-22 22:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola has found herself a fun activity for the afternoon: to break a Guinness World record. To do so she intends to build the biggest cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 22:00:00" d="2020-05-22 22:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings shiver with cold sneeze and are glassy-eyed: they have a big fat cold!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 22:06:00" d="2020-05-22 22:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings find a pack of icy mints that literally chill your breath. One blast from anyone who eats them freezes everything in sight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 22:13:00" d="2020-05-22 22:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy can't believe it: he has just swallowed a spoonful of his favorite food chocolate spread and he hates it!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 22:19:00" d="2020-05-22 22:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy discovers the fondness of his beloved she-bear for meditation. To seduce her he sets out to prove to her that he too can attain the Zen attitude</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 22:26:00" d="2020-05-22 22:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a super-secret Canadian Army prototype which resembles a simple computer keyboard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 22:32:00" d="2020-05-22 22:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings are having a blast with a bowling game they found in the Ranger's storeroom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 22:39:00" d="2020-05-22 23:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% After the rains to the great delight of the Lemmings strange bouncing mushrooms have sprouted in the yard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 23:00:00" d="2020-05-22 23:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy loses Torpedo in a bet with Lance, Lance trades Henri’s horse to the Black Rats. It’s not a good time, as Henri has to deliver a peace agreement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 23:10:00" d="2020-05-22 23:21:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Cat and Cynthia bicker in class, Lady Fontaine assigns them as partners who have to make a gown together for the upcoming fashion show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 23:21:00" d="2020-05-22 23:31:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Jimmy wants to make a squire out of the school’s doormat, Kurt, and teach him how to stand up for himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-22 23:31:00" d="2020-05-23 00:00:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy accidentally spills the beans to the Red Knight’s visiting father that Red is a gym teacher and not First Knight, Grandpa Red expresses his disapproval</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 00:00:00" d="2020-05-23 00:06:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley and Taffy decide to order a robot to help Forsythe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 00:06:00" d="2020-05-23 00:13:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy is completely hulked out!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 00:13:00" d="2020-05-23 00:20:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy has a cavity and goes to the vet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 00:20:00" d="2020-05-23 00:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The vet comes for a stay at Muchmore Manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 00:26:00" d="2020-05-23 00:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>A new kitten is found into the mansion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 00:33:00" d="2020-05-23 00:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Fuffernin is looking for a star for his next movie!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 00:39:00" d="2020-05-23 00:46:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy has a birthday party and a makeover at the same time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 00:46:00" d="2020-05-23 00:52:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley is provoked in a duel against a corgi!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 00:52:00" d="2020-05-23 01:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs. Muchmore buys Bentley a godawful holiday doggy sweater</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 01:00:00" d="2020-05-23 01:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy and the Lemmings clumsily destroy the TV remote control while fighting over who gets to watch his favorite program</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 01:06:00" d="2020-05-23 01:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings discover that by changing the speed limit sign on the side of the road, they can create a huge draft that is just perfect for their extreme kiting game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 01:13:00" d="2020-05-23 01:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% While trying to stop the Lemmings, Grizzy slips on the canvas and unwittingly executes an amazing somersault in front of his beloved she-bear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 01:19:00" d="2020-05-23 01:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings have hitched up a racoon with a sweet-tooth to their sled and get a ride by throwing cookies in front of the creature with a sling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 01:26:00" d="2020-05-23 01:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings have unearthed a strange little gadget from amongst the Forest Ranger's belongings: a hand spinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 01:32:00" d="2020-05-23 01:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings play with figurines of wild Canadian animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 01:39:00" d="2020-05-23 01:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy discovers a new generation Tamagotchi game on the Ranger's tablet: the camera scans the player and gives him a virtual avatar of himself to take care of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 01:45:00" d="2020-05-23 01:51:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy and the Lemmings find a vase with a genie inside that will make anyone's dreams come true, if they only let him out by rubbing the vase</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 01:51:00" d="2020-05-23 02:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings get their hands on a secret weapon that belongs to the Canadian Army: anyone hit with it becomes non-violent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 02:00:00" d="2020-05-23 02:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola enrolls Pat on a dog firefighter training program. But Victor is convinced that Tank is made for the job. An impromptu contest is held composed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 02:07:00" d="2020-05-23 02:13:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Victor tests his new remote-controlled car in the park with Lola and the dogs. But he loses control over the car and Tank is carried away by the car and hits his owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 02:13:00" d="2020-05-23 02:19:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola receives an invitation from the museum to attend the premiere of an exhibition about extinct species with one of her friends. She invites Victor who’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 02:19:00" d="2020-05-23 02:26:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is thrilled she just won the first prize in a contest and will get the visit of her favourite star! Unfortunately there’s a minor problem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 02:26:00" d="2020-05-23 02:33:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>The huge tree in the park is set to be cut down to make room for a new parking lot. Lola is outraged. They can't do this! It’s our special tree! With Victor's help Lola decides to protest against the plan while Pat forms an alliance with Tank and the Guanos to save the tree. But they have to use all their ingeniousness to outsmart the work-proud construction worker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 02:33:00" d="2020-05-23 02:39:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>To play an April fool’s trick on Lola Victor makes her believe that he has seen Hoodie in the subway whereas in fact Hoodie is actually locked in his room</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 02:39:00" d="2020-05-23 02:46:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>While playing with Pat and Hoodie Lola hears beautiful bird song. She looks in her dad’s ornithology book and finds out the bird is actually a parrot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 02:46:00" d="2020-05-23 02:52:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola wants to take part in an animal photography contest organized by the museum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 02:52:00" d="2020-05-23 03:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Bubbely encounters difficulties in his pond – the oxygen supply is running low</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 03:00:00" d="2020-05-23 03:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When the Queen wishes she could give her knights a break during a particularly intense period of battles with the Villains, Jimmy suggests she call a truce</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 03:10:00" d="2020-05-23 03:21:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy and Cat use science to help them win the school Sorcery Faire, their classmates think they’re masters of the Dark Arts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 03:21:00" d="2020-05-23 03:31:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>As Jimmy tells Cat and Bjorn about yet another cool day he had with Henri, his two friends sigh their own parents aren’t as cool</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 03:31:00" d="2020-05-23 03:42:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Henri is convinced that he wins his fights because he’s got a (ridiculous) ritual with a lucky charm. Wilfried steals it, which makes Henri completely lose his confidence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 03:42:00" d="2020-05-23 04:00:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Colbert catches Jimmy and the knights trading their assignments to get the mission worth the most victory points, Colbert assigns the knights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 04:00:00" d="2020-05-23 04:06:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley and Taffy decide to order a robot to help Forsythe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 04:06:00" d="2020-05-23 04:13:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy is completely hulked out!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 04:13:00" d="2020-05-23 04:20:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy has a cavity and goes to the vet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 04:20:00" d="2020-05-23 04:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The vet comes for a stay at Muchmore Manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 04:26:00" d="2020-05-23 04:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>A new kitten is found into the mansion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 04:33:00" d="2020-05-23 04:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Fuffernin is looking for a star for his next movie!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 04:39:00" d="2020-05-23 04:46:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy has a birthday party and a makeover at the same time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 04:46:00" d="2020-05-23 04:52:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley is provoked in a duel against a corgi!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-23 04:52:00" d="2020-05-23 05:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs. Muchmore buys Bentley a godawful holiday doggy sweater</k>  </p>
</a>
