<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="138" t="2021-07-13 04:55:33"><p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 05:00:00" d="2021-07-20 05:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (167)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Return Of Scraggs
A new fashion becoming all the rage in the Country Club. Farewell cats, say hello to raccoons, the best pets that exist! Mr. Fuffernin enthusiast asks to an afflicted Mrs Muchmore to organize a party in honor of these wild beasts . Bentley must review h</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 05:05:00" d="2021-07-20 05:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (168)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Twin Or Lose
Hector, Nestor's twin brother arrives at the Manor to attend a butler training. Unlike his brother, the latter is a calamity with regard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 05:10:00" d="2021-07-20 05:20:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (169)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Little Monster
Binikos, to keep Addie busy, offers her candies. Unfortunately by the action of sugar she turns into a terrifying and clumsy monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 05:20:00" d="2021-07-20 05:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (170)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Boot Camp Manor
While visiting her grandmother, Addie discovers the story of her ancestor, a legendary hero of garbage collection. Wanting to do the same</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 05:25:00" d="2021-07-20 05:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (171)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mirror Mansion
Mrs. Muchmore has found a rare object: a mirror of inestimable value. But when Taffy and Bentley fall against him, they pass through</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 05:30:00" d="2021-07-20 05:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (172)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Besties
A rebel punk raccoon moves into the back yard at Muchmore Manor. She gets all the scraps by being an unbelievable raccoon badass. Taffy, seeing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 05:40:00" d="2021-07-20 05:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (173)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>I Love Lamp
&quot; Bentley and Taffy discover in the cellar of the manor a magic lamp with a genius. Obviously, this is an opportunity for our two companions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 05:45:00" d="2021-07-20 05:50:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (174)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A Mouse In The House
Taffy is called into service to get rid of mice in the Manor. The problem is Taffy doesn't have the slightest idea how to do this</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 05:50:00" d="2021-07-20 06:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (175)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Phony Pony
When Mrs M welcomes a new resident to the Manor, Taffy and Bentley don't stand for this new pet that appeals all their mistress's attentions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 06:00:00" d="2021-07-20 06:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (55)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Prophecy of the Goldensand's Dragon
Fizz is at the beach trying to build the most beautiful sandcastle in history. Magoo thinks he is in the legendary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 06:05:00" d="2021-07-20 06:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (56)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hornets Attack!
Volunteer firefighter Magoo patrols the park. Fizz and Weasel perched on a fake cloud like two Cupids shoot people with arrows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 06:15:00" d="2021-07-20 06:30:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (57)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Star Man
Fizz rehearses a dance number that’ll make him the world’s greatest star. But when Weasel catapults him next door onto the roof Magoo thinks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 06:30:00" d="2021-07-20 06:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (58)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Last Oak Tree Standing
Fizz and Weasel have set up their super-antenna in the middle of the desert. Magoo thinking he’s walking in the forest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 06:35:00" d="2021-07-20 06:45:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (59)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Super Duper Sale
Hidden inside a robot Fizz and Weasel hack the world’s Internet server but Magoo shopping the sales mistakes it for a shopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 06:45:00" d="2021-07-20 07:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (60)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Chill Out
Fizz is recording a chill CD to de-stress the world so he needs peace and quiet. Unlucky for him: Magoo’s come over to borrow a wrench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 07:00:00" d="2021-07-20 07:05:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Double Dog Trouble
Spike the bulldog comes to Tom and Jerry, complaining he is being harassed by unknown creditors, ex-girlfriends, and other problems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 07:05:00" d="2021-07-20 07:10:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Hockey Jockeys
Jerry and Tuffy discover Ginger's surprise for Rick in the garage: a brand-new air hockey table. They enjoy floating in zero gravity before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 07:10:00" d="2021-07-20 07:25:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Dis-Repair Man
When Tom and Jerry break a picture frame on the wall, Rick gives Tom an ultimatum that he's out for good if he breaks one more thing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 07:25:00" d="2021-07-20 07:30:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Hyde and Shriek
A fast-talking sales cat named Dr. Jake L. appears to Tom from a trap door in the floor, selling &quot;Ache-Eee Bones&quot; tonic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 07:30:00" d="2021-07-20 07:40:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Perfume Party
Hoping to woo Toodles, Tom decides to make some homemade perfume for her. He throws in many unusual ingredients and gets a surprisingly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 07:40:00" d="2021-07-20 07:45:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% The Royal Treatment
When Jerry overhears that a brand-new butler will arrive at the household later that day, the crafty mouse whips together a butler's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 07:45:00" d="2021-07-20 07:50:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Thief In The Museum
The orange blob is down at the Museum, nerding out about ancient Egypt, when the Docs show up and ruin Lamput’s day. Darn science geeks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 07:50:00" d="2021-07-20 08:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Evolution
Lamput spends the day at the beach, and, in a pair of swimming trunks, cuts a fine figure indeed. That is to say; a small, round and blobby figure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 08:00:00" d="2021-07-20 08:10:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Scout Bean
Mr Bean inadvertently causes an accident which prevents Irma taking the scout troop to Big Bear’s Scout Camp. With the scout master</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 08:10:00" d="2021-07-20 08:30:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Back To School
Mr Bean cannot find anywhere to park other than the space he spots in a school’s car park. There’s a case of mistaken identity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 08:30:00" d="2021-07-20 08:40:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Lord Bean
Mr Bean is in the library studying his family heritage. Someone brings to his attention Mr Bean’s resemblance to a certain Lord Bean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 08:40:00" d="2021-07-20 09:00:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Car Wars
Mr Bean and his beloved car find themselves in a crash for crash battle with his arch nemesis the Reliant Robin. It’s a contest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 09:00:00" d="2021-07-20 09:30:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% The Norse Case. 
The gang goes on a camping trip, although they can't really agree on why. Fred's desire for the gang to get in touch with their natural</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 09:30:00" d="2021-07-20 10:00:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% The People vs. Fred Jones
Fred is on trial, convicted of being the real mastermind behind all the mysteries he's solved. With the help of his defence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 10:00:00" d="2021-07-20 11:15:00"><n>Scooby-Doo! And The Samurai Sword</n><t>Q</t>    <k>64% Scooby-doo and the Mystery Inc. crew get partial to the martial arts! Career slackers Scooby-Doo and Shaggy must put the &quot;chi&quot; in &quot;muchie&quot; to solve</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 11:15:00" d="2021-07-20 11:40:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Saga of the Swamp. 
The gang’s trip to be bayou is ruined by a shambling Swamp Beast that’s scaring away anyone who dares to enter it’s soggy domain!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 11:40:00" d="2021-07-20 12:00:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Dinner Is Swerved
When Rick and Ginger leave Tom home alone Tom and Jerry decide to invite their lady friends Toodles and Toots over for a romantic dinner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 12:00:00" d="2021-07-20 12:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Golden Fizz
Fizz plans on replacing the statue from an Oscar-like award's ceremony, with a statue in his effigy. But Magoo grabs it, thinking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 12:05:00" d="2021-07-20 12:10:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Saving the Gnomes of Astroturf
Magoo mistakes some kids at the park for gnomes in a magic forest. Fizz uses a remote to immobilize them to win over their parents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 12:10:00" d="2021-07-20 12:30:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dusk of the Cucumber
Fizz invents a cucumber that turns whoever is holding it into an object of human worship. When Magoo sees hypnotized passers-by being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 12:30:00" d="2021-07-20 12:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Spinning Headlock Elbow Drop
Magoo thinks that he is auditioning for a circus troop but he is actually in a professional wrestling ring in the middle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 12:35:00" d="2021-07-20 12:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mega Magoo vs Dr. Fizz
Fizz controlling a robot distributes free ice cream to everyone in the city. When Magoo mistakes him for a destructive monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 12:40:00" d="2021-07-20 13:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ghost Hunt
Fizz has invented a machine which stops toast from landing butter-side down. Magoo paying his neighbor a visit sees some floating toast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 13:00:00" d="2021-07-20 13:10:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Siberian Sam / Hole Gag: Fishing Pole /…
When Yosemite Sam loses his warm hat while dogsledding through frozen Siberia, he meets Bugs Bunny and decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 13:10:00" d="2021-07-20 13:30:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Grilled Rabbit / Cactus if You Can /…
When Elmer's carrots are stolen, he interrogates his prime suspect: Bugs Bunny. / Wile E. Coyote tries to catch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 13:30:00" d="2021-07-20 13:35:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Renaissance Fair-Thee Well
Police Officers Horace and Porky go undercover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 13:35:00" d="2021-07-20 13:40:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% CinderPorker - Part 1
Porky falls in love with Petunia queen of the land</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 13:40:00" d="2021-07-20 13:45:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% CinderPorker - Part 2
Porky falls in love with Petunia queen of the land</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 13:45:00" d="2021-07-20 14:00:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% You Ain't Nothin' but a Foghorn
Daffy Duck crashes a music festival and wreaks havoc</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 14:00:00" d="2021-07-20 14:10:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Wedding Day
Mr Bean has got everything ready for Irma’s birthday; card cake candles but he just needs to get her some flowers. But nothing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 14:10:00" d="2021-07-20 14:25:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Bean Phone
Mr Bean is keen to own a brand new smart phone when he discovers all the wonderful things it can do. But after a trip to the mobile phone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 14:25:00" d="2021-07-20 14:40:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Hotel Bean
A confused Japanese tourist couple mistake Mr Bean’s house for a hotel and because of the language barrier it is difficult to explain otherwise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 14:40:00" d="2021-07-20 15:00:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Jurassic Bean
Mr Bean is on a photography jaunt in the countryside snapping the normal everyday wildlife – a fox a bird a dinosaur! A DINOSAUR?!! Mr Bean is terrified until he realises what fame and fortune it could bring him. Does he get the photograph of a lifetime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 15:00:00" d="2021-07-20 15:30:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Some Fred Time
The gang force the over-worked Fred to relax and take time off from mysteries at Daphne’s family’s beach house. Unfortunately</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 15:30:00" d="2021-07-20 16:00:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% There Wolf
Feeling unwell Scooby is brought to a vet clinic. Soon the gang finds a werewolf is roaming around the place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 16:00:00" d="2021-07-20 16:05:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Lightning Bug Blues
Kept awake by Tom watching TV, Jerry goes outside and encounters some lightning bugs. The smallest one can't keep up, so Jerry steals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 16:05:00" d="2021-07-20 16:10:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% The Beast from the Bayou
When Tom goes through reverse evolution and is transformed into a swamp monster, he uses it to his advantage, scaring creatures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 16:10:00" d="2021-07-20 16:25:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (78)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% All Cat Jazz
Tom blows on a trumpet to dislodge Jerry from his hiding place, which leads to Frankie the rat convincing Tom he's a great trumpeter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 16:25:00" d="2021-07-20 16:30:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Alley Oops!
Butch gets muscled out of his alley by a bullying runt of an alley cat and Tom, Jerry and Spike team up to help Butch win back his territory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 16:30:00" d="2021-07-20 16:40:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (53)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Magic Hat Cat
A magician's hat is left behind at Ginger and Rick's house. Jerry runs into it, but when Tom reaches in after him, all he gets are multiple magician props</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 16:40:00" d="2021-07-20 16:45:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Wrap Star
Skullie warns Tom that it's almost midnight, so he'd best be on alert for one of the Catsylvania ghouls to show up. Tom reaches for a towel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 16:45:00" d="2021-07-20 17:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Shrunk Docs
Safety standards at the Docs' Lab remain shockingly low. Once, just once, it would be nice to invent something that doesn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 17:00:00" d="2021-07-20 17:10:00"><n u="Mush Mush And The Mushables">Mush Mush And The Mushables I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Get The Egg Home
When an egg blows down into the village, it is Mush-Mush and friends mission to return it to Mush Mountain. Two problems though:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 17:10:00" d="2021-07-20 17:30:00"><n u="Mush Mush And The Mushables">Mush Mush And The Mushables I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fly, Chase, Fly
Chep is disappointed Mush-Mush and Lilit are too busy leaf-gliding to play moss-ball with him, so he hangs out with a new weevil friend instead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 17:30:00" d="2021-07-20 17:40:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (53)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A Star Passes By
Lola is thrilled she has just won first prize in a contest and will get to see her favorite star Justin Fever! There's just one hitch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 17:40:00" d="2021-07-20 17:45:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (54)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Gang Gangs Up
The huge tree in the park is set to be cut down to make room for a new parking lot. Lola is outraged. They can't do this! It’s our special tree! With Victor's help Lola decides to protest against the plan while Pat forms an alliance with Tank and the Gu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 17:45:00" d="2021-07-20 18:00:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (55)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>April Fool
To play an April fool’s trick on Lola Victor makes her believe that he has seen Hoodie in the subway whereas in fact Hoodie is actually locked in his room</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 18:00:00" d="2021-07-20 18:10:00"><n u="Kingdom Force">Kingdom Force I (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Alpha-Magnet
Jalopi's feelings are hurt after she overhears Dalilah talking about her behind her back, and when the team gets in trouble facing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 18:10:00" d="2021-07-20 18:30:00"><n u="Kingdom Force">Kingdom Force I (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fleas &amp; Thank You
Sprocket sends the team on a treasure hunting training mission, but where there's treasure there's often Envie, and she's itching</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 18:30:00" d="2021-07-20 18:35:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Masked Racoon
The Lemmings have hitched up a racoon with a sweet-tooth to their sled and get a ride by throwing cookies in front of the creature with a sling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 18:35:00" d="2021-07-20 18:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Spinning Lemmings
The Lemmings have unearthed a strange little gadget from amongst the Forest Ranger's belongings: a hand spinner. Grizzy thinks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 18:40:00" d="2021-07-20 19:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Game Madness
The Lemmings play with poseable figurines of wild Canadian animals. When Grizzy sees that the bear figurine has been put inside a little</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 19:00:00" d="2021-07-20 19:10:00"><n u="Alice &amp; Lewis">Alice &amp; Lewis I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Swap-Swap
After getting struck by a lightning bolt courtesy of a grumpy magic cloud named Mr. Gray, the Queen and Lewis find themselves in a “swap-swap</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 19:10:00" d="2021-07-20 19:30:00"><n u="Alice &amp; Lewis">Alice &amp; Lewis I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Mole and the Mirror
It’s a disaster! Narcissio, the Queen’s facetious little mirror has made her royal mole vanish! Alice and Lewis promise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 19:30:00" d="2021-07-20 19:40:00"><n u="Baby Looney Tunes">Baby Looney Tunes I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Cereal Boxing
Baby Looney Tunes introduces the world's most beloved cartoon characters as precocious preschoolers, discovering the world one baby-step at a time!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 19:40:00" d="2021-07-20 20:00:00"><n u="Baby Looney Tunes">Baby Looney Tunes I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% Who Said That?
Baby Looney Tunes introduces the world's most beloved cartoon characters as precocious preschoolers, discovering the world one baby-step at a time!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 20:00:00" d="2021-07-20 20:10:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Siberian Sam / Hole Gag: Fishing Pole /…
When Yosemite Sam loses his warm hat while dogsledding through frozen Siberia, he meets Bugs Bunny and decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 20:10:00" d="2021-07-20 20:30:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Grilled Rabbit / Cactus if You Can /…
When Elmer's carrots are stolen, he interrogates his prime suspect: Bugs Bunny. / Wile E. Coyote tries to catch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 20:30:00" d="2021-07-20 20:35:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Renaissance Fair-Thee Well
Police Officers Horace and Porky go undercover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 20:35:00" d="2021-07-20 20:40:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% CinderPorker - Part 1
Porky falls in love with Petunia queen of the land</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 20:40:00" d="2021-07-20 20:45:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% CinderPorker - Part 2
Porky falls in love with Petunia queen of the land</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 20:45:00" d="2021-07-20 21:00:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% You Ain't Nothin' but a Foghorn
Daffy Duck crashes a music festival and wreaks havoc</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 21:00:00" d="2021-07-20 21:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Reach Out and Touch Someone
Mrs. M receives a visit from her old friend Coonskin Carl, a famous trapper who holds the world record for most raccoons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 21:05:00" d="2021-07-20 21:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The White Gloves
Forsythe can not stand the battle between Taffy and Bentley anymore! He decides to get rid of the pets but that's without counting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 21:10:00" d="2021-07-20 21:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Machine Dreams
It's time for the annual International Butling Associate inspection. And each year Forsythe has received its highest honor the coveted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 21:25:00" d="2021-07-20 21:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Taffyzilla
Binikos is concerned about Mrs. M's lack of strength, so he orders a special muscle-building machine. But Taffy crashes into it during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 21:30:00" d="2021-07-20 21:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Laughy Taffy
Taffy has been eating too many sweets and has a cavity. He'll have to go to the vet and get a filling. Bentley tries to show to Dr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 21:40:00" d="2021-07-20 21:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Pet Therapist
The vet comes for a stay at Muchmore Manor. She immediately declares Taffy and Bentley have big issues. She knows because</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 21:45:00" d="2021-07-20 22:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>There Kitty Kitty
A new kitten is found into the mansion. Now Mrs. M is in love with the kitten and Taffy must try to do him in but something is weird</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 22:00:00" d="2021-07-20 22:05:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (76)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Moonwalk Bear
Whilst trying to stop the Lemmings from playing with a crate of firework rockets, Grizzy is literally carried away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 22:05:00" d="2021-07-20 22:10:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (77)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Grizzy The Wizard
In a casing that fell from a circus caravan, the Lemmings find a magic stick that can enchant objects and make them come alive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 22:10:00" d="2021-07-20 22:25:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (76)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Mirror, Mirror On The Wall
While salmon fishing on the riverbank, Grizzy hauls in an unusual catch: an old hand mirror straight out of a fairytale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 22:25:00" d="2021-07-20 22:30:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Camping in the Wild
With their endless battles over the ranger's cabin which they do not want to share, Grizzy and the Lemmings end up blowing the cabin up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 22:30:00" d="2021-07-20 22:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Ice and Bears
The Lemmings encounter a white bear which has drifted all the way to them on a chunk of ice which is slowly melting. The bear makes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 22:40:00" d="2021-07-20 22:45:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Carried Away Bear
Grizzy gets rid of the Lemmings by crushing them with one of the ranger's heavy trunks which he immediately clears out of the cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 22:45:00" d="2021-07-20 23:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Fountain of Bear Youth
The Lemmings discover a strange pond in a Native American grotto that has the power to rejuvenate anyone who dips in it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 23:00:00" d="2021-07-20 23:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (77)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ratman
Magoo mistakes Fizz for billionaire Bruce Payne aka the superhero Ratman. When Ratman gets kidnapped by his mortal enemy Bozo (in reality Weasel)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 23:05:00" d="2021-07-20 23:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (78)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Here Kitty
Weasel tends to Fizz’s toothache but Magoo turns up thinking he’s busting into an animal-testing lab where cruel experiments are being carried</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 23:15:00" d="2021-07-20 23:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>They Are Among US
Busy observing the sky in search of UFOS Magoo accidentally finds himself wandering over to Fizz’s house. Thinking that the hamster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 23:25:00" d="2021-07-20 23:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Skyfall
When Magoo treats Mr Cat to a parachute jump the two friends land on the top of the AeroFizz. Convinced that they are marooned on a desert island</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 23:35:00" d="2021-07-20 23:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Nice Little Doggy
Magoo is handing out food to the local neighborhood animals when he stumbles on a gigantic horrific hamster that Fizz has released</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 23:40:00" d="2021-07-21 00:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hats Off Magoo!!
Magoo thinks that Fizz is a hat he is going to wear for his romantic date with Marnie. The hamster is going to have</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 00:00:00" d="2021-07-21 00:05:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Vampire Attack
The weather is miserable so Mike decides to stay in and catch up on his reading. However the book he's reading on Vampires is scarier</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 00:05:00" d="2021-07-21 00:10:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% In the Box
Mike has his work cut out for him when Stephan leaves a beautiful gift for his wife on the counter and goes to work for the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 00:10:00" d="2021-07-21 00:25:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% That Magnificent Mike!
It's Iris's birthday and Mike wants to surprise her with a special party. Balloons, gifts, Pinata - the works! Everything has been perfectly planned but the relentless raccoons decide to crash the party and steal all the candy. The racoons discover the h</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 00:25:00" d="2021-07-21 00:35:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Mikeyzushi
While Mike prepares a special sushi dinner to win Iris's heart, the racoons break into the garage intent on creating some mischief</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 00:35:00" d="2021-07-21 00:40:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Sneezed To Meet You!
Mike has the perfect gift idea for Iris, flowers! The only snag is that Mike discovers he's horribly allergic and the raccoons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 00:40:00" d="2021-07-21 00:48:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Mike Crooner
Mike decides to try to win Iris's affection by singing her a romantic musical number. As Mike has zero musical ability he uses Stephan's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 00:48:00" d="2021-07-21 00:50:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Memory Loss
It's back to basics as Specs attempts to catch Lamput with a net. Not being much good at anything at all physical, Specs ends up whacking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 00:50:00" d="2021-07-21 01:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Basketball
Lamput outsmarts the Docs by luring them onto a street basketball court and pitting them against the toughest ballerz in town. When the jocks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 01:00:00" d="2021-07-21 01:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (158)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Scare Tactics
Overhearing Mrs. M's passion for ghosts and other supernatural things, Bentley at last hits on the perfect solution to get rid of Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 01:05:00" d="2021-07-21 01:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (59)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Petty Shack
Today it's the world's only golf tourney where the pets caddy for their owners. This year's grand prize is an all-expenses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 01:10:00" d="2021-07-21 01:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (160)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Rival
Ms. M is being delivered a powerful dog robot: Blaze. Very quickly, Bentley is overwhelmed by this super machine with zero defects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 01:25:00" d="2021-07-21 01:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (61)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mrs ZZZ
Mrs. M. starts sleepwalking all over the mansion. While Bentley's trying to wake up his mistress to reveal Taffy's secret, the racoon wants to keep Mrs M. asleep</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 01:30:00" d="2021-07-21 01:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (63)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>My Fair Puppy
When Bentley realizes that Madame Muchmore is totally in Taffy's spell, he decides to ask some seduction lessons to his rival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 01:40:00" d="2021-07-21 01:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (64)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rags to Ostriches
Mrs. Muchmore decides to raise a very rare, expensive ostrich for a feather competition. But by unfortunate chance, the ostrich</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 01:45:00" d="2021-07-21 02:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (165)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Big Sneeze
Lunch is served and Forsythe cracks some fresh ground pepper on Taffy's meal. Taffy inhales some pepper and sneezes the entire plate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 02:00:00" d="2021-07-21 02:05:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (74)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Clean Bear
Grizzy wants to give the she-bear he's in love with a plastic ring which he finds really swell. But since the object was found in the trash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 02:05:00" d="2021-07-21 02:10:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (75)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Wandering Spirits
Grizzy finds a strange American Indian figurine with the power to switch the spirits of two living beings and finds himself imprisoned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 02:10:00" d="2021-07-21 02:20:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (76)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Mirror, Mirror on the Wall
While salmon fishing on the riverbank, Grizzy hauls in an unusual catch: an old hand mirror straight out of a fairytale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 02:20:00" d="2021-07-21 02:25:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (77)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Grizzy The Wizard
In a casing that fell from a circus caravan, the Lemmings find a magic stick that can enchant objects and make them come alive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 02:25:00" d="2021-07-21 02:30:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (76)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Moonwalk Bear
Whilst trying to stop the Lemmings from playing with a crate of firework rockets, Grizzy is literally carried away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 02:30:00" d="2021-07-21 02:35:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Camping in the Wild
With their endless battles over the ranger's cabin which they do not want to share, Grizzy and the Lemmings end up blowing the cabin up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 02:35:00" d="2021-07-21 02:45:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Carried Away Bear
Grizzy gets rid of the Lemmings by crushing them with one of the ranger's heavy trunks which he immediately clears out of the cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 02:45:00" d="2021-07-21 02:50:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lemmings Board
A strange object is delivered to the Ranger's cabin: an over-board! It's a latest generation skateboard which levitates above the ground without wheels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 02:50:00" d="2021-07-21 03:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Ice and Bears
The Lemmings encounter a white bear which has drifted all the way to them on a chunk of ice which is slowly melting. The bear makes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 03:00:00" d="2021-07-21 03:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Love Thy Neighbour
Magoo thinks he is housesitting for Weasel while the latter is on vacation. When he sees him returning from the grocery store</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 03:05:00" d="2021-07-21 03:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dances with Walruses
Magoo thinks he’s herding cattle through the desert but is in fact on an ice floe with walruses. He takes Fizz and Weasel for cattle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 03:15:00" d="2021-07-21 03:20:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Bodyguard
Fizz has dressed Weasel up as a supervillain in order to pretend to save the city. Magoo mistakes his disguised neighbor for an actress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 03:20:00" d="2021-07-21 03:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Not Without My Hamster
Fizz and Weasel are at the supermarket buying ingredients to make the world’s best cake. They bump into Magoo who thinks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 03:25:00" d="2021-07-21 03:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Curse of the Pyramid
Magoo thinks that he is lost in a pyramid but he is in fact in a big conference room where Fizz is about to perform a stand-up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 03:35:00" d="2021-07-21 03:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Deep Sea Diving
Magoo thinks he’s underwater scooting and has discovered Atlantis. In fact he’s in New York riding Fizz’s latest invention:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 03:40:00" d="2021-07-21 03:50:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Shaaaaaark!
Magoo thinks he’s a beach lifeguard but is actually on an ice floe and the swimmers are penguins! When Fizz shows up in a submarine to kidnap</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 03:50:00" d="2021-07-21 04:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Magoo the Sorcerer
Fizz and Weasel are trying to steal the president’s jokebook. Magoo thinking he is visiting a museum of sorcery mistakes Weasel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 04:00:00" d="2021-07-21 04:05:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Ice Rink
It's sweltering outside and Mike has invited Iris onto the terrace for a cooling cocktail. But the raccoons steal the ice maker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 04:05:00" d="2021-07-21 04:10:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Amnesia
Mercury suffers a huge blow to the head while trying to break into the Mikkelsen's house. When he wakes up, to Mike's great surprise, he seems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 04:10:00" d="2021-07-21 04:20:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Mike Unchained
Tom leaves his beautiful train set out in the house and the raccoons see it as a fantastic way to ship their loot back to their den</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 04:20:00" d="2021-07-21 04:25:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Petal To The Metal
Mike comes up with new plan to win Iris's affection by showering her with a cascade of rose petals. To do it, he needs to borrow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 04:25:00" d="2021-07-21 04:30:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Abraca-Disaster!
There's nothing better than a little magic trick to impress your crush. Iris isn't the only one impressed when Mike puts on a magic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 04:30:00" d="2021-07-21 04:40:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Itchy Frenzy
The racoons have fleas! They head over to Mike's to find something they can use to relieve the itch and pass the fleas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 04:40:00" d="2021-07-21 04:45:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Handcuffed
The crafty racoons manage to handcuff Mike's back legs together. The raccoons are convinced that with Mike incapacitated, they're finally going</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 04:45:00" d="2021-07-21 04:50:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Sleepy Head
Mike hasn't sleep at all. He can barely keep his eyes open and all he wants is nice long nap, but the raccoons are in top form, wreaking havoc</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-21 04:50:00" d="2021-07-21 05:00:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Diamond Dogs
Mike gets himself into a tough situation when Fluffy takes a necklace belonging to his owner into Iris's yard. Iris thinks the necklace</k>  </p>
</a>
