<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="136" t="2020-04-14 04:26:00"><p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 05:00:00" d="2020-04-21 05:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have laid hand on special magnets which turn any object they are stuck to into flying objects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 05:06:00" d="2020-04-21 05:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% With a lion-tamer's whip a sugar bowl and lots of work the Lemmings have successfully trained a caribou to go through their obstacle course</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 05:13:00" d="2020-04-21 05:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy happens onto the electronic version of the Ranger Lemming toy which is capable of reproducing the movements one teaches it like a smart robot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 05:19:00" d="2020-04-21 05:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Ranger's cabin is equipped with an ultra-effective pest detector capable of sensing the presence of an intruder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 05:26:00" d="2020-04-21 05:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy finds himself unwillingly caught up in a race between two teams of Lemmings. When he understands the stakes he tries to win but loses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 05:32:00" d="2020-04-21 05:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have placed giant remote-controlled hydraulic jacks under the cabin to transform it into a life-sized rolling ball game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 05:39:00" d="2020-04-21 05:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy is disturbed during his nap by a few uncatchable flies which buzz incessantly around his head</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 05:45:00" d="2020-04-21 05:52:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have unearthed a crate of competition boomerangs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 05:52:00" d="2020-04-21 06:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Exasperated by the Lemmings who prevent him from watching his favorite TV show in peace Grizzy catapults them out of the cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 06:00:00" d="2020-04-21 06:09:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Rick and Ginger leave Tom home alone./ Dr. Bigby works on creating a formula for a love potion which accidentally gets on Jerry when Napoleon tries to use it against Tom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 06:09:00" d="2020-04-21 06:19:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Rick and Ginger leave Tom home alone./ Dr. Bigby works on creating a formula for a love potion which accidentally gets on Jerry when Napoleon tries to use it against Tom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 06:19:00" d="2020-04-21 06:28:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Butch locks Tom in the basement to keep him from attending a date with Toodles./ Tom accidentally puts a spell on Santa that transforms him into a cookie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 06:28:00" d="2020-04-21 06:38:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Butch locks Tom in the basement to keep him from attending a date with Toodles./ Tom accidentally puts a spell on Santa that transforms him into a cookie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 06:38:00" d="2020-04-21 07:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% When Tom finds Butch having a bath he gives him the boot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 07:00:00" d="2020-04-21 07:10:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean runs rings around the town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 07:10:00" d="2020-04-21 07:21:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean is 'storked' by an unwelcome visitor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 07:21:00" d="2020-04-21 07:31:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean finds that tons of toads weigh loads and loads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 07:31:00" d="2020-04-21 07:45:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean is all at sea with the landed gentry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 07:45:00" d="2020-04-21 08:00:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr. Bean accidentally spills all of Mrs. Wicket’s new expensive perfume on the floor. In an attempt to hide his crime and refill the empty bottle he tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 08:00:00" d="2020-04-21 08:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings discover a strange pond in an American Indian grotto that has the power to rejuvenate anyone who dips in it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 08:06:00" d="2020-04-21 08:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% While chasing the Lemmings, Grizzy crashes into an arcade cabinet near the supermarket which displays a model fortuneteller and her crystal ball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 08:13:00" d="2020-04-21 08:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have turned the entire cabin topsy-turvy to organize medieval jousts with the ranger's fencing gear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 08:19:00" d="2020-04-21 08:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy finds a bottle containing a love potion, anyone who drinks it immediately falls in love with the first creature he sees</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 08:26:00" d="2020-04-21 08:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Before taking a nap, Grizzy locks the food in a cupboard to prevent the Lemmings from getting into it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 08:32:00" d="2020-04-21 08:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% When Grizzy and the Lemmings accidentally activate a magic disk representing the earth, they are sent back in time to the prehistoric era</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 08:39:00" d="2020-04-21 08:50:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% While fighting over a jar of chocolate spread, Grizzy and the Lemmings set off a chain reaction which sends the jar flying into space, where it damages a space station</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 08:50:00" d="2020-04-21 09:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings discover a top-secret Canadian Army prototype that allows you to pass through solid surfaces for a window of several seconds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 09:00:00" d="2020-04-21 10:10:00"><n>Scooby-Doo! Mask of the Blue Falcon</n>    <k>When the Scooby gang visits a comic book convention, the monster from a classic television show appears</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 10:10:00" d="2020-04-21 10:30:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>It's Christmas Eve and Fred is ready to solve a Christmas mystery! Unfortunately the town the gang has arrived in is being attacked by a Pterodactyl!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 10:30:00" d="2020-04-21 11:00:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>Daphne brings the gang to Ireland to visit an ancient Blake family castle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 11:00:00" d="2020-04-21 11:21:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>When Scooby and the gang come to Gotham City to visit Alfred Pennyworth they stumble into a dangerous mystery!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 11:21:00" d="2020-04-21 12:00:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>When Scooby and the gang are taking a tour of merry old London they run afoul of horrible screaming skulls of English legend!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 12:00:00" d="2020-04-21 12:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>No one believes Ben when he insists that one of the other patrons waiting on line at the World of Wet Water Park is the nefarious Frightwig disguised as a common girl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 12:10:00" d="2020-04-21 12:20:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>During a book signing at a medieval castle, Ben must stop Hex from getting his hands on a grimoire that can fuse its user with mythical beasts, creating monstrous hybrids!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 12:20:00" d="2020-04-21 12:31:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben goes Upgrade to get a better signal to watch his favourite show Xingo but the titular Xingo leaps from his animated dimension to ours – bringing mad chaos with him!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 12:31:00" d="2020-04-21 12:50:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>After the Rust Bucket breaks down at a Mobile Home Park, Ben discovers they’ve stumbled on to the last leg of the Cali 10 Hundred, an epic off-road auto race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 12:50:00" d="2020-04-21 13:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>After their attempt to get a photo with every storefront mascot is foiled, Ben and Gwen sneak out at night to get their photo with the wooden bear totem known as &quot;Yawk&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 13:00:00" d="2020-04-21 13:09:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Rick and Ginger leave Tom home alone./ Dr. Bigby works on creating a formula for a love potion which accidentally gets on Jerry when Napoleon tries to use it against Tom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 13:09:00" d="2020-04-21 13:19:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Rick and Ginger leave Tom home alone./ Dr. Bigby works on creating a formula for a love potion which accidentally gets on Jerry when Napoleon tries to use it against Tom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 13:19:00" d="2020-04-21 13:28:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Butch locks Tom in the basement to keep him from attending a date with Toodles./ Tom accidentally puts a spell on Santa that transforms him into a cookie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 13:28:00" d="2020-04-21 13:38:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Butch locks Tom in the basement to keep him from attending a date with Toodles./ Tom accidentally puts a spell on Santa that transforms him into a cookie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 13:38:00" d="2020-04-21 14:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% When Tom finds Butch having a bath he gives him the boot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 14:00:00" d="2020-04-21 14:10:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>High-tech wizardry and low-tech cunning get Mr Bean out of a jam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 14:10:00" d="2020-04-21 14:21:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean learns that generosity can be an effective weapon against greed, gluttony and getting your hands back on your own TV remote control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 14:21:00" d="2020-04-21 14:32:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean goes to buy the biggest TV in the world only to find that it has a price- tag to match</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 14:32:00" d="2020-04-21 14:45:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Determined to play the piano, Mr Bean finds a tune in his heart and sausages for fingers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 14:45:00" d="2020-04-21 15:00:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr. Bean is trying to impress some kids in the park with his football skills but winds up kicking their ball into a dilapidated scary-looking house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 15:00:00" d="2020-04-21 15:09:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% With Floyd's adult assistance, Baby Bugs and the Baby Looney Tunes learn an effective way to deal with a bully</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 15:09:00" d="2020-04-21 15:19:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Everyone's excited about a grand bicycle outing through the park, everyone except Tweety whose little legs don't quite reach the pedals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 15:19:00" d="2020-04-21 15:29:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% When Bugs loses a baby tooth, Daffy tries to figure out how to scam the tooth fairy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 15:29:00" d="2020-04-21 15:45:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Taz learns a tough lesson. He shouldn't spin after eating too much candy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 15:45:00" d="2020-04-21 16:00:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Taz decides he doesn't like taking a bath</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 16:00:00" d="2020-04-21 16:10:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>After a magical artifact combines Chester, Harold, and Bunnicula into one uberpet, they must find a way to unmesh themselves without Mina finding out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 16:10:00" d="2020-04-21 16:20:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Mina wants to see a real ghost so her pets hire one to give her a little bit of a scare</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 16:20:00" d="2020-04-21 16:29:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>After an evil portrait swallows up Mina and her dad, the pets must find a way to break the spell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 16:29:00" d="2020-04-21 16:45:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>After Mina's imaginary friend returns to her life, Bunnicula is set on a collision course with a type of supernatural creature he has never had to deal with</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 16:45:00" d="2020-04-21 17:00:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Bunnicula and his gang, &quot;The Bunny Boys,&quot; go through New Orleans to retrieve his stolen ears</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 17:00:00" d="2020-04-21 17:09:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Jerry and Tuffy are getting ready to go to a family reunion./ Tom and Jerry are hired by a bad magician to find out where his Pidgeon friend disappeared to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 17:09:00" d="2020-04-21 17:19:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Jerry and Tuffy are getting ready to go to a family reunion./ Tom and Jerry are hired by a bad magician to find out where his Pidgeon friend disappeared to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 17:19:00" d="2020-04-21 17:29:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Tom and Butch compete for the Golden Fez and chance to be top cat./Hildie and Beatie commemorate the passing of their Mother and Tom tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 17:29:00" d="2020-04-21 17:39:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Tom and Butch compete for the Golden Fez and chance to be top cat./Hildie and Beatie commemorate the passing of their Mother and Tom tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 17:39:00" d="2020-04-21 18:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Trouble ensues when Tom is separated from his own shadow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 18:00:00" d="2020-04-21 18:10:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean runs rings around the town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 18:10:00" d="2020-04-21 18:21:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean is 'storked' by an unwelcome visitor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 18:21:00" d="2020-04-21 18:31:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean finds that tons of toads weigh loads and loads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 18:31:00" d="2020-04-21 18:45:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean is all at sea with the landed gentry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 18:45:00" d="2020-04-21 19:00:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr. Bean accidentally spills all of Mrs. Wicket’s new expensive perfume on the floor. In an attempt to hide his crime and refill the empty bottle he tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 19:00:00" d="2020-04-21 19:22:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>When our mystery solving gang is driving in Japan they are stopped by none-other than famous actor Mark Hamill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 19:22:00" d="2020-04-21 20:00:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>When the Mystery Inc. gang gets lost in the Pocono Mountains of Pennsylvania they stumble into Psychic University well off the beaten track</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 20:00:00" d="2020-04-21 20:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy's TV remote control is stolen by a partridge who collects high-tech objects in his nest perched high up in a tree. This is a case of absolute urgency!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 20:06:00" d="2020-04-21 20:12:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Whilst trying to stop the Lemmings from playing with a crate of firework rockets Grizzy is literally carried away with them when the largest specimen shoots off</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 20:12:00" d="2020-04-21 20:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% With their endless battles over the ranger's cabin, which they do not want to share, Grizzy and the Lemmings end up blowing the cabin up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 20:19:00" d="2020-04-21 20:25:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy gets rid of the Lemmings by crushing them with one of the ranger's heavy trunks, which he immediately clears out of the cabin, his enemies stuck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 20:25:00" d="2020-04-21 20:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% A strange object is delivered to the Ranger's cabin: an over-board! It's a latest generation skateboard which levitates above the ground without wheels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 20:32:00" d="2020-04-21 20:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings encounter a white bear which has drifted all the way to them on a chunk of ice which is slowly melting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 20:38:00" d="2020-04-21 20:50:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% After studying a magazine advertisement with a couple standing in front of an SUV, Grizzy imagines that if only he had a nice car, his favorite she-bear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 20:50:00" d="2020-04-21 21:00:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Super sees Luna struggling to nail her latest routines. He decides to discreetly use his superpowers to help her succeed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 21:00:00" d="2020-04-21 21:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends plan to go to the Wonder Fun park but Victor is ill. Envious of his healthy neighbour he plans on passing her his microbes and prevent her from going</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 21:07:00" d="2020-04-21 21:14:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola finds out that her mother used to be a mini-golf champion. She gathers all her mothers old golf clubs and decides to build a small golf course in the garden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 21:14:00" d="2020-04-21 21:20:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>After another twisted move from the Guanos the sausage truck breaks down in front of Lola’s house. The little girl is in charge of guarding the truck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 21:20:00" d="2020-04-21 21:27:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>It’s grooming day for Pat and he loves being pampered! Lola believes that Hoodie as well could benefit from some care</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 21:27:00" d="2020-04-21 21:33:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her parents left for a couple of hours and Pat is in charge of guarding the house. He even received a special training from Lola. Soon a weird</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 21:33:00" d="2020-04-21 21:40:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola organises a picnic in the park with her friends to test a new Virtual Reality game. She even invites Victor to join them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 21:40:00" d="2020-04-21 22:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola’s mother installed a Geocaching application on Lola’s phone. When Lola heads outside to play Victor decides to install the app to find the treasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 22:00:00" d="2020-04-21 22:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% On a very hot day an ice cream commercial awakes the desire of Grizzy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 22:06:00" d="2020-04-21 22:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have discovered a truly wild new game: an augmented reality program on the ranger's digital tablet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 22:13:00" d="2020-04-21 22:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The only edible food item left in the ranger's cabin is a gorgeous salmon which is stuck inside a block of ice at the back of the freezer compartment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 22:19:00" d="2020-04-21 22:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have unearthed a box filled with birthday fountains of light that spit forth giant bursts of sparks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 22:26:00" d="2020-04-21 22:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy's last jar of chocolate spread was pinched by the Lemmings, who are savoring it in secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 22:32:00" d="2020-04-21 22:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Wedged in his sofa to relieve his aching back Grizzy balks at getting up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 22:39:00" d="2020-04-21 23:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The vibrations created by Grizzy's snoring during his nap give the Lemmings an idea for a bouncing game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 23:00:00" d="2020-04-21 23:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Epic, the Queen asks Henri to compose a song to lift the spirits of her beloved subjects for this year’s Harvest Festival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 23:10:00" d="2020-04-21 23:21:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>As Henri and Bad Jack go head-to-head in a race to find an extremely rare treasure, Jimmy lies to Bjorn and then has to try to repair their friendship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 23:21:00" d="2020-04-21 23:31:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Heart of gold Henri and Jimmy host the bad Witch, who has been kicked out of her house by her sister Stinky Swamp Witch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-21 23:31:00" d="2020-04-22 00:00:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy and Cat discover Colbert never completed his officiant exam, he has to go on a &quot;field mission&quot; with Henri to keep his job</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 00:00:00" d="2020-04-22 00:06:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Ms. M is being delivered a powerful dog robot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 00:06:00" d="2020-04-22 00:13:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M. is sleepwalking and Bentley wants to trick Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 00:13:00" d="2020-04-22 00:20:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy’s friends from the dump discover Mrs M manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 00:20:00" d="2020-04-22 00:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy learns Bentley how to appeal to Mrs M</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 00:26:00" d="2020-04-22 00:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M decides to raise a sensitive ostrich</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 00:33:00" d="2020-04-22 00:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley tries to make Taffy sneeze so that he is unmasked</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 00:39:00" d="2020-04-22 00:46:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Today everyone goes into Mrs M hot air balloon!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 00:46:00" d="2020-04-22 00:52:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Raccoons are now trendy pets !</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 00:52:00" d="2020-04-22 01:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Hector, Nestor's twin brother arrives at the Manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 01:00:00" d="2020-04-22 01:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% A strange new object figures prominently in the cabin: a big wall clock that resembles a Swiss cuckoo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 01:06:00" d="2020-04-22 01:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Woken with a start by a nightmare filled with Lemmings Grizzy stumbles on the Ranger's dream machine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 01:13:00" d="2020-04-22 01:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy happens onto an old American India medallion bearing the symbol of the wind. He who wears it has the power to command air streams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 01:19:00" d="2020-04-22 01:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings inherit a crate that fell off a Canadian army convoy. Inside a case emits a sort of laser beam that divides objects into multiple miniaturized</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 01:26:00" d="2020-04-22 01:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% A magic Amerindian top modifies the mental age of anyone who watches it spin. From now on, Grizzy has the mind of a 10-month old baby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 01:32:00" d="2020-04-22 01:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% A magic horn lands on the muzzle of a moose endowing it with grace and the ability to fly. It soars off leaving a rainbow-colored streak in its wake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 01:39:00" d="2020-04-22 01:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% While looking for the TV remote-control device Grizzy happens onto a box that can localize a bunch of keys thanks to its key ring which is equipped with a tracker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 01:45:00" d="2020-04-22 01:52:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have turned the cabin topsy-turvy and created an obstacle course to race through in a hamster ball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 01:52:00" d="2020-04-22 02:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings create a customized hang-glider using a supermarket shopping cart for the nacelle and a ventilator as an engine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 02:00:00" d="2020-04-22 02:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Today is vaccination day for Pat and the least to say is that he hates it! After many failed attempts at hiding he must face the harsh reality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 02:07:00" d="2020-04-22 02:14:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is in her garden taking pictures of Pat and Hoodie. But when the kitten who’s covered in black decides to go for a walk in the neighbourhood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 02:14:00" d="2020-04-22 02:20:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends plan to go to the Wonder Fun park but Victor is ill. Envious of his healthy neighbour he plans on passing her his microbes and prevent her from going</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 02:20:00" d="2020-04-22 02:27:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola finds out that her mother used to be a mini-golf champion. She gathers all her mothers old golf clubs and decides to build a small golf course in the garden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 02:27:00" d="2020-04-22 02:34:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>After another twisted move from the Guanos the sausage truck breaks down in front of Lola’s house. The little girl is in charge of guarding the truck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 02:34:00" d="2020-04-22 02:40:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>It’s grooming day for Pat and he loves being pampered! Lola believes that Hoodie as well could benefit from some care</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 02:40:00" d="2020-04-22 02:47:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her parents left for a couple of hours and Pat is in charge of guarding the house. He even received a special training from Lola. Soon a weird</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 02:47:00" d="2020-04-22 02:54:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola organises a picnic in the park with her friends to test a new Virtual Reality game. She even invites Victor to join them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 02:54:00" d="2020-04-22 03:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola’s mother installed a Geocaching application on Lola’s phone. When Lola heads outside to play Victor decides to install the app to find the treasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 03:00:00" d="2020-04-22 03:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy and Cat use science to help them win the school Sorcery Faire, their classmates think they’re masters of the Dark Arts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 03:10:00" d="2020-04-22 03:21:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>As Jimmy tells Cat and Bjorn about yet another cool day he had with Henri, his two friends sigh their own parents aren’t as cool</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 03:21:00" d="2020-04-22 03:31:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Henri is convinced that he wins his fights because he’s got a (ridiculous) ritual with a lucky charm. Wilfried steals it, which makes Henri completely lose his confidence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 03:31:00" d="2020-04-22 03:42:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Colbert catches Jimmy and the knights trading their assignments to get the mission worth the most victory points, Colbert assigns the knights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 03:42:00" d="2020-04-22 04:00:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When our trio lets success get to their heads, they boast about their team and inadvertently inspire the Cursed Forest Witch and Bad Jack to create their own deadly duo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 04:00:00" d="2020-04-22 04:06:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Ms. M is being delivered a powerful dog robot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 04:06:00" d="2020-04-22 04:13:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M. is sleepwalking and Bentley wants to trick Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 04:13:00" d="2020-04-22 04:20:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy’s friends from the dump discover Mrs M manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 04:20:00" d="2020-04-22 04:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy learns Bentley how to appeal to Mrs M</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 04:26:00" d="2020-04-22 04:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M decides to raise a sensitive ostrich</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 04:33:00" d="2020-04-22 04:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley tries to make Taffy sneeze so that he is unmasked</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 04:39:00" d="2020-04-22 04:46:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Today everyone goes into Mrs M hot air balloon!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 04:46:00" d="2020-04-22 04:52:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Raccoons are now trendy pets !</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 04:52:00" d="2020-04-22 05:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Hector, Nestor's twin brother arrives at the Manor</k>  </p>
</a>
