<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="140" t="2019-08-13 01:57:18"><p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 05:01:00" d="2019-08-19 05:08:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>When he brandishes an Indian scepter that the Lemmings brought home, Grizzy sees the Lemmings bow low before him and behave like servants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 05:08:00" d="2019-08-19 05:15:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy tries to impress the she-bear he's in love with by making a sculpture of her from a piece of wood. But the Lemmings gnaw at the</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 05:15:00" d="2019-08-19 05:25:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean, badgered by a strange pink animal, warms to the creature when it shows its true colours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 05:25:00" d="2019-08-19 05:35:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>When invited to dinner by Mr Bean, it’s probably best to take your own sandwiches</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 05:35:00" d="2019-08-19 05:45:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean makes it to the top of the ladder… and gets stuck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 05:45:00" d="2019-08-19 06:00:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean bites off more than he can chew when he attempts DIY dentistry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 06:00:00" d="2019-08-19 06:07:00"><n>Pink Panther and Pals - Elements</n>    <k>Pink Panther and pals Hoarse, Aardvark and Ant are up to their usual adventures. The coolest cat around, Pink Panther continues to run circles around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 06:07:00" d="2019-08-19 06:14:00"><n>Pink Panther and Pals - Elements</n>    <k>Pink Panther and pals Hoarse, Aardvark and Ant are up to their usual adventures. The coolest cat around, Pink Panther continues to run circles around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 06:14:00" d="2019-08-19 06:30:00"><n>Pink Panther and Pals - Elements</n>    <k>Pink Panther and pals Hoarse, Aardvark and Ant are up to their usual adventures. The coolest cat around, Pink Panther continues to run circles around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 06:30:00" d="2019-08-19 06:35:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Darkbat seeks vengeance against Blacque Jacque Shellacque</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 06:35:00" d="2019-08-19 06:40:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Police Officers Horace and Porky go undercover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 06:40:00" d="2019-08-19 06:45:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Porky falls in love with Petunia, queen of the land</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 06:45:00" d="2019-08-19 06:55:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Porky falls in love with Petunia, queen of the land</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 06:55:00" d="2019-08-19 07:00:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>When Super Happo catches a cold, his super sized sneezes threaten to reveal his secret heroidentity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 07:00:00" d="2019-08-19 07:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Freed by the thawing ice, a mysterious giant egg slides up to the front door of the log cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 07:06:00" d="2019-08-19 07:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>In order to seduce the she-bear he's infatuated with, Grizzy decides to take things in hand and slim down with the ranger's bodybuilding equipment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 07:13:00" d="2019-08-19 07:25:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>By chance, Grizzy discovers that the ranger's new robot vacuum cleaner also gives very pleasant back massages. But the Lemmings see the new gadget</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 07:25:00" d="2019-08-19 07:31:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom is put in charge of getting the manor's dog into showdog shape, unfortunately Jerry will try to sabotage him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 07:31:00" d="2019-08-19 07:38:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry are left with Aunt Loella, a kindly woman who accidentally mistakes them for a dog and cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 07:38:00" d="2019-08-19 07:50:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom is in charge of keeping a snobby cat, Prancy Van der Snoot, clean and out of trouble. Unfortunately, she has her eye on Jerry who leads her on a manic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 07:50:00" d="2019-08-19 07:56:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Ginger loves that Little Quacker visits her new birdbath. Unfortunately, Tom and Spike try their hardest to get him to move out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 07:56:00" d="2019-08-19 08:03:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Jerry's cousins come for a visit to the manor, but turn out to bring more trouble than they're worth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 08:03:00" d="2019-08-19 08:20:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Jerry uses Tom's fear of cucumbers to startle him at every turn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 08:20:00" d="2019-08-19 08:30:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean wants a smart phone but they’re too expensive especially when you can build your own!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 08:30:00" d="2019-08-19 08:45:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean has some unexpected guests who think he runs a hotel!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 08:45:00" d="2019-08-19 08:51:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>It's Christmas Eve. Some ghosts come to haunt Bentley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 08:51:00" d="2019-08-19 08:58:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>A freak accident leads Bentley and Taffy to switch bodies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 08:58:00" d="2019-08-19 09:15:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M discovers a new social network app for pet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 09:15:00" d="2019-08-19 09:36:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>To escape a snowstorm, the gang checks into a creepy, massive hotel run by a man very strict about the hotel rules established by his deceased mother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 09:36:00" d="2019-08-19 09:57:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>The gang tours an old Hollywood Studio, but they soon uncover a mystery concerning the ghost of a silent film comedy star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 09:57:00" d="2019-08-19 10:40:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>Fred lives out his childhood dream of being a stage magician as he and the gang go undercover at a private magic club being terrorized by a mutant Rabbit monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 10:40:00" d="2019-08-19 11:55:00"><n>Scooby-Doo! Curse of the Lake Monster</n>    <k>School is out and the familiar Scooby gang are looking to enjoy a long vacation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 11:55:00" d="2019-08-19 12:05:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>When Super Happo catches a cold, his super sized sneezes threaten to reveal his secret heroidentity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 12:05:00" d="2019-08-19 12:15:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean goes in search of wildlife, but he isn’t expecting to see anything prehistoric!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 12:15:00" d="2019-08-19 12:30:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean has to look after an injured Mrs Wicket, whose demands start to become a pain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 12:30:00" d="2019-08-19 12:36:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry must work together to prove Bog is overkill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 12:36:00" d="2019-08-19 12:43:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% After working hard to get Tom to drift off to sleep, Jerry heads for the coveted wedge of cheese in the kitchen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 12:43:00" d="2019-08-19 12:55:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Feeling bad for giving Tom’s precious blanky to Badwill, Jerry’s determined to get it back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 12:55:00" d="2019-08-19 13:01:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom gets a can of Cat Cop, a spray that creates a tiny cop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 13:01:00" d="2019-08-19 13:08:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Jerry, Tom and Spike need rescuing on their snowy vacation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 13:08:00" d="2019-08-19 13:25:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% When Tom finds Butch having a bath, he gives him the boot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 13:25:00" d="2019-08-19 13:32:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Scraggs a raccoon uses a cat disguise to enter Mrs M manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 13:32:00" d="2019-08-19 13:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy tries to get rid of Addie who knows he’s a raccoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 13:39:00" d="2019-08-19 13:46:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The pets help an unconscious Mrs M pass an inspection</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 13:46:00" d="2019-08-19 13:53:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M meets a handsome trillionnaire… allergic to dogs!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 13:53:00" d="2019-08-19 14:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The pets team up to recreate Mrs M's wedding video</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 14:00:00" d="2019-08-19 14:07:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley has a secret admirer…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 14:07:00" d="2019-08-19 14:14:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy gets scared as Mrs M tests him to discover his lineage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 14:14:00" d="2019-08-19 14:21:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Vacation's coming! But before the manor must be secured…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 14:21:00" d="2019-08-19 14:28:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy’s friends from the dump discover Mrs M manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 14:28:00" d="2019-08-19 14:35:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>It's Christmas Eve. Some ghosts come to haunt Bentley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 14:35:00" d="2019-08-19 14:42:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>A freak accident leads Bentley and Taffy to switch bodies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 14:42:00" d="2019-08-19 14:49:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M discovers a new social network app for pet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 14:49:00" d="2019-08-19 14:56:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>The entire mansion is on a kale diet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 14:56:00" d="2019-08-19 15:03:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley helps a cat burglar stealing Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 15:03:00" d="2019-08-19 15:10:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Driiing! Taffy lives the same day for ever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 15:10:00" d="2019-08-19 15:35:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy becomes a huge star on internet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 15:35:00" d="2019-08-19 15:45:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Striker is not having much luck getting other Happos to be goalie so he can practice awesome penalty shots. Until Super flies in and uses all his powers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 15:45:00" d="2019-08-19 15:55:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>When a vampire tick gets on Harold's butt, Bunnicula has to get it off of his butt before bad stuff goes down</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 15:55:00" d="2019-08-19 16:15:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>After a magical artifact combines Chester, Harold, and Bunnicula into one uberpet, they must find a way to unmesh themselves without Mina finding out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 16:15:00" d="2019-08-19 16:21:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>It's Christmas Eve. Some ghosts come to haunt Bentley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 16:21:00" d="2019-08-19 16:28:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>A freak accident leads Bentley and Taffy to switch bodies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 16:28:00" d="2019-08-19 16:40:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M discovers a new social network app for pet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 16:40:00" d="2019-08-19 16:50:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 3</n>    <k>59% Angelo Rules follows twelve-year-old Angelo as he tries to control his life by using funny schemes - with a little help from his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 16:50:00" d="2019-08-19 17:10:00"><n u="Angelo Rules - Season">Angelo Rules - Season 3</n>    <k>59% Angelo Rules follows twelve-year-old Angelo as he tries to control his life by using funny schemes - with a little help from his friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 17:10:00" d="2019-08-19 17:15:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Daffy Duck crashes a music festival and wreaks havoc</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 17:15:00" d="2019-08-19 17:20:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Blacque Jacque Shellacque kidnaps Santa Clause</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 17:20:00" d="2019-08-19 17:25:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% The Mice have their juice stand destroyed by Yosemite Sam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 17:25:00" d="2019-08-19 17:35:00"><n>New Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>56% Bugs eats at Slugsworthy's gaudy restaurant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 17:35:00" d="2019-08-19 17:41:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Meathead has lost his marbles- really! Tom and Jerry visit the place where he last saw them, so he can compete in the marble championship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 17:41:00" d="2019-08-19 17:48:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Jerry goes out on a blind date set up by his cousin Muscles with a feisty girl mouse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 17:48:00" d="2019-08-19 18:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Little Quacker develops a rich operatic voice, and competes in a television pet contest, while Tom tries to make him stop singing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 18:00:00" d="2019-08-19 18:06:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Jerry impersonates a missing hamster, while Tom tries to hide her rapidly multiplying babies from Rick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 18:06:00" d="2019-08-19 18:13:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom is in charge of the manor's clay shooting machine, but Jerry and Tuffy interfere with the afternoon's events</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 18:13:00" d="2019-08-19 18:30:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Jerry's cousin Muscles tries to teach Tom and Spike his anger management tools to no avail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 18:30:00" d="2019-08-19 18:55:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>The gang goes to Salem, Massachusetts for the historical festival, only to discover a demon has been set loose on the town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 18:55:00" d="2019-08-19 19:25:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>Fred and the gang help with a mystery involving a figure from Fred's past. Fred discovers his old childhood friend has also arrived with her gang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 19:25:00" d="2019-08-19 19:35:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben, Gwen, and Max’s trip to Niagara Falls is cut short by the horrid Hydromanders – creatures menacing them and their fellow tourists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 19:35:00" d="2019-08-19 19:50:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>While chilling at a monastery with a no-noise policy, Ben can’t keep quiet and accidentally awakens a dangerous Dragon hidden in a secret chamber below the hallowed halls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 19:50:00" d="2019-08-19 20:01:00"><n>The Zoo</n>    <k>It’s the Zoo’s annual inspection day and evil-genius monkey Brutus hatches an explosive plan to get Jürgen kicked out of the zoo, forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 20:01:00" d="2019-08-19 20:20:00"><n>The Zoo</n>    <k>A mystery illness leaves Topaz the kangaroo without a hop. Gorilla Jürgen also comes down with ‘attention-seeker-itis’ and wants treatment too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 20:20:00" d="2019-08-19 20:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>It's Christmas Eve. Some ghosts come to haunt Bentley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 20:26:00" d="2019-08-19 20:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>A freak accident leads Bentley and Taffy to switch bodies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 20:33:00" d="2019-08-19 20:50:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M discovers a new social network app for pet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 20:50:00" d="2019-08-19 20:56:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings throw a surprise birthday party for one of the clan. When &quot;Happy Birthday&quot; rings out, the &quot;surpriiiiiise&quot; is as great for Grizzy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 20:56:00" d="2019-08-19 21:03:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy finds communicating vessels. If he sticks his hand in one, it comes out the other, regardless of the distance between them. This should satisfy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 21:03:00" d="2019-08-19 21:15:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>A gust of wind sweeps away the flower that Grizzy's adored she-bear wears in her hair. Grizzy sees this as a golden opportunity to dazzle her by bringing it back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 21:15:00" d="2019-08-19 21:21:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy finds a vintage stopwatch in the garage which lets you wind back the minute that has just passed by and it can even stop time and movement in one's surroundings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 21:21:00" d="2019-08-19 21:28:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy discovers with great delight that the ranger has purchased a brand new multi-function Stressless recliner. But the Lemmings transform</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 21:28:00" d="2019-08-19 21:40:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy is disturbed in the middle of his TV-snack by a flow of incongruous objects that have been transformed into hot-air balloons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 21:40:00" d="2019-08-19 21:50:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy and Cat discover Colbert never completed his officiant exam, he has to go on a &quot;field mission&quot; with Henri to keep his job</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 21:50:00" d="2019-08-19 22:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Cat’s morale is low about ever becoming a knight, Henri tries to save her with a song and inadvertently sends her on a dangerous solo quest into the dark lands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 22:10:00" d="2019-08-19 22:20:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Henri offers to help Jimmy win the school talent show, he mentors his son in the “Zen of mandolin.” But one of the judges of the show turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 22:20:00" d="2019-08-19 22:40:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy makes a bargain with Bad Jack’s family-outcast brother Jeff, he gets Bad Jack banished from the kingdom. But Jeff turns out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 22:40:00" d="2019-08-19 22:47:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is thrilled, she just won the first prize in a contest, and will get the visit of her favourite star! Unfortunately, there’s a minor problem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 22:47:00" d="2019-08-19 22:53:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>To play an April fool’s trick on Lola, Victor makes her believe that he has seen Hoodie in the subway, whereas in fact, Hoodie is actually locked in his room</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 22:53:00" d="2019-08-19 23:05:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>The huge tree in the park is set to be cut down to make room for a new parking lot. Lola is outraged. They can't do this! It’s our special tree! With Victor's help, Lola decides to protest against the plan, while Pat forms an alliance with Tank and the Guanos to save the tree. But they have to use all their ingeniousness to outsmart the work-proud construction worker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 23:05:00" d="2019-08-19 23:12:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>While playing with Pat and Hoodie, Lola hears beautiful bird song. She looks in her dad’s ornithology book and finds out the bird is actually a parrot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 23:12:00" d="2019-08-19 23:19:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Bubbely encounters difficulties in his pond – the oxygen supply is running low</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 23:19:00" d="2019-08-19 23:30:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola wants to take part in an animal photography contest organized by the museum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 23:30:00" d="2019-08-19 23:39:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean has a bad hair day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 23:39:00" d="2019-08-19 23:55:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Bean’s pursuit of a quiet life ends in a major row</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-19 23:55:00" d="2019-08-20 00:05:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean discovers being in hospital isn't always a bed of roses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 00:05:00" d="2019-08-20 00:20:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean has to replace his landlady’s cat after an unfortunate ‘accident’</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 00:20:00" d="2019-08-20 00:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy's TV remote control is stolen by a partridge who collects high-tech objects in his nest perched high up in a tree. This is a case of absolute urgency!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 00:26:00" d="2019-08-20 00:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy has got it into his head to offer a butterfly to the she bear he's in love with. But the Lemmings fight with him over the rare specimens he's spotted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 00:32:00" d="2019-08-20 00:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings have discovered an addictive new game based on the astonishing bouncing properties of the ranger's new running shoes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 00:38:00" d="2019-08-20 00:44:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy babysits for the she-bear he has a crush on. There's no question of Grizzy tripping up, for he has no intention of taking any risks! But he hadn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 00:44:00" d="2019-08-20 00:50:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Unwilling to share the food both he and the Lemmings are wild about, Grizzy locks it up inside the ranger's brand new and apparently burglar proof safe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 00:50:00" d="2019-08-20 00:55:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>Party’s boom box has run out of power so without any music he turns his attention to Star’srunning machine. Fiddling with the controls causes maximum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 00:55:00" d="2019-08-20 01:05:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy and Cat find a witch’s broom, they can’t resist taking it for a spin. But the fun quickly ends when their joyride inflames the rage of every</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 01:05:00" d="2019-08-20 01:20:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Epic, the Queen asks Henri to compose a song to lift the spirits of her beloved subjects for this year’s Harvest Festival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 01:20:00" d="2019-08-20 01:30:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>As Henri and Bad Jack go head-to-head in a race to find an extremely rare treasure, Jimmy lies to Bjorn and then has to try to repair their friendship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 01:30:00" d="2019-08-20 01:40:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Heart of gold Henri and Jimmy host the bad Witch, who has been kicked out of her house by her sister Stinky Swamp Witch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 01:40:00" d="2019-08-20 01:47:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Tonight, Lola and Pat are taking part in a huge flash mob event. They have rehearsed extensively and everything is set. Except that in the meantime Hoodie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 01:47:00" d="2019-08-20 01:54:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends are supposed to watch a performance at Moon Circus, but unfortunately they miss it. No worries. Lola decides to put</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 01:54:00" d="2019-08-20 02:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>At the end of their tether with their sworn enemy Pat, the Guanos decide to do away with him. With a little help from their bird friends, they decide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 02:00:00" d="2019-08-20 02:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola enrolls Pat on a dog firefighter training program. But Victor is convinced that Tank is made for the job. An impromptu contest is held composed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 02:07:00" d="2019-08-20 02:13:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Victor tests his new remote-controlled car in the park with Lola and the dogs. But he loses control over the car, and Tank is carried away by the car and hits his owner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 02:13:00" d="2019-08-20 02:25:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola receives an invitation from the museum to attend the premiere of an exhibition about extinct species with one of her friends. She invites Victor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 02:25:00" d="2019-08-20 02:31:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy builds a look-alike robot to keep the Lemmings away while he prepares a party for his beloved she-bear. But his double's artificial intelligence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 02:31:00" d="2019-08-20 02:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>When she is accidentally hit over the head, the she-bear Grizzy's in love with thinks she's a Lemming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 02:38:00" d="2019-08-20 02:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>When a meteorite falls not far from the log cabin, strange berries start to grow. One of their properties is that they make anyone who</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 02:45:00" d="2019-08-20 02:51:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Under the wood floor of the log cabin, Grizzy and the Lemmings discover the entrance to an underground gallery with an old treasure card that indicates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 02:51:00" d="2019-08-20 02:58:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>When he brandishes an Indian scepter that the Lemmings brought home, Grizzy sees the Lemmings bow low before him and behave like servants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 02:58:00" d="2019-08-20 03:05:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy tries to impress the she-bear he's in love with by making a sculpture of her from a piece of wood. But the Lemmings gnaw at the</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 03:05:00" d="2019-08-20 03:15:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy and Cat discover Colbert never completed his officiant exam, he has to go on a &quot;field mission&quot; with Henri to keep his job</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 03:15:00" d="2019-08-20 03:25:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Cat’s morale is low about ever becoming a knight, Henri tries to save her with a song and inadvertently sends her on a dangerous solo quest into the dark lands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 03:25:00" d="2019-08-20 03:35:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Henri offers to help Jimmy win the school talent show, he mentors his son in the “Zen of mandolin.” But one of the judges of the show turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 03:35:00" d="2019-08-20 03:50:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy makes a bargain with Bad Jack’s family-outcast brother Jeff, he gets Bad Jack banished from the kingdom. But Jeff turns out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 03:50:00" d="2019-08-20 03:57:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is thrilled, she just won the first prize in a contest, and will get the visit of her favourite star! Unfortunately, there’s a minor problem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 03:57:00" d="2019-08-20 04:04:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>The huge tree in the park is set to be cut down to make room for a new parking lot. Lola is outraged. They can't do this! It’s our special tree! With Victor's help, Lola decides to protest against the plan, while Pat forms an alliance with Tank and the Guanos to save the tree. But they have to use all their ingeniousness to outsmart the work-proud construction worker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 04:04:00" d="2019-08-20 04:10:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>To play an April fool’s trick on Lola, Victor makes her believe that he has seen Hoodie in the subway, whereas in fact, Hoodie is actually locked in his room</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 04:10:00" d="2019-08-20 04:17:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>While playing with Pat and Hoodie, Lola hears beautiful bird song. She looks in her dad’s ornithology book and finds out the bird is actually a parrot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 04:17:00" d="2019-08-20 04:24:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola wants to take part in an animal photography contest organized by the museum</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 04:24:00" d="2019-08-20 04:35:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Bubbely encounters difficulties in his pond – the oxygen supply is running low</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 04:35:00" d="2019-08-20 04:41:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>The Lemmings throw a surprise birthday party for one of the clan. When &quot;Happy Birthday&quot; rings out, the &quot;surpriiiiiise&quot; is as great for Grizzy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 04:41:00" d="2019-08-20 04:48:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>A gust of wind sweeps away the flower that Grizzy's adored she-bear wears in her hair. Grizzy sees this as a golden opportunity to dazzle her by bringing it back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 04:48:00" d="2019-08-20 04:55:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy finds communicating vessels. If he sticks his hand in one, it comes out the other, regardless of the distance between them. This should satisfy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2019-08-20 04:55:00" d="2019-08-20 05:01:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>Grizzy finds a vintage stopwatch in the garage which lets you wind back the minute that has just passed by and it can even stop time and movement in one's surroundings</k>  </p>
</a>
