<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="135" t="2020-04-15 04:27:40"><p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 05:00:00" d="2020-04-22 05:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% A strange new object figures prominently in the cabin: a big wall clock that resembles a Swiss cuckoo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 05:06:00" d="2020-04-22 05:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Woken with a start by a nightmare filled with Lemmings Grizzy stumbles on the Ranger's dream machine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 05:13:00" d="2020-04-22 05:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy happens onto an old American India medallion bearing the symbol of the wind. He who wears it has the power to command air streams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 05:19:00" d="2020-04-22 05:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings inherit a crate that fell off a Canadian army convoy. Inside a case emits a sort of laser beam that divides objects into multiple miniaturized</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 05:26:00" d="2020-04-22 05:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% A magic Amerindian top modifies the mental age of anyone who watches it spin. From now on, Grizzy has the mind of a 10-month old baby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 05:32:00" d="2020-04-22 05:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% A magic horn lands on the muzzle of a moose endowing it with grace and the ability to fly. It soars off leaving a rainbow-colored streak in its wake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 05:39:00" d="2020-04-22 05:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% While looking for the TV remote-control device Grizzy happens onto a box that can localize a bunch of keys thanks to its key ring which is equipped with a tracker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 05:45:00" d="2020-04-22 05:52:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have turned the cabin topsy-turvy and created an obstacle course to race through in a hamster ball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 05:52:00" d="2020-04-22 06:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings create a customized hang-glider using a supermarket shopping cart for the nacelle and a ventilator as an engine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 06:00:00" d="2020-04-22 06:09:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Jerry and Tuffy are getting ready to go to a family reunion./ Tom and Jerry are hired by a bad magician to find out where his Pidgeon friend disappeared to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 06:09:00" d="2020-04-22 06:19:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Jerry and Tuffy are getting ready to go to a family reunion./ Tom and Jerry are hired by a bad magician to find out where his Pidgeon friend disappeared to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 06:19:00" d="2020-04-22 06:29:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Tom and Butch compete for the Golden Fez and chance to be top cat./Hildie and Beatie commemorate the passing of their Mother and Tom tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 06:29:00" d="2020-04-22 06:39:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Tom and Butch compete for the Golden Fez and chance to be top cat./Hildie and Beatie commemorate the passing of their Mother and Tom tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 06:39:00" d="2020-04-22 07:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Trouble ensues when Tom is separated from his own shadow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 07:00:00" d="2020-04-22 07:10:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean redecorates his room, making it fit for a Queen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 07:10:00" d="2020-04-22 07:21:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean gets green eyes and green fingers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 07:21:00" d="2020-04-22 07:31:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean becomes smitten with a beautiful singer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 07:31:00" d="2020-04-22 07:45:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean meets a soul mate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 07:45:00" d="2020-04-22 08:00:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean is on his way to the seaside when the mini runs out of petrol</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 08:00:00" d="2020-04-22 08:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy discovers the ranger's collection of bird calls by chance. With a simple blow of the whistle, he can attract a flock of partridges that are at his beck and call</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 08:06:00" d="2020-04-22 08:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings notice that Grizzy moves away from the jar of chocolate spread whenever he chases the fly buzzing around him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 08:13:00" d="2020-04-22 08:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% A magic tomahawk divides Grizzy into two identical bears with diametrically opposite personalities, one short-tempered, the other super-sweet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 08:19:00" d="2020-04-22 08:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy finds a magician's hat that tosses out objects stored inside beforehand with the tap of a magic wand. He decides to impress his beloved she-bear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 08:26:00" d="2020-04-22 08:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% A newly unpacked UV tanning booth holds the place of honor in the middle of the cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 08:32:00" d="2020-04-22 08:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy wants to try out the brand new packaging format of chocolate spread that he discovers in the ranger's cupboard, a yummy-looking XXL jar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 08:38:00" d="2020-04-22 08:50:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy and the Lemmings discover the joys of photography with the ranger's instant print camera</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 08:50:00" d="2020-04-22 09:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have found an Amerindian eagle amulet that endows he who wears it with the powers of a bird of prey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 09:00:00" d="2020-04-22 10:25:00"><n>Big Top Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>The gang travel to Atlantic City. They go undercover at a circus when a werewolf haunts the area</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 10:25:00" d="2020-04-22 11:00:00"><n>Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!</n>    <k>The gang is honored to take part in the wedding of two close friends. But can Shaggy and Daphne, save their friend’s perfect day from a tragic Ghost Bride?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 11:00:00" d="2020-04-22 11:22:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>Shaggy and Scooby take the gang to meet their good friend actor and comedian Kenan Thompson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 11:22:00" d="2020-04-22 12:00:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>When Daphne gets a call from her good friend singer-songwriter Sia the gang finds themselves in a mystery involving an evil demon ghost</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 12:00:00" d="2020-04-22 12:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>When the Rust Bucket runs out of gas on a foggy East Coast road Ben Gwen and Max are forced to stay at hotel being menaced by Creepy Carl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 12:10:00" d="2020-04-22 12:20:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben is attacked by Dr. Animo mutants. When they realize the faux mini-golf village they are at isn’t an actual town, Ben must stop them before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 12:20:00" d="2020-04-22 12:31:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben, Gwen and Max make a return to Max's alma-mater but this time it's no homecoming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 12:31:00" d="2020-04-22 12:50:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>When Max drags the kids to see a defunct House of the Future built by his childhood idol Ben discovers Steam Smythe is busy searching for a powerful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 12:50:00" d="2020-04-22 13:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>When a cavity forces Ben to the dentist his day gets even worse when the malevolent magician Hex uses a nearby dream catcher to bring our hero's fears to life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 13:00:00" d="2020-04-22 13:09:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Jerry and Tuffy are getting ready to go to a family reunion./ Tom and Jerry are hired by a bad magician to find out where his Pidgeon friend disappeared to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 13:09:00" d="2020-04-22 13:19:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Jerry and Tuffy are getting ready to go to a family reunion./ Tom and Jerry are hired by a bad magician to find out where his Pidgeon friend disappeared to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 13:19:00" d="2020-04-22 13:29:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Tom and Butch compete for the Golden Fez and chance to be top cat./Hildie and Beatie commemorate the passing of their Mother and Tom tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 13:29:00" d="2020-04-22 13:39:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Tom and Butch compete for the Golden Fez and chance to be top cat./Hildie and Beatie commemorate the passing of their Mother and Tom tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 13:39:00" d="2020-04-22 14:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Trouble ensues when Tom is separated from his own shadow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 14:00:00" d="2020-04-22 14:10:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean runs rings around the town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 14:10:00" d="2020-04-22 14:21:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean is 'storked' by an unwelcome visitor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 14:21:00" d="2020-04-22 14:31:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean finds that tons of toads weigh loads and loads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 14:31:00" d="2020-04-22 14:45:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean is all at sea with the landed gentry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 14:45:00" d="2020-04-22 15:00:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr. Bean accidentally spills all of Mrs. Wicket’s new expensive perfume on the floor. In an attempt to hide his crime and refill the empty bottle he tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 15:00:00" d="2020-04-22 15:10:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Overhearing Granny on the phone say she's expecting a baby, Baby Bugs goes into overdrive, revving up the Baby Looney Tunes to prepare to care for an infant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 15:10:00" d="2020-04-22 15:20:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Baby Bugs tries to realise his dream of traveling to the moon while the Baby Looney Tunes are on a space museum visit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 15:20:00" d="2020-04-22 15:31:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Granny takes the Baby Looney Tunes back to a simpler lifestyle during a rustic weekend spent in an 1800's log cabin, where they learn to enjoy life minus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 15:31:00" d="2020-04-22 15:45:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% The Baby Looney Tunes first Halloween involves a costume contest, group trick-or-treating and Sylvester overcoming his fear of confronting a scary neighbour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 15:45:00" d="2020-04-22 16:00:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Bugs and Lola temporarily decide that they don't want to be friends any longer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 16:00:00" d="2020-04-22 16:10:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>After Chester feeds mixed vegetable juices to Bunnicula to get him to clean the house, the results are so amazing that the cat keeps on feeding the juice to the rabbit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 16:10:00" d="2020-04-22 16:19:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>When tiny troll has its sights set on eating Mina and Becky for dinner, Bunnicula must save the day! There’s just one problem: he’s never been invited</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 16:19:00" d="2020-04-22 16:29:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Bunnicula drains an old yam and turns invisible</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 16:29:00" d="2020-04-22 16:45:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Chester's determined to find a way to explain what, exactly, Bunnicula is… with science!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 16:45:00" d="2020-04-22 17:00:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>The pets encounter a strange creature on a camping trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 17:00:00" d="2020-04-22 17:09:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Tom stars in a documentary that mischaracterises his daily activities./ Dr. Bigby latest invention transports Tom and Jerry to Paris where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 17:09:00" d="2020-04-22 17:19:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Tom stars in a documentary that mischaracterises his daily activities./ Dr. Bigby latest invention transports Tom and Jerry to Paris where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 17:19:00" d="2020-04-22 17:29:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Rick and Ginger are going on a vacation and bringing Tom and Spike aboard the plane./Rick and Ginger sneak Tom and Spike into a hotel where pets are not allowed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 17:29:00" d="2020-04-22 17:39:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show - Elements</n>    <k>68% Rick and Ginger are going on a vacation and bringing Tom and Spike aboard the plane./Rick and Ginger sneak Tom and Spike into a hotel where pets are not allowed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 17:39:00" d="2020-04-22 18:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Jerry leads an accident-prone scouting troop earning badges and creating mayhem for Tom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 18:00:00" d="2020-04-22 18:10:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean redecorates his room, making it fit for a Queen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 18:10:00" d="2020-04-22 18:21:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean gets green eyes and green fingers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 18:21:00" d="2020-04-22 18:31:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean becomes smitten with a beautiful singer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 18:31:00" d="2020-04-22 18:45:00"><n>Mr Bean: The Animated Series - Elements</n>    <k>Mr Bean meets a soul mate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 18:45:00" d="2020-04-22 19:00:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean is on his way to the seaside when the mini runs out of petrol</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 19:00:00" d="2020-04-22 19:22:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>Scooby and Shaggy love hanging out with their very best eating buddy Barry Allen/The Flash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 19:22:00" d="2020-04-22 20:00:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>When Scooby and the gang come to Gotham City to visit Alfred Pennyworth they stumble into a dangerous mystery!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 20:00:00" d="2020-04-22 20:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have discovered a truly wild new game: an augmented reality program on the ranger's digital tablet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 20:06:00" d="2020-04-22 20:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% While chasing the Lemmings, Grizzy crashes into an arcade cabinet near the supermarket which displays a model fortuneteller and her crystal ball</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 20:13:00" d="2020-04-22 20:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have turned the entire cabin topsy-turvy to organize medieval jousts with the ranger's fencing gear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 20:19:00" d="2020-04-22 20:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy finds a bottle containing a love potion, anyone who drinks it immediately falls in love with the first creature he sees</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 20:26:00" d="2020-04-22 20:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Before taking a nap, Grizzy locks the food in a cupboard to prevent the Lemmings from getting into it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 20:32:00" d="2020-04-22 20:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% When Grizzy and the Lemmings accidentally activate a magic disk representing the earth, they are sent back in time to the prehistoric era</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 20:39:00" d="2020-04-22 20:50:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy finds a birthday pinata in the ranger's living room. The idea of bursting open a papier-mâché statue with a bat like it says in the instructions pleases him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 20:50:00" d="2020-04-22 21:00:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>With Doc’s help Star blows an enormous liquid bubble which absorbs both her and Bellataking them on a rip-roaring roller-coaster ride across the enclosure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 21:00:00" d="2020-04-22 21:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and Pat are in the garden digging the ground pretending to be archaeologists. Victor mocks their game: he shall become an astronaut and fly in space!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 21:07:00" d="2020-04-22 21:14:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>It’s Pat’s birthday Lola decides to offer him a huge balloon which she customised in his honour. But Hoodie makes the balloon fly away through the window</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 21:14:00" d="2020-04-22 21:20:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola picks up a bird who slammed into the bay window. But it seems like it’s one of the Guanos determined to take full advantage of the comfort of the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 21:20:00" d="2020-04-22 21:26:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola Lucie and Hugo are in the middle of a Pirates of the Caribbean remake. Pat is taking his role as a sea pirate very seriously</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 21:26:00" d="2020-04-22 21:34:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is playing ball with a friend when the ball falls in Victor’s garden. Pat goes next door to retrieve the ball but Tank wouldn’t just let him go</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 21:34:00" d="2020-04-22 21:40:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>While on a hike in the mountains Lola discovers a bird imprisoned within an ice cube. The three rebellious pigeons are convinced this is a prehistoric Guano</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 21:40:00" d="2020-04-22 22:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and Lucy decide to spend the night in the tent. Pat helps the girls set the tent and is in charge of guarding it but soon terrifying shadows appear in the night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 22:00:00" d="2020-04-22 22:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy finds a birthday pinata in the ranger's living room. The idea of bursting open a papier-mâché statue with a bat like it says in the instructions pleases him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 22:06:00" d="2020-04-22 22:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Inside a mysterious cave Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a magical Game of the Goose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 22:13:00" d="2020-04-22 22:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy is bothered by an object stuck in between the sofa cushions: a big fur lemming puppet glove</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 22:19:00" d="2020-04-22 22:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy discovers the leftovers of a Halloween party in the ranger's cabin which was entirely redecorated for the occasion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 22:26:00" d="2020-04-22 22:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy wants to give the she-bear he's in love with a plastic ring which he finds really swell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 22:32:00" d="2020-04-22 22:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy finds a strange figurine with the power to switch the spirits of two living beings and finds himself imprisoned in the body of a caribou</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 22:39:00" d="2020-04-22 23:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% While salmon fishing on the riverbank Grizzy hauls in an unusual catch: an old hand mirror straight out of a fairytale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 23:00:00" d="2020-04-22 23:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Cat’s morale is low about ever becoming a knight, Henri tries to save her with a song and inadvertently sends her on a dangerous solo quest into the dark lands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 23:10:00" d="2020-04-22 23:21:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Henri offers to help Jimmy win the school talent show, he mentors his son in the “Zen of mandolin.” But one of the judges of the show turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 23:21:00" d="2020-04-22 23:31:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy makes a bargain with Bad Jack’s family-outcast brother Jeff, he gets Bad Jack banished from the kingdom. But Jeff turns out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-22 23:31:00" d="2020-04-23 00:00:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy enables the Witch of the Cursed Forest to kidnap the Queen, Wilfried becomes the regent’s realm. Wilfried immediately decrees foolish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 00:00:00" d="2020-04-23 00:06:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Addie turns into a clumsy and terrifying monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 00:06:00" d="2020-04-23 00:13:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Addie wants to find the best acolyte for a special mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 00:13:00" d="2020-04-23 00:20:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley and Taffy go through a mirror…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 00:20:00" d="2020-04-23 00:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>A rebel raccoon moves into the back yard at Mrs M Manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 00:26:00" d="2020-04-23 00:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley and Taffy discover a magic lamp with a genius</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 00:33:00" d="2020-04-23 00:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy is called to get rid of mice in the Manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 00:39:00" d="2020-04-23 00:46:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M welcomes a new resident, an adorable little pony</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 00:46:00" d="2020-04-23 00:52:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley has a 'squeakophobia'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 00:52:00" d="2020-04-23 01:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M decides to clone his adorable Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 01:00:00" d="2020-04-23 01:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings scribble all over the book Snow White on the living room sofa. Grizzy throws them off with scant ceremony and they crash to the floor with their book</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 01:06:00" d="2020-04-23 01:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy and the Lemmings' favorite chocolate spread brand is organizing a big competition where the prize is a giant jar of spread</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 01:13:00" d="2020-04-23 01:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Freed from the ice which had preserved him for millions of years a saber-toothed bear bursts into the cabin starving to death</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 01:19:00" d="2020-04-23 01:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings discover a top-secret Canadian Army prototype that allows you to pass through solid surfaces for a window of several seconds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 01:26:00" d="2020-04-23 01:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings have found an Amerindian eagle amulet that endows he who wears it with the powers of a bird of prey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 01:32:00" d="2020-04-23 01:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings are having a blast with the ranger's electric guitar and the cabin walls tremble with their experimental rock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 01:39:00" d="2020-04-23 01:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% To finally be on an equal footing with Grizzy's imposing build and throw their own weight around in the cabin the Lemmings decide to wear a blowup sumotori costume</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 01:45:00" d="2020-04-23 01:52:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% Grizzy and the Lemmings discover an ancient Amerindian table with the power to show you past events</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 01:52:00" d="2020-04-23 02:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>65% The Lemmings discover an old book of magic spells with a formula that enables one to take on the appearance of any other creature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 02:00:00" d="2020-04-23 02:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and Pat are in the garden digging the ground pretending to be archaeologists. Victor mocks their game: he shall become an astronaut and fly in space!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 02:07:00" d="2020-04-23 02:14:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>It’s Pat’s birthday Lola decides to offer him a huge balloon which she customised in his honour. But Hoodie makes the balloon fly away through the window</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 02:14:00" d="2020-04-23 02:20:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola picks up a bird who slammed into the bay window. But it seems like it’s one of the Guanos determined to take full advantage of the comfort of the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 02:20:00" d="2020-04-23 02:26:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola Lucie and Hugo are in the middle of a Pirates of the Caribbean remake. Pat is taking his role as a sea pirate very seriously</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 02:26:00" d="2020-04-23 02:34:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is playing ball with a friend when the ball falls in Victor’s garden. Pat goes next door to retrieve the ball but Tank wouldn’t just let him go</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 02:34:00" d="2020-04-23 02:40:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>While on a hike in the mountains Lola discovers a bird imprisoned within an ice cube. The three rebellious pigeons are convinced this is a prehistoric Guano</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 02:40:00" d="2020-04-23 02:47:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and Lucy decide to spend the night in the tent. Pat helps the girls set the tent and is in charge of guarding it but soon terrifying shadows appear in the night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 02:47:00" d="2020-04-23 02:53:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola has to keep a little puppy for the day but he turns out to be a real fury. Pat will have to do everything in his power to keep him from turning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 02:53:00" d="2020-04-23 03:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola agrees on pet-sitting the goldfish belonging to Honorine her former neighbor. Of course the Guanos have set their sights on the poor creature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 03:00:00" d="2020-04-23 03:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy complains that Henri treats him like a baby, Henri lets him do “grownup” things for himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 03:10:00" d="2020-04-23 03:21:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Jimmy, Cat and Henri have to organise a fake kidnapping of Lance by Bjorn, in order to retrieve Lance’s smart-mirror, which contains films of Cat, Henri</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 03:21:00" d="2020-04-23 03:31:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Jimmy squires for the Red Knight, and his insistence on showing Red he’s a great squire causes Red to get captured by the Black Sorcerer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 03:31:00" d="2020-04-23 03:42:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy loses Torpedo in a bet with Lance, Lance trades Henri’s horse to the Black Rats. It’s not a good time, as Henri has to deliver a peace agreement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 03:42:00" d="2020-04-23 04:00:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Cat and Cynthia bicker in class, Lady Fontaine assigns them as partners who have to make a gown together for the upcoming fashion show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 04:00:00" d="2020-04-23 04:06:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Addie turns into a clumsy and terrifying monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 04:06:00" d="2020-04-23 04:13:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Addie wants to find the best acolyte for a special mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 04:13:00" d="2020-04-23 04:20:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley and Taffy go through a mirror…</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 04:20:00" d="2020-04-23 04:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>A rebel raccoon moves into the back yard at Mrs M Manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 04:26:00" d="2020-04-23 04:33:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley and Taffy discover a magic lamp with a genius</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 04:33:00" d="2020-04-23 04:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy is called to get rid of mice in the Manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 04:39:00" d="2020-04-23 04:46:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M welcomes a new resident, an adorable little pony</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 04:46:00" d="2020-04-23 04:52:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley has a 'squeakophobia'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-04-23 04:52:00" d="2020-04-23 05:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M decides to clone his adorable Taffy</k>  </p>
</a>
