<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="138" t="2021-07-09 06:34:49"><p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 05:00:00" d="2021-07-14 05:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Cute Or Boot
Mrs. M comes home from the club all aflutter. Her ladies who lunch are all raving about the new social network app that allows everyone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 05:05:00" d="2021-07-14 05:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>License to Kale
Mrs. Muchmore is in good shape but still wants to improve her health. Binikos immediately puts the entire mansion on kale diet. Taffy goes crazyy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 05:10:00" d="2021-07-14 05:20:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Cat Burglar
Bentley learns about a cat burglar in the neighborhood. That night, Bentley lures the cat burglar into the mansion and tries to help him steal Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 05:20:00" d="2021-07-14 05:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Racoon's Day
Driiing ! The beautiful sound of the alarm clock awakes Taffy for another beautiful day in the beautiful and comfy Muchmore Manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 05:25:00" d="2021-07-14 05:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Logging Off
Taffy becomes a real star on internet! Everybody thinks he is a real cute lolcat. Bentley gets angry and jealous. But, maybe internet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 05:30:00" d="2021-07-14 05:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Smell of the Chase
Bentley comes up with a fool-proof way to get rid of Taffy: he'll order a bottle of caviar eau online, then simply pour a trail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 05:40:00" d="2021-07-14 05:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Showtime
Mrs. M is feeling quite inferior. All her friends' cats have won so many awards at cat shows. She's got to win a trophy! So she registers Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 05:45:00" d="2021-07-14 05:50:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Old Home Reek
After inhaling a huge gourmet feast, Taffy feels nostalgia for his former home - the dump. He goes back to throw a party, where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 05:50:00" d="2021-07-14 06:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Factory Flaw
Mrs. Muchmore went against a counterfeit that she returned immediately. Bentley arranges for Taffy to be part of the trip and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 06:00:00" d="2021-07-14 06:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Poolwatch!
Magoo thinks that the whole neighborhood has been flooded when in fact he is just at the local swimming pool. He starts trying to rescue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 06:05:00" d="2021-07-14 06:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Hibernafizz
Magoo comes across Fizz encased in ice and thinks he has found a prehistoric man. He thaws him out and acts like a Cro-Magnon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 06:15:00" d="2021-07-14 06:30:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Fizz Tower
Thinking he’s hunting down a rat in his attic Magoo finds himself on the theme park devoted to…the glory of Fizz. He decides to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 06:30:00" d="2021-07-14 06:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Magoo in Shining Armor
Magoo on a construction site thinks he’s been hired for a medieval theater show. Fizz and Weasel bump into Magoo at</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 06:35:00" d="2021-07-14 06:45:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Space Hamster
In order to make himself an object of worship Fizz makes people believe he’s an alien coming to share his wisdom. Magoo mistakes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 06:45:00" d="2021-07-14 07:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Doctor Magoo
Magoo thinks he’s helping out at an understaffed veterinary clinic. In fact he’s at the supermarket where Fizz is trying to gain popularity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 07:00:00" d="2021-07-14 07:05:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Don't Cut the Cheese
It's that special time of year when the Lady of the House's rare, exotic (and very stinky) cheese gets delivered to the manor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 07:05:00" d="2021-07-14 07:10:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Calamari Jerry
Ginger leaves some frozen fish on the kitchen counter to thaw. Ginger and Rick warn Tom to keep his paws away, or he will not get anything to eat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 07:10:00" d="2021-07-14 07:25:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Cattyshack
It's time for the annual croquet tournament at the Manor. The butler tells Tom how important it is to the Lady of the Manor to always win…no matter what! The last thing they need is any pesky rodents interfering with the game. Knowing any sighting of Je</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 07:25:00" d="2021-07-14 07:30:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Drone Sweet Drone
Up to their usual antics, Tom, Jerry and Spike get into monkey business with a drone at Rick and Ginger's house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 07:30:00" d="2021-07-14 07:40:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Home Away from Home
Tom falls asleep inside a rolled-up carpet left out on the curb by Rick with a &quot;free&quot; sign attached. When the new owners unload their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 07:40:00" d="2021-07-14 07:45:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% From Riches to Rags
After a series of beatings from Tom, Jerry storms off into his mouse hole. Soon he falls asleep and dreams himself to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 07:45:00" d="2021-07-14 08:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Shrunk Docs
Safety standards at the Docs' Lab remain shockingly low. Once, just once, it would be nice to invent something that doesn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 08:00:00" d="2021-07-14 08:10:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Keyboard Capers
Determined to play the piano Mr Bean finds a tune in his heart and sausages for fingers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 08:10:00" d="2021-07-14 08:30:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% A Running Battle
Mr Bean runs rings around the town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 08:30:00" d="2021-07-14 08:40:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Egg and Bean
Mr Bean is 'storked' by an unwelcome visitor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 08:40:00" d="2021-07-14 09:00:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Hopping Mad!
Mr Bean finds that tons of toads weigh loads and loads</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 09:00:00" d="2021-07-14 09:30:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Me, Myself and A.I.
When an Artificial Intelligence takes over the building of a trendy tech company the Gang has to solve the computerised mystery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 09:30:00" d="2021-07-14 10:00:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Gremlin on a Plane
The gang has seats on the largest airplane ever to fly the open skies! Unfortunately the plane is also beset by a Gremlin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 10:00:00" d="2021-07-14 11:15:00"><n>Scooby-Doo!: Camp Scare</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Back-to-nature chills and thrills with Scooby-Doo's all-new original movie! Welcome to Camp Little Moose -- where the counselors are friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 11:15:00" d="2021-07-14 11:35:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Grand Scam
Shaggy takes the gang to the Minor League Baseball stadium of his youth only to learn that it's about to be shut down because a Ghostly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 11:35:00" d="2021-07-14 11:40:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show V (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% A Kick in the Butler
A Tom and Jerry chase through Postlewaite Manor results in major injuries to Cates which places his defense of the Butler's Linen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 11:40:00" d="2021-07-14 12:00:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show V (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Tom Thumblestein
Papa tells his fractured version of the Tom Thumb story to the Bavarian mouse trio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 12:00:00" d="2021-07-14 12:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (4)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Wallpapering Magoo
Magoo thinks that he is peeling off old wallpaper on Linda’s walls but he is actually destroying Fizz’ hypnotic posters In order</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 12:05:00" d="2021-07-14 12:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (3)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A Mountaineer Like No Other
Magoo has decided to go mountain climbing but in reality, he is climbing up a skyscraper! He mixes Fizz up with a wounded</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 12:15:00" d="2021-07-14 12:30:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Legs of Steel
Thinking he is in the middle of a work-out at his local gym Magoo inadvertently climbs onto a delivery boy’s bicycle. It just so happens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 12:30:00" d="2021-07-14 12:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A Recipe for Success
Magoo thinks Weasel has opened a restaurant and wants to help him improve it. He mistakes the FizzLab for a kitchen and prevents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 12:35:00" d="2021-07-14 12:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Honey Bear
Magoo thinks that he is on a camping trip but he is actually just in the city park. When he sees Weasel wearing a suit that allows him to stock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 12:40:00" d="2021-07-14 13:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Halloween Hold-up
Magoo is thinks is out trick-or-treating for Halloween. But he unwittingly robs a bank instead of Weasel. Fizz, whose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 13:00:00" d="2021-07-14 13:10:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% The Case of Porky's Pants / Fully Vetted
Porky Pig comes home in a panic and tells his roommate Daffy, that his pants are missing. Donning his fedora</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 13:10:00" d="2021-07-14 13:30:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% E-Rabbitcator / Marvin Flag Gag: Planet Split in 2 / The Sales Duck
After Elmer Fudd builds a robot to catch Bugs, the rabbit must outsmart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 13:30:00" d="2021-07-14 13:35:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% The Towering Hamsterno
It's up to Pepe and Claudette to stop the evil hamsters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 13:35:00" d="2021-07-14 13:40:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Viktor the Science Swede
TV Scientist Viktor is filming his science show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 13:40:00" d="2021-07-14 13:45:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Dorlock and the Disorient Express
Dorlock Holmes and Watkins are on The Orient Express</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 13:45:00" d="2021-07-14 14:00:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Regatta de Rabbit
Bugs Bunny and Cecil the Turtle battle it out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 14:00:00" d="2021-07-14 14:10:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Grand Invitation
Mr Bean is all at sea with the landed gentry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 14:10:00" d="2021-07-14 14:25:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% A Royal Makeover
Mr Bean redecorates his room making it fit for a Queen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 14:25:00" d="2021-07-14 14:40:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Super Marrow
Mr Bean gets green eyes and green fingers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 14:40:00" d="2021-07-14 15:00:00"><n u="Mr Bean: The Animated Series">Mr Bean: The Animated Series I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Bean in Love
Mr Bean becomes smitten with a beautiful singer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 15:00:00" d="2021-07-14 15:30:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Where There's a Will, There's a Wraith
It's a classic haunted house caper when a rich man, whose life Scooby once saved, writes Scooby into his will! Now, to collect his share of the fortune, the gang must spend a night in a creepy mansion along with the rich man's kooky relative: a spooky pha</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 15:30:00" d="2021-07-14 16:00:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Sorcerer Snacks Scare
Shaggy and Scooby discover their new favorite food as the gang investigates the mystery of a frightening Sorcerer that’s haunting a snack factory!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 16:00:00" d="2021-07-14 16:05:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Chew Toy
Tom is watching a hypnotist on TV, when the words &quot;you are asleep&quot; hit him hard. He becomes a virtual rag doll and ends up in a jumble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 16:05:00" d="2021-07-14 16:10:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Live and Let Diet
The Lady of the Manor's prize Pomeranian, Alfred, must get some pounds off before the big dog show. The butler suggests exercise—chasing a cat perhaps? Tom happily obliges, as Alfred's successful weight loss guarantees him a cushy spot upstairs. Meanwhi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 16:10:00" d="2021-07-14 16:25:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Auntie Social
When Rick and Ginger go to a couple's retreat, they leave Tom with Rick's Auntie Louella. Hearing that she's a whiz in the kitchen, Jerry comes along</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 16:25:00" d="2021-07-14 16:30:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% A Snootful
The Lady of the House's cousins, the Van der Snoots, visit with their prize-winning Persian cat, Prancy Van der Snoot. Tom is warned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 16:30:00" d="2021-07-14 16:40:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Lame Duck
Ginger and Rick have installed a new birdbath, and Little Quacker has taken up residence in it. Ginger forbids Tom from going</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 16:40:00" d="2021-07-14 16:46:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% It's All Relative
When Jerry's country cousins visit the Abbey, the cook is convinced Downton is in the midst of a vermin invasion! Cates (the butler)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 16:46:00" d="2021-07-14 16:47:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rock Concert
&quot;“Chasing Lamput” turns out to be the ultimate backstage pass; the Docs pursue the orange blob through the dressing room and directly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 16:47:00" d="2021-07-14 17:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Boss's Mom
Specs and Skinny get the day off from Lamput chasing, and receive a super important assignment: go to the train station, and pick up the Boss' beloved mom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 17:00:00" d="2021-07-14 17:10:00"><n u="Mush Mush And The Mushables">Mush Mush And The Mushables I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Snake Dance
When Mush-Mush and Chep lose Lilit's flying disc down a snake tunnel, he is confident he can get it back. All animals love Chep and no-one</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 17:10:00" d="2021-07-14 17:30:00"><n u="Mush Mush And The Mushables">Mush Mush And The Mushables I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Grasshopper Chep
All the Mushables have fun zooming down a long mudslide except Chep, who just can't get up the courage to do it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 17:30:00" d="2021-07-14 17:40:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Ransom
With Lola and Hoodie Pat goes to the vet to get his leg cast removed. But in the waiting room Hoodie accidentally releases a puppy from its cage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 17:40:00" d="2021-07-14 17:45:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Commander Sandy
Surfing the internet Lola finds a lamp her mother has been looking for. She now has to find an old toy to exchange</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 17:45:00" d="2021-07-14 18:00:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rescue Tank
When Victor goes away for the weekend Lola offers to petsit Tank even though she knows how Tank and her pets simply don't get on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 18:00:00" d="2021-07-14 18:10:00"><n u="Kingdom Force">Kingdom Force I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ground Breakin', Earth Shakin', No Fakin'
Luka is annoyed after Max Volume repeatedly cries wolf, but what happens when the threat is real and Max really does need help? Will Kingdom Force answer the call?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 18:10:00" d="2021-07-14 18:30:00"><n u="Kingdom Force">Kingdom Force I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Control Yourself
Max Volume hypnotizes the badger community to do his bidding, leaving no badger unaffected. ncluding TJ! Will Kingdom Force</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 18:30:00" d="2021-07-14 18:35:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Yummy Fly
The Lemmings notice that Grizzy moves away from the jar of chocolate spread whenever he chases the fly buzzing around him. But the insect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 18:35:00" d="2021-07-14 18:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Good Bear Bad Bear
A magic tomahawk divides Grizzy into two identical bears with diametrically opposite personalities: one short-tempered, the other super-sweet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 18:40:00" d="2021-07-14 19:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Hat Tricks
Grizzy finds a magician's hat that tosses out objects stored inside beforehand with the tap of a magic wand. He decides to impress his beloved</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 19:00:00" d="2021-07-14 19:10:00"><n u="Alice &amp; Lewis">Alice &amp; Lewis I (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Because I Said So!
Mom is super busy. So when Alice comes to her to ask if she can go out, she refuses. And when questioned, she responds: “Because I said so!” So Alice decides to go see Lewis instead. But the rabbit is refusing to leave his house, on the Queen’s orde</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 19:10:00" d="2021-07-14 19:30:00"><n u="Alice &amp; Lewis">Alice &amp; Lewis I (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dodson’s Egg
Dodson has been “couch-surfing” in Lewis’ living-room for a whole three days now: he needs to hatch his egg with lots of “tea, cookies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 19:30:00" d="2021-07-14 19:40:00"><n u="Baby Looney Tunes">Baby Looney Tunes I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% War of the Weirds
Marvin the Martian comes to visit and the babies learn to accept differences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 19:40:00" d="2021-07-14 20:00:00"><n u="Baby Looney Tunes">Baby Looney Tunes I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% The Harder They Fall
Baby Looney Tunes introduces the world's most beloved cartoon characters as precocious preschoolers, discovering the world one baby-step at a time!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 20:00:00" d="2021-07-14 20:10:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% The Case of Porky's Pants / Fully Vetted
Porky Pig comes home in a panic and tells his roommate Daffy, that his pants are missing. Donning his fedora</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 20:10:00" d="2021-07-14 20:30:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% E-Rabbitcator / Marvin Flag Gag: Planet Split in 2 / The Sales Duck
After Elmer Fudd builds a robot to catch Bugs, the rabbit must outsmart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 20:30:00" d="2021-07-14 20:35:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% The Towering Hamsterno
It's up to Pepe and Claudette to stop the evil hamsters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 20:35:00" d="2021-07-14 20:40:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Viktor the Science Swede
TV Scientist Viktor is filming his science show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 20:40:00" d="2021-07-14 20:45:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Dorlock and the Disorient Express
Dorlock Holmes and Watkins are on The Orient Express</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 20:45:00" d="2021-07-14 21:00:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Regatta de Rabbit
Bugs Bunny and Cecil the Turtle battle it out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 21:00:00" d="2021-07-14 21:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (160)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Rival
Ms. M is being delivered a powerful dog robot: Blaze. Very quickly, Bentley is overwhelmed by this super machine with zero defects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 21:05:00" d="2021-07-14 21:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (61)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mrs ZZZ
Mrs. M. starts sleepwalking all over the mansion. While Bentley's trying to wake up his mistress to reveal Taffy's secret, the racoon wants to keep Mrs M. asleep</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 21:10:00" d="2021-07-14 21:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (63)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>My Fair Puppy
When Bentley realizes that Madame Muchmore is totally in Taffy's spell, he decides to ask some seduction lessons to his rival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 21:25:00" d="2021-07-14 21:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (64)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rags To Ostriches
Mrs. Muchmore decides to raise a very rare, expensive ostrich for a feather competition. But by unfortunate chance, the ostrich</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 21:30:00" d="2021-07-14 21:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (165)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Big Sneeze
Lunch is served and Forsythe cracks some fresh ground pepper on Taffy's meal. Taffy inhales some pepper and sneezes the entire plate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 21:40:00" d="2021-07-14 21:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (166)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Flying High
Mrs. M has arranged to take the entire family hot air ballooning from her own backyard. Unfortunately, Bentley plans on releasing the balloon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 21:45:00" d="2021-07-14 22:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (167)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Return of Scraggs
A new fashion becoming all the rage in the Country Club. Farewell cats, say hello to raccoons, the best pets that exist! Mr. Fuffernin enthusiast asks to an afflicted Mrs Muchmore to organize a party in honor of these wild beasts . Bentley must review h</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 22:00:00" d="2021-07-14 22:05:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Countdown
Grizzy finds a vintage stopwatch in the garage which lets him wind back the minute that has just passed by, and can</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 22:05:00" d="2021-07-14 22:10:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lemming Airlines
Grizzy is disturbed in the middle of his TV-snack by a flow of strange objects that have been transformed into hot-air balloons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 22:10:00" d="2021-07-14 22:25:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Relax Bear
Grizzy discovers with great delight that the ranger has purchased a brand new multifunction Stressless recliner. But even an armchair designed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 22:25:00" d="2021-07-14 22:30:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Gliding
The Lemmings play kite-surf with a homemade kite. Grizzy notices that the she-bear he's in love with watches the kite perform arabesques</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 22:30:00" d="2021-07-14 22:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% The Sound of a Lemming
Grizzy snatches the last jar of chocolate spread out from under the noses of the Lemmings. In exchange, he offers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 22:40:00" d="2021-07-14 22:45:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear in the Wind
The Lemmings play a new game, floating like flags in the breeze from the fan which is set at maximum. Grizzy, who has decided to watch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 22:45:00" d="2021-07-14 23:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Construction Bear
The Lemmings have a grand old time tearing down their Kapla block buildings, which they rebuild just as fast. Grizzy remarks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 23:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Curse of the Pyramid
Magoo thinks that he is lost in a pyramid but he is in fact in a big conference room where Fizz is about to perform a stand-up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 23:05:00" d="2021-07-14 23:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Deep Sea Diving
Magoo thinks he’s underwater scooting and has discovered Atlantis. In fact he’s in New York riding Fizz’s latest invention:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 23:15:00" d="2021-07-14 23:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Shaaaaaark!
Magoo thinks he’s a beach lifeguard but is actually on an ice floe and the swimmers are penguins! When Fizz shows up in a submarine to kidnap</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 23:25:00" d="2021-07-14 23:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Magoo the Sorcerer
Fizz and Weasel are trying to steal the president’s jokebook. Magoo thinking he is visiting a museum of sorcery mistakes Weasel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 23:35:00" d="2021-07-14 23:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Concrete Jungle
Fizz has invented a machine which turns spoiled brats into perfect children. Weasel accidentally launches Fizz next to Magoo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-14 23:40:00" d="2021-07-15 00:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Letter to Santa Claus
Magoo forgets to include a gift for Mr Cat in his letter to Santa! Trying to make amends he follows Weasel disguised</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 00:00:00" d="2021-07-15 00:05:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (72)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Freddy's Blues
Mercury's clumsiness leads to his brother Freddy being locked in the safe in their den. Now Mercury has to break into the Mikkelsens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 00:05:00" d="2021-07-15 00:10:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (73)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Dognapped
The raccoons resort to kidnapping Iris in order to create a diversion so Freddy can rob the Mikkelsens' house. Back in the lair, Mercury</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 00:10:00" d="2021-07-15 00:25:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (74)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Fluffy the Fugitive
Mike rescues Fluffy from the raccoon's lair but he doesn't notice that the kitty has pocketed one the racoon's favourite toys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 00:25:00" d="2021-07-15 00:35:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (75)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% And then there were none
Mike is forced into action when the raccoons steal the turtles to help Freddy hold up his newly made throne. The crazy raccoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 00:35:00" d="2021-07-15 00:40:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (77)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% In The Doghouse
Mike is forced to spend the day outside in his doghouse due to Grandma Mikkelsen's fur allergy. Mike makes the best of being exiled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 00:40:00" d="2021-07-15 00:45:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (78)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Slippery When Wet
The Mikkelsen's house has been cleaned and the floor has been polished to a deep sheen. Mike has been told to keep his paws off it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 00:45:00" d="2021-07-15 01:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Reward
The Docs run out of puff and decide to cut some corners. All it takes is a sharpie, as it happens; just change a wanted poster to offer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 01:00:00" d="2021-07-15 01:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Logging Off
Taffy becomes a real star on internet! Everybody thinks he is a real cute lolcat. Bentley gets angry and jealous. But, maybe internet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 01:05:00" d="2021-07-15 01:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Smell Of The Chase
Bentley comes up with a fool-proof way to get rid of Taffy: he'll order a bottle of caviar eau online, then simply pour a trail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 01:10:00" d="2021-07-15 01:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Showtime
Mrs. M is feeling quite inferior. All her friends' cats have won so many awards at cat shows. She's got to win a trophy! So she registers Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 01:25:00" d="2021-07-15 01:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Old Home Reek
After inhaling a huge gourmet feast, Taffy feels nostalgia for his former home - the dump. He goes back to throw a party, where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 01:30:00" d="2021-07-15 01:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Factory Flaw
Mrs. Muchmore went against a counterfeit that she returned immediately. Bentley arranges for Taffy to be part of the trip and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 01:40:00" d="2021-07-15 01:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Robo House
Mrs. Muchmore has equipped her home with a defense system. During his sleep, Taffy and Bentley use it against each other, in an escalation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 01:45:00" d="2021-07-15 02:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Whisperer To A Scream
Forsythe, fed up with cleaning up all the Taffy-Bentley destruction, urges Mrs. M to bring in a &quot;pet whisperer&quot; to improve their behaviour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 02:00:00" d="2021-07-15 02:05:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Luck
Decidedly, this is not Grizzy's day: after making a fool of himself in front of the she-bear he's in love with, he is ousted from the log cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 02:05:00" d="2021-07-15 02:10:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Magnetic Bear
Grizzy can't believe his eyes when he sees objects moving all by themselves. When he realises it's the Lemmings who are playing around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 02:10:00" d="2021-07-15 02:20:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Charm
Further to a misunderstanding, Grizzy is persuaded that the she-bear he's in love with has been turned into a frog. While he looks through</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 02:20:00" d="2021-07-15 02:25:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear's Best Friend
Grizzy discovers a baby raccoon not far from the log cabin. When he sees its big, moist eyes, Grizzy melts and adopts the creature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 02:25:00" d="2021-07-15 02:30:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Super Grizzy Bros
By chance, Grizzy discovers the pleasures of video games on the ranger's console. The Lemmings want to try their hand at the joystick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 02:30:00" d="2021-07-15 02:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Fake Brothers
Grizzy builds a look-alike robot to keep the Lemmings away while he prepares a popcorn party for his beloved she-bear. But his double?s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 02:40:00" d="2021-07-15 02:45:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Mind in a Whirl
When she is accidentally hit over the head, Grizzy's beloved she-bear thinks she's a Lemming. Grizzy thinks that another little</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 02:45:00" d="2021-07-15 02:50:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% A Sizeable Problem
When a meteorite falls not far from the log cabin, strange berries start to grow. One of their properties is that they make any animal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 02:50:00" d="2021-07-15 03:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Treasure Bear
Under the wood floor of the log cabin, Grizzy and the Lemmings discover the entrance to an underground gallery with an old treasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 03:00:00" d="2021-07-15 03:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (67)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Gluttons for Punishment
Fizz and Weasel plan to enter Fizz’s revolutionary new condiment in an international culinary contest. Magoo mistakes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 03:05:00" d="2021-07-15 03:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (68)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Brain Washed
While helping Linda clean her attic Magoo gets shrunken and teleported into Fizz’s brain. Fizz himself had intended for his brain to become</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 03:15:00" d="2021-07-15 03:20:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (69)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>MAG007
Magoo takes Fizz for a toy containing top secret information which he steals from a secret agent (in reality Weasel). Hell-bent on destroying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 03:20:00" d="2021-07-15 03:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (70)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Maggie Magoo
A bear has escaped from the zoo and Fizz is hell-bent on making it his pet. Magoo mistakes the bear for his niece who’s come to spend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 03:25:00" d="2021-07-15 03:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (71)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Magoo's Best Friend
Magoo mistakes Fizz for his best friend Harry from school and thinks the two of them are visiting their old school. In fact they’ve</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 03:35:00" d="2021-07-15 03:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (72)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Welcome to Translovenia
Magoo thinks he’s on a trip to Translovenia and takes shelter in a mansion owned by a vampire. In reality this vampire is Weasel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 03:40:00" d="2021-07-15 03:50:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (73)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>7 Minutes Flat
Weasel tests out Fizz’s latest invention: a 3-piece swimsuit to make beachgoers look chic. Magoo mistakes him for the President</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 03:50:00" d="2021-07-15 04:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (74)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>MAG007 is back
Fizz writes a genius plan on a post-it that gets stuck to Magoo’s forehead. When Weasel tries to get it back Magoo thinks he’s being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 04:00:00" d="2021-07-15 04:05:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Robotix 3000
Mike's chess game with Iris is rudely interrupted by a loud commotion from the house. Fluffy has found the robotic vacuum and is riding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 04:05:00" d="2021-07-15 04:10:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Rancind Raccoons
Mercury is rummaging through the trash bin and digs out a piece of rotten, disgusting Camembert. He wolfs the rancid cheese down, turning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 04:10:00" d="2021-07-15 04:20:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Show Must Go On!
The turtles have a falling out and Aramis decides she's had enough and stalks off. The other two turtles realize that things aren't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 04:20:00" d="2021-07-15 04:25:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Main E-Vent
Things are mysteriously disappearing from the Mikkelsen's house and Mike can't seem to get to the bottom of it. The raccoons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 04:25:00" d="2021-07-15 04:30:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Mike The Eggspert
It's Easter, and Mike organizes a super special Easter egg hunt for Iris but the raccoons can't resist crashing the party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 04:30:00" d="2021-07-15 04:40:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Wahwahland
Mike decides to invite Iris over to dance so he can show off his moves. Unfortunately, the raccoons sabotage Mike's plans by breaking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 04:40:00" d="2021-07-15 04:45:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% It's Been A Slice
The Mikkelsens order a pizza for a post sports game dinner. It's the worst kind of torture for Mike. He can barely resist the delicious</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 04:45:00" d="2021-07-15 04:50:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (46)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Baritoon
The raccoons break into the Mikkelsens and Mercury stumbles upon a didgeridoo and he just can't get enough of it. It's so powerful that its music</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-15 04:50:00" d="2021-07-15 05:00:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (47)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Paws For Tought
Mike's owner buys him a pair of cute new shoes for his paws. Mike isn't pleased by the new footwear at all and they make some seriously</k>  </p>
</a>
