<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="138" t="2021-07-12 04:52:43"><p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 05:00:00" d="2021-07-19 05:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (57)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Caged
Forsythe has caught vermin on the property using a cage. Unfortunately for Taffy, the vermin are Mish and Mash! Forsythe entrusts Bentley to guard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 05:05:00" d="2021-07-19 05:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (158)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Scare Tactics
Overhearing Mrs. M's passion for ghosts and other supernatural things, Bentley at last hits on the perfect solution to get rid of Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 05:10:00" d="2021-07-19 05:20:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (59)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Petty Shack
Today it's the world's only golf tourney where the pets caddy for their owners. This year's grand prize is an all-expenses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 05:20:00" d="2021-07-19 05:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (160)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Rival
Ms. M is being delivered a powerful dog robot: Blaze. Very quickly, Bentley is overwhelmed by this super machine with zero defects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 05:25:00" d="2021-07-19 05:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (61)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mrs ZZZ
Mrs. M. starts sleepwalking all over the mansion. While Bentley's trying to wake up his mistress to reveal Taffy's secret, the racoon wants to keep Mrs M. asleep</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 05:30:00" d="2021-07-19 05:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (63)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>My Fair Puppy
When Bentley realizes that Madame Muchmore is totally in Taffy's spell, he decides to ask some seduction lessons to his rival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 05:40:00" d="2021-07-19 05:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (64)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Rags to Ostriches
Mrs. Muchmore decides to raise a very rare, expensive ostrich for a feather competition. But by unfortunate chance, the ostrich</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 05:45:00" d="2021-07-19 05:50:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (165)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Big Sneeze
Lunch is served and Forsythe cracks some fresh ground pepper on Taffy's meal. Taffy inhales some pepper and sneezes the entire plate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 05:50:00" d="2021-07-19 06:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (166)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Flying High
Mrs. M has arranged to take the entire family hot air ballooning from her own backyard. Unfortunately, Bentley plans on releasing the balloon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 06:00:00" d="2021-07-19 06:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (49)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Great Outdoors
In the forest Fizz and Weasel go in search of a legendary berry to make the best jam in the world. But Magoo out hiking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 06:05:00" d="2021-07-19 06:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Aerofizz!
Weasel tries for his AeroFizz pilot’s license again. Magoo throws a wrench in the works when convinced that he’s fixing his roof he pierces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 06:15:00" d="2021-07-19 06:30:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mountain Rescue
In the desert Fizz and Weasel plan a global fireworks display in Fizz’s honor. But Mountain Rescuer Magoo mistakes Weasel for a skier in distress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 06:30:00" d="2021-07-19 06:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Air Magoo
Run! Magoo’s going to miss his flight! Unfortunately he’s not at the airport but the supermarket precisely where Fizz and Weasel are hatching</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 06:35:00" d="2021-07-19 06:45:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (53)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Nanogamba Tribe
When Fizz and Weasel shoot an ad for their special new fragrance “Fizz Scent” Fizz falls into the sewers only to bump into Magoo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 06:45:00" d="2021-07-19 07:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (54)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Kung Fizz
Fizz and Weasel are after the president’s jokebook! But Magoo thinking he’s in his dojo enters the high-security unit where it’s kept</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 07:00:00" d="2021-07-19 07:05:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% You Are What You Eat
Rick and Ginger wake up late and, in their hurry, they accidentally put dog food in Tom's bowl and cat food in Spike's. This causes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 07:05:00" d="2021-07-19 07:10:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Not My Tyke
Spike orders Tom and Jerry to watch Tyke while he's away, but instead Tom takes the opportunity to chase Jerry in the backyard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 07:10:00" d="2021-07-19 07:25:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show V (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Tom Thumblestein
Papa tells his fractured version of the Tom Thumb story to the Bavarian mouse trio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 07:25:00" d="2021-07-19 07:30:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (37)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Everyone Into the Pool
When Tom and Jerry go to a pool party at Toodles's place, Tom shows off in the pool with ridiculous stunts. Butch and Meathead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 07:30:00" d="2021-07-19 07:40:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% A Head for Science
On the edge of the village of Catsylvania, Tom is carried off to Dr. Frankenstein's castle lab. Several lightning bolts later</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 07:40:00" d="2021-07-19 07:45:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (41)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Cat Cop
Ginger brings home an aerosol can of Rat Cop, rat and mouse repellent, to help Tom do his job. And it's not your typical rodent repellent! When the spray makes a human-shaped cop appear, it yells at Jerry and starts pursuit, along with Tom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 07:45:00" d="2021-07-19 08:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (40)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Wig
To escape the clutches of his dastardly pursuers, Lamput leaps onto Skinny's head and poses as a luscious mane of auburn hair. Shouldn't work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 08:00:00" d="2021-07-19 08:10:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Holiday Teddy
Mr Bean decides to take Teddy on holiday to the seaside. But when he arrives at his hotel a spoilt little girl wants Teddy all for herself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 08:10:00" d="2021-07-19 08:30:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% The Newspaper
Mr Bean is left in peace when Mrs Wicket goes off on her holidays. This means Mr Bean has free access to her daily newspaper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 08:30:00" d="2021-07-19 08:40:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Viral Bean
Mr Bean is trying to find a nice quiet place to read his book so he sets off for the Library. But instead of reading he becomes distracted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 08:40:00" d="2021-07-19 09:00:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Super Spy
Mr Bean is obsessed by his favourite TV hero ‘Super Spy’ and is excited when his very own Super-Spy spy kit arrives in the post</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 09:00:00" d="2021-07-19 09:30:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% El Bandito
The gang heads out to a Day of the Dead festival. There, they learn that the spirit of the old, legendary criminal, El Bandito, has returned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 09:30:00" d="2021-07-19 10:00:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Into the Mouth of Madcap
Daphne agrees to watch her friend’s kid Wayne and convinces Fred to take a night off from mysteries to go to the boardwalk amusement park</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 10:00:00" d="2021-07-19 11:20:00"><n>Scooby-Doo! Shaggy's Showdown</n><t>Q</t>    <k>66% Join Scooby-doo and the gang for a frightfully wacky ride in this all-new original movie as they visit the Crazy Q Dude Ranch. But before they can strap</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 11:20:00" d="2021-07-19 11:45:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% Sorcerer Snacks Scare
Shaggy and Scooby discover their new favorite food as the gang investigates the mystery of a frightening Sorcerer that’s haunting a snack factory!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 11:45:00" d="2021-07-19 12:00:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show V (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Pinata Yadda Yadda
Tom has trouble keeping track of a pinata full of stolen loot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 12:00:00" d="2021-07-19 12:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Toes in the Sand
Magoo thinks he is on a beach and that sailors are emptying their oil tanker right into the ocean. Wanting to put a stop to the pollution</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 12:05:00" d="2021-07-19 12:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (34)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dinosaur Island
Fizz has reduced the size of the moon in order to model it in his own image. But Magoo thinks it’s a dinosaur egg ready to hatch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 12:15:00" d="2021-07-19 12:30:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Santa's Little Helper
Magoo a Christmas volunteer in a supermarket thinks a burglar is entering overnight and decides to stop him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 12:30:00" d="2021-07-19 12:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>At the Heart of the Crater
Magoo thinks that he is at the foot of a volcano but in fact he’s next to a huge soup vat. And he sets it all awry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 12:35:00" d="2021-07-19 12:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lost in the Subway
Magoo thinks he is in the subway but actually he’s in a cave. Running into Weasel he thinks he’s lost and decides to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 12:40:00" d="2021-07-19 13:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Baby Steps
Magoo is babysitting the Neighbors' toddler. The baby flees and kidnaps Fizz mistaking him for a plush toy. Thinking he’s playing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 13:00:00" d="2021-07-19 13:10:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Pest Coaster / Rhino Ya Don't
When Bugs Bunny wants to take a ride on the roller coaster, Yosemite Sam, the carnie, claims he's too short to ride</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 13:10:00" d="2021-07-19 13:30:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Buzzard School / Marvin Flag Gag: Giant Alien Mouth / Wet Cement
Tasked with bringing home a nice juicy rabbit, Beaky Buzzard attempts to capture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 13:30:00" d="2021-07-19 13:35:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Fashion Viktor
Bugs seeks revenge on Viktor the male model</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 13:35:00" d="2021-07-19 13:40:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Sam the Roughrider
Roughrider Yosemite Sam seeks glory in battle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 13:40:00" d="2021-07-19 13:45:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Fool's Gold
Daffy Ducks decides to help out Red Omaha mine for gold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 13:45:00" d="2021-07-19 14:00:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Bonjour DarkBat
Darkbat seeks vengeance against Blacque Jacque Shellacque</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 14:00:00" d="2021-07-19 14:10:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Scout Bean
Mr Bean inadvertently causes an accident which prevents Irma taking the scout troop to Big Bear’s Scout Camp. With the scout master</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 14:10:00" d="2021-07-19 14:25:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (17)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Back To School
Mr Bean cannot find anywhere to park other than the space he spots in a school’s car park. There’s a case of mistaken identity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 14:25:00" d="2021-07-19 14:40:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Lord Bean
Mr Bean is in the library studying his family heritage. Someone brings to his attention Mr Bean’s resemblance to a certain Lord Bean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 14:40:00" d="2021-07-19 15:00:00"><n u="The Mr. Bean Animated Series">The Mr. Bean Animated Series II (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>68% Car Wars
Mr Bean and his beloved car find themselves in a crash for crash battle with his arch nemesis the Reliant Robin. It’s a contest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 15:00:00" d="2021-07-19 15:30:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% The Norse Case. 
The gang goes on a camping trip, although they can't really agree on why. Fred's desire for the gang to get in touch with their natural</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 15:30:00" d="2021-07-19 16:00:00"><n u="Be Cool, Scooby-Doo!">Be Cool, Scooby-Doo! I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>65% The People vs. Fred Jones
Fred is on trial, convicted of being the real mastermind behind all the mysteries he's solved. With the help of his defence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 16:00:00" d="2021-07-19 16:05:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (38)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Double Dog Trouble
Spike the bulldog comes to Tom and Jerry, complaining he is being harassed by unknown creditors, ex-girlfriends, and other problems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 16:05:00" d="2021-07-19 16:10:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (42)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Hockey Jockeys
Jerry and Tuffy discover Ginger's surprise for Rick in the garage: a brand-new air hockey table. They enjoy floating in zero gravity before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 16:10:00" d="2021-07-19 16:25:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (43)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Dis-Repair Man
When Tom and Jerry break a picture frame on the wall, Rick gives Tom an ultimatum that he's out for good if he breaks one more thing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 16:25:00" d="2021-07-19 16:30:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (39)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Hyde and Shriek
A fast-talking sales cat named Dr. Jake L. appears to Tom from a trap door in the floor, selling &quot;Ache-Eee Bones&quot; tonic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 16:30:00" d="2021-07-19 16:40:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (48)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% Perfume Party
Hoping to woo Toodles, Tom decides to make some homemade perfume for her. He throws in many unusual ingredients and gets a surprisingly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 16:40:00" d="2021-07-19 16:45:00"><n u="The Tom and Jerry Show">The Tom and Jerry Show III (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>71% The Royal Treatment
When Jerry overhears that a brand-new butler will arrive at the household later that day, the crafty mouse whips together a butler's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 16:45:00" d="2021-07-19 16:50:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Thief In The Museum
The orange blob is down at the Museum, nerding out about ancient Egypt, when the Docs show up and ruin Lamput’s day. Darn science geeks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 16:50:00" d="2021-07-19 17:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Evolution
Lamput spends the day at the beach, and, in a pair of swimming trunks, cuts a fine figure indeed. That is to say; a small, round and blobby figure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 17:00:00" d="2021-07-19 17:10:00"><n u="Mush Mush And The Mushables">Mush Mush And The Mushables I (1)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Save the Fun Tree
Mush-Mush and friends &quot;favourite play tree&quot; the Fun Tree - is rotten and doomed. But Mush-Mush refuses to give up on it. In a last ditch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 17:10:00" d="2021-07-19 17:30:00"><n u="Mush Mush And The Mushables">Mush Mush And The Mushables I (2)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Stuck in the Mud
When Fung and Miff spoil Mush-Mush's fun tunnel surprise he has been working on for ages, he wishes their day was ruined too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 17:30:00" d="2021-07-19 17:40:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (50)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>All Fired Up
Lola enrolls Pat on a dog firefighter training program. But Victor is convinced that Tank is made for the job. An impromptu contest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 17:40:00" d="2021-07-19 17:45:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (51)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Good Dog
Victor tests his new remote-controlled car in the park in the company of Lola and the dogs. But he loses control over the car, and Tank</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 17:45:00" d="2021-07-19 18:00:00"><n u="Pat the Dog">Pat the Dog I (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>A Day at the Museum
Lola receives an invitation from the museum to attend the premiere of an exhibition about extinct species with one of her friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 18:00:00" d="2021-07-19 18:10:00"><n u="Kingdom Force">Kingdom Force I (44)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Outfoxed
Envie Fernandez has her eyes on King Cat's crown, and only Sprocket can keep her from getting it. Can she do it without the team?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 18:10:00" d="2021-07-19 18:30:00"><n u="Kingdom Force">Kingdom Force I (45)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Burden of Tooth
Max Volume's shooting his latest music video, and it's a wild one - so wild that there's an actual tornado wreaking havoc in the Forest Kingdom! Can Kingdom Force shut down production before Max's 'Rocknado' tears the forest apart?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 18:30:00" d="2021-07-19 18:35:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Wild Zapping
Grizzy and the Lemmings clumsily destroy the TV remote control while fighting over who gets to watch his favorite program. While looking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 18:35:00" d="2021-07-19 18:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Warning: Unlimited Lemmings
The Lemmings discover that by changing the speed limit sign on the side of the road, they can accelerate truck traffic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 18:40:00" d="2021-07-19 19:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings II (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bouncing Bear
While trying to stop the Lemmings from playing their extreme trampoline game, Grizzy slips on the canvas and unwittingly executes an amazing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 19:00:00" d="2021-07-19 19:10:00"><n u="Alice &amp; Lewis">Alice &amp; Lewis I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ahahaha!
Feeling in a jokey mood, Alice catches up with Lewis while he’s paying a visit to the Book-Wizard. Unfortunately, the latter doesn’t appreciate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 19:10:00" d="2021-07-19 19:30:00"><n u="Alice &amp; Lewis">Alice &amp; Lewis I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Too Full For School
Alice has to learn a bunch of math for a school test. She pays a visit to Lewis, hoping he might be able to help her. But his method</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 19:30:00" d="2021-07-19 19:40:00"><n u="Baby Looney Tunes">Baby Looney Tunes I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% The Magic of Spring
Baby Looney Tunes introduces the world's most beloved cartoon characters as precocious preschoolers, discovering the world one baby-step at a time!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 19:40:00" d="2021-07-19 20:00:00"><n u="Baby Looney Tunes">Baby Looney Tunes I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>60% For Whom the Toll Calls
Baby Looney Tunes introduces the world's most beloved cartoon characters as precocious preschoolers, discovering the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 20:00:00" d="2021-07-19 20:10:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (5)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Pest Coaster / Rhino Ya Don't
When Bugs Bunny wants to take a ride on the roller coaster, Yosemite Sam, the carnie, claims he's too short to ride</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 20:10:00" d="2021-07-19 20:30:00"><n u="Looney Tunes Cartoons">Looney Tunes Cartoons I (6)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>78% Buzzard School / Marvin Flag Gag: Giant Alien Mouth / Wet Cement
Tasked with bringing home a nice juicy rabbit, Beaky Buzzard attempts to capture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 20:30:00" d="2021-07-19 20:35:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Fashion Viktor
Bugs seeks revenge on Viktor the male model</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 20:35:00" d="2021-07-19 20:40:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Sam the Roughrider
Roughrider Yosemite Sam seeks glory in battle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 20:40:00" d="2021-07-19 20:45:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Fool's Gold
Daffy Ducks decides to help out Red Omaha mine for gold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 20:45:00" d="2021-07-19 21:00:00"><n u="New Looney Tunes">New Looney Tunes III (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>57% Bonjour DarkBat
Darkbat seeks vengeance against Blacque Jacque Shellacque</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 21:00:00" d="2021-07-19 21:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (18)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Showtime
Mrs. M is feeling quite inferior. All her friends' cats have won so many awards at cat shows. She's got to win a trophy! So she registers Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 21:05:00" d="2021-07-19 21:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (19)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Old Home Reek
After inhaling a huge gourmet feast, Taffy feels nostalgia for his former home - the dump. He goes back to throw a party, where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 21:10:00" d="2021-07-19 21:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (20)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Factory Flaw
Mrs. Muchmore went against a counterfeit that she returned immediately. Bentley arranges for Taffy to be part of the trip and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 21:25:00" d="2021-07-19 21:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (21)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Robo House
Mrs. Muchmore has equipped her home with a defense system. During his sleep, Taffy and Bentley use it against each other, in an escalation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 21:30:00" d="2021-07-19 21:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (22)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Whisperer to a Scream
Forsythe, fed up with cleaning up all the Taffy-Bentley destruction, urges Mrs. M to bring in a &quot;pet whisperer&quot; to improve their behaviour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 21:40:00" d="2021-07-19 21:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (23)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Bentley Of The Jungle
Bentley gets a huge bang on his head and when he wakes up. Doesn't know who he is anymore! After thinking of another sneaky trap</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 21:45:00" d="2021-07-19 22:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (24)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Out Of The Woods
Mrs. M takes the family to a beautiful retreat in a pristine forest -- but they soon find themselves lost in the woods. When all their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 22:00:00" d="2021-07-19 22:05:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (69)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Shaken-Up Bear
The vibrations created by Grizzy's snoring during his nap give the Lemmings an idea for a bouncing game. But when Grizzy changes positions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 22:05:00" d="2021-07-19 22:10:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (70)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Pinata Party
Grizzy finds a birthday pinata in the ranger's living room. The idea of bursting open a papier-mâché statue with a bat like</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 22:10:00" d="2021-07-19 22:25:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (71)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Game
Inside a mysterious cave, Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a magical Game of the Goose. The events displayed in the squares that the players</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 22:25:00" d="2021-07-19 22:30:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (72)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Ranger Lemming
Grizzy is bothered by an object stuck in between the sofa cushions: a big fur lemming puppet glove. He puts his hand inside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 22:30:00" d="2021-07-19 22:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (73)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Halloween Bear
Grizzy discovers the leftovers of a Halloween party in the ranger's cabin, which was entirely redecorated for the occasion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 22:40:00" d="2021-07-19 22:45:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (74)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Clean Bear
Grizzy wants to give the she-bear he's in love with a plastic ring which he finds really swell. But since the object was found in the trash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 22:45:00" d="2021-07-19 23:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (75)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Wandering Spirits
Grizzy finds a strange American Indian figurine with the power to switch the spirits of two living beings and finds himself imprisoned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 23:00:00" d="2021-07-19 23:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (71)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Magoo's Best Friend
Magoo mistakes Fizz for his best friend Harry from school and thinks the two of them are visiting their old school. In fact they’ve</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 23:05:00" d="2021-07-19 23:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (72)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Welcome to Translovenia
Magoo thinks he’s on a trip to Translovenia and takes shelter in a mansion owned by a vampire. In reality this vampire is Weasel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 23:15:00" d="2021-07-19 23:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (73)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>7 Minutes Flat
Weasel tests out Fizz’s latest invention: a 3-piece swimsuit to make beachgoers look chic. Magoo mistakes him for the President</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 23:25:00" d="2021-07-19 23:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (74)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>MAG007 is back
Fizz writes a genius plan on a post-it that gets stuck to Magoo’s forehead. When Weasel tries to get it back Magoo thinks he’s being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 23:35:00" d="2021-07-19 23:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (75)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Family Meal
Fizz wants to cure Magoo’s near-sightedness for good. He and Weasel go over to his house only to be taken for Magoo’s parents on a surprise visit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-19 23:40:00" d="2021-07-20 00:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (76)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Free the Rabbit!
As Fizz gets ready to travel to another dimension populated entirely by other Fizzes Magoo turns up and thinks that Weasel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 00:00:00" d="2021-07-20 00:05:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Boing Boing
A kids' trampoline gives Mike the chance to amaze Iris and show off his acrobatic moves. But the raccoons are determined to sneak</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 00:05:00" d="2021-07-20 00:10:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Invitation
Mike's over the moon. Iris has invited him over for the cup of tea on her terrace. He's been waiting for this moment for weeks. But between</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 00:10:00" d="2021-07-20 00:25:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (27)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Fluffystein
While Mike is distracted by flirting with Iris, the raccoons sneak into the house and begin mixing up a foul concoction in the kitchen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 00:25:00" d="2021-07-20 00:35:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (28)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Muscle Mike
If only Mike were a little bit more muscular, Iris would definitely look at him in a new light. At least that's what he tells himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 00:35:00" d="2021-07-20 00:40:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Photobombed!
Louise snaps a photo of Mike while they play a game together. The only problem is that Mike looks absolutely ridiculous in it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 00:40:00" d="2021-07-20 00:48:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (30)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% The Garden Games
The turtles organize a sports contest and whoever wins gets a special trophy. Iris volunteers a reluctant Mike to take part in the games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 00:48:00" d="2021-07-20 00:50:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Meet The Shrink
The Docs are so obsessed with catching Lamput that even in their dreams, the chase goes on. It’s really not a restful sleep</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 00:50:00" d="2021-07-20 01:00:00"><n u="Lamput">Lamput III (16)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Invisible Necklace
You never can tell when inspiration’s gonna strike. Specs and Skinny are having a nice evening at the theatre, enjoying a magic show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 01:00:00" d="2021-07-20 01:05:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (151)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Jitter Fever
The town is gripped by the fear of jitter fever, a nasty malady that affects house pets. The only way to cure it is to send the affected</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 01:05:00" d="2021-07-20 01:10:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (52)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Recall
Mrs. M gets an alarming notice in the mail: there's been a recall of fancy cat bows, which look a lot like the one Taffy wears</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 01:10:00" d="2021-07-20 01:25:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (53)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>New Leaf Taffy
Taffy has a near-death experience, where a raccoon tells him he has to turn his life around, and be kind to Bentley in every</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 01:25:00" d="2021-07-20 01:30:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (54)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The New Mrs M
During a particularly epic chase, Taffy and Bentley collide with Mrs. Muchmore. She suddenly looses her mind and adores raccoons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 01:30:00" d="2021-07-20 01:40:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (55)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Upgrade
Taffy orders a new bow. But not just any bow: this is the Extra-Strength Non-Tear Accept-No-Substitutes Guaranteed-Unsnatchable Maxwell Deluxe 3000! When it arrives, Taffy gleefully puts it on and throws the old one away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 01:40:00" d="2021-07-20 01:45:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (156)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Honey I Shrunk the Raccoon
It's Spring Cleaning day and everyone is throwing out old useless junk. Suddenly, Taffy and Bentley have shrunk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 01:45:00" d="2021-07-20 02:00:00"><n u="Taffy">Taffy I (57)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Caged
Forsythe has caught vermin on the property using a cage. Unfortunately for Taffy, the vermin are Mish and Mash! Forsythe entrusts Bentley to guard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 02:00:00" d="2021-07-20 02:05:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (65)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lemmings Under Pressure
The only edible food item left in the ranger's cabin is a gorgeous salmon. which is stuck inside a block of ice at</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 02:05:00" d="2021-07-20 02:10:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (66)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Lemmings in Space
The Lemmings have unearthed a box filled with birthday fountains of light that spit forth giant bursts of sparks. They have a blast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 02:10:00" d="2021-07-20 02:20:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (67)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Sniffer Sniffler Raccoon
Grizzy's last jar of chocolate spread was pinched by the Lemmings, who are savoring it in secret. To localize the Lemmings'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 02:20:00" d="2021-07-20 02:25:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (68)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Transformational Bear
Wedged in his sofa to relieve his aching back, Grizzy balks at getting up. He designs clever strategies to do everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 02:25:00" d="2021-07-20 02:30:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (69)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Shaken-Up Bear
The vibrations created by Grizzy's snoring during his nap give the Lemmings an idea for a bouncing game. But when Grizzy changes positions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 02:30:00" d="2021-07-20 02:40:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (70)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Pinata Party
Grizzy finds a birthday pinata in the ranger's living room. The idea of bursting open a papier-mâché statue with a bat like</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 02:40:00" d="2021-07-20 02:45:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (71)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Bear Game
Inside a mysterious cave, Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a magical Game of the Goose. The events displayed in the squares that the players</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 02:45:00" d="2021-07-20 02:50:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (72)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Ranger Lemming
Grizzy is bothered by an object stuck in between the sofa cushions: a big fur lemming puppet glove. He puts his hand inside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 02:50:00" d="2021-07-20 03:00:00"><n u="Grizzy and the Lemmings">Grizzy and the Lemmings I (73)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>67% Halloween Bear
Grizzy discovers the leftovers of a Halloween party in the ranger's cabin, which was entirely redecorated for the occasion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 03:00:00" d="2021-07-20 03:05:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (33)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Lost in the Subway
Magoo thinks he is in the subway but actually he’s in a cave. Running into Weasel he thinks he’s lost and decides to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 03:05:00" d="2021-07-20 03:15:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (25)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Baby Steps
Magoo is babysitting the Neighbors' toddler. The baby flees and kidnaps Fizz mistaking him for a plush toy. Thinking he’s playing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 03:15:00" d="2021-07-20 03:20:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (36)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>The Golden Fizz
Fizz plans on replacing the statue from an Oscar-like award's ceremony, with a statue in his effigy. But Magoo grabs it, thinking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 03:20:00" d="2021-07-20 03:25:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (35)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Saving the Gnomes of Astroturf
Magoo mistakes some kids at the park for gnomes in a magic forest. Fizz uses a remote to immobilize them to win over their parents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 03:25:00" d="2021-07-20 03:35:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (31)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Dusk of the Cucumber
Fizz invents a cucumber that turns whoever is holding it into an object of human worship. When Magoo sees hypnotized passers-by being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 03:35:00" d="2021-07-20 03:40:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (32)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Spinning Headlock Elbow Drop
Magoo thinks that he is auditioning for a circus troop but he is actually in a professional wrestling ring in the middle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 03:40:00" d="2021-07-20 03:45:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (29)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Mega Magoo vs Dr. Fizz
Fizz controlling a robot distributes free ice cream to everyone in the city. When Magoo mistakes him for a destructive monster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 03:45:00" d="2021-07-20 04:00:00"><n u="Mr Magoo">Mr Magoo I (26)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>Ghost Hunt
Fizz has invented a machine which stops toast from landing butter-side down. Magoo paying his neighbor a visit sees some floating toast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 04:00:00" d="2021-07-20 04:05:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (7)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Chickie's Return
Mike's worst nightmare comes true when Louise digs out her old toy Chikie from her trunk. Chikie is a horrifying squeaky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 04:05:00" d="2021-07-20 04:10:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (8)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Feline A Little Racoon
Mike's yoga session is rudely interrupted when Fluffy comes to annoy him. Mike pushes him away and Fluffy ends up landing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 04:10:00" d="2021-07-20 04:20:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (9)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Electric Turtles
The turtles are struck by lightning during a storm, turning them into positively charged projectiles zapping everything they touch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 04:20:00" d="2021-07-20 04:25:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (10)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Rescuing Roxanne
Playing with Louise and her doll gives Mike an idea. He decides to stage a rescue mission with the doll from the roof of the Mikkelson's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 04:25:00" d="2021-07-20 04:30:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (11)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% A Sick Trick
The racoons watch Mike enviously as he makes himself comfortable in his living room. If only they could get a piece of that sweet action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 04:30:00" d="2021-07-20 04:40:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (12)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Aye Aye Aye Phone
Laura leaves her cell phone at home and Mike discovers a hilarious video of Fluffy on it that he absolutely has to show Iris</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 04:40:00" d="2021-07-20 04:45:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (13)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Agent 000
Wanting to impress Iris, Mike slips his bowtie on and does his best James Bond impression. What a stud! Meanwhile the turtles are using</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 04:45:00" d="2021-07-20 04:50:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (14)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% What A Circus
Mike tries to brighten Iris's day by putting together an impromptu circus on the patio. Mike plays ringmaster as Fluffy pretends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2021-07-20 04:50:00" d="2021-07-20 05:00:00"><n u="Mighty Mike">Mighty Mike I (15)</n><t>Q</t>    <k>81% Double Dog
When Stephan brings a new robot into the house that looks exactly like Mike - he gets an idea. He can use the robot as his stunt double</k>  </p>
</a>
