<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="133" t="2020-05-17 04:29:09"><p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 05:00:00" d="2020-05-24 05:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% When they find an old book on traditional Japanese origami, the Lemmings churn out paper birds to play gliding games</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 05:06:00" d="2020-05-24 05:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings are all lined up on the couch to watch a cartoon film where a mouse plays nasty tricks on a cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 05:13:00" d="2020-05-24 05:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Once again Grizzy shows the Lemmings that they just don't measure up to him physically and that the last jar of chocolate spread is for the strongest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 05:19:00" d="2020-05-24 05:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings lay their hands on a full crate of chocolate spread which they hide somewhere behind Grizzy's back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 05:26:00" d="2020-05-24 05:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy is persuaded that he's discovered the ultimate gadget for good living</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 05:32:00" d="2020-05-24 05:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings clamor for their turn to play with the ranger's mobile phone but Grizzy isn't in the sharing mood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 05:39:00" d="2020-05-24 05:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy is captivated by a mime artist on TV who makes viewers believe in the presence of an invisible wall</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 05:45:00" d="2020-05-24 05:52:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings shiver with cold sneeze and are glassy-eyed: they have a big fat cold!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 05:52:00" d="2020-05-24 06:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a super fun app that allows you to see yourself as a rabbit or a robot or else decked out with lots of animated accessories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 06:00:00" d="2020-05-24 06:11:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>When Gordon is taken over by aliens (code name: fleas), the PURST team has to help get rid of them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 06:11:00" d="2020-05-24 06:22:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>Binky’s favourite sweater is being eaten by aliens (code name: moths), and it’s up to the team to save to stop the aliens and save &quot;Fuzzy Wuzzy&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 06:22:00" d="2020-05-24 06:33:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>Ted is accidentally thrust into outer space during a mission and Binky is determined to get him back!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 06:33:00" d="2020-05-24 07:00:00"><n>Agent Binky: Pets of the Universe</n>    <k>When Gracie comes for a sleepover, the gang is excited for a party but she has other plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 07:00:00" d="2020-05-24 07:10:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean’s electricity is cut off so he builds a wind turbine – all fine until there’s too much wind!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 07:10:00" d="2020-05-24 07:20:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean attempts to retrieve his cash card and ‘accidently’ ends up inside a bank vault</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 07:20:00" d="2020-05-24 07:30:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean is tired of litterbugs and attempts to clean up the whole town himself…with disastrous results</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 07:30:00" d="2020-05-24 07:50:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean has to deal with an unwanted house guest, but the stubborn pest refuses to leave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 07:50:00" d="2020-05-24 08:00:00"><n>The HAPPOS Family</n>    <k>A large monster footprint is found which Doc thinks has been made by a Happo Yeti.Doc and Fixit attempt to track and catch this scary beast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 08:00:00" d="2020-05-24 08:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy's nap is interrupted by an annoying vibration. He sees the forest ranger's cell phone on the couch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 08:06:00" d="2020-05-24 08:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Freed by the thawing ice a mysterious giant egg slides up to the front door of the log cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 08:13:00" d="2020-05-24 08:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% In order to seduce the she-bear he's infatuated with Grizzy decides to take things in hand and slim down with the ranger's bodybuilding equipment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 08:19:00" d="2020-05-24 08:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% By chance Grizzy discovers that the ranger's new robot vacuum cleaner also gives very pleasant back massages. But the Lemmings see the new gadget</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 08:26:00" d="2020-05-24 08:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy discovers a gadget that controls various functions in the cabin. He will finally be able to rid of the Lemmings without even leaving the couch!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 08:32:00" d="2020-05-24 08:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% To make sure that the Lemmings don’t snatch his chocolate spread Grizzy turns the fridge into a safe. But the Lemmings see Grizzy open the door while sleepwalking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 08:39:00" d="2020-05-24 09:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings have invented a new popcorn game which consists of throwing popcorn and catching it with their mouths</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 09:00:00" d="2020-05-24 09:10:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean makes his own horror movie and ropes in Mrs Wicket as the star!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 09:10:00" d="2020-05-24 09:20:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean has to look after Mrs Wicket’s goldfish, but Scrapper the cat is keen to ‘help’</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 09:20:00" d="2020-05-24 09:30:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean wins tickets for a Cruise, but if only he could stay on it!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 09:30:00" d="2020-05-24 10:00:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean hopes to win some cash prizes at the funfair, but it’s not as easy as it seems!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 10:00:00" d="2020-05-24 10:09:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% The babies learn the importance of telling time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 10:09:00" d="2020-05-24 10:19:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Lola learns she can't be the best at every sport</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 10:19:00" d="2020-05-24 10:28:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% Daffy learns a lesson in doing the right thing when he finds a purse filled with money</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 10:28:00" d="2020-05-24 11:00:00"><n>Baby Looney Tunes - Elements</n>    <k>60% An attention-starved Sylvester won't let Granny have any time to herself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 11:00:00" d="2020-05-24 11:22:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>Scooby and our gang of mystery solving teens have been invited by famous comedian Jeff Foxworthy to help him move an old mansion that he's just purchased</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 11:22:00" d="2020-05-24 12:00:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>Scooby and the Mystery Inc. gang meet Wanda Sykes who is helping save a bunch of cute fuzzy animals up for adoption</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 12:00:00" d="2020-05-24 12:10:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben must go alien to save the Hoover Dam from disaster but when tough guy hero Tim Buktu swoops in to &quot;help&quot; Ben must figure out if Tim is friend… or foe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 12:10:00" d="2020-05-24 12:20:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben, Gwen and Max go on a tour of the impervious Fort Knox when Dr. Animo sicks a hungry ani-mutate on the Fort</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 12:20:00" d="2020-05-24 12:30:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>Ben and Gwen are excited to attend an Earth Day EDM concert in Portland until the show is hijacked by the sound-manipulating baddy Lord Decibel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 12:30:00" d="2020-05-24 13:00:00"><n u="Ben">Ben 10</n>    <k>When Ben goes Upgrade to transform the lawnmower into a superfast mowing machine he accidently draws the ire of Bob’s gnome-neighbours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 13:00:00" d="2020-05-24 13:10:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>Pebbles suspects a new fashion trend from the Crags is actually a form of mind control and tries to stop it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 13:10:00" d="2020-05-24 13:21:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>Bamm-Bamm wakes up in the Crags next to a giant crater where the treehouse used to be and with no memory of the night before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 13:21:00" d="2020-05-24 13:32:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>Pebbles and Bamm-Bamm get recruited into an underground rock racing league in the Crags</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 13:32:00" d="2020-05-24 14:00:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>Dino is taken to a special obedience school to help stop his increasingly bad behavior</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 14:00:00" d="2020-05-24 14:11:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>Bamm-Bamm thinks he's helping protect a turtle who lost his shell but he's actually being duped into using his club and super strength as an enforcer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 14:11:00" d="2020-05-24 14:22:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>Pebbles is forced to babysit the infant daughter of a family friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 14:22:00" d="2020-05-24 14:33:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>Dino meets a dinosaur in the crags who looks exactly like him but he can talk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 14:33:00" d="2020-05-24 15:00:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>A Businessaurus breezes into the Crags and all the dinosaurs get swept up by his buzz words and smooth lifestyle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 15:00:00" d="2020-05-24 15:11:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>Pebbles picks up painting as a new hobby, but a paranoid Doomasaurus convinces the dinosaurs of the Crags that her artwork is evil magic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 15:11:00" d="2020-05-24 15:22:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>Bamm-Bamm befriends a dinosaur who can molt her skin and use the shell casing to pull practical jokes and pranks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 15:22:00" d="2020-05-24 15:33:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>Pebbles meets her idol Jeanine Gravel, an entrenched biologist living out in a remote and disgusting part of the Crags</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 15:33:00" d="2020-05-24 16:00:00"><n>Yabba Dabba Dinosaurs!</n>    <k>Pebbles and Bamm-Bamm go their seperate ways after a big fight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 16:00:00" d="2020-05-24 16:10:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Madame Poloduri has known that there's something off about Mina's pets for a while. She's no fool. So she kidnaps the secretly supernatural animal living</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 16:10:00" d="2020-05-24 16:20:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Who or what could possibly get the best of Bunnicula? Chester and Harold decide to find out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 16:20:00" d="2020-05-24 16:30:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>After some particularly gassy cabbage gives Bunnicula a case of the burps, he puts himself right into orbit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 16:30:00" d="2020-05-24 17:00:00"><n>Bunnicula</n>    <k>Chester and Harold learn the Orlock itself is haunted, and Bunnicula's presence is key to keeping the building from literally falling apart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 17:00:00" d="2020-05-24 17:07:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% A lemur belonging to the Duchess' adventurous cousin puts Tom's job as Under-Butler in jeopardy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 17:07:00" d="2020-05-24 17:14:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% The detectives agree to escort a goofy Canadian goose back across the border before duck hunting season begins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 17:14:00" d="2020-05-24 17:20:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom and Jerry fight each other with the balloons that Rick has placed all over the house to surprise Ginger on their anniversary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 17:20:00" d="2020-05-24 17:27:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% When Tom and Jerry's antics unearth an autographed baseball, a childhood souvenir of Rick's, he warns Tom to keep his paws off it, or else!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 17:27:00" d="2020-05-24 17:34:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Frankenstein turns Tom into a colossus and Tom ends up terrorizing the village mice until Jerry Van Mouseling saves the day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 17:34:00" d="2020-05-24 18:00:00"><n>The Tom and Jerry Show</n>    <k>68% Tom finds himself trapped inside a Catsylvania bedtime story and fleeing from a furious Jabberwock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 18:00:00" d="2020-05-24 18:10:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean’s electricity is cut off so he builds a wind turbine – all fine until there’s too much wind!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 18:10:00" d="2020-05-24 18:20:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean attempts to retrieve his cash card and ‘accidently’ ends up inside a bank vault</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 18:20:00" d="2020-05-24 18:30:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean is tired of litterbugs and attempts to clean up the whole town himself…with disastrous results</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 18:30:00" d="2020-05-24 19:00:00"><n>The Mr. Bean Animated Series</n>    <k>Mr Bean has to deal with an unwanted house guest, but the stubborn pest refuses to leave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 19:00:00" d="2020-05-24 19:22:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>Daphne's makeup vlog lands her as the prime consultant to the famous rock band, the Hex Girls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 19:22:00" d="2020-05-24 20:00:00"><n>Scooby-Doo and Guess Who?</n>    <k>Our mystery solving gang agrees to help Ricky Gervais with a haunted antique Egyptian statue of a cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 20:00:00" d="2020-05-24 20:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings have found an Amerindian eagle amulet that endows he who wears it with the powers of a bird of prey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 20:06:00" d="2020-05-24 20:12:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings are having a blast with the ranger's electric guitar and the cabin walls tremble with their experimental rock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 20:12:00" d="2020-05-24 20:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% To finally be on an equal footing with Grizzy's imposing build and throw their own weight around in the cabin the Lemmings decide to wear a blowup sumotori costume</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 20:19:00" d="2020-05-24 20:25:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy and the Lemmings discover an ancient Amerindian table with the power to show you past events</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 20:25:00" d="2020-05-24 20:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings discover an old book of magic spells with a formula that enables one to take on the appearance of any other creature</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 20:32:00" d="2020-05-24 20:38:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Nutty Hill is suffering from a stifling heat wave. Grizzy decides to get into the fridge, where the temperature will be more bearable, but the shelves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 20:38:00" d="2020-05-24 21:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy is frustrated: just as he was about to coat a nice big fresh salmon with chocolate spread and snuggle up in front of the TV he discovers that the pantry is empty!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 21:00:00" d="2020-05-24 21:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola plans for a fun play date with her friends. But when Victor erupts with the trendiest video games the little girl seems embarrassed by her cheapish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 21:07:00" d="2020-05-24 21:14:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola finds out that her mother used to be a mini-golf champion. She gathers all her mothers old golf clubs and decides to build a small golf course in the garden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 21:14:00" d="2020-05-24 21:20:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>After another twisted move from the Guanos the sausage truck breaks down in front of Lola’s house. The little girl is in charge of guarding the truck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 21:20:00" d="2020-05-24 21:27:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Today is vaccination day for Pat and the least to say is that he hates it! After many failed attempts at hiding he must face the harsh reality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 21:27:00" d="2020-05-24 21:34:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>It’s grooming day for Pat and he loves being pampered! Lola believes that Hoodie as well could benefit from some care</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 21:34:00" d="2020-05-24 21:40:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola is in her garden taking pictures of Pat and Hoodie. But when the kitten who’s covered in black decides to go for a walk in the neighbourhood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 21:40:00" d="2020-05-24 22:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola and her friends plan to go to the Wonder Fun park but Victor is ill. Envious of his healthy neighbour he plans on passing her his microbes and prevent her from going</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 22:00:00" d="2020-05-24 22:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings have unearthed a crate of competition boomerangs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 22:06:00" d="2020-05-24 22:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Exasperated by the Lemmings who prevent him from watching his favorite TV show in peace Grizzy catapults them out of the cabin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 22:13:00" d="2020-05-24 22:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% A strange new object figures prominently in the cabin: a big wall clock that resembles a Swiss cuckoo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 22:19:00" d="2020-05-24 22:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Woken with a start by a nightmare filled with Lemmings Grizzy stumbles on the Ranger's dream machine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 22:26:00" d="2020-05-24 22:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy happens onto an old American India medallion bearing the symbol of the wind. He who wears it has the power to command air streams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 22:32:00" d="2020-05-24 22:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% A magic Amerindian top modifies the mental age of anyone who watches it spin. From now on, Grizzy has the mind of a 10-month old baby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 22:39:00" d="2020-05-24 23:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% A magic horn lands on the muzzle of a moose endowing it with grace and the ability to fly. It soars off leaving a rainbow-colored streak in its wake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 23:00:00" d="2020-05-24 23:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Cat wants to enter a tournament to prove she’s as good as the squires, Jimmy lends her a helmet so she can compete anonymously</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 23:10:00" d="2020-05-24 23:21:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When the first live-action Angry knights game is announced, Henri tells Jimmy games aren’t his thing. But when Jimmy picks the knight of Red, Henri becomes a jealous daddy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 23:21:00" d="2020-05-24 23:31:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Lance beats Jimmy by cheating in a gym class competition, Jimmy vows to get revenge by using invisible ink to erase Lance’s name from the “Banner of the Brave.”</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-24 23:31:00" d="2020-05-25 00:00:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>One of Henri's songs becomes such a hit that Henri turns rock star. Eager not to disappoint his fans he puts his career as a knight on hold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 00:00:00" d="2020-05-25 00:06:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M thinks about putting a flea collar on Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 00:06:00" d="2020-05-25 00:13:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy has a new friend and bodyguard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 00:13:00" d="2020-05-25 00:20:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>It's hibernation time for Taffy!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 00:20:00" d="2020-05-25 00:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy and Bentley bonk heads and lose their memories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 00:26:00" d="2020-05-25 00:32:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>A treasure hunt for Taffy and Bentley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 00:32:00" d="2020-05-25 00:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley realizes that Mrs. M is superstitious</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 00:39:00" d="2020-05-25 00:45:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>A nasty malady is spreading to all pets in the city</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 00:45:00" d="2020-05-25 00:52:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>All fancy bows must be sent back to the factory immediately!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 00:52:00" d="2020-05-25 01:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy is trying to save is damned soul</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 01:00:00" d="2020-05-25 01:06:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings find a pack of icy mints that literally chill your breath. One blast from anyone who eats them freezes everything in sight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 01:06:00" d="2020-05-25 01:13:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy can't believe it: he has just swallowed a spoonful of his favorite food chocolate spread and he hates it!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 01:13:00" d="2020-05-25 01:19:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy discovers the fondness of his beloved she-bear for meditation. To seduce her he sets out to prove to her that he too can attain the Zen attitude</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 01:19:00" d="2020-05-25 01:26:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy and the Lemmings discover a super-secret Canadian Army prototype which resembles a simple computer keyboard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 01:26:00" d="2020-05-25 01:32:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings are having a blast with a bowling game they found in the Ranger's storeroom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 01:32:00" d="2020-05-25 01:39:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% After the rains to the great delight of the Lemmings strange bouncing mushrooms have sprouted in the yard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 01:39:00" d="2020-05-25 01:45:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% The Lemmings have laid hand on special magnets which turn any object they are stuck to into flying objects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 01:45:00" d="2020-05-25 01:52:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% With a lion-tamer's whip a sugar bowl and lots of work the Lemmings have successfully trained a caribou to go through their obstacle course</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 01:52:00" d="2020-05-25 02:00:00"><n>Grizzy and the Lemmings</n>    <k>66% Grizzy happens onto the electronic version of the Ranger Lemming toy which is capable of reproducing the movements one teaches it like a smart robot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 02:00:00" d="2020-05-25 02:07:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Today Lola is spending the afternoon in the company of her former neighbor Honorine. On the menu: games and homemade pies. At least that’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 02:07:00" d="2020-05-25 02:14:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola looks on as an old lady throws seed to the birds and observes how the Guanos use their brute force to push other birds out of the way to hog the food</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 02:14:00" d="2020-05-25 02:20:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola has to play a violin solo during the big show tonight. When she is on stage Victor creates an accident as a pretext to make Lola believe the place is haunted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 02:20:00" d="2020-05-25 02:27:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola’s mother has just received the latest prototype for a food processor to test. Even though Lola promises to wait till evening before trying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 02:27:00" d="2020-05-25 02:34:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>A renowned pastry chef has organized a pie tasting contest. The winner will get to present a TV show with him. Lola is naturally taking part in the contest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 02:34:00" d="2020-05-25 02:40:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Today is the big Robot Battle day! Lola’s robot which looks like Pat has to face down Victor’s. But the boy cheats and breaks RoboPat. However Pat decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 02:40:00" d="2020-05-25 02:47:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola has found herself a fun activity for the afternoon: to break a Guinness World record. To do so she intends to build the biggest cat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 02:47:00" d="2020-05-25 02:54:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola has to write an essay on the theme My Hero Pet. It's not easiest task in the world for her she explains to Victor for while Pat is the loveliest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 02:54:00" d="2020-05-25 03:00:00"><n>Pat the Dog</n>    <k>Lola leaves the supermarket with all the ingredients for a super smoothie party. But disaster! She realizes she has forgotten the milk. She entrusts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 03:00:00" d="2020-05-25 03:10:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Cat and Cynthia bicker in class, Lady Fontaine assigns them as partners who have to make a gown together for the upcoming fashion show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 03:10:00" d="2020-05-25 03:21:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Jimmy wants to make a squire out of the school’s doormat, Kurt, and teach him how to stand up for himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 03:21:00" d="2020-05-25 03:31:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>When Jimmy accidentally spills the beans to the Red Knight’s visiting father that Red is a gym teacher and not First Knight, Grandpa Red expresses his disapproval</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 03:31:00" d="2020-05-25 03:42:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>Jimmy fears that being a “shrimp” will prevent him from getting knight missions when he grows up and decides to become a gym rat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 03:42:00" d="2020-05-25 04:00:00"><n>My Knight and Me</n>    <k>While Bad Jack gets some sleep, he leaves Bjorn to guard his treasure. Bjorn enlists help from Jimmy and Cat who make a silly suggestion to keep thieves away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 04:00:00" d="2020-05-25 04:06:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Mrs M thinks about putting a flea collar on Taffy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 04:06:00" d="2020-05-25 04:13:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy has a new friend and bodyguard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 04:13:00" d="2020-05-25 04:20:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>It's hibernation time for Taffy!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 04:20:00" d="2020-05-25 04:26:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy and Bentley bonk heads and lose their memories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 04:26:00" d="2020-05-25 04:32:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>A treasure hunt for Taffy and Bentley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 04:32:00" d="2020-05-25 04:39:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Bentley realizes that Mrs. M is superstitious</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 04:39:00" d="2020-05-25 04:45:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>A nasty malady is spreading to all pets in the city</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 04:45:00" d="2020-05-25 04:52:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>All fancy bows must be sent back to the factory immediately!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="64" o="2020-05-25 04:52:00" d="2020-05-25 05:00:00"><n>Taffy</n>    <k>Taffy is trying to save is damned soul</k>  </p>
</a>
