<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="54" t="2019-07-11 00:20:26"><p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 05:05:00" d="2019-07-16 05:30:00"><n u="SpongeBob SquarePants">SpongeBob SquarePants III (49)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% After watching a movie where robots take over the world, Spongebob thinks Mr. Krabs is a robot. Spongebob and Patrick find a baby clam and decide to raise it as their own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 05:30:00" d="2019-07-16 06:00:00"><n u="SpongeBob SquarePants">SpongeBob SquarePants III (50)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% Spongebob and Patrick must paint Mr. Krabs living room without getting a drop of paint on anything but the walls. Learn how to become a Krusty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 06:00:00" d="2019-07-16 06:30:00"><n u="SpongeBob SquarePants">SpongeBob SquarePants III (51)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% Spongebob decides to throw a big party after discovering a &quot;how to throw a party&quot; kit in the grocery store</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 06:30:00" d="2019-07-16 07:00:00"><n u="SpongeBob SquarePants">SpongeBob SquarePants III (52)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% To make some extra cash, Spongebob and Patrick decide to sell chocolate door to door. Barnacle Boy wants to be called &quot;Barnacle Man&quot; and rebels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 07:00:00" d="2019-07-16 07:30:00"><n u="SpongeBob SquarePants">SpongeBob SquarePants III (53)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% Patrick joins Ms. Puff's class but begins to get Spongebob in a lot of trouble causing him to lose gold stars. Mr. Krabs takes Spongebob and Squidward</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 07:30:00" d="2019-07-16 08:00:00"><n u="SpongeBob SquarePants">SpongeBob SquarePants III (54)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% It is prehistoric Bikini Bottom, and we spend a day in the life of SpongeGar, Patar, and Squog. (Spongebob, Patrick, and Squidward's prehistoric alter-egos.)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 08:00:00" d="2019-07-16 08:30:00"><n u="SpongeBob SquarePants">SpongeBob SquarePants III (55)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% Squidward gets a pure-bread snail, Snelle, and decides to race her in the snail races. Mr. Krabs feels old so he asks if he could join Spongebob</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 08:30:00" d="2019-07-16 09:00:00"><n u="SpongeBob SquarePants">SpongeBob SquarePants III (56)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% Mr. Krabs gets ill after eating an old Krabby Patty that he refused to throw away. SpongeBob has an accident while sand sledding! Afraid for his safety</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 09:00:00" d="2019-07-16 09:25:00"><n u="Punk'd">Punk'd III (307)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Jena Malone is given the wrong car from a velt and is blamed for missing cash upon return, Shannon Elizabeth is told she's the star of a so-called</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 09:25:00" d="2019-07-16 09:50:00"><n u="Punk'd">Punk'd III (308)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Tyra Banks and her family get caught in the middle of a &quot;Girls Gone Crazy&quot; Shoot, Kayne West experiences a video shoot shutdown, all brought</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 09:50:00" d="2019-07-16 10:15:00"><n u="Instant Mom">Instant Mom III (311)</n><t>S</t>    <k>65% When the Phillips’ cousin Jamal, an older doppelganger of James, comes to town, Charlie fears he will be a bad influence on his younger cousin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 10:15:00" d="2019-07-16 10:40:00"><n u="SpongeBob SquarePants">SpongeBob SquarePants III (45)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% Spongebob gets a hold of Mermaid Man's utility belt and accidentally shrinks all of Bikini Bottom. Ms. Puff takes the blame for an accident Spongebob</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 10:40:00" d="2019-07-16 11:05:00"><n u="Stand Up Express">Stand Up Express I (106)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Stand Up Express is the first in-house production of Comedy Central Extra which contains 15-30 minute stand performances by various comedians</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 11:05:00" d="2019-07-16 11:30:00"><n u="Stand Up Express">Stand Up Express I (107)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Stand Up Express is the first in-house production of Comedy Central Extra which contains 15-30 minute stand performances by various comedians</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 11:30:00" d="2019-07-16 11:55:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness I (113)</n><t>S</t>    <k>62% Rob breaks down Why Rollerblading Should Make a Comeback. Witness a merry-goround of pain in Worst Case Scenario, Almost Made It and Not Even Close</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 11:55:00" d="2019-07-16 12:20:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness I (114)</n><t>S</t>    <k>62% Learn How Not to Treadmill and why Grass is Your Friend. See a wake of damage after Trees Strike Back. Guest dancer Cole Hernandez brings some Weird Dancing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 12:20:00" d="2019-07-16 12:45:00"><n u="Punk'd">Punk'd IV (401)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Things get messy when Penelope Cruz gives Salma Hayek a lesson in potty training. Things get desperate for Eva Longoria when she is stopped by the cops</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 12:45:00" d="2019-07-16 13:10:00"><n u="Punk'd">Punk'd IV (402)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Kirsten Dunst learns that friends don't let friends get Punk'd. Jesse Metcalf gets hung up on a role, and Michelle Rodriguez plays convenience store dominos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 13:10:00" d="2019-07-16 13:35:00"><n u="Instant Mom">Instant Mom III (312)</n><t>S</t>    <k>65% Stephanie tries to teach James and Aaron selfless generosity by helping Mr. Ebnetter fix his boat. Soon, the whole family is helping, but for all the wrong reasons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 13:35:00" d="2019-07-16 14:00:00"><n u="SpongeBob SquarePants">SpongeBob SquarePants III (46)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% It's snowing! Spongebob and Patrick try to show Squidward how much fun it can be to play in the snow. Mr. Krabs has a garage sale and sells Spongebob</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 14:00:00" d="2019-07-16 14:30:00"><n u="SpongeBob SquarePants">SpongeBob SquarePants III (47)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% Spongebob makes a one second cameo in a Krusty Krabs commercial. Fed up with Mr. Krabs insults, Squidward quits his job - but has a hard time finding a new job</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 14:30:00" d="2019-07-16 15:00:00"><n u="SpongeBob SquarePants">SpongeBob SquarePants III (48)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% Spongebob has to prove that he's tough so he can get into the Salty Spitoon. Squidward's arch nemesis, Squilliam, returns to harass Squidward on his failed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 15:00:00" d="2019-07-16 15:30:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness I (115)</n><t>S</t>    <k>62% The Dingo is back! Laugh as a whole lot of people having a Tough Day on the Job, find out if You’re Too Old For That, and who’s Almost Awesome. Rob breaks down Skiers vs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 15:30:00" d="2019-07-16 16:00:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness I (116)</n><t>S</t>    <k>62% Big Black is back and he’s showing off Black Lavender. See what happens When Bad Ideas Go Worse and people suffer a Failure to Launch. Rob’s got a special</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 16:00:00" d="2019-07-16 16:25:00"><n u="Punk'd">Punk'd IV (403)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ashton Aces Serena Williams with a car chase. Zach Braff gets scrubbed by co-star Donald Faison when his precious Porsche gets Punk'd</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 16:25:00" d="2019-07-16 16:50:00"><n u="Punk'd">Punk'd IV (404)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Summer gets schooled when Rachel Bilson gets a wet and wild punk. Jadakiss jams to traffic when he gets Punk'd in the car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 16:50:00" d="2019-07-16 17:15:00"><n u="Punk'd">Punk'd IV (405)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ashton lobs an overhead smash to Andy Roddick when he gets stuck on the way to the Tonight Show. Soprano's Jamie Lynn-Discala gives a bad tip and gets a waitress fired</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 17:15:00" d="2019-07-16 17:40:00"><n u="Punk'd">Punk'd IV (406)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Jon Heder gets his tater tots in a twist when he accidentally visits a brothel! Ashton gets Chingy with it when the recording star gets a fan beaten up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 17:40:00" d="2019-07-16 18:05:00"><n u="Stand Up Express">Stand Up Express II (202)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Stand Up Express is the first in-house production of Comedy Central Extra which contains 15-30 minute stand performances by various comedians</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 18:05:00" d="2019-07-16 18:30:00"><n u="Stand Up Express">Stand Up Express II (203)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Stand Up Express is the first in-house production of Comedy Central Extra which contains 15-30 minute stand performances by various comedians</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 18:30:00" d="2019-07-16 19:00:00"><n u="Instant Mom">Instant Mom III (313)</n><t>S</t>    <k>65% The night before taking the SATs, Gabby decides to take a different path, much to Charlie and Maggie’s dismay, and exposes a secret about Stephanie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 19:00:00" d="2019-07-16 19:30:00"><n u="Punk'd">Punk'd IV (407)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Life ain't so simple for Nicole Richie when she gets a waiter fired for hitting on her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 19:30:00" d="2019-07-16 20:00:00"><n u="Punk'd">Punk'd IV (408)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ashlee Simpson falls to pieces when she accidentally burns down an art gallery. Stone Cold Steve Austin heats up when he gets a parking valet fired</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 20:00:00" d="2019-07-16 20:30:00"><n u="Punk'd">Punk'd VI (602)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Kelly Monaco can't dance her way out of this one when her car gets towed then smashed. It's lobsters, lobsters everywhere when Brittany Snow punks Sophia Bush</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 20:30:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00"><n u="Punk'd">Punk'd VI (603)</n><t>S</t>    <k>TV Vampire, David Boreanaz, freaks at the sight of blood when his wife bites into a salad of broken glass. It's dunzo for Kristin Cavalleri when road rage takes a hold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 21:30:00"><n u="Broad City">Broad City II (202)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New opportunities arise as Abbi is finally able to train somebody at Soulstice and Ilana finds success as a corporate overlord</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 21:30:00" d="2019-07-16 22:00:00"><n u="Broad City">Broad City II (203)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Abbi gets her wisdom teeth removed, and Ilana makes it her mission to nurse her back to health -- which naturally involves a cocktail of drugs and a lack of supervision</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 22:00:00" d="2019-07-16 22:25:00"><n u="South Park">South Park XI (1103)</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% South Park details the lives and misadventures of four elementary school students in a small Colorado town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 22:25:00" d="2019-07-16 22:50:00"><n u="South Park">South Park XI (1104)</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% South Park details the lives and misadventures of four elementary school students in a small Colorado town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 22:50:00" d="2019-07-16 23:15:00"><n u="Big Time In Hollywood">Big Time In Hollywood I (105)</n><t>S</t>    <k>While Alan and Diana enjoy a romantic dinner, the boys are threatened at gunpoint, and an unexpected turn of events leaves them tasked with unforeseen challenges</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 23:15:00" d="2019-07-16 23:40:00"><n u="Big Time In Hollywood">Big Time In Hollywood I (106)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben returns home and tries to get his life together while Jack continues working on his films; Del pursues a budding love interest; and Malloy and Zdorkin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-16 23:40:00" d="2019-07-17 00:05:00"><n u="SpongeBob SquarePants">SpongeBob SquarePants III (56)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% Mr. Krabs gets ill after eating an old Krabby Patty that he refused to throw away. SpongeBob has an accident while sand sledding! Afraid for his safety</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-17 00:05:00" d="2019-07-17 00:30:00"><n u="Instant Mom">Instant Mom II (207)</n><t>S</t>    <k>65% Stephanie feels unneeded when all of the kids have their own plans and ditch her on Halloween. Meanwhile, Charlie tries to maintain his perfect rating</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-17 00:30:00" d="2019-07-17 00:55:00"><n u="Jackass">Jackass II (214)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Rake Yohn and Johnny Knoxville suit up in haz-mat gear to transfer a unknown chemical through the streets of Portland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-17 00:55:00" d="2019-07-17 01:20:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness III (309)</n><t>S</t>    <k>62% During an all-new episode of Ridiculousness: Rob and Gymkhana phenomenon Ken Block show us how not to be a &quot;Gymkhanabe&quot; and we see first hand what being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-17 01:20:00" d="2019-07-17 01:45:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness III (310)</n>    <k>62% This week on an all-new episode of Ridiculousness: rapper Riff Raff shows off his Brain Freeze and joins Rob in breaking down some unbelievable Middle of the Mall Sh</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-17 01:45:00" d="2019-07-17 02:10:00"><n u="South Park">South Park XI (1101)</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% South Park details the lives and misadventures of four elementary school students in a small Colorado town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-17 02:10:00" d="2019-07-17 02:35:00"><n u="South Park">South Park XI (1102)</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% South Park details the lives and misadventures of four elementary school students in a small Colorado town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-17 02:35:00" d="2019-07-17 03:00:00"><n u="Jackass">Jackass II (214)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Rake Yohn and Johnny Knoxville suit up in haz-mat gear to transfer a unknown chemical through the streets of Portland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-17 03:00:00" d="2019-07-17 03:25:00"><n u="Instant Mom">Instant Mom II (208)</n><t>S</t>    <k>65% Stephanie and Charlie plan a kid-free weekend in New York, only to find that Aaron has stowed away in their car. Meanwhile, both James and Gabby have plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-17 03:25:00" d="2019-07-17 03:50:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness III (309)</n><t>S</t>    <k>62% During an all-new episode of Ridiculousness: Rob and Gymkhana phenomenon Ken Block show us how not to be a &quot;Gymkhanabe&quot; and we see first hand what being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-17 03:50:00" d="2019-07-17 04:15:00"><n u="Ridiculousness">Ridiculousness III (310)</n>    <k>62% This week on an all-new episode of Ridiculousness: rapper Riff Raff shows off his Brain Freeze and joins Rob in breaking down some unbelievable Middle of the Mall Sh</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-17 04:15:00" d="2019-07-17 04:40:00"><n u="Big Time In Hollywood">Big Time In Hollywood I (106)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ben returns home and tries to get his life together while Jack continues working on his films; Del pursues a budding love interest; and Malloy and Zdorkin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="703" o="2019-07-17 04:40:00" d="2019-07-17 05:05:00"><n u="SpongeBob SquarePants">SpongeBob SquarePants III (54)</n><t>S</t>    <k>73% It is prehistoric Bikini Bottom, and we spend a day in the life of SpongeGar, Patar, and Squog. (Spongebob, Patrick, and Squidward's prehistoric alter-egos.)</k>  </p>
</a>
