<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="42" t="2019-07-11 00:20:26"><p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 05:10:00" d="2019-07-17 05:35:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With The Engagement Picture
Joey teaches Chandler how to smile for an engagement picture with Monica. Phoebe and Ross each date the members</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 05:35:00" d="2019-07-17 06:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With The Nap Partners
Joey and Ross accidentally take a nap together and much to their dismay, find that they like it. Phoebe and Rachel compete</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 06:00:00" d="2019-07-17 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 07:00:00" d="2019-07-17 09:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 09:00:00" d="2019-07-17 09:35:00"><n>The Middle</n>    <k>Things don't go as planned when Mike and the kids give Frankie a day without the family as a Mother's Day gift</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 09:35:00" d="2019-07-17 10:00:00"><n>The Middle</n>    <k>Axl invites the wrong girl to the prom, then decides to stand her up; Sue tries to fit in with the school's B crowd; Brick bores Frankie and Mike with his one-man plays</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 10:00:00" d="2019-07-17 10:30:00"><n>The Middle</n>    <k>Two youngsters undertake a scientific challenge with the help of their families. They must complete the task using the objects they receive in a mysterious box</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 10:30:00" d="2019-07-17 11:00:00"><n>The Middle</n>    <k>Brick must write a daily journal for school or risk being held back; Axl has time left in his community service requirement; Sue must prove she had perfect attendance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 11:00:00" d="2019-07-17 11:30:00"><n u="My Name Is Earl">My Name Is Earl III (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Early Release
The warden reneges on his promise to Earl to grant an early release, so Earl launches a plan to escape from prison</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 11:30:00" d="2019-07-17 11:55:00"><n u="My Name Is Earl">My Name Is Earl III (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>77% I Won't Die with a Little Help from My Friends (Part 1)
Earl is in a coma after being hit by a car. So Randy steals an ambulance, but getting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 11:55:00" d="2019-07-17 12:30:00"><n>Friends</n>    <k>When a fire damages their apartment, Rachel and Phoebe must choose between living with Joey or Monica. Ross gets into trouble by dating a student</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 12:30:00" d="2019-07-17 13:00:00"><n>Friends</n>    <k>Ross tries to contain his paranoia when his student girlfriend goes on spring break with her wild friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 13:00:00" d="2019-07-17 13:30:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VI (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With Mac And C.H.E.E.S.E
Joey auditions for a major television role, but Chandler almost ruins everything by forgetting to write down a telephone message</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 13:30:00" d="2019-07-17 14:00:00"><n>Friends</n>    <k>Ross fails to impress his girlfriend's father (Bruce Willis). Joey gets off on the wrong foot with the operator of his robotic co-star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 14:00:00" d="2019-07-17 14:30:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VI (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One Where Paul's The Man
While Ross and Elizabeth are on a romantic weekend getaway at her family's cabin, Elizabeth's father (Bruce Willis)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 14:30:00" d="2019-07-17 15:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VI (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With The Ring
Chandler finds the perfect engagement ring, and then loses it. Rachel tries to get Paul (Bruce Willis) to reveal his emotions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 15:00:00" d="2019-07-17 15:30:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With Monica's Thunder
Monica excitedly reveals the good news of her engagement to everyone, but Rachel and Ross upstage her by reuniting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 15:30:00" d="2019-07-17 16:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With Rachel's Book
Joey finds out that Rachel is reading a steamy romance novel and Monica discovers that her parents have spent the money</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 16:00:00" d="2019-07-17 16:30:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With Phoebe's Cookies
Monica becomes obsessed with obtaining Phoebe's secret cookie recipe. Meanwhile, whilst trying to bond, Chandler</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 16:30:00" d="2019-07-17 17:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With Rachel's Assistant
Rachel wants to hire a cute, young male assistant over a more qualified woman. Meanwhile, Joey's show gets cancelled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 17:00:00" d="2019-07-17 17:30:00"><n u="My Name Is Earl">My Name Is Earl III (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>77% I Won't Die with a Little Help from My Friends (Part 2)
Nothing can get Earl out of his coma, so Randy turns to a young faith healer from their past</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 17:30:00" d="2019-07-17 18:00:00"><n u="My Name Is Earl">My Name Is Earl III (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Killerball
Earl is still in a coma but released from the hospital, and Randy finds a way to get him to cross an item off the list by helping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 18:00:00" d="2019-07-17 18:30:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One Where Rosita Dies
Phoebe becomes involved with a suicidal office worker (Jason Alexander). Meanwhile, Rachel and Chandler both think they've</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 18:30:00" d="2019-07-17 19:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One Where They All Turn Thirty
Rachel's 30th birthday prompts the friends to reminisce about their own 30th celebrations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 19:00:00" d="2019-07-17 19:30:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With Joey's New Brain
Joey learns that his character in his daytime drama is about to gain prominence at the expense of the show's diva star (Susan Sarandon)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 19:30:00" d="2019-07-17 20:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With The Truth About London
Chandler finds out who Monica really wanted to have sex with on the night they became lovers. Ross is angry after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 20:00:00" d="2019-07-17 20:30:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With The Cheap Wedding Dress
Monica battles another shopper for the perfect wedding dress. Meanwhile, Joey and Ross fight over</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 20:30:00" d="2019-07-17 21:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With Joey's Award
Joey is nominated for a &quot;Soapie&quot; but loses. However, when he accepts a different award on behalf of a co-star, he finds himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 21:00:00" d="2019-07-17 21:30:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (19)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With Ross and Monica's Cousin
Monica's gorgeous cousin (Denise Richards) unwittingly wreaks havoc on Chandler and Ross as they become infatuated by her good looks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 21:30:00" d="2019-07-17 22:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With Rachel's Big Kiss
Rachel reveals a titillating secret about her and a former sorority sister (Winona Ryder). Meanwhile, Ross and Chandler</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 22:00:00" d="2019-07-17 23:00:00"><n u="Russell Howard's Good News">Russell Howard's Good News VII (2)</n>    <k>Russell Howard takes a cheeky trawl through the news. Tonight features; MDMA, a West Country George Michael, talking robots, Ed Milliband The Movie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 23:00:00" d="2019-07-17 23:30:00"><n u="The Ricky Gervais Show">The Ricky Gervais Show I (9)</n>    <k>In ''Questions for Karl,'' the anointed pundit discusses time travel and adult diapers. Stephen reads entries from Karl's diary, which entertain Ricky immensely</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 23:30:00" d="2019-07-18 00:00:00"><n u="The Ricky Gervais Show">The Ricky Gervais Show I (10)</n>    <k>Karl discusses his unusual approach to teaching. Examples of discussion topics include a dishwasher being found on Mars and dinosaurs as a form of population control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-18 00:00:00" d="2019-07-18 00:30:00"><n>South Park</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% South Park residents are forced out of their homes when an Indian casino takes their land</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-18 00:30:00" d="2019-07-18 01:15:00"><n>South Park</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% While assisting an ex-Vice President in his quest for attention, the boys get trapped by a cave-in and while searching for a way out, Cartman discovers treasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-18 01:15:00" d="2019-07-18 02:15:00"><n>Joe Rogan: Rocky Mountain High</n>    <k>Tune in to find out the real meaning of infinity, why Joe will lie to you on stage, and why Kim Kardashian is the most popular woman in the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-18 02:15:00" d="2019-07-18 02:45:00"><n>South Park</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% Cartman leads a campaign against the Jews after seeing &quot;The Passion Of The Christ.&quot; Meanwhile, Stan and Kenny try to get their money back from Mel Gibson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-18 02:45:00" d="2019-07-18 03:20:00"><n>South Park</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% A gang of kids from the O.C. challenge Stan do a dance-off. But before the big event, Butters must confront a painful event from his past</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-18 03:20:00" d="2019-07-18 03:55:00"><n>South Park</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% Cartman dresses up as a robot from Japan, sent to Butters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-18 03:55:00" d="2019-07-18 04:20:00"><n>South Park</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% When people from a poverty-stricken future travel back in time to find work, South Park residents accuse them of taking their jobs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-18 04:20:00" d="2019-07-18 04:45:00"><n>South Park</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% Stan refuses to vote in the school mascot election because his choices are a giant douche and a turd sandwich</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-18 04:45:00" d="2019-07-18 05:10:00"><n u="My Name Is Earl">My Name Is Earl III (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bad Earl
Earl and Randy are broke and homeless. So when he sees Ralph living the good life doing bad things, he declares that there is no karma and throws away the list</k>  </p>
</a>
