<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="42" t="2019-07-11 00:20:26"><p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 05:15:00" d="2019-07-15 05:40:00"><n u="Most Ridiculous European Vacation">Most Ridiculous European Vacation III (16)</n>    <k>Pack your bags as we go on a European Vacation. Greg James is on a whistle-stop tour featuring French fools, bonkers Brits, silly Swedes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 05:40:00" d="2019-07-15 06:00:00"><n u="Most Ridiculous Workers">Most Ridiculous Workers III (17)</n>    <k>This time workers are getting the Most Ridiculous treatment. Just the job if you're after bungling builders, stupid sales assistants, and waiters throwing a wobbly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 06:00:00" d="2019-07-15 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 07:00:00" d="2019-07-15 09:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 09:00:00" d="2019-07-15 09:35:00"><n>The Middle</n>    <k>After Aunt Ginny's funeral, Frankie decides the family needs to start celebrating more milestones; Axl eats Brick's school project; Sue learns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 09:35:00" d="2019-07-15 10:00:00"><n>The Middle</n>    <k>Frankie is deeply disappointed with her volunteer assignment at the Indiana-hosted Super Bowl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 10:00:00" d="2019-07-15 10:30:00"><n>The Middle</n>    <k>Mike angers Frankie on Valentine's Day by refusing to present her with a romantic gesture; Axl struggles with a school assignment; Brick must write a report on love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 10:30:00" d="2019-07-15 11:00:00"><n>The Middle</n>    <k>Frankie vows to get tickets to a Justin Bieber concert for Sue; Mike coaches Brick for the school's annual spelling bee</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 11:00:00" d="2019-07-15 11:30:00"><n u="My Name Is Earl">My Name Is Earl IV (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Quit Your Snitchin'
Earl discovers he is no longer covered by the criminal code of ethics when someone steals Randy's birthday present from him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 11:30:00" d="2019-07-15 12:00:00"><n u="My Name Is Earl">My Name Is Earl IV (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sold a Guy a Lemon Car
Earl discovers that the apparent psychopath who has moved in next door to him and Randy at the hotel is actually</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 12:00:00" d="2019-07-15 12:30:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With Ross's Library Book
Ross discovers that his dissertation is in a section of the library where students go to have &quot;relations&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 12:30:00" d="2019-07-15 13:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One Where Chandler Doesn't Like Dogs
Chandler's irrational fear of dogs causes problems when Phoebe brings home a cute canine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 13:00:00" d="2019-07-15 13:30:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With All The Candy
Monica becomes popular with her neighbours because of her homemade candy. Meanwhile, Ross teaches Phoebe how to ride a bike. literally</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 13:30:00" d="2019-07-15 14:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (10)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With The Holiday Armadillo
Ross dresses up as an Armadillo to try and teach Ben about Hanukkah. Meanwhile, Phoebe worries that Rachel wants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 14:00:00" d="2019-07-15 14:30:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With All The Cheesecakes
Chandler and Rachel can't help eating the irresistible cheesecakes that are meant for a neighbour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 14:30:00" d="2019-07-15 15:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One Where They're Up All Night
After the gang head to the roof to see a passing comet, separate events unfold that lead to all of them having a sleepless night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 15:00:00" d="2019-07-15 15:30:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (15)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With Joey's New Brain
Joey learns that his character in his daytime drama is about to gain prominence at the expense of the show's diva star (Susan Sarandon)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 15:30:00" d="2019-07-15 16:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (16)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With The Truth About London
Chandler finds out who Monica really wanted to have sex with on the night they became lovers. Ross is angry after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 16:00:00" d="2019-07-15 16:30:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (17)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With The Cheap Wedding Dress
Monica battles another shopper for the perfect wedding dress. Meanwhile, Joey and Ross fight over</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 16:30:00" d="2019-07-15 17:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (18)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With Joey's Award
Joey is nominated for a &quot;Soapie&quot; but loses. However, when he accepts a different award on behalf of a co-star, he finds himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 17:00:00" d="2019-07-15 17:30:00"><n u="My Name Is Earl">My Name Is Earl IV (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Nature's Game Show
A series of tornados hitting Camden County aren't Earl's biggest concern when he loses his list. A wild ride in a boat causes Randy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 17:30:00" d="2019-07-15 18:00:00"><n u="My Name Is Earl">My Name Is Earl IV (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Reading Is a Fundamental Case
While reading to children, Earl reminisces about a recent list item. It all began when Earl found his old friend Raynard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 18:00:00" d="2019-07-15 18:30:00"><n>Friends</n>    <k>Monica sways Chandler's dislike of baths but he soon becomes addicted to them. Meanwhile, Monica mistakenly tells Phoebe that Joey has a crush on her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 18:30:00" d="2019-07-15 19:00:00"><n>Friends</n>    <k>Chandler becomes obsessed with finding out what is behind the door of Monica's secret closet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 19:00:00" d="2019-07-15 19:30:00"><n>Friends</n>    <k>Monica prepares a special Valentine's Day for Chandler which doesn't quite go to plan. Meanwhile, Joey ends up telling Ross about his feelings for Rachel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 19:30:00" d="2019-07-15 20:00:00"><n>Friends</n>    <k>The guys agree that Joey should tell Rachel about his feelings for her over dinner, regardless of the potential consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 20:00:00" d="2019-07-15 20:30:00"><n>Friends</n>    <k>After studying tea leaves, Phoebe believes she will encounter the man of her dreams - and she soon meets a very handsome guy, Parker (Alec Baldwin)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 20:30:00" d="2019-07-15 21:00:00"><n>Friends</n>    <k>Monica writes a speech for her parents' 35th wedding anniversary. Phoebe dates Parker (Alec Baldwin), whose enthusiasm for everything begins to wear on everyone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 21:00:00" d="2019-07-15 21:30:00"><n>Friends</n>    <k>Joey prepares for an interview with Soap Opera Digest, although he's afraid of saying something stupid that may jeopardize his career. again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 21:30:00" d="2019-07-15 22:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VIII (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With The Baby Shower
During her baby shower Rachel has the realization that she is totally unprepared to care for a baby, sparking her mother's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-15 22:00:00" d="2019-07-16 00:05:00"><n>Hall Pass</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Rick (Owen Wilson) and Fred (Jason Sudeikis), two husbands who are having difficulty in their marriages, are given a Hall Pass by their wives
for</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 00:05:00" d="2019-07-16 00:35:00"><n>South Park</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% Cartman plans an elaborate revenge when an older boy cons him out of money</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 00:35:00" d="2019-07-16 01:05:00"><n>South Park</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% Butters is sacked by the boys as their replacement best friend for Kenny - the hunt for a new friend is on! Out for revenge, Butters becomes. Professor Chaos!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 01:05:00" d="2019-07-16 01:35:00"><n u="South Park">South Park IX (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Marjorine
Cartman is convinced that the girls have a device which can see into the future. The boys come up with a plan to take it. Unfortunately</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 01:35:00" d="2019-07-16 02:05:00"><n>South Park</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% In a bid to prevent Mr. Slave from marrying Big Gay Al, Mrs. Garrison forces the children to help him in an experiment to prove that gay marriages are unstable. Will he succeed?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 02:05:00" d="2019-07-16 02:35:00"><n u="South Park">South Park IX (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ginger Kids
After giving a hate speech against 'the gingers', Cartman awakens the next day with a case of 'Gingervitus' and soon rallies against</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 02:35:00" d="2019-07-16 03:05:00"><n>South Park</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% Free Willzyx
The boys are tricked into believing the killer whale at Sea Park is from the moon. How will Timmy's wheelchair, the Russian government</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 03:05:00" d="2019-07-16 03:35:00"><n u="South Park">South Park IX (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bloody Mary
Randy is arrested for drunk driving and must attend AA, where he is told he is powerless to control himself. Maybe the bleeding Virgin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 03:35:00" d="2019-07-16 04:05:00"><n>South Park</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% The Return of Chef
The boys notice that Chef is acting weird after returning from the 'The Super Adventure Club'. Why is he trying to seduce them? Can a trip to a strip joint help?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 04:05:00" d="2019-07-16 04:25:00"><n u="South Park">South Park X (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% Smug Alert
Kyle's father buys a new hybrid car but it's not long before his smug levels reach ridiculous levels - must be time to move to San Fran! How will Cartman deal with no Kyle?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 04:25:00" d="2019-07-16 04:50:00"><n u="South Park">South Park X (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% A Million Little Fibbers
Towlie writes his memoirs and it's not long before he's invited onto The Oprah Winfrey Show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 04:50:00" d="2019-07-16 05:15:00"><n>South Park</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% While assisting an ex-Vice President in his quest for attention, the boys get trapped by a cave-in and while searching for a way out, Cartman discovers treasure</k>  </p>
</a>
