<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="42" t="2019-07-11 00:20:26"><p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 05:15:00" d="2019-07-16 05:35:00"><n u="Impractical Jokers: Inside Jokes">Impractical Jokers: Inside Jokes I (8)</n>    <k>See classic, fan-favourite episodes with shareable pop-up facts throughout. Plus behind-the-scenes stories and factoids. Tonight; the loser faces their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 05:35:00" d="2019-07-16 06:00:00"><n u="Impractical Jokers: Inside Jokes">Impractical Jokers: Inside Jokes I (9)</n>    <k>See classic, fan-favourite episodes with shareable pop-up facts throughout. Plus behind-the-scenes stories and factoids. Tonight; one prankster attends a rodeo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 06:00:00" d="2019-07-16 07:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 07:00:00" d="2019-07-16 09:00:00"><n>Teleshopping</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 09:00:00" d="2019-07-16 09:35:00"><n>The Middle</n>    <k>Sue, Axl and Brick have a meeting with Frankie and Mike to air complaints about their parenting styles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 09:35:00" d="2019-07-16 10:00:00"><n>The Middle</n>    <k>Sue wants a big celebration for her leap year birthday; Frankie learns that Mike has been caring for a stray cat; Brick develops a crush on a girl in his class</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 10:00:00" d="2019-07-16 10:30:00"><n>The Middle</n>    <k>Brick takes a newspaper delivery job in order to earn money for night vision goggles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 10:30:00" d="2019-07-16 11:00:00"><n>The Middle</n>    <k>After attending a new church, Frankie is inspired by a pastor who wants people to live without regrets by fulfilling their own destiny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 11:00:00" d="2019-07-16 11:30:00"><n u="My Name Is Earl">My Name Is Earl IV (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Nature's Game Show
A series of tornados hitting Camden County aren't Earl's biggest concern when he loses his list. A wild ride in a boat causes Randy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 11:30:00" d="2019-07-16 12:00:00"><n u="My Name Is Earl">My Name Is Earl IV (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Reading Is a Fundamental Case
While reading to children, Earl reminisces about a recent list item. It all began when Earl found his old friend Raynard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 12:00:00" d="2019-07-16 12:30:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (21)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With The Vows
Chandler and Monica struggle to write their wedding vows. This prompts the group to remember the journey Monica and Chandler</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 12:30:00" d="2019-07-16 13:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (22)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With Chandler's Dad
Chandler confronts his estranged cross-dressing father (Kathleen Turner). Meanwhile, Rachel gets into trouble driving Monica's Porsche</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 13:00:00" d="2019-07-16 13:30:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (23)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With Monica and Chandler's Wedding Part 1
Chandler gets the pre-wedding jitters and runs away. Meanwhile, Phoebe finds a positive pregnancy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 13:30:00" d="2019-07-16 14:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VII (24)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With Monica and Chandler's Wedding Part 2
Monica remains unaware of the potential disasters on her wedding day. Meanwhile, Joey's drunk co-star</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 14:00:00" d="2019-07-16 14:30:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VIII (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One After &quot;I Do&quot;
Everybody thinks Monica's pregnant, but her denial quickly shifts the focus to Phoebe, thereby taking the heat off of a nervous Rachel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 14:30:00" d="2019-07-16 15:00:00"><n>Friends</n>    <k>Rachel won't tell anybody who the father is until she tells him. Meanwhile, Joey mistakenly thinks Phoebe is pregnant and makes a gallant gesture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 15:00:00" d="2019-07-16 15:30:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VIII (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One Where Rachel Tells. 
Chandler and Monica prepare to leave for their honeymoon as Rachel prepares to tell the father of her baby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 15:30:00" d="2019-07-16 16:00:00"><n>Friends</n>    <k>Ross and Rachel disagree over who came onto whom when they hooked up. Meanwhile, Monica and Chandler meet another couple while on their honeymoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 16:00:00" d="2019-07-16 16:30:00"><n>Friends</n>    <k>Chandler hires a maid to help Monica but she thinks the maid is stealing her clothes. Meanwhile, Eric (Sean Penn) breaks up with Ursula and wants to date Phoebe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 16:30:00" d="2019-07-16 17:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VIII (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The One With The Stripper
Rachel tells her short-tempered father that she is pregnant with Ross' baby. Monica arranges to have a 'stripper' perform</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 17:00:00" d="2019-07-16 17:30:00"><n u="My Name Is Earl">My Name Is Earl IV (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Orphan Earl
When Earl tries to make amends to a man that he conned out of $100, he discovers that Joy and her friends are still conning him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 17:30:00" d="2019-07-16 18:00:00"><n u="My Name Is Earl">My Name Is Earl IV (14)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Got the Babysitter Pregnant
Earl tries to help his old babysitter, whom he got pregnant by poking holes in her condom, by whipping her deadbeat son into shape</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 18:00:00" d="2019-07-16 18:30:00"><n>Friends</n>    <k>Joey prepares for an interview with Soap Opera Digest, although he's afraid of saying something stupid that may jeopardize his career. again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 18:30:00" d="2019-07-16 19:00:00"><n>Friends</n>    <k>During her baby shower Rachel has the realization that she is totally unprepared to care for a baby, sparking her mother's offer to move in with Ross and her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 19:00:00" d="2019-07-16 19:30:00"><n>Friends</n>    <k>Monica's cooking skills get a bad review in a newspaper. After confronting the critic who wrote it, she decides to join a cooking class, with Joey in tow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 19:30:00" d="2019-07-16 20:00:00"><n>Friends</n>    <k>When Rachel's pregnancy goes beyond her due date, the pain makes Rachel increasingly irritable. Meanwhile, Chandler falls asleep at Joey's movie premiere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 20:00:00" d="2019-07-16 20:30:00"><n>Friends</n>    <k>Ross and Rachel arrive at the hospital. Ross' mum gives Ross her mother's engagement ring to propose to Rachel with</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 20:30:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00"><n>Friends</n>    <k>After forty-seven hours of labour, Rachel has her baby. However, Joey finds Ross' engagement ring and accidently proposes to a vulnerable Rachel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 21:30:00"><n>Friends</n>    <k>Following Joey's accidental proposal to Rachel, he tries to tell her it was an accident but can't find an opportune moment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 21:30:00" d="2019-07-16 22:00:00"><n>Friends</n>    <k>When Joey attempts to gain Ross' forgiveness for mistakenly asking Rachel to marry him, they end up in the emergency room</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 22:00:00" d="2019-07-16 23:00:00"><n u="Russell Howard's Good News">Russell Howard's Good News VII (3)</n>    <k>Russell Howard takes a cheeky trawl through the news. Tonight features; phone sex lines, a man stuck in a bin, squirrel cam, a sex toy mushroom, gay water</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 23:00:00" d="2019-07-16 23:30:00"><n u="The Ricky Gervais Show">The Ricky Gervais Show I (11)</n>    <k>Topics include; Karl's Valentine's Day advice, interpreting Wittgenstein and the rights of fish. Stephen and Ricky explain Kafka's 'Metamorphosis,'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-16 23:30:00" d="2019-07-17 00:00:00"><n u="The Ricky Gervais Show">The Ricky Gervais Show I (12)</n>    <k>Stephen and Ricky have Karl complete the 'Inside the Actor's Studio' questionnaire, Karl ponders organ donation in light of the afterlife, and Stephen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 00:00:00" d="2019-07-17 00:30:00"><n u="South Park">South Park IX (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ginger Kids
After giving a hate speech against 'the gingers', Cartman awakens the next day with a case of 'Gingervitus' and soon rallies against</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 00:30:00" d="2019-07-17 01:15:00"><n u="South Park">South Park XII (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Breast Cancer Show Ever
Cartman's reputation is at stake when he is too afraid to fight Wendy, who is furious about his breast cancer jibes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 01:15:00" d="2019-07-17 02:15:00"><n>Joe Rogan: Rocky Mountain High</n>    <k>Tune in to find out the real meaning of infinity, why Joe will lie to you on stage, and why Kim Kardashian is the most popular woman in the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 02:15:00" d="2019-07-17 02:45:00"><n>South Park</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% Cartman leads a campaign against the Jews after seeing &quot;The Passion Of The Christ.&quot; Meanwhile, Stan and Kenny try to get their money back from Mel Gibson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 02:45:00" d="2019-07-17 03:20:00"><n>South Park</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% A gang of kids from the O.C. challenge Stan do a dance-off. But before the big event, Butters must confront a painful event from his past</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 03:20:00" d="2019-07-17 03:55:00"><n>South Park</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% Cartman dresses up as a robot from Japan, sent to Butters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 03:55:00" d="2019-07-17 04:20:00"><n>South Park</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% When people from a poverty-stricken future travel back in time to find work, South Park residents accuse them of taking their jobs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 04:20:00" d="2019-07-17 04:45:00"><n>South Park</n><t>S</t>    <k>86% Stan refuses to vote in the school mascot election because his choices are a giant douche and a turd sandwich</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="721" o="2019-07-17 04:45:00" d="2019-07-17 05:10:00"><n u="My Name Is Earl">My Name Is Earl III (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Bad Earl
Earl and Randy are broke and homeless. So when he sees Ralph living the good life doing bad things, he declares that there is no karma and throws away the list</k>  </p>
</a>
