<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="44" t="2020-05-17 04:34:16"><p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 05:00:00" d="2020-05-24 05:30:00"><n u="Thrillbillies">Thrillbillies IV (13)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Thrillbillie Gold
Revisit the most misguided adventures, ridiculous stunts, and golden moments of the Thrillbillies' fourth season</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 05:30:00" d="2020-05-24 06:00:00"><n u="Thrillbillies">Thrillbillies IV (14)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Thrillbillies Road Trip
Everyone's favorite gang of ridiculous redneck hits the road for a group getaway to the Grand Canyon, with more twists, turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 06:00:00" d="2020-05-24 06:30:00"><n u="Thrillbillies">Thrillbillies IV (1)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Shrimpy the Kid
Insane stunts and shenanigans performed by the most loveable rednecks on the planet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 06:30:00" d="2020-05-24 07:00:00"><n u="Thrillbillies">Thrillbillies IV (2)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Whitney's Fairy Tale
&quot;The Thrillbillies crew brings a fairy tale to life for Whitney, the lone fem-billie of the redneck clan, and a big surprise is in store.&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 07:00:00" d="2020-05-24 07:30:00"><n u="World of X Games">World of X Games V (16)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Alex Ferreira - The Scenic Route
Join the world-champion skier Alex Ferreira as he travels across the globe to increase his love for the sport</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 07:30:00" d="2020-05-24 08:00:00"><n u="World of X Games">World of X Games V (15)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Woodward Peace Park Championships 2019</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 08:00:00" d="2020-05-24 09:15:00"><n>Modern Collective</n><t>O</t>    <k>Join six big names of the surfing world in a trip that changes your perspective on modern surfing. They will leave crystal waters and perfect pointbreaks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 09:15:00" d="2020-05-24 10:00:00"><n>Lost in Thought</n><t>O</t>    <k>A new surf video featuring the next generation of up &amp; coming surfers shot in California, Panama, Portugal, Mexico. Featuring Shane Borland, Eithan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 10:00:00" d="2020-05-24 10:30:00"><n u="World Surf Weekly">World Surf Weekly (9)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Episode 9
Watch the latest highlights from the surfing world with exclusive interviews, events and best moments spent in the water</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 10:30:00" d="2020-05-24 11:00:00"><n u="On Surfari">On Surfari (8)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Taiwan
Shannon and Shayne score epic, typhoon-powered waves in Taiwan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 11:00:00" d="2020-05-24 13:00:00"><n u="Kickin' It With Sneaker Steve">Kickin' It With Sneaker Steve (4)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Matt Halfhill
Episode 4 features Nice Kicks founder Matt Halfhill. Steve and Matt trace the history of Nice Kicks and the way the blog pushed sneaker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 13:00:00" d="2020-05-24 13:15:00"><n>Flow State</n><t>O</t>    <k>Three years after the great Bezerke part, Russell Bierke invites you to follow him on a new surfing adventure. A powerful audiovisual journey tastefully</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 13:15:00" d="2020-05-24 13:30:00"><n>Glitch</n><t>O</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 13:30:00" d="2020-05-24 14:30:00"><n>This Time Tomorrow</n><t>O</t>    <k>&quot;This Time Tomorrow&quot; follows the surfing moments of Dave Rastovich and Craig Anderson along the Pacific for eight days while trying to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 14:30:00" d="2020-05-24 15:00:00"><n>Sink or Swim</n><t>O</t>    <k>Swimming, fishing, surfing, snorkelling. the ocean offers a wide variety of amusements and this group of friends is determined to take the most of it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 15:00:00" d="2020-05-24 15:30:00"><n u="SLAM!">SLAM! (7)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Power bomb
Tons of thrills and spills. Millions of makes and breaks. Loads of lands and slams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 15:30:00" d="2020-05-24 16:00:00"><n u="SLAM!">SLAM! (8)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Session Over
Tons of thrills and spills. Millions of makes and breaks. Loads of lands and slams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 16:00:00" d="2020-05-24 16:30:00"><n u="Built To Shred">Built To Shred IV (7)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Flutag: Flight of the Shredheaded Stepchildren
Jeff and the crew take a flying leap in a new direction as they work around the clock to create</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 16:30:00" d="2020-05-24 17:00:00"><n u="Built To Shred">Built To Shred IV (8)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Sink or Swim
The BTS crew takes over the Projects Wake Skate Park in Florida to harvest floating fun, and make amazing obstacles that have everybody shredding on water</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 17:00:00" d="2020-05-24 17:30:00"><n u="Thrillbillies">Thrillbillies IV (7)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Tom Spond
Dusty may seem like a simple redneck, but this 'billie's got a few secrets up his sleeve that come in handy for a covert operation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 17:30:00" d="2020-05-24 18:00:00"><n u="Thrillbillies">Thrillbillies IV (8)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Clay's Dream
Clay has a crazy dream that stays with him, leaving more questions than answers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 18:00:00" d="2020-05-24 18:30:00"><n u="Maverick Moments">Maverick Moments (7)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Episode 7
After a significant stretch of flat waters, a storm in Antarctica sends massive swells to Pico Alto: the next stop on the Big Wave World Tour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 18:30:00" d="2020-05-24 19:00:00"><n u="Maverick Moments">Maverick Moments (8)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Episode 8
With Hurricane Marie intensifying to a category five, big wave surfers from around the world converge in Puerto Escondido, Mexico</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 19:00:00" d="2020-05-24 20:10:00"><n u="Kickin' It With Sneaker Steve">Kickin' It With Sneaker Steve (6)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Louis Colon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 20:10:00" d="2020-05-24 20:30:00"><n>The Come Up</n><t>O</t>    <k>Season 2
In this animated series, we have the opportunity to discover the adventures that some artists and athletes have had with several iconic sneaker models</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 20:30:00" d="2020-05-24 21:00:00"><n u="Bubba's World">Bubba's World II (4)</n><t>O</t>    <k>The Chick
James &quot;Bubba&quot; Stewart returns home from a grueling boot camp and goes wakeboarding. James gets tips from pro wakeboarder hottie Barrett Perlman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 21:00:00" d="2020-05-24 21:30:00"><n u="Bubba's World">Bubba's World II (5)</n><t>O</t>    <k>The Sponsors
James &quot;Bubba&quot; Stewart jets out to California for filming and photo shoots. James must spend the trip filming a Nike commercial</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 21:30:00" d="2020-05-24 22:00:00"><n u="Bubba's World">Bubba's World II (6)</n><t>O</t>    <k>The Doctor
The Outdoor Nationals Race season is half over and the former champion James &quot;Bubba&quot; Stewart is not able to ride. James is staying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 22:00:00" d="2020-05-24 23:00:00"><n>A Fly in the Champagne</n><t>O</t>    <k>The mythical surfing adversaries Kelly Slater and Andy Irons in a special documentary that follows the two icons through Indonesia showcasing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 23:00:00" d="2020-05-24 23:15:00"><n>X Games Oslo 2019</n><t>O</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 23:15:00" d="2020-05-24 23:30:00"><n>Ultimate X 2019</n><t>O</t>    <k>Africa's biggest action sports event is back. With BMX and skateboarding as new olympic sports, athletes from 28 different countries join the best African</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 23:30:00" d="2020-05-24 23:45:00"><n>HELride 2019</n><t>O</t>    <k>Fuel TV traveled to Helsinki Finland to attend one of the most iconic skateboarding celebration in Europe. An inner look at this competition which gathered</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 23:45:00" d="2020-05-25 00:00:00"><n>Darkfest</n><t>O</t>    <k>For the second year in a row, Stellenbosch, South Africa, has welcomed 15 world class free riders for another round of Darkfest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-25 00:00:00" d="2020-05-25 00:30:00"><n u="Thrillbillies">Thrillbillies III (6)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Try-Outs
Reefus gives a Thrillbillie &quot;wannabe&quot; a shot at the big time, Derek and Dusty do some tandem moto freestyle, and big jumps happen at the little swimmin' hole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-25 00:30:00" d="2020-05-25 01:00:00"><n u="Thrillbillies">Thrillbillies III (7)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Charity Work
Refus and Shrimpy try to help their fellow man, Crum jumps his snowmobile into the lake, Whitney meets her match in quad wars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-25 01:00:00" d="2020-05-25 01:20:00"><n>Cobblestone Riders - The Documentary</n><t>O</t>    <k>Is it skate or surf? Neither. Follow the story of crazy riders surfing tram tracks. Check out this new extreme sport invented in Portugal!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-25 01:20:00" d="2020-05-25 01:40:00"><n>Catch Up with Kevin Nikulski &amp; Dustyn Alt</n><t>O</t>    <k>When they are not attending competitions, flatland riders Kevin Nikulski and Dustyn Alt wander in their host city of the day in the look for new spots to ride</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-25 01:40:00" d="2020-05-25 02:00:00"><n>Bezerke</n><t>O</t>    <k>Russell Bierke is not the average Australian young surfer. Bitten by the surf bug since his early childhood, he now leads the new generation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-25 02:00:00" d="2020-05-25 02:30:00"><n u="The Adventures of Danny &amp; The Dingo">The Adventures of Danny &amp; The Dingo IV (6)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Trophy Truck Rally
Danny &amp; The Dingo take a trip to Odessa, TX to compete in a trophy truck race. The guys learn the race is dangerous and also that their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-25 02:30:00" d="2020-05-25 03:00:00"><n u="The Adventures of Danny &amp; The Dingo">The Adventures of Danny &amp; The Dingo IV (7)</n><t>O</t>    <k>European Vacation
The Grenade team kicks of their European vacation in the French Alps. A snowboard competition and pranks keep the team on their toes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-25 03:00:00" d="2020-05-25 03:30:00"><n u="The Great Ride Open">The Great Ride Open II (4)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Delta
The crew meets up with JJ Romans and explores the unchartered 9,000 acres of the adobe badland hills in Delta - famous for excellent trail riding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-25 03:30:00" d="2020-05-25 04:00:00"><n u="The Great Ride Open">The Great Ride Open II (5)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Montrose / Salina
The crew escapes the local crowds of the Flat Top area of Montrose, CO with a sneaky trip to the Quarry and winds up in Nielson's secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-25 04:00:00" d="2020-05-25 04:30:00"><n u="New Pollution">New Pollution III (7)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Ezekiel Lau, Maddy Schaffrick, Daniel Powers
Matt heads to Honolulu to meet surfer Ezekiel Lau, then visits Colorado snowboarder Maddy Schaffrick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-25 04:30:00" d="2020-05-25 05:00:00"><n u="New Pollution">New Pollution III (8)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Nick Rupp, Brooke, Voight, Louie Lopez
Matt visits surfer Nick Rupp in North Carolina. Then it's up to Canada to meet snowboarder Brooke Voight</k>  </p>
</a>
