<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="38" t="2020-05-16 04:51:51"><p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 05:00:00" d="2020-05-23 05:30:00"><n u="Maverick Moments">Maverick Moments (7)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Episode 7
After a significant stretch of flat waters, a storm in Antarctica sends massive swells to Pico Alto: the next stop on the Big Wave World Tour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 05:30:00" d="2020-05-23 06:00:00"><n u="Maverick Moments">Maverick Moments (8)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Episode 8
With Hurricane Marie intensifying to a category five, big wave surfers from around the world converge in Puerto Escondido, Mexico</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 06:00:00" d="2020-05-23 06:45:00"><n u="Riding Portugal">Riding Portugal (7)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Madeira
Joăo Kopke sets out on a new adventure of finding the best waves, this time in Madeira Island. Along the way, with him always carrying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 06:45:00" d="2020-05-23 07:30:00"><n u="Riding Portugal">Riding Portugal (8)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Riding North</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 07:30:00" d="2020-05-23 08:00:00"><n>Ideais2</n><t>O</t>    <k>The digital platform &quot;Olho de Peixe&quot; is celebrating 10 years and all the goodies are going to the fans with the release of its recent project IDEAIS2</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 08:00:00" d="2020-05-23 10:00:00"><n u="Kickin' It With Sneaker Steve">Kickin' It With Sneaker Steve (4)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Matt Halfhill
Episode 4 features Nice Kicks founder Matt Halfhill. Steve and Matt trace the history of Nice Kicks and the way the blog pushed sneaker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 10:00:00" d="2020-05-23 10:30:00"><n u="Maverick Moments">Maverick Moments (7)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Episode 7
After a significant stretch of flat waters, a storm in Antarctica sends massive swells to Pico Alto: the next stop on the Big Wave World Tour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 10:30:00" d="2020-05-23 11:00:00"><n u="Maverick Moments">Maverick Moments (8)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Episode 8
With Hurricane Marie intensifying to a category five, big wave surfers from around the world converge in Puerto Escondido, Mexico</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 11:00:00" d="2020-05-23 11:20:00"><n u="Shop Talk with Jason Stevenson">Shop Talk with Jason Stevenson (1)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Jason Stevenson, the head shaper and founder of JS - the brand with the recognizable tractor, spent some time in Portugal during which we caught up with him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 11:20:00" d="2020-05-23 11:40:00"><n u="Shop Talk with Matt Biolos">Shop Talk with Matt Biolos (2)</n><t>O</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 11:40:00" d="2020-05-23 12:00:00"><n u="Shop Talk with Semente Surfboards">Shop Talk with Semente Surfboards (3)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Semente surfboards have seen the day when Portugal started to emerge as a global surfing destination. The co-founders, Nick Uricchio and Miguel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 12:00:00" d="2020-05-23 13:00:00"><n>Scratching the Surface</n><t>O</t>    <k>Scratching the Surface shows us the first steps of Julian Wilson in the surfing scene, since his very first wave until he became a world renowned and talented surfer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 13:00:00" d="2020-05-23 13:30:00"><n u="World Surf Weekly">World Surf Weekly (9)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Episode 9
Watch the latest highlights from the surfing world with exclusive interviews, events and best moments spent in the water</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 13:30:00" d="2020-05-23 14:00:00"><n u="Drive Thru Australia">Drive Thru Australia VI (1)</n><t>O</t>    <k>The Departure
The Drive Thru crew, Donavon Frankenreiter, Benji Weatherley, and Pat O'Connell, embark on an adventure to Western Australia with newcomers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 14:00:00" d="2020-05-23 15:00:00"><n>Woodsy's World</n><t>O</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 15:00:00" d="2020-05-23 16:00:00"><n u="Occ-Cast">Occ-Cast (32)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Rob Machado
Occy welcomes surf legend Rob Machado. Find out more about the life and career of this famous Californian surfer who is also a musician and activist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 16:00:00" d="2020-05-23 16:20:00"><n>Beach Head</n><t>O</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 16:20:00" d="2020-05-23 16:40:00"><n>Bezerke</n><t>O</t>    <k>Russell Bierke is not the average Australian young surfer. Bitten by the surf bug since his early childhood, he now leads the new generation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 16:40:00" d="2020-05-23 17:00:00"><n>Blastoid</n><t>O</t>    <k>Blastoid is the video of Shaun Manners, the young australian surfer who is only 20 years old. Filmed in Western Australia, Shaun's clip gathers great</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 17:00:00" d="2020-05-23 17:25:00"><n>It's Not Only About Waves</n><t>O</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 17:25:00" d="2020-05-23 17:45:00"><n>Fogo de Graxa</n><t>O</t>    <k>'Fogo de Graxa' is the latest release of American free surfer Simon Hetrick. It retraces a fantastic 2019 season where the young man oscillates between</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 17:45:00" d="2020-05-23 18:00:00"><n>Highline</n><t>O</t>    <k>A movie celebrating surf as a way of life and featuring talented surfers from various horizons in the iconic J-Bay. Brilliantly directed by Kai Neville</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 18:00:00" d="2020-05-23 19:00:00"><n>Every Third Thursday</n><t>O</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 19:00:00" d="2020-05-23 19:45:00"><n u="Riding Portugal">Riding Portugal (5)</n><t>O</t>    <k>A Ride Through The South of Portugal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 19:45:00" d="2020-05-23 20:30:00"><n u="Riding Portugal">Riding Portugal (6)</n><t>O</t>    <k>A Ride Between Rivers
A Ride Between Rivers was filmed between rivers Tejo and Sado and it's an inspirational trip between Lisbon and Setúbal, discovering</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 20:30:00" d="2020-05-23 22:00:00"><n>The Search</n><t>O</t>    <k>What is it that makes us Explore? The restless urge to pack up and go. When the rumor of a perfect wave won't leave your mind. The anticipation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 22:00:00" d="2020-05-23 23:00:00"><n>Here &amp; Now</n><t>O</t>    <k>Here &amp; Now was filmed in just one day but it gathered more than 25 filmmakers and a stellar list of surfers such as Kelly Slater, Stephanie Gilmore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-23 23:00:00" d="2020-05-24 00:00:00"><n u="World of X Games">World of X Games V (4)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Real Ski 2019</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 00:00:00" d="2020-05-24 00:15:00"><n>X Games Oslo 2019</n><t>O</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 00:15:00" d="2020-05-24 00:30:00"><n>Ultimate X 2019</n><t>O</t>    <k>Africa's biggest action sports event is back. With BMX and skateboarding as new olympic sports, athletes from 28 different countries join the best African</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 00:30:00" d="2020-05-24 00:45:00"><n>HELride 2019</n><t>O</t>    <k>Fuel TV traveled to Helsinki Finland to attend one of the most iconic skateboarding celebration in Europe. An inner look at this competition which gathered</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 00:45:00" d="2020-05-24 01:00:00"><n>Darkfest</n><t>O</t>    <k>For the second year in a row, Stellenbosch, South Africa, has welcomed 15 world class free riders for another round of Darkfest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 01:00:00" d="2020-05-24 01:30:00"><n u="The Inertia">The Inertia (13)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Episode 13
In this episode of The Inertia, Mark Carter tells us about his origins, Kelly Slater explains the concept behind his new furniture business</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 01:30:00" d="2020-05-24 02:00:00"><n u="The Inertia">The Inertia (14)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Episode 14</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 02:00:00" d="2020-05-24 02:30:00"><n u="The Inertia">The Inertia (15)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Episode 15
In this episode of The Inertia, Greg Long tells us about the recovery he faced after the accident that almost took his life; Dane Reynolds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 02:30:00" d="2020-05-24 03:00:00"><n u="The Inertia">The Inertia (16)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Episode 16
Ace Buchan tells us what it was like to beat Kelly Slater. Sherry McConkey talks about yoga, love and living life to the fullest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 03:00:00" d="2020-05-24 04:30:00"><n>Stuntwood</n><t>O</t>    <k>Covering the life and death of a skateboard, &quot;Stuntwood&quot; chronicles the production process behind designing a board, from its first breath as a maple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2020-05-24 04:30:00" d="2020-05-24 05:00:00"><n>Sink or Swim</n><t>O</t>    <k>Swimming, fishing, surfing, snorkelling. the ocean offers a wide variety of amusements and this group of friends is determined to take the most of it</k>  </p>
</a>
