<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="45" t="2021-07-09 06:59:06"><p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 05:00:00" d="2021-07-16 05:18:00"><n u="Catch Up with Jorge Simőes">Catch Up with Jorge Simőes (6)</n><t>O</t>    <k>In this episode we talk to professional skater Jorge Simőes, one of the most promising athletes in the sport</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 05:18:00" d="2021-07-16 05:36:00"><n u="Catch Up with Gustavo Ribeiro">Catch Up with Gustavo Ribeiro (9)</n><t>O</t>    <k>In this episode we talk to the Portuguese skater Gustavo Ribeiro, one of the greatest talents in his country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 05:36:00" d="2021-07-16 06:00:00"><n u="Catch Up with Marcelo Garcia">Catch Up with Marcelo Garcia (10)</n><t>O</t>    <k>In this episode we talk to the Brazilian skater Marcelo Garcia, who participates in several audiovisual projects of brands such as Adidas, Contraste and Crail Trucks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 06:00:00" d="2021-07-16 06:30:00"><n u="Joy of Bike">Joy of Bike (5)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Episode 5</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 06:30:00" d="2021-07-16 06:50:00"><n u="Catch Up with Kevin Nikulski &amp; Dustyn Alt">Catch Up with Kevin Nikulski &amp; Dustyn Alt (1)</n><t>O</t>    <k>When they are not attending competitions, flatland riders Kevin Nikulski and Dustyn Alt wander in their host city of the day in the look for new spots to ride</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 06:50:00" d="2021-07-16 07:06:00"><n u="Catch Up with Adolf Silva">Catch Up with Adolf Silva (3)</n><t>O</t>    <k>In this episode, we talk to MTB rider Adolf Silva, a promising talent in the modality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 07:06:00" d="2021-07-16 07:30:00"><n>DarkFEST: The Darkumentary</n><t>O</t>    <k>Follow Sam Reynold's and his all time crew journey from the roots of Pure Darkness to DarkFEST and all the carnage in-between!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 07:30:00" d="2021-07-16 08:00:00"><n u="Joy of Bike">Joy of Bike (2)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Episode 2</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 08:00:00" d="2021-07-16 08:30:00"><n>Locked in Hellsend</n><t>O</t>    <k>Filmed in Lockdown at Hellsend, where the crew have been living their best lives shredding and building every day. From Dirt Jumps and Downhill Mountain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 08:30:00" d="2021-07-16 09:00:00"><n u="MXGP: Against All Odds">MXGP: Against All Odds (1)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Episode 1</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 09:00:00" d="2021-07-16 09:30:00"><n u="Getting Heated">Getting Heated (24)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Episode 24
Mick Fanning, Ross Williams and others clash on today's hottest topics with explosive debates, unfiltered takes, and bold predictions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 09:30:00" d="2021-07-16 10:00:00"><n u="World Surf Weekly">World Surf Weekly II (4)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Episode 4
Watch the latest highlights from the surfing world with exclusive interviews, events and best moments spent in the water</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 10:00:00" d="2021-07-16 11:00:00"><n u="WSL Presents">WSL Presents 2021 (6)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Rip Curl Rottnest Search</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 11:00:00" d="2021-07-16 11:40:00"><n>Living the Van Life</n><t>O</t>    <k>Vanlife is a lifestyle that becomes more popular day by day, mainly in the surf community. Therefore, &quot;Living the Vanlife&quot; is a documentary that looks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 11:40:00" d="2021-07-16 12:00:00"><n>Pablito</n><t>O</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 12:00:00" d="2021-07-16 13:00:00"><n u="Rad Season">Rad Season (10)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Shaun Tomson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 13:00:00" d="2021-07-16 13:15:00"><n u="Firsthand">Firsthand 13 XIII (1)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Simon Hetrick
Meet Simon Hetrick, a surfer from Maryland, USA, who has found Ericeira to be a special place to test new surfboards and to expand on his surfing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 13:15:00" d="2021-07-16 13:45:00"><n u="Firsthand">Firsthand 13 XIII (2)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Matt Bromley
Join Matt Bromley in his hometown of Kommetjie, South Africa, and learn more about the journey of this big wave rider who grew up surfing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 13:45:00" d="2021-07-16 14:00:00"><n u="Firsthand">Firsthand 13 XIII (3)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Victoria Vergara</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 14:00:00" d="2021-07-16 15:00:00"><n u="Riding Portugal">Riding Portugal (8)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Riding North</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 15:00:00" d="2021-07-16 15:30:00"><n u="Drive Thru New Zealand">Drive Thru New Zealand V (2)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Kiwis, Ozzies and Occys
Ozzie and Occy finally arrive, and everyone heads south to pick up Maz in Gisborne. Then danger awaits when the crew goes water-rafting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 15:30:00" d="2021-07-16 16:00:00"><n u="Drive Thru New Zealand">Drive Thru New Zealand V (3)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Handbags
A fight breaks out between Pat and Donavon, a member of the crew gets hurt, and Occy tries out his new wetsuit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 16:00:00" d="2021-07-16 16:30:00"><n u="The Moto: Inside The Outdoors">The Moto: Inside The Outdoors II (5)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Keep Fighting
With the championship title near Dungey's grasp, Brett Metcalfe and Andrew Short gear up to battle for second place overall in the 450cc Outdoor Series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 16:30:00" d="2021-07-16 17:00:00"><n u="The Moto: Inside The Outdoors">The Moto: Inside The Outdoors II (6)</n><t>O</t>    <k>A Waking Giant
An inside look at one of the most grueling professional race series in the world; the AMA Pro Motocross Series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 17:00:00" d="2021-07-16 18:00:00"><n u="Rad Season">Rad Season (11)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Episode 11
Join Oli Russell-Cowan and his guests on the Action Sports and Adventure Show where they chat about pushing boundaries daily to achieve the ultimate adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 18:00:00" d="2021-07-16 18:45:00"><n u="Riding Portugal">Riding Portugal (2)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Exploring the Coast of Freedom
Joăo Kopke continues to explore Portugal and discover the best that nature and Portuguese culture have to offer! See how Joăo Kopke combines adrenaline and tranquility along the Coast of Freedom with the Riding Portugal series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 18:45:00" d="2021-07-16 19:30:00"><n u="Riding Portugal">Riding Portugal (3)</n><t>O</t>    <k>A Ride through my City
Joăo Kopke continues to explore Portugal and discover the best that nature and Portuguese culture have to offer! See how the Portuguese Surfer enjoys Lisbon, his hometown, with this new episode from Riding Portugal series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 19:30:00" d="2021-07-16 20:00:00"><n u="Shop Talk with Jason Stevenson">Shop Talk with Jason Stevenson (1)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Jason Stevenson, the head shaper and founder of JS - the brand with the recognizable tractor, spent some time in Portugal during which we caught up with him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 20:00:00" d="2021-07-16 20:30:00"><n u="The Adventures of Danny &amp; The Dingo">The Adventures of Danny &amp; The Dingo IV (13)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Lazy Americans
It's the last day of the trip and Dingo, Tom and Dustin are targets for paintball-wakeboarding. They all hit the glacier for the last day of riding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 20:30:00" d="2021-07-16 21:00:00"><n u="The Adventures of Danny &amp; The Dingo">The Adventures of Danny &amp; The Dingo V (1)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Spread the Shred
The fifth season premiere opens with Danny and The Dingo beginning their mission to &quot;Spread the Shred&quot; across the globe by living</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 21:00:00" d="2021-07-16 21:30:00"><n u="Thrillbillies">Thrillbillies III (13)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Good Times
Refus looks back on some of the Thrillbillies' more historic moments, featuring Gavin, Shrimpy, Dusty, and Pat. Great moments in Thrillbillie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 21:30:00" d="2021-07-16 22:00:00"><n u="Thrillbillies">Thrillbillies IV (1)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Shrimpy the Kid
Insane stunts and shenanigans performed by the most loveable rednecks on the planet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 22:00:00" d="2021-07-16 22:30:00"><n u="Built To Shred">Built To Shred III (13)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Surf Rail of Death 2
Jeff King and the crew try to make lightning strike twice and this Surf Rail proves to be a lot harder than the last</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 22:30:00" d="2021-07-16 23:00:00"><n u="Built To Shred">Built To Shred IV (1)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Shred Ranch RIP</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-16 23:00:00" d="2021-07-17 00:00:00"><n u="Occ-Cast">Occ-Cast (29)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Tom Curren
In episode 29 of the Occ-Cast, Occy is joined by former rival and fellow legend, Tom Curren. The two talk about their epic head-to-head match</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-17 00:00:00" d="2021-07-17 00:30:00"><n u="Joy of Bike">Joy of Bike (3)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Episode 3</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-17 00:30:00" d="2021-07-17 01:00:00"><n u="Snowchef Japan">Snowchef Japan (1)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Episode 1
Japan is calling and it is time to an adventure into a little of Japanese unknown. First stop, lost in the underbelly of Tokyo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-17 01:00:00" d="2021-07-17 01:30:00"><n u="Montreal Skate District">Montreal Skate District (1)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Episode 1
In the first episode, we discovered the Ville-Marie and Hochelaga-Maisonneuve areas through the skaters Seb Lucas and Seb Carranza</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-17 01:30:00" d="2021-07-17 02:00:00"><n>Taj Burrow: Life After The Tour</n><t>O</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-17 02:00:00" d="2021-07-17 02:30:00"><n u="Thrillbillies">Thrillbillies IV (9)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Cam's Roll
Always the adventurer, Cam enlists the Thrillbillies' help to take his life in his hands and barrel-roll a buggy – but can he manage such a ridiculous stunt?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-17 02:30:00" d="2021-07-17 03:00:00"><n u="Thrillbillies">Thrillbillies IV (10)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Extreme Skating
Skateboarding gets the Thrillbillies treatment when Johnny and Whitney try to take it to the next level, with mixed (and hilarious) results</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-17 03:00:00" d="2021-07-17 03:30:00"><n u="Thrillbillies">Thrillbillies IV (11)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Bikin' Buddies
Derek and Dusty team up to test their mettle on tandem bikes, but can they manage the thrills -- and spills -- with double the danger?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-17 03:30:00" d="2021-07-17 04:00:00"><n u="Thrillbillies">Thrillbillies IV (12)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Sir Crumsalot &amp; King Shrimpy
Crum takes Shrimpy on a medieval adventure. Also, in this episode, paper bag rally cross, pond gap slip n' slide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-17 04:00:00" d="2021-07-17 04:30:00"><n u="SLAM!">SLAM! (3)</n><t>O</t>    <k>On the couch
Tons of thrills and spills. Heaps of whamies and wipeouts. Special guest slammers Chris Grenier, Dan Drehobl, John John Florence, and Dennis Enarson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="723" o="2021-07-17 04:30:00" d="2021-07-17 05:00:00"><n u="SLAM!">SLAM! (4)</n><t>O</t>    <k>Taste of Glory
A bunch of ouchies and boo boos with no kiss to make it feel better. Special guest slammers John Peacy, Dave Abair, JP Tomich, and Lizard King</k>  </p>
</a>
