<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="13" t="2020-05-15 04:51:02"><p id_tv="731" o="2020-05-22 05:50:00" d="2020-05-22 07:30:00"><n>Rosa</n><t>D</t>    <k>Rosa, a quirky and eccentric French girl in London, decides to give up men in order to write a book. She soon finds her vow of abstinence much harder than expected and turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="731" o="2020-05-22 07:30:00" d="2020-05-22 09:30:00"><n>Educating reeves</n>    <k>Caroline's rustic existence is shattered when petrol-head, Reeves, drives into her picturesque valley with the purpose of buying her land to build a raceway. Reeves soon discovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="731" o="2020-05-22 09:30:00" d="2020-05-22 12:10:00"><n>Copz</n>    <k>In a world filled with criminals and misfits, justice takes a back seat to some sucking and fucking. These cops throw their pussies around to keep control over the bums that steal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="731" o="2020-05-22 12:10:00" d="2020-05-22 13:45:00"><n>Kiss, the</n>    <k>The Kiss is Lisa Loves' Fifth film for Daring Media Group and this time she has decided to look deep into the art of kissing. His fingertip traced the line of her body</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="731" o="2020-05-22 13:45:00" d="2020-05-22 15:20:00"><n>Style</n><t>D</t>    <k>She was the type of woman who knew what she wanted and he was the type of man who could give it to her. As the jazzy notes filled the smokey atmosphere the sexual chemistry played</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="731" o="2020-05-22 15:20:00" d="2020-05-22 16:50:00"><n>Stilettos</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="731" o="2020-05-22 16:50:00" d="2020-05-22 18:20:00"><n>Rock chicks</n>    <k>The music filled the room as the smell of his leathers turned her on, penetrating her softly again and again, her whispers like butterflies fluttering, fluttering for a brief</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="731" o="2020-05-22 18:20:00" d="2020-05-22 20:00:00"><n>Playing</n><t>D</t>    <k>The quality of the mind sometimes engages in activities not conventionally viewed as being sexual in nature but enhances the sexual bond between lovers alike</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="731" o="2020-05-22 20:00:00" d="2020-05-22 22:30:00"><n>Night crawlers</n><t>D</t>    <k>As the night falls, the hedonism begins. The City is calling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="731" o="2020-05-22 22:30:00" d="2020-05-23 00:05:00"><n>Mystique</n><t>D</t>    <k>As the subtle underlying sexual tones of her voice echoed the room the mysteriousness of the shadowy man sat watching</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="731" o="2020-05-23 00:05:00" d="2020-05-23 01:40:00"><n>Into the dark</n>    <k>With Into the Dark, Joey takes us into a dark fantasy world in which girls are indulged with their wildest thoughts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="731" o="2020-05-23 01:40:00" d="2020-05-23 03:15:00"><n>Inspiration</n><t>D</t>    <k>As the radio tuned into his Inspiration she walked into a new sexual awareness and the darkness became light</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="731" o="2020-05-23 03:15:00" d="2020-05-23 05:20:00"><n>Exploring fantasies</n>    <k>With Exploring Fantasies I look into the fantasy not only for its sexual nature but also for the chemistry that it brings to my camera</k>  </p>
</a>
