<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="31" t="2020-05-13 04:32:50"><p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 05:00:00" d="2020-05-20 06:00:00"><n>I HAVE SEEN THE EARTH CHANGE - CANADA: THE DISAPPEARING ICE SHELF</n><t>D</t>    <k>A courageous and spirited Inuit woman, Ulaayu Pilurtuut lives in the heart of the Canadian Great North, where she teaches Inuktut, language of her people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 06:00:00" d="2020-05-20 07:00:00"><n>MAKE ME A LOG BOAT!</n><t>D</t>    <k>Around the Parandu lake, two groups of volunteers go about to make a logboat using antique tools and getting back in a 5,000 years journey while meeting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 07:00:00" d="2020-05-20 08:00:00"><n>SCEPTICS - TRANSGENIC FOOD</n><t>D</t>    <k>Do we know what it is? Is it harmless or should we fear its possible effects? Will it be able to resolve the world’s hunger problems? Will we be able to eradicate malnutrition thanks to genetic engineering? Only time will tell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 08:00:00" d="2020-05-20 09:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE - MASAI</n><t>D</t>    <k>In this chapter, Claudio and his team venture into Kenya to reach the villa inhabited by the Maasai tribe. Before heading to Kenya from Tanzania, Claudio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 09:00:00" d="2020-05-20 10:00:00"><n u="ANCIENT CULTURE -">ANCIENT CULTURE - (7)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 10:00:00" d="2020-05-20 11:00:00"><n>BEAUTIFUL MINDS - PABLO VALENZUELA PHD</n><t>D</t>    <k>Albert Einstein said that the mind is like a parachute: it only works if we have it opened. Beautiful Minds is a documentary series that summarizes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 11:00:00" d="2020-05-20 11:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - VI (5)</n><t>D</t>    <k>SPACE FLIGHT: A look at the history of NASA and the space program through the decades including the many triumphs and all too many tragedies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 11:30:00" d="2020-05-20 12:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - VI (6)</n><t>D</t>    <k>ANATOMY OF A DEPARTURE: Get up and go? Not quite. The process of just leaving the airport sometimes involves talking to a half a dozen separate air traffic controllers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 12:00:00" d="2020-05-20 12:30:00"><n u="TAXI TO ASIA - MIDNIGHT COWBOYS">TAXI TO ASIA - MIDNIGHT COWBOYS (HO CHI MINH VS TOKYO)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Ho Chi Minh: This post-communist city is trying to rival Bangkok and won’t let anything stand in the way of its accelerating economy. Our taxi driver</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 12:30:00" d="2020-05-20 13:00:00"><n u="GOING SOUTH -">GOING SOUTH - (6)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Going South: Cycling through the Americas an adventurous environmental cycling documentary. As the climate changes, an environmental crisis is proclaimed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 13:00:00" d="2020-05-20 14:00:00"><n>DON'T FORGET YOUR PASSPORT - SRI LANKA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Host Gordon Sivell explores the tropical island of Sri Lanka off the southern tip of India. He finds it to be a crowded destination teetering</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 14:00:00" d="2020-05-20 14:30:00"><n u="TRAVEL PLAN - CORUNA - PART">TRAVEL PLAN - CORUNA - PART 1</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 14:30:00" d="2020-05-20 15:00:00"><n u="TRAVEL PLAN - CORUNA - PART">TRAVEL PLAN - CORUNA - PART 2</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 15:00:00" d="2020-05-20 16:00:00"><n u="MUNDO AD PORTAS -">MUNDO AD PORTAS - I (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 16:00:00" d="2020-05-20 16:30:00"><n u="ANIMAL ALLIES -">ANIMAL ALLIES - II (9)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Two lives are on the line in this week’s Animal Allies, but thankfully, both are in the skilled hands of veterinarian Celia Newlove</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 16:30:00" d="2020-05-20 17:00:00"><n u="ANIMAL ALLIES -">ANIMAL ALLIES - II (10)</n><t>D</t>    <k>In this week’s Animal Allies, the desperate fight to save the life of a much-loved pet, stricken with cancer. Animal Doctor Tanya Schoeman advises</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 17:00:00" d="2020-05-20 18:00:00"><n u="TIMELESS TREASURES -">TIMELESS TREASURES - (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>A series celebrating the extraordinary preservation of human heritage. Discover the world’s most beautiful sites in an exceptional series of short programs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 18:00:00" d="2020-05-20 19:00:00"><n>POSTCARD PERFECT - REUNION</n><t>D</t>    <k>Reunion Island is a little corner of paradise to the east of Madagascar. But behind the bright white beaches, glittering sea and sunny skies hides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 19:00:00" d="2020-05-20 19:30:00"><n u="RACING GREEN -">RACING GREEN - (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>RACING GREEN is a 3 hour long BBC World News TV series about an electric car world record established by 8 engineering graduates from London. They succeed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 19:30:00" d="2020-05-20 20:00:00"><n u="RACING GREEN -">RACING GREEN - (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Racing Green expedition starts with a heavy rainstorm in Alaska - a serious challenge in an open top electric car packed with a 600 volt battery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 20:00:00" d="2020-05-20 21:00:00"><n>NOMADS - FREESKIING THE WASATCH MOUNTAINS IN UTAH</n><t>D</t>    <k>A season accessing the front and back of Wasatch mountains from one of America’s best winter sport gems: Salt Lake City, Utah</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 21:00:00" d="2020-05-20 22:00:00"><n>BIOTIFUL PLANET - MADAGSCAR</n><t>D</t>    <k>A nine-part series on the treasures of France’s overseas territories. The French overseas territories are a treasure trove of biodiversity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 22:00:00" d="2020-05-20 22:30:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - ESCAPE TO CAPE VERDE">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - ESCAPE TO CAPE VERDE (CAPE VERDE)</n><t>D</t>    <k>On the Island of Boa Vista, in Cape Verde, along the coast and also inland to get acquainted with its many different faces. Together with Eliseu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 22:30:00" d="2020-05-20 23:00:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - WHERE NATURE IS SACRED">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - WHERE NATURE IS SACRED (GAMBIA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>The smallest country in Africa, The Gambia, rises from and follows the river of the same name, but most of all it is a country surrounded by Senegal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 23:00:00" d="2020-05-21 00:00:00"><n u="ASSASSINATION">ASSASSINATION II</n><t>D</t>    <k>Assassination II, portrays the murder of Venustiano Carranza, Francisco Villa and Alvaro Obregon, occurred during the last years of the Mexican Revolution</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 00:00:00" d="2020-05-21 01:00:00"><n>TECHNO-SCIENCE - EL DESAFIO CIENTIFICO EN EL CAMBIO CLIMATICO</n><t>D</t>    <k>Andrea Obaid and Cristián Campos visit the south of our country. Andrea goes to Dichato to study the effects of hypoxia, lack of oxygen at sea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 01:00:00" d="2020-05-21 02:00:00"><n>NOMAD'S LAND - CANADA</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Great North. ‘up north’ as the Canadians say, is one of the most isolated regions in the world. Although the Great North occupies 40% of Canada’s total</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 02:00:00" d="2020-05-21 03:00:00"><n>IN CONCERT - SURKALEN</n><t>M</t>    <k>Surkalén is composed of three Chileans from Valparaíso and a Russian-Canadian violinist. The word Surkalén consists of the words Sur, for the South</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 03:00:00" d="2020-05-21 03:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - V (6)</n><t>D</t>    <k>PYROTECHNICS: We showcase Rich Gibson, the man behind some of the most explosive airshow spectacles. HANGAR FLYING 2: Kurtis, Sara, and Anthony debate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 03:30:00" d="2020-05-21 04:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - V (7)</n><t>D</t>    <k>100 YEARS OF COMMERCIAL FLIGHT: The highs and the lows of an industry that has become an essential part of our lives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 04:00:00" d="2020-05-21 05:00:00"><n>EARTH: CRACKS OF RAGE: GROWLING EARTH</n><t>D</t>    <k>Rescuers testify about their involvement, specialists explain to us how these catastrophes come to life and how they evolve Victims explain</k>  </p>
</a>
