<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="37" t="2020-05-10 04:30:59"><p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 05:00:00" d="2020-05-17 05:30:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - STOCKHOLM</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Shards set sail from the island of Gotland and begin exploring the vast archipelagos along the east coast of Sweden. They fish for flounder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 05:30:00" d="2020-05-17 06:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - GOTA CANAL</n><t>D</t>    <k>It's September and Paul and Sheryl travel inland waterways across Sweden taking their sailboat from Stockholm on the east coast to Gothenburg</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 06:00:00" d="2020-05-17 07:00:00"><n>IN CONCERT - JOSÉ MARIA GIANELLI</n><t>M</t>    <k>Tangos, milongas and other melodies. This group sings the joys and sorrows of the immigrant - relating the story of Argentine songwriter and pianist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 07:00:00" d="2020-05-17 07:30:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - VIETNAM'S YOUNG AND RESTLESS URBANITES</n><t>D</t>    <k>At the turn of the 21st century, all pundits were predicting the dawn f the so-called &quot;Asian Century&quot;. But even If no one today disputes the geopolitcal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 07:30:00" d="2020-05-17 08:00:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - SHANGHAI'S TWO-CHILDREN POLICY</n><t>D</t>    <k>China, with a population of 1. 3 billion, would hardly be in need of a baby boom. However, Shanghai paints a starkly different picture. Ageing faster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 08:00:00" d="2020-05-17 08:30:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - BUCHAREST</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 08:30:00" d="2020-05-17 09:00:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - BUDAPEST</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 09:00:00" d="2020-05-17 09:30:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - JERUSALEM GENERAL</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 09:30:00" d="2020-05-17 10:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF MEXICO - THE COLONIAL HEARTLAND</n><t>D</t>    <k>Presenter Charlie Ottley explores Mexico's dusty heartland and the beguilingly beautiful state of Michoacan where he learns some culinary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 10:00:00" d="2020-05-17 10:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - III (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>P-19: Wayne Boggs introduces us to his historic P-19 trainer aircraft. Winter Flying: How do pilots prepare for winter flying? Anthony shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 10:30:00" d="2020-05-17 11:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - III (5)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Border Patrol Aerial Unit: U. S. Customs and Border Protection in action. from the air! Basler DC-3 Conversions: Just when you think a classic old airliner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 11:00:00" d="2020-05-17 11:30:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - EAST COAST OF IRELAND</n><t>D</t>    <k>From Waterford on the southeast coast of Ireland, Paul and Sheryl sail north along the coast of the Irish Sea visiting small fishing ports</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 11:30:00" d="2020-05-17 12:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - CRINAN CANAL</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Shards begin their visit to Scotland at the Mull of Kintyre and make a trip through the Crinan Canal visiting small inland towns and hiking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 12:00:00" d="2020-05-17 12:30:00"><n>ANIMAL ALLIES - PLUGGER THE HORSE</n><t>D</t>    <k>In Australia, Animal Doctors have to perform emergency surgery to help a young racehorse that has stopped breathing, while in the UK Animal Helper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 12:30:00" d="2020-05-17 13:00:00"><n>ANIMAL ALLIES - LACK OF VITAMIN A IN LIONS</n><t>D</t>    <k>In Animal Doctors, Doctor Rogers has a problem with the local lion pride on the Kapama Game reserve when some of the cubs start dying, while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 13:00:00" d="2020-05-17 13:30:00"><n u="ALL ABOUT ANIMALS -">ALL ABOUT ANIMALS - (10)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 13:30:00" d="2020-05-17 14:00:00"><n u="ALL ABOUT ANIMALS -">ALL ABOUT ANIMALS - (11)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 14:00:00" d="2020-05-17 15:00:00"><n>DON'T FORGET YOUR PASSPORT - MALAYSIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Adventure traveler Gordon Sivell tours an old Japanese Prisoner of War Camp in the jungles of Malaysia, and just off the coast of southern Thailand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 15:00:00" d="2020-05-17 15:30:00"><n u="TRAJECTORY -">TRAJECTORY - (5)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Today, although a cloud of satellites surrounds the planet, many records set during the early decades of space exploration remain unsurpassed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 15:30:00" d="2020-05-17 16:00:00"><n u="TRAJECTORY -">TRAJECTORY - (6)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Today, although a cloud of satellites surrounds the planet, many records set during the early decades of space exploration remain unsurpassed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 16:00:00" d="2020-05-17 17:30:00"><n>ZAPATA VIVE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Ten years of war, more than one million dead. The struggle for the political freedom transforms in a conflict for the ground from the appearance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 17:30:00" d="2020-05-17 18:00:00"><n>THE PATH IS THE GOAL - EVEREST 2012</n><t>D</t>    <k>Even if you have a complete climbing group, there are mountains that are not for beginners and sometimes not even for experts. The &quot;Path is the Goal&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 18:00:00" d="2020-05-17 19:00:00"><n>BEAUTIFUL MINDS - FERNANDO MONCKEBERG</n><t>D</t>    <k>Albert Einstein said that the mind is like a parachute: it only works if we have it opened. Beautiful Minds is a documentary series that summarizes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 19:00:00" d="2020-05-17 19:30:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - EAST COAST OF IRELAND</n><t>D</t>    <k>From Waterford on the southeast coast of Ireland, Paul and Sheryl sail north along the coast of the Irish Sea visiting small fishing ports</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 19:30:00" d="2020-05-17 20:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - CRINAN CANAL</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Shards begin their visit to Scotland at the Mull of Kintyre and make a trip through the Crinan Canal visiting small inland towns and hiking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 20:00:00" d="2020-05-17 21:30:00"><n>TIERRA DE PATOGONES</n><t>D</t>    <k>The gauchos del mar pursue their goal of surfing at one of the southernmost areas of the world: Staten Island. They travel with a truck and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 21:30:00" d="2020-05-17 22:00:00"><n u="ANIMAL ALLIES -">ANIMAL ALLIES - II (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the UK, we meet our Animal Allies vet, Doctor Martin Andrews. Sparky the fox terrier has a hernia and Dr. Andrews prepares for what should be a routine operation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 22:00:00" d="2020-05-17 23:00:00"><n>DESTINATION WILDERNESS - AFRICA, BLUE GOLD BENEATH THE SANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Embark on five thrilling adventures into the wild and explore the most extraordinary landscapes as you are led though water, ice, rocks and fire alongside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-17 23:00:00" d="2020-05-18 00:00:00"><n>MAKE ME A LOG BOAT!</n><t>D</t>    <k>Around the Parandu lake, two groups of volunteers go about to make a logboat using antique tools and getting back in a 5,000 years journey while meeting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-18 00:00:00" d="2020-05-18 00:30:00"><n>KITCHEN RUSH - BRUSSELS - RESTAURANTS LA MAREE &amp; L'ALBAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>A journey to some of the best restaurants around the globe. We're going to try everything from sushi to steak tartare. Surprise some of the great Chefs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-18 00:30:00" d="2020-05-18 01:00:00"><n>KITCHEN RUSH - MARSEILLE - RESTAURANTS L'EPUISTTE &amp; LAURACEE</n><t>D</t>    <k>A journey to some of the best restaurants around the globe. We're going to try everything from sushi to steak tartare. Surprise some of the great Chefs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-18 01:00:00" d="2020-05-18 02:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE - MASAI MARA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra (conductor) part to Kenya to go into the Massai Mara National Park, one of the most beautiful nature reserves of Planet Earth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-18 02:00:00" d="2020-05-18 02:30:00"><n>LOW COST - PARIS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Each city is in its native language (ie. Parisis in French, Rome is in Italian, Berlin is in German, etc. with English Scripts) showing the viewer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-18 02:30:00" d="2020-05-18 03:00:00"><n>LOW COST - PRAGUE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Each city is in its native language (ie. Parisis in French, Rome is in Italian, Berlin is in German, etc. with English Scripts) showing the viewer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-18 03:00:00" d="2020-05-18 03:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - IV (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>FLS Microjet: This spunky little jet weighs in at a mere 400 pounds! We profile this incredible (and tiny) aircraft and its full-sized pilot. SR-71:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-18 03:30:00" d="2020-05-18 04:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - IV (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Zenith 801: No runway? No problem! We challenge the limits faced in the world of bush flying in this amazing utilitarian aircraft. Legacy Flight:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-18 04:00:00" d="2020-05-18 05:00:00"><n>THE DESCENT</n><t>D</t>    <k>Is it possible to travel through time? By digging deep into caves and rocks, let's travel through time to the latest Ice Age</k>  </p>
</a>
