<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="35" t="2020-05-26 04:33:55"><p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 05:00:00" d="2020-06-02 06:00:00"><n>SCEPTICS - DID WE REALLY LAND A MAN ON THE MOON</n><t>D</t>    <k>Theory questioning whether man set foot on the Moon in 1969</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 06:00:00" d="2020-06-02 06:30:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - AFRICA-JINKA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 06:30:00" d="2020-06-02 07:00:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - JORDAN-PETRA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 07:00:00" d="2020-06-02 07:30:00"><n>FISH LIFE - COLOURS CODE</n><t>D</t>    <k>In tropical seas, the first impression is stunning. It’s a firework of colours competing in vividness and intensity: red, yellow, blue, green</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 07:30:00" d="2020-06-02 08:00:00"><n>FISH LIFE - A SEA OF LOVE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Submarine sexuality displays some very strange facets. Anything is possible underwater from behaviors close to ours to the most disturbing. There are those</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 08:00:00" d="2020-06-02 09:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE - HIMBA</n><t>D</t>    <k>A curious reporter, outdoor lover, will not rest until he shows us every mystery of the wild, black heart of Central Africa, discovering the stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 09:00:00" d="2020-06-02 09:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - III (7)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Kickin’ the Tires: How do you shop for a used aircraft? Anthony takes us through the process of finding that perfect used aircraft for you! Sonex:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 09:30:00" d="2020-06-02 10:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - III (8)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mackinac Island: Our fly-in destination of the year. This rustic Michigan area has plenty to offer and is accessible via its secluded private airport</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 10:00:00" d="2020-06-02 11:00:00"><n>SOUTHERN FLOWER IN THE PACIFIC - TOWARDS POLYNESIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Great Adventure starts between Mexico and the Marquesas Islands, over 15 jrs ocean! a journey that goes well without great storm and with the passage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 11:00:00" d="2020-06-02 12:00:00"><n u="ANCIENT CULTURE -">ANCIENT CULTURE - (13)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 12:00:00" d="2020-06-02 12:30:00"><n>PASSPORT TO EXPLORE - LAS VEGAS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Passport to Explore is an internationallysyndicated half hour educational travel ad-venture series designed for 13-16 year olds. Syndicated on stations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 12:30:00" d="2020-06-02 13:00:00"><n>PASSPORT TO EXPLORE - LOS ANGELES</n><t>D</t>    <k>Passport to Explore is an internationallysyndicated half hour educational travel ad-venture series designed for 13-16 year olds. Syndicated on stations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 13:00:00" d="2020-06-02 13:30:00"><n u="ALL ABOUT ANIMALS -">ALL ABOUT ANIMALS - (17)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 13:30:00" d="2020-06-02 14:00:00"><n u="ALL ABOUT ANIMALS -">ALL ABOUT ANIMALS - (18)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 14:00:00" d="2020-06-02 15:00:00"><n>SPIRULINA: THE AMAZING ALGAE</n><t>D</t>    <k>The film presents an exploration of a nearly invisible fresh water algae with scientific name Spirulina Arthrospira Platensis. But what exactly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 15:00:00" d="2020-06-02 16:00:00"><n u="MUNDO AD PORTAS -">MUNDO AD PORTAS - I (9)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 16:00:00" d="2020-06-02 17:00:00"><n>NOMADS - WHITEWATER KAYAKING IN NORWAY</n><t>D</t>    <k>International kayakers travel the whitewater of Norway and show us the natural beauty that Norway has to offer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 17:00:00" d="2020-06-02 17:30:00"><n u="RACING GREEN -">RACING GREEN - (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>After 5 star accommodation in Seattle the Racing Green engineers continue their epic journey across the USA. They meet a team of Zeromotorcycle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 17:30:00" d="2020-06-02 18:00:00"><n u="RACING GREEN -">RACING GREEN - (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Getting into Mexico makes the team nervous because they hear more and more stories about drug wars along the US border. Exactly in that danger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 18:00:00" d="2020-06-02 19:00:00"><n>PANTANAL, THE JAGUAR'S LAST SANCTUARY</n><t>D</t>    <k>Situated in south-west Brazil, the Pantanal basin is the largest area of wetland in the world. This very particular ecosystem is home to a biodiversity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 19:00:00" d="2020-06-02 20:00:00"><n>DESTINATION WILDERNESS - ARCTIC, SEPENTRION</n><t>D</t>    <k>I’m about to take you across the Great North, from Denmark to Greenland via Iceland, in the footsteps of the conquering Vikings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 20:00:00" d="2020-06-02 20:30:00"><n u="TRAJECTORY -">TRAJECTORY - (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Today, although a cloud of satellites surrounds the planet, many records set during the early decades of space exploration remain unsurpassed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 20:30:00" d="2020-06-02 21:00:00"><n u="TRAJECTORY -">TRAJECTORY - (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Today, although a cloud of satellites surrounds the planet, many records set during the early decades of space exploration remain unsurpassed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 21:00:00" d="2020-06-02 22:00:00"><n>POSTCARD PERFECT - SAINT MARTIN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Saint Martin, a small Franco-Dutch island in the French Caribbean, is a tourist and tax haven. However, the postcard has been fading for several years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 22:00:00" d="2020-06-02 22:30:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - LAOS PDR'S BLESSING OR BANE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Twenty years ago, Laos was one of the top 10 poorest countries in the world. Today, the Lao economy is growing at an impressive rate of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 22:30:00" d="2020-06-02 23:00:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - SINGAPORE LIGHTENS UP</n><t>D</t>    <k>Since a decade ago, Singapore has made plans to re-brand itself as a Renaissance City of arts and culture. There were strong economic imperatives for this</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 23:00:00" d="2020-06-03 00:00:00"><n>THE NAZI NETWORK IN MEXICO</n><t>D</t>    <k>In 1985, had been released the documents about the nazis activities during the world War II in Mexico. But, what could be Hitler's interest in a country away from war? The answer that had remained hidden and generated legends, tries to be unveiled through this documentary that narrates and recreates Nazi activities in Mexico during World War II</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 00:00:00" d="2020-06-03 00:30:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - FULL IMMERSION IN THE SEA</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the middle of the Atlantic Ocean, about one hours flying time from Miami, we go to discover the Turks &amp; Caicos archipelago in the Caribbean Sea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 00:30:00" d="2020-06-03 01:00:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - LOS ROQUES, THE WINDY ARCHIPELAGO</n><t>D</t>    <k>We fly over the waters that separate the Venezuelan coast from Los Roques, we are going to visit this archipelago together with Francesca and her father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 01:00:00" d="2020-06-03 02:00:00"><n>SACRED CULTURE - GOLDEN TEMPLE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra embarks on a trip to India and Nepal, to show the life of its inhabitants, their customs, the architecture of its temples and holy cities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 02:00:00" d="2020-06-03 03:00:00"><n>DON'T FORGET YOUR PASSPORT - VIETNAM</n><t>D</t>    <k>Vietnam may be on the move economically but the ‘Communist Manifesto’ still lingers at the Ho Chi Minh Mausoleum and Lenin Square in the frenzied city of Hanoi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 03:00:00" d="2020-06-03 03:30:00"><n>PASSPORT TO EXPLORE - NASHVILLE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Passport to Explore is an internationallysyndicated half hour educational travel ad-venture series designed for 13-16 year olds. Syndicated on stations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 03:30:00" d="2020-06-03 04:00:00"><n>PASSPORT TO EXPLORE - NEW YORK CITY</n><t>D</t>    <k>Passport to Explore is an internationallysyndicated half hour educational travel ad-venture series designed for 13-16 year olds. Syndicated on stations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 04:00:00" d="2020-06-03 04:30:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF GREECE - CRETE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Come with us as we explore the cradle of European civilisation. Join intrepid gastronomer Charlie Ottley as he uncovers the true spirit of Greece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 04:30:00" d="2020-06-03 05:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF GREECE - THE DODECANESE &amp; EASTERN AEGEAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Join us for a trip around the North Aegean and the Dodecanese. Starting on the stunning Pelion peninsular, gastronomer Charlie Ottley goes in search</k>  </p>
</a>
