<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="33" t="2020-04-13 04:28:25"><p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 05:00:00" d="2020-04-20 05:30:00"><n>PASSPORT TO EXPLORE - ORLANDO</n><t>D</t>    <k>Passport to Explore is an internationallysyndicated half hour educational travel adventure series designed for 13-16 year olds. Syndicated on stations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 05:30:00" d="2020-04-20 06:00:00"><n>PASSPORT TO EXPLORE - PHILADELPHIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Passport to Explore is an internationallysyndicated half hour educational travel adventure series designed for 13-16 year olds. Syndicated on stations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 06:00:00" d="2020-04-20 07:00:00"><n>DON'T FORGET YOUR PASSPORT - LAOS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Join host Gordon Sivell as he explores northern Laos with a long-tail boat ride down the Mekong River to some ancient Buddhist caves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 07:00:00" d="2020-04-20 07:30:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A JOURNEY TO INFINITY - PART">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A JOURNEY TO INFINITY - PART 1 (PATAGONIA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>It is in Santiago, Chile that we begin the extraordinary journey into the infinity that, place by place, will take us to South Patagonia, which</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 07:30:00" d="2020-04-20 08:00:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A JOURNEY TO INFINITY - PART">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A JOURNEY TO INFINITY - PART 2 (PATAGONIA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>The journey to the edge of the world in the icy waters of Tierra del Fuego continues. On board our expedition ship we arrive to Tucker island</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 08:00:00" d="2020-04-20 08:30:00"><n u="INLAND ICE -">INLAND ICE - (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>We learn about the realities of camping out, taking pictures and how much food/water is enough. There is a new danger in the snow and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 08:30:00" d="2020-04-20 09:00:00"><n u="GOING SOUTH -">GOING SOUTH - (6)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Going South: Cycling through the Americas an adventurous environmental cycling documentary. As the climate changes, an environmental crisis is proclaimed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 09:00:00" d="2020-04-20 10:00:00"><n>NEXOS - THE MEDITERRANEAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>The two countries that lead the proposal for the Alliance of Civilizations are at the same time at the opposite end of a continent and yet separate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 10:00:00" d="2020-04-20 10:30:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - PORTO</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 10:30:00" d="2020-04-20 11:00:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - PRAUGE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 11:00:00" d="2020-04-20 12:00:00"><n>NOMAD'S LAND - NIGERIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Christopher arrived in Agadez, the capital of Niger Tuareg gates of the Sahara. After a short stint at the market, here on the slopes in search</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 12:00:00" d="2020-04-20 12:30:00"><n u="ALL ABOUT ANIMALS -">ALL ABOUT ANIMALS - (19)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 12:30:00" d="2020-04-20 13:00:00"><n u="ALL ABOUT ANIMALS -">ALL ABOUT ANIMALS - (20)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 13:00:00" d="2020-04-20 13:30:00"><n>LOW COST - BERLIN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Each city is in its native language (ie. Parisis in French, Rome is in Italian, Berlin is in German, etc. with English Scripts) showing the viewer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 13:30:00" d="2020-04-20 14:00:00"><n>LOW COST - BERLIN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Each city is in its native language (ie. Parisis in French, Rome is in Italian, Berlin is in German, etc. with English Scripts) showing the viewer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 14:00:00" d="2020-04-20 15:00:00"><n>TRACK RIDER - VIETNAM</n><t>D</t>    <k>Let yourself be taken away to the heart of Russia, Australia, Thailand, Vietnam, Mexico or the United States, and discover along the tracks, colourful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 15:00:00" d="2020-04-20 16:00:00"><n>NOMADS - MOUNTAIN BIKING MEXICO</n><t>D</t>    <k>Pro mountain bikers take to the rocky mountain terrain of Mexico’s Copper Canyon for the ride of their life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 16:00:00" d="2020-04-20 17:00:00"><n u="LIVING JUNGLE -">LIVING JUNGLE - (8)</n><t>D</t>    <k>“Living Jungle” is an invitation to explore the most impressive biodiversity in the whole world: the Amazonian Forest. An experimented host starts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 17:00:00" d="2020-04-20 17:30:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - BRITISH VIRGIN ISLANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Series 9 of Distant Shores follows Paul and Sheryl Shard on a diverse voyage from England through the inland waterways of France to the Mediterranean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 17:30:00" d="2020-04-20 18:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - MARTINIQUE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Series 9 of Distant Shores follows Paul and Sheryl Shard on a diverse voyage from England through the inland waterways of France to the Mediterranean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 18:00:00" d="2020-04-20 19:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - BRITISH VIRGIN ISLANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Series 9 of Distant Shores follows Paul and Sheryl Shard on a diverse voyage from England through the inland waterways of France to the Mediterranean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 19:00:00" d="2020-04-20 19:30:00"><n u="TRAJECTORY -">TRAJECTORY - (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Today, although a cloud of satellites surrounds the planet, many records set during the early decades of space exploration remain unsurpassed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 19:30:00" d="2020-04-20 20:00:00"><n u="TRAJECTORY -">TRAJECTORY - (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Today, although a cloud of satellites surrounds the planet, many records set during the early decades of space exploration remain unsurpassed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 20:00:00" d="2020-04-20 21:30:00"><n u="INTO THE ARCTIC -">INTO THE ARCTIC - (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>For years, artists Cory Trepanier has explored some of the wildest places in the North. Few have walked in these landscapes and even fewer have captures them on canvas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 21:30:00" d="2020-04-20 22:00:00"><n u="PEPITES VERTES OF BRAZIL -">PEPITES VERTES OF BRAZIL - (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>After reconstituting walk the Ho Chi Minh trail, François Picard and Cécile Clocheret through Brazil cycling. From the covered hinterland of soybean fields</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 22:00:00" d="2020-04-20 22:30:00"><n u="KUNG FU KITCHEN - KUNG FU TEA">KUNG FU KITCHEN - KUNG FU TEA (HANGZHOU, CHINA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the kitchens of the Far East, the best cooks are Kung Fu Masters. Kung Fu Kitchen is an action-packed culinary adventure series delving into the highly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 22:30:00" d="2020-04-20 23:00:00"><n u="KUNG FU KITCHEN - MOCHI">KUNG FU KITCHEN - MOCHI (NARA, JAPAN)</n><t>D</t>    <k>The traditional ceremony of making mochi involves using a large mallet and mortar. One person will pound the hot glutinous rice in a lightning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-20 23:00:00" d="2020-04-21 00:00:00"><n u="METRONOME -">METRONOME - (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Métronome offers you a journey through the centuries one landmark metro station at a time, revealing the history of Paris by criss-crossing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 00:00:00" d="2020-04-21 01:00:00"><n>BOKASSA 1ST, THE LAST AFRICAN EMPEROR</n><t>D</t>    <k>Perish the thought of us falling into an angelical rehabiliatation of such a contestable and impugned dictator. It seemed impossible for</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 01:00:00" d="2020-04-21 02:00:00"><n>NOMADS - BIG WAVE HUNTING IN TODOS SANTOS, MEXICO</n><t>D</t>    <k>Two renowned surfers surf their home breaks and venture to Mexico’s famous Todos Santo in search of giant tow-in surf to test their skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 02:00:00" d="2020-04-21 03:00:00"><n>GREAT AMERICAN FESTIVALS - ST. PAUL WINTER CARNIVAL</n><t>D</t>    <k>The United States oldest and largest winter festival, filled with a rich cultural tradition, the St. Paul Winter Carnival is a winter carnival like no other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 03:00:00" d="2020-04-21 04:00:00"><n>THE STATIONS AND SUSTAINABLE DEVELOPMENT</n><t>D</t>    <k>Learn how ski stations in France put together plans to have a sustainable development of their surroundings taking into account the yearly flows of tourists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 04:00:00" d="2020-04-21 05:00:00"><n>IN CONCERT - SERGIU POPA ENSEMBLE</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sergiu Popa is an acoustic quintet from Montreal, directed by accordionist Tzigane (Roma) Sergiu Popa. The group offers its own musical arrangements</k>  </p>
</a>
