<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="32" t="2021-07-09 06:47:35"><p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 05:00:00" d="2021-07-15 06:00:00"><n>I HAVE SEEN THE EARTH CHANGE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Abid'allah Quanwati, a fisherman, and Tarek Al-Cheikh, a farmer, are childhood friends. They live in Rosetta, which is located in the mouth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 06:00:00" d="2021-07-15 07:00:00"><n>NOMADS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Three paragliders explore the flight opportunities in Tenerife, a volcanic region of Mt. Teide, in the Canary Islands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 07:00:00" d="2021-07-15 08:00:00"><n>TRIBES OF THE HIMALAYAS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Likden is a trekking guide living in Skaagam located 3700 meters high in the Himalayan valley of Zanskar. After four long years of negotiation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 08:00:00" d="2021-07-15 09:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra, with his team, is directed to the Serengeti National Park in Tanzania, Africa. During their journey, they encounter an African celebration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 09:00:00" d="2021-07-15 10:00:00"><n>ANCIENT CULTURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 10:00:00" d="2021-07-15 11:00:00"><n>ISLANDERS, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Discovering some the world’s hidden treasures by revealing the hidden face of life and the inhabitants of the islands. Island folk are generally proud</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 11:00:00" d="2021-07-15 11:30:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 11:30:00" d="2021-07-15 12:00:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 12:00:00" d="2021-07-15 12:30:00"><n>GOING SOUTH</n><t>D</t>    <k>Going South: Cycling through the Americas an adventurous environmental cycling documentary. As the climate changes, an environmental crisis is proclaimed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 12:30:00" d="2021-07-15 13:00:00"><n>GOING SOUTH</n><t>D</t>    <k>Going South: Cycling through the Americas an adventurous environmental cycling documentary. As the climate changes, an environmental crisis is proclaimed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 13:00:00" d="2021-07-15 13:30:00"><n u="ICONS OF THE WORLD EP.">ICONS OF THE WORLD EP. 01</n><t>D</t>    <k>There are so many beautiful places, famous landmarks and cultural monuments worldwide, which, are symbols for a city or a country, however</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 13:30:00" d="2021-07-15 14:00:00"><n u="ICONS OF THE WORLD EP.">ICONS OF THE WORLD EP. 02</n><t>D</t>    <k>There are so many beautiful places, famous landmarks and cultural monuments worldwide, which, are symbols for a city or a country, however</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 14:00:00" d="2021-07-15 15:00:00"><n>NOMADS</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Waiting is the hardest part. The anticipation of the next face shot, of an uncut heli run, and of an approaching storm is enough to drive this group</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 15:00:00" d="2021-07-15 16:00:00"><n>MUNDO AD PORTAS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 16:00:00" d="2021-07-15 16:30:00"><n u="TASTING BRAZIL">TASTING BRAZIL 5</n><t>D</t>    <k>Bel Coelho a celebrity chef and star in Brazil invites us on a trip through Brazil, seeking new flavors. From one region to another, we will discover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 16:30:00" d="2021-07-15 17:00:00"><n u="TASTING BRAZIL">TASTING BRAZIL 6</n><t>D</t>    <k>Bel Coelho a celebrity chef and star in Brazil invites us on a trip through Brazil, seeking new flavors. From one region to another, we will discover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 17:00:00" d="2021-07-15 17:30:00"><n u="MUSIC VOYAGER EP.">MUSIC VOYAGER EP. 08</n><t>D</t>    <k>Music Voyager is a music and travel broadcast series (television/cable, broadband, in-flight and mobile) that invites viewers to discover the exciting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 17:30:00" d="2021-07-15 18:00:00"><n u="MUSIC VOYAGER EP.">MUSIC VOYAGER EP. 09</n><t>D</t>    <k>Music Voyager is a music and travel broadcast series (television/cable, broadband, in-flight and mobile) that invites viewers to discover the exciting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 18:00:00" d="2021-07-15 19:30:00"><n>PANCHO VILLA HERE AND THERE</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Centaur of the North, bandit for some, revolutionary leader for the others. The life, the character and the fights of one of the greatest symbols</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 19:30:00" d="2021-07-15 20:30:00"><n>BEAUTIFUL CHILE</n><t>D</t>    <k>The most arid desert in the world, millenary Patagonial ice fields, abundant forests lost in the heart of a mountain, are some of the geographical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 20:30:00" d="2021-07-15 21:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF SOUTH AFRICA</n><t>D</t>    <k>From the savage Kruger National Park via Suweto to the oldest Baobab tree in the world, Charlie Ottley takes us on a breathless safari across South</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 21:00:00" d="2021-07-15 22:00:00"><n>SOUND CHASER, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>The world still keeps many secrets, some just waiting to be revealed, if you just listen, led by a sound hunter. A peaceful and nomadic hunter, who unveils</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 22:00:00" d="2021-07-15 22:30:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Adventures in Tanzania. On board of a little Cessna plane, we reach the Songo Songo archipelago, 50 km south from Mafia. It’s from here that, after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 22:30:00" d="2021-07-15 23:00:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>We’re in Messinia, looking out over the Mediterranean Sea. Here we find the beautiful Navarino Coast, with its’ rich vegetation, historically important</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 23:00:00" d="2021-07-16 00:00:00"><n>ANCIENT CULTURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-16 00:00:00" d="2021-07-16 00:30:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF SCOTLAND</n><t>D</t>    <k>Take a trip to bonny Scotland, as you’ve never seen it before. Join Charlie Ottley as he sets off through the highlands and lowlands in search</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-16 00:30:00" d="2021-07-16 01:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF SCOTLAND</n><t>D</t>    <k>Charlie explores the breath-taking Scottish highlands from the Michelin starred Summer Isles Hotel in Achiltibuie to a remote glen where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-16 01:00:00" d="2021-07-16 02:00:00"><n>NOMADS</n><t>D</t>    <k>This episode of Nomads provides a sneak peek at life as a professional wakeboarder, what the sport is, and the east coast world of wakeboarding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-16 02:00:00" d="2021-07-16 02:30:00"><n>AVIATORS, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>EPIC AIRCRAFT: Surprise! Anthony gets an unexpected opportunity to fly a brand new turboprop driven aircraft. JET TRUCK: 3 jet engines, 48,000 horsepower</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-16 02:30:00" d="2021-07-16 03:00:00"><n>AVIATORS, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>AIRCRAFT TIRES: Tires are one of the most overlooked parts of an aircraft so we highlight the importance of a plane’s rubber. CONTROL TOWER:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-16 03:00:00" d="2021-07-16 04:00:00"><n>NOMAD'S LAND</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mongolia. Vast territory covered steppes and deserts. This is where Christophe Cousin goes - in search of nomads. There, he borrows not men with soles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-16 04:00:00" d="2021-07-16 05:00:00"><n>I HAVE SEEN THE EARTH CHANGE</n><t>D</t>    <k>At the heart of the Valencia Huerta, Antonio Gadčs watches worriedly the orange trees of his parcel wither away. This semi-arid region, true garden</k>  </p>
</a>
