<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2021-07-13 04:58:16"><p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 05:00:00" d="2021-07-20 05:30:00"><n>RACING GREEN</n><t>D</t>    <k>After 5 star accommodation in Seattle the Racing Green engineers continue their epic journey across the USA. They meet a team of Zeromotorcycle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 05:30:00" d="2021-07-20 06:00:00"><n>RACING GREEN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Getting into Mexico makes the team nervous because they hear more and more stories about drug wars along the US border. Exactly in that danger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 06:00:00" d="2021-07-20 06:30:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 06:30:00" d="2021-07-20 07:00:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 07:00:00" d="2021-07-20 07:30:00"><n>FISH LIFE</n><t>D</t>    <k>In tropical seas, the first impression is stunning. It’s a firework of colours competing in vividness and intensity: red, yellow, blue, green</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 07:30:00" d="2021-07-20 08:00:00"><n>FISH LIFE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Submarine sexuality displays some very strange facets. Anything is possible underwater from behaviors close to ours to the most disturbing. There are those</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 08:00:00" d="2021-07-20 09:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>A curious reporter, outdoor lover, will not rest until he shows us every mystery of the wild, black heart of Central Africa, discovering the stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 09:00:00" d="2021-07-20 09:30:00"><n>AVIATORS, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Kickin’ the Tires: How do you shop for a used aircraft? Anthony takes us through the process of finding that perfect used aircraft for you! Sonex:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 09:30:00" d="2021-07-20 10:00:00"><n>AVIATORS, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mackinac Island: Our fly-in destination of the year. This rustic Michigan area has plenty to offer and is accessible via its secluded private airport</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 10:00:00" d="2021-07-20 11:00:00"><n>SOUTHERN FLOWER AT SEA, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Great Adventure starts between Mexico and the Marquesas Islands, over 15 jrs ocean! a journey that goes well without great storm and with the passage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 11:00:00" d="2021-07-20 12:00:00"><n>ANCIENT CULTURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 12:00:00" d="2021-07-20 13:00:00"><n>CRISIS 2001</n><t>D</t>    <k>In December 2001, Argentina lived the worst financial, social and institutional crisis, since the restitution of the democracy in 1983. Crisis of 2001</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 13:00:00" d="2021-07-20 13:30:00"><n>ALL ABOUT ANIMALS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 13:30:00" d="2021-07-20 14:00:00"><n>ALL ABOUT ANIMALS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 14:00:00" d="2021-07-20 15:00:00"><n>SPIRULINA: THE AMAZING ALGAE</n><t>D</t>    <k>The film presents an exploration of a nearly invisible fresh water algae with scientific name Spirulina Arthrospira Platensis. But what exactly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 15:00:00" d="2021-07-20 16:00:00"><n>MUNDO AD PORTAS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 16:00:00" d="2021-07-20 17:00:00"><n>NOMADS</n><t>D</t>    <k>International kayakers travel the whitewater of Norway and show us the natural beauty that Norway has to offer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 17:00:00" d="2021-07-20 18:00:00"><n>CRAZY FOR MADONNA</n><t>D</t>    <k>A biography of a universal icon of music and Hollywood, Madonna, better known as the Queen of Pop. Sabbatical Entertainment celebrates Madonna’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 18:00:00" d="2021-07-20 19:00:00"><n>PANTANAL, THE JAGUAR'S LAST SANCTUARY</n><t>D</t>    <k>Situated in south-west Brazil, the Pantanal basin is the largest area of wetland in the world. This very particular ecosystem is home to a biodiversity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 19:00:00" d="2021-07-20 19:30:00"><n>MUSIC VOYAGER</n><t>D</t>    <k>Music Voyager is a music and travel broadcast series (television/cable, broadband, in-flight and mobile) that invites viewers to discover the exciting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 19:30:00" d="2021-07-20 20:00:00"><n>MUSIC VOYAGER</n><t>D</t>    <k>Music Voyager is a music and travel broadcast series (television/cable, broadband, in-flight and mobile) that invites viewers to discover the exciting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 20:00:00" d="2021-07-20 20:30:00"><n u="INSIDE OUTER SPACE EP.">INSIDE OUTER SPACE EP. 05</n><t>D</t>    <k>Come with us as we explore and unravel the mysteries of what lies beyond our planet Earth. This is a series packed with space stories and information about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 20:30:00" d="2021-07-20 21:00:00"><n>TWENTY MASTERPIECES OF NATURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Throughout the world, there are men and women who strive to protect the planet, rather than exploiting its resources. They know that man cannot exist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 21:00:00" d="2021-07-20 22:00:00"><n>WINDQUEST</n><t>D</t>    <k>Arthur de Kersauson, a young city-dweller hooked on extreme sports, and Antoine Auriol, World Champion in the Kiteboard Pro World Tour, set out in search</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 22:00:00" d="2021-07-20 22:30:00"><n>ASIAN CENTURY, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Twenty years ago, Laos was one of the top 10 poorest countries in the world. Today, the Lao economy is growing at an impressive rate of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 22:30:00" d="2021-07-20 23:00:00"><n>ASIAN CENTURY, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Since a decade ago, Singapore has made plans to re-brand itself as a Renaissance City of arts and culture. There were strong economic imperatives for this</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-20 23:00:00" d="2021-07-21 00:00:00"><n>NAZI NETWORK IN MEXICO, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>In 1985, had been released the documents about the nazis activities during the world War II in Mexico. But, what could be Hitler's interest in a country away from war? The answer that had remained hidden and generated legends, tries to be unveiled through this documentary that narrates and recreates Nazi activities in Mexico during World War II</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-21 00:00:00" d="2021-07-21 00:30:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the middle of the Atlantic Ocean, about one hours flying time from Miami, we go to discover the Turks &amp; Caicos archipelago in the Caribbean Sea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-21 00:30:00" d="2021-07-21 01:00:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>We fly over the waters that separate the Venezuelan coast from Los Roques, we are going to visit this archipelago together with Francesca and her father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-21 01:00:00" d="2021-07-21 02:00:00"><n>SACRED CULTURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra embarks on a trip to India and Nepal, to show the life of its inhabitants, their customs, the architecture of its temples and holy cities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-21 02:00:00" d="2021-07-21 03:00:00"><n>HAPPINESS IS ON THE PLATE</n><t>D</t>    <k>A tasty series blending travel, cooking, nature and civic sense, following the daily work of five &quot;green&quot; chefs fighting for eco-friendly cooking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-21 03:00:00" d="2021-07-21 04:00:00"><n>CHINA, A TIMELESS COUNTRY</n><t>D</t>    <k>This series goes through the most unknown places in the Republic of China, discovering at each step the marks that its history has left in the present</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-21 04:00:00" d="2021-07-21 04:30:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF GREECE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Come with us as we explore the cradle of European civilisation. Join intrepid gastronomer Charlie Ottley as he uncovers the true spirit of Greece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-21 04:30:00" d="2021-07-21 05:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF GREECE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Join us for a trip around the North Aegean and the Dodecanese. Starting on the stunning Pelion peninsular, gastronomer Charlie Ottley goes in search</k>  </p>
</a>
