<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="33" t="2019-08-13 02:06:55"><p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 05:00:00" d="2019-08-20 06:00:00"><n>SCEPTICS - DID WE REALLY LAND A MAN ON THE MOON</n><t>D</t>    <k>Theory questioning whether man set foot on the Moon in 1969</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 06:00:00" d="2019-08-20 07:00:00"><n>MAKE ME A LOG BOAT!</n><t>D</t>    <k>Around the Parandu lake, two groups of volunteers go about to make a logboat using antique tools and getting back in a 5,000 years journey while meeting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 07:00:00" d="2019-08-20 07:30:00"><n>FISH LIFE - COLOURS CODE</n><t>D</t>    <k>In tropical seas, the first impression is stunning. It’s a firework of colours competing in vividness and intensity: red, yellow, blue, green</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 07:30:00" d="2019-08-20 08:00:00"><n>FISH LIFE - A SEA OF LOVE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Submarine sexuality displays some very strange facets. Anything is possible underwater from behaviors close to ours to the most disturbing. There are those</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 08:00:00" d="2019-08-20 09:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE - HIMBA</n><t>D</t>    <k>A curious reporter, outdoor lover, will not rest until he shows us every mystery of the wild, black heart of Central Africa, discovering the stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 09:00:00" d="2019-08-20 09:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - II (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Can a kid land an airliner?: A follow up to some of the popular sim segments from season one, but this time with a 12 year old at the controls! MCAF Miramar (formerly Top Gun): Spending the day with US Marine fighter pilots at their legendary base. Corsair: Jeff flies one of the most capable carrier-based fighter aircraft of WW2</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 09:30:00" d="2019-08-20 10:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - II (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Private pilot emergency: Anthony closes the season 2 sim segments by having everything but the kitchen sink thrown at him. Can he do it? Flight services</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 10:00:00" d="2019-08-20 11:00:00"><n>THE DRAGON HOUSE</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Dragon House portrays the confrontation between tradition and modernity which the Kingdom of Bhutan is currently experiencing. This is done by means</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 11:00:00" d="2019-08-20 12:00:00"><n u="ANCIENT CULTURE -">ANCIENT CULTURE - (13)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 12:00:00" d="2019-08-20 12:30:00"><n>PASSPORT TO EXPLORE - LAS VEGAS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Passport to Explore is an internationallysyndicated half hour educational travel ad-venture series designed for 13-16 year olds. Syndicated on stations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 12:30:00" d="2019-08-20 13:00:00"><n>PASSPORT TO EXPLORE - LOS ANGELES</n><t>D</t>    <k>Passport to Explore is an internationallysyndicated half hour educational travel ad-venture series designed for 13-16 year olds. Syndicated on stations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 13:00:00" d="2019-08-20 13:30:00"><n u="ALL ABOUT ANIMALS -">ALL ABOUT ANIMALS - (17)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 13:30:00" d="2019-08-20 14:00:00"><n u="ALL ABOUT ANIMALS -">ALL ABOUT ANIMALS - (18)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 14:00:00" d="2019-08-20 15:00:00"><n>SPIRULINA: THE AMAZING ALGAE</n><t>D</t>    <k>The film presents an exploration of a nearly invisible fresh water algae with scientific name Spirulina Arthrospira Platensis. But what exactly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 15:00:00" d="2019-08-20 16:00:00"><n u="MUNDO AD PORTAS -">MUNDO AD PORTAS - I (9)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 16:00:00" d="2019-08-20 16:30:00"><n>THE GREAT JOURNEY - FROM STUDENTS TO TEACHERS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jorge Newbery, the mentor of the crossing of the Andes by air, dies in a tragic accident and someone must take the challenge. We will attend a class on balloon flight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 16:30:00" d="2019-08-20 17:00:00"><n>THE GREAT JOURNEY - THE CORDILLERAN CHALLENGE</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the mind of two bold pilots the challenge of crossing the Cordillera de Los Andes. We will discover the hot air balloon with which the first crossing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 17:00:00" d="2019-08-20 17:30:00"><n u="RACING GREEN -">RACING GREEN - (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>After 5 star accommodation in Seattle the Racing Green engineers continue their epic journey across the USA. They meet a team of Zeromotorcycle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 17:30:00" d="2019-08-20 18:00:00"><n u="RACING GREEN -">RACING GREEN - (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Getting into Mexico makes the team nervous because they hear more and more stories about drug wars along the US border. Exactly in that danger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 18:00:00" d="2019-08-20 19:00:00"><n>NOMADS - BIG MOUNTAIN EXTREME SKIING IN LAS LENAS, ARGENTINA</n><t>D</t>    <k>A group of pro skiers travel a tough journey to South America in the hopes of experiencing the world-renown ski terrain Las Lenas, Argentina</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 19:00:00" d="2019-08-20 20:00:00"><n>PANTANAL, THE JAGUAR'S LAST SANCTUARY</n><t>D</t>    <k>Situated in south-west Brazil, the Pantanal basin is the largest area of wetland in the world. This very particular ecosystem is home to a biodiversity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 20:00:00" d="2019-08-20 21:00:00"><n u="TIMELESS TREASURES -">TIMELESS TREASURES - (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>A series celebrating the extraordinary preservation of human heritage. Discover the world’s most beautiful sites in an exceptional series of short programs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 21:00:00" d="2019-08-20 22:00:00"><n>SOUTHERN FLOWER IN THE PACIFIC - TOWARDS POLYNESIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Great Adventure starts between Mexico and the Marquesas Islands, over 15 jrs ocean! a journey that goes well without great storm and with the passage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 22:00:00" d="2019-08-20 22:30:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - LAOS PDR'S BLESSING OR BANE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Twenty years ago, Laos was one of the top 10 poorest countries in the world. Today, the Lao economy is growing at an impressive rate of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 22:30:00" d="2019-08-20 23:00:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - SINGAPORE LIGHTENS UP</n><t>D</t>    <k>Since a decade ago, Singapore has made plans to re-brand itself as a Renaissance City of arts and culture. There were strong economic imperatives for this</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-20 23:00:00" d="2019-08-21 00:00:00"><n u="INTO THE ARCTIC -">INTO THE ARCTIC - (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>For years, artists Cory Trepanier has explored some of the wildest places in the North. Few have walked in these landscapes and even fewer have captures them on canvas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 00:00:00" d="2019-08-21 00:30:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - FULL IMMERSION IN THE SEA</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the middle of the Atlantic Ocean, about one hours flying time from Miami, we go to discover the Turks &amp; Caicos archipelago in the Caribbean Sea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 00:30:00" d="2019-08-21 01:00:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - LOS ROQUES, THE WINDY ARCHIPELAGO</n><t>D</t>    <k>We fly over the waters that separate the Venezuelan coast from Los Roques, we are going to visit this archipelago together with Francesca and her father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 01:00:00" d="2019-08-21 02:00:00"><n>SACRED CULTURE - GOLDEN TEMPLE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra embarks on a trip to India and Nepal, to show the life of its inhabitants, their customs, the architecture of its temples and holy cities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 02:00:00" d="2019-08-21 03:00:00"><n>DON'T FORGET YOUR PASSPORT - VIETNAM</n><t>D</t>    <k>Vietnam may be on the move economically but the ‘Communist Manifesto’ still lingers at the Ho Chi Minh Mausoleum and Lenin Square in the frenzied city of Hanoi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 03:00:00" d="2019-08-21 04:00:00"><n>IN CONCERT - MYSTIKI KOMPANIA</n><t>M</t>    <k>Whether sung in Greek, Turkish or Sephardic, none of these cultures can claim to own the Rebetiko. It is most likely a product of its environment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 04:00:00" d="2019-08-21 04:30:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF GREECE - CRETE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Come with us as we explore the cradle of European civilisation. Join intrepid gastronomer Charlie Ottley as he uncovers the true spirit of Greece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 04:30:00" d="2019-08-21 05:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF GREECE - THE DODECANESE &amp; EASTERN AEGEAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Join us for a trip around the North Aegean and the Dodecanese. Starting on the stunning Pelion peninsular, gastronomer Charlie Ottley goes in search</k>  </p>
</a>
