<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2020-05-30 04:33:48"><p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 05:00:00" d="2020-06-06 05:30:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - CHESAPEAKE EASTERN SHORE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Few sailors reach the eastern shore of the Chesapeake Bay due to the shallow water but with the Shards are able to visit unique and isolated communities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 05:30:00" d="2020-06-06 06:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - SECRET PLACES</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Shards celebrate the cruising lifestyle and look back over some of the best destinations they have sailed to over the years and give hints to fellow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 06:00:00" d="2020-06-06 07:00:00"><n>DON'T FORGET YOUR PASSPORT - MALAYSIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Adventure traveler Gordon Sivell tours an old Japanese Prisoner of War Camp in the jungles of Malaysia, and just off the coast of southern Thailand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 07:00:00" d="2020-06-06 07:30:00"><n>FISH LIFE - FEEDING</n><t>D</t>    <k>In order to live, you need to eat and, in the sea, we imagine that this boils down to one fish eating another. Reality is a bit more complex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 07:30:00" d="2020-06-06 08:00:00"><n>FISH LIFE - THE ODD, THE WEIRD AND THE UNUSUAL</n><t>D</t>    <k>Going by the dictionnary, which is strange can strike us by its unique, unusual, surprising or odd features. And according to this definition, certain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 08:00:00" d="2020-06-06 08:30:00"><n u="ALL ABOUT ANIMALS -">ALL ABOUT ANIMALS - (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 08:30:00" d="2020-06-06 09:00:00"><n u="ALL ABOUT ANIMALS -">ALL ABOUT ANIMALS - (5)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 09:00:00" d="2020-06-06 09:30:00"><n>THE GREAT JOURNEY - FROM STUDENTS TO TEACHERS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jorge Newbery, the mentor of the crossing of the Andes by air, dies in a tragic accident and someone must take the challenge. We will attend a class on balloon flight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 09:30:00" d="2020-06-06 10:00:00"><n>THE GREAT JOURNEY - THE CORDILLERAN CHALLENGE</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the mind of two bold pilots the challenge of crossing the Cordillera de Los Andes. We will discover the hot air balloon with which the first crossing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 10:00:00" d="2020-06-06 10:30:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - WHERE NATURE IS PUREST">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - WHERE NATURE IS PUREST (MNORCA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>On this trip we’re going to visit Minorca, a Balearic island full of nature and traditions. Here we see the huge Mahon harbor, where regattas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 10:30:00" d="2020-06-06 11:00:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - THE GARDEN OF THE ATLANTIC OCEAN">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - THE GARDEN OF THE ATLANTIC OCEAN (MADEIRA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the waters of the Atlantic Ocean there is a Portuguese island that is characterized by luxuriant nature and majestic elevations, a mild climate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 11:00:00" d="2020-06-06 12:00:00"><n>NOMADS - KITESURFING TAHITI</n><t>O</t>    <k>Kitesurfing is a sport that could not be better suited to an island location like Tahiti. With the sun, sand and an ocean breeze it is an ideal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 12:00:00" d="2020-06-06 12:30:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - AYYATUYA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 12:30:00" d="2020-06-06 13:00:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - BAHIR DAR</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 13:00:00" d="2020-06-06 13:30:00"><n>THE GREAT JOURNEY - THE ADVENTURE BEGINS</n><t>D</t>    <k>The crossing must be made from west to east, that is from Chile to Argentina. Installed in the Chilean capital a group of specialists finalize details for the trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 13:30:00" d="2020-06-06 14:00:00"><n>THE GREAT JOURNEY - EXPEDITION IN DANGER</n><t>D</t>    <k>The technician team can't make the right gas to raise the hot air balloon. In a chemical laboratory we will reproduce the gas production process</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 14:00:00" d="2020-06-06 15:00:00"><n>DARWIN'S VOYAGE - ADAPT OR DIE</n><t>D</t>    <k>The story of a man who spent two and a half years at the end of the world in an experience that changed him forever. Darwin’s Voyage is a miniseries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 15:00:00" d="2020-06-06 16:00:00"><n u="MUNDO AD PORTAS -">MUNDO AD PORTAS - I (13)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 16:00:00" d="2020-06-06 17:00:00"><n u="HAPPINESS IS ON THE PLATE -">HAPPINESS IS ON THE PLATE - (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>A tasty series blending travel, cooking, nature and civic sense, following the daily work of five &quot;green&quot; chefs fighting for eco-friendly cooking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 17:00:00" d="2020-06-06 18:00:00"><n>THE BISHNOIS: INDIA'S ECO-WARRIORS</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Bishnois remain the first eco-friendly religious community in Historical records. Originating from the Thar Desert in Rajasthan, their guru Jimbaji</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 18:00:00" d="2020-06-06 19:00:00"><n>TRAVEL NOTEBOOKS - CAP</n><t>D</t>    <k>This series invites the viewer to visit unusual countries, cities and places through the eye of a traveler-illustrator</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 19:00:00" d="2020-06-06 21:00:00"><n>PROJEKT HUEMUL, FOURTH REICH IN ARGENTINA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Towards the end of the Second World War, German physicists were doing everything possible to build an atomic bomb, and other &quot;secret weapons&quot;, before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 21:00:00" d="2020-06-06 22:30:00"><n>THE CARDENA'S ERA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Lázaro Cárdenas, Mexico's president between 1943 and 1940, came from a modest aborigin family. In 1914 he joined the Mexican Revolution and later</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 22:30:00" d="2020-06-06 23:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF SOUTH AFRICA - THE WINELANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>A viticultural romp around Capetown’s historic wine lands - presenter Charlie Ottley checks out the ultimate designer winery, the last word in chic hotels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 23:00:00" d="2020-06-07 01:00:00"><n>TRACK RIDER - USA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Let yourself be taken away to the heart of Russia, Australia, Thailand, Vietnam, Mexico or the United States, and discover along the tracks, colourful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 01:00:00" d="2020-06-07 02:00:00"><n>SACRED CULTURE - CALCUTA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra embarks on a trip to India and Nepal, to show the life of its inhabitants, their customs, the architecture of its temples and holy cities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 02:00:00" d="2020-06-07 03:00:00"><n>THE FORCE OF EARTH - ENERGIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Force of Earth is an educational documentary series of the journey of a Chilean scientist. In every episode we will learn about geography and geology</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 03:00:00" d="2020-06-07 04:00:00"><n>IN CONCERT - ROSE EKOSSO</n><t>M</t>    <k>Ontario Pop winner and semi-finalist at the International Song Festival of Granby 09. Rose Ekosso captivates the audience with her vocal and her unique</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 04:00:00" d="2020-06-07 05:00:00"><n>NEXOS - IN CENTRAL ASIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>There are a number of countries that given the situation, both geographically and geopolitically serve as an ideological frontier between different civilizations</k>  </p>
</a>
