<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2020-05-31 04:33:07"><p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 05:00:00" d="2020-06-07 06:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE - OKAVANGO</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra returns to Namibia in search of a new African tribe, the Manfred, which is located in the Caprivi Region in the northern</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 06:00:00" d="2020-06-07 06:30:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - SEVILLE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 06:30:00" d="2020-06-07 07:00:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - THILAND- KHO PANGAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 07:00:00" d="2020-06-07 08:00:00"><n u="ANCIENT CULTURE -">ANCIENT CULTURE - (23)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 08:00:00" d="2020-06-07 08:30:00"><n u="ALL ABOUT ANIMALS -">ALL ABOUT ANIMALS - (17)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 08:30:00" d="2020-06-07 09:00:00"><n u="ALL ABOUT ANIMALS -">ALL ABOUT ANIMALS - (18)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 09:00:00" d="2020-06-07 09:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - II (12)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Panel makeover: The Aviators’ 210 gets gutted as all the traditional instruments are replaced with an ultra-impressive state-of-the-art glass panel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 09:30:00" d="2020-06-07 10:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - II (13)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Oxygen: We experiment in an oxygen deprivation lab and examine the use of oxygen at various altitudes. Winter flying: There’s really no such thing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 10:00:00" d="2020-06-07 10:30:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - IN THE KINGDOM OF SHARKS - PART">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - IN THE KINGDOM OF SHARKS - PART 2 (CUBA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>In this incredible eco-system of mangroves, reefs and sandy sea beds of the labyrinth of small islands and channels that make up the archipelago</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 10:30:00" d="2020-06-07 11:00:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - THE RED GOLD OF THE MEDITERRANEAN SEA">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - THE RED GOLD OF THE MEDITERRANEAN SEA (SARDEGNA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>It is in Sardinia that we discover the secrets of red coral, the underwater jewel of the Mediterranean Sea, where in Alghero you can find the centre</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 11:00:00" d="2020-06-07 11:30:00"><n>ANIMAL ALLIES - DR. DARIO</n><t>D</t>    <k>In Australia Dr Dario takes on a herd of pregnant cows and takes his student through the steps of dealing with the rather smelly procedure, while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 11:30:00" d="2020-06-07 12:00:00"><n>ANIMAL ALLIES - LONDON'S CAT OVERPOPULATION</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the UK, Animal Doctor Justine Braun performs routine but extremely delicate operations on two cats and tells us why these procedures are so important</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 12:00:00" d="2020-06-07 12:30:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - BANKOK</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 12:30:00" d="2020-06-07 13:00:00"><n u="TRAVEL PLAN - BARCELONA - PART">TRAVEL PLAN - BARCELONA - PART 1</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 13:00:00" d="2020-06-07 14:00:00"><n>NOMADS - ALASKA SNOWMOBILE FREERIDING</n><t>D</t>    <k>Pro snowmobilers ride on the edge; tackling uncharted terrain, risky terrain for the ultimate freeride snowmobile experience in the uncharted mountains of Valdez, Alaska</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 14:00:00" d="2020-06-07 14:30:00"><n u="GOING SOUTH -">GOING SOUTH - (7)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Going South: Cycling through the Americas an adventurous environmental cycling documentary. As the climate changes, an environmental crisis is proclaimed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 14:30:00" d="2020-06-07 15:00:00"><n u="GOING SOUTH -">GOING SOUTH - (8)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Going South: Cycling through the Americas an adventurous environmental cycling documentary. As the climate changes, an environmental crisis is proclaimed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 15:00:00" d="2020-06-07 16:00:00"><n u="MUNDO AD PORTAS -">MUNDO AD PORTAS - I (14)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 16:00:00" d="2020-06-07 16:30:00"><n u="GARONGA SAFARI -">GARONGA SAFARI - (6)</n><t>D</t>    <k>In this chapter René will visit with his teammates Sabiepark nature reserve, a place with quite specific rules. Later they will go to enormous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 16:30:00" d="2020-06-07 17:00:00"><n u="GARONGA SAFARI -">GARONGA SAFARI - (7)</n><t>D</t>    <k>In this chapter René with his fellow Safari they have the lesson to learn to recognize the types of birds and feathered edges of Africa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 17:00:00" d="2020-06-07 18:00:00"><n>ISLE OF MAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Isle of Man sits at the heart of the Irish Sea, easily overlooked but of great importance to the many species of birds, mammals and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 18:00:00" d="2020-06-07 19:00:00"><n u="PLANT SECRETS -">PLANT SECRETS - (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>To most of us, plants make up a familiar background decoration, albeit a beautiful one, but we don't really pay them that much attention</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 19:00:00" d="2020-06-07 20:30:00"><n>ARAMBURUS ASSASSINATION</n><t>D</t>    <k>July, 1st 1970, though Pindapoy operation, Montoneros guerrilla group assassinated Lieutenant General Pedro Aramburu, who in 1955 lead the power</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 20:30:00" d="2020-06-07 21:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF SOUTH AFRICA - KWAZULU NATAL</n><t>D</t>    <k>Gastronomer Charlie Ottley takes a non-stop tour of the magical state of Kwazulu Natal. From the street markets of Durban to the battlefields</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 21:00:00" d="2020-06-07 22:30:00"><n>VOLCANIC PLANET</n><t>D</t>    <k>Volcanoes are the most extreme, dramatic, and explosive forces of nature on our planet. Volcanoes have produced many of the most valuable minerals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 22:30:00" d="2020-06-07 23:00:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - FOLLOWING THE NOBLE ECHO OF THE SEA</n><t>D</t>    <k>In every sea, a shell, in every shell, a voice and a hypnotic recall. This is the &quot;common thread&quot; that accompanies us on our trip through the world’s hemispheres</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 23:00:00" d="2020-06-07 23:30:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - CHICHESTER HARBOUR</n><t>D</t>    <k>Paul and Sheryl test sail their new 49-foot boat by exploring small ports around Chichester Harbour - one of England's largest boating centres</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-07 23:30:00" d="2020-06-08 00:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - THE SOLENT</n><t>D</t>    <k>Satisfied that their new boat is ready for sea trials, Paul and Sheryl leave Chichester Harbour and sail to ports around the Solent and Isle of Wight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 00:00:00" d="2020-06-08 01:00:00"><n>NOMAD'S LAND - KYRGYZSTAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Christophe travels to every corner of the planet in the steps of nomadic peoples. He experiences their everyday life and follows their seasonal migrations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 01:00:00" d="2020-06-08 01:30:00"><n>REBUILDING OUR ENVIRONMENT - PHOTOVOLTAIC PANELS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Solar photovoltaic energy as an alternative energy-saving method and renewable energy. Examples of places where this type of energy is used and how it works</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 01:30:00" d="2020-06-08 02:00:00"><n>REBUILDING OUR ENVIRONMENT - BIOMASS</n><t>D</t>    <k>The use of organic materials and biomass. What it is, how it is produced and ways of using it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 02:00:00" d="2020-06-08 03:00:00"><n>ANTARCTICA FLOWERS - ANTARCTICA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Adrenaline rises at our crew, the start is iminent. Christmas party early with the family before the departure to 8 weeks of hostile seas along</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 03:00:00" d="2020-06-08 04:00:00"><n>THE FORCE OF EARTH - VOLCANES</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Force of Earth is an educational documentary series of the journey of a Chilean scientist. In every episode we will learn about geography and geology</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 04:00:00" d="2020-06-08 05:00:00"><n u="NOMADS - BREAKING BARRIERS: KAYAKING CHINA - PART">NOMADS - BREAKING BARRIERS: KAYAKING CHINA - PART 1</n><t>D</t>    <k>World-class Kayakers take on the rivers of China for better or for worse they will go to the extreme for the decent</k>  </p>
</a>
