<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="31" t="2019-08-11 01:33:28"><p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 05:00:00" d="2019-08-17 06:00:00"><n>I HAVE SEEN THE EARTH CHANGE - UNITED STATES: FAHRENHEIT 1,5</n><t>D</t>    <k>Colleen Gregory (truck farmer, beekeeper and sheep breeder) lives in the San Juan Islands, off Seattle. Fed up with the city and its ongoing activity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 06:00:00" d="2019-08-17 06:30:00"><n>GUIDES &amp; GURUS - ARIZONA</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Navajo way tradition and way of life is vastly different from the one many people live in this modern world. Henry Walters, a teacher and medicine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 06:30:00" d="2019-08-17 07:00:00"><n>GUIDES &amp; GURUS - SRI LANKA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Veddha people, of Sri Lanka, have a magical link with the jungle and a tradition of elaborate rituals to placate angry gods as well as amazing medicinal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 07:00:00" d="2019-08-17 07:30:00"><n u="ALL ABOUT ANIMALS -">ALL ABOUT ANIMALS - (13)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 07:30:00" d="2019-08-17 08:00:00"><n u="ALL ABOUT ANIMALS -">ALL ABOUT ANIMALS - (14)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 08:00:00" d="2019-08-17 09:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE - BUSHMAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>A curious reporter, outdoor lover, will not rest until he shows us every mystery of the wild, black heart of Central Africa, discovering the stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 09:00:00" d="2019-08-17 10:00:00"><n u="ANCIENT CULTURE -">ANCIENT CULTURE - (10)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 10:00:00" d="2019-08-17 11:00:00"><n>BEAUTIFUL MINDS - PABLO VALENZUELA PHD</n><t>D</t>    <k>Albert Einstein said that the mind is like a parachute: it only works if we have it opened. Beautiful Minds is a documentary series that summarizes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 11:00:00" d="2019-08-17 12:00:00"><n u="CHINA, A TIMELESS COUNTRY - PART">CHINA, A TIMELESS COUNTRY - PART 2</n><t>D</t>    <k>This series goes through the most unknown places in the Republic of China, discovering at each step the marks that its history has left in the present</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 12:00:00" d="2019-08-17 13:00:00"><n>IN CONCERT - SERGIU POPA ENSEMBLE</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sergiu Popa is an acoustic quintet from Montreal, directed by accordionist Tzigane (Roma) Sergiu Popa. The group offers its own musical arrangements</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 13:00:00" d="2019-08-17 14:00:00"><n>THE FORCE OF EARTH - VOLCANES</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Force of Earth is an educational documentary series of the journey of a Chilean scientist. In every episode we will learn about geography and geology</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 14:00:00" d="2019-08-17 15:00:00"><n u="MANHATTAN">MANHATTAN 1609</n><t>D</t>    <k>Some four centuries ago, Protestants from Belgium and the North of France, chased from their region by war and religion, left to build</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 15:00:00" d="2019-08-17 16:00:00"><n u="MUNDO AD PORTAS -">MUNDO AD PORTAS - I (6)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 16:00:00" d="2019-08-17 17:00:00"><n>THE CHARRO</n><t>D</t>    <k>The &quot;charro&quot;, term that comes from military charreteras (Epaulettes) that horse riders use, is one of Mexico's national symbols. Their figure appeared</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 17:00:00" d="2019-08-17 18:00:00"><n>MISTS OF MANENGOUBA</n><t>D</t>    <k>The African continent still contains numerous unexplored regions. Recently, one of these lost worlds was discovered in Cameroon, by a British researcher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 18:00:00" d="2019-08-17 18:30:00"><n>THE GREAT JOURNEY - EXPEDITION IN DANGER</n><t>D</t>    <k>The technician team can't make the right gas to raise the hot air balloon. In a chemical laboratory we will reproduce the gas production process</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 18:30:00" d="2019-08-17 19:00:00"><n>THE GREAT JOURNEY - FLYING TO THE ANDES</n><t>D</t>    <k>They manage to fly over the first hills of the Chilean mountain range, but fail and fall in a small town and must be rescued. Next to the pilot Cristian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 19:00:00" d="2019-08-17 19:30:00"><n>TERRUA - MISTRAL VINEYARD</n><t>D</t>    <k>Doctors recommend wine for its antioxidant properties and nutrients. We recommend it simply because it’s good. That’s why in Terruá, we invite you to learn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 19:30:00" d="2019-08-17 20:00:00"><n>TERRUA - TAMAYA VINEYARD</n><t>D</t>    <k>Doctors recommend wine for its antioxidant properties and nutrients. We recommend it simply because it’s good. That’s why in Terruá, we invite you to learn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 20:00:00" d="2019-08-17 21:00:00"><n>BOKASSA 1ST, THE LAST AFRICAN EMPEROR</n><t>D</t>    <k>Perish the thought of us falling into an angelical rehabiliatation of such a contestable and impugned dictator. It seemed impossible for</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 21:00:00" d="2019-08-17 22:00:00"><n>SMALL CAMS, BIG BEASTS</n><t>D</t>    <k>25 years ago in wildlife filmmaking, it took about four people to carry camera and lighting equipment. Back then celluloid was loaded into cameras</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 22:00:00" d="2019-08-17 22:30:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - INDIA'S RETURNING NRIs</n><t>D</t>    <k>Having risen from the ashes of one of the poorest economies, India now is walking the road to becoming a superpower. Come the turn of the century</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 22:30:00" d="2019-08-17 23:00:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - KOREA'S YOUTH EMPLOYMENT</n><t>D</t>    <k>South Korea boasts a population with one of the most highly educated youth in the world. However, with one in ten youth being unemployed, the nation’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 23:00:00" d="2019-08-18 00:00:00"><n>THE FORCE OF THE AIR - INTRODUCTION TO METEOROLOGY</n><t>D</t>    <k>Multidisciplinary documentary series that reveals some of the particular weather conditions of the Chilean territory and its evolution</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 00:00:00" d="2019-08-18 00:30:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - THE SAINTES</n><t>D</t>    <k>Just south of Guadeloupe is a small group of islands known as &quot;The Saints&quot;. Paul and Sheryl discover a little bit of French heaven in the Caribbean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 00:30:00" d="2019-08-18 01:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - VOYAGE TO ELEUTHERA</n><t>D</t>    <k>A spring journey north through the lovely Bahamas! We sail first to Mayaguana, then Ragged and the Jumentos Cays before heading to the Exumas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 01:00:00" d="2019-08-18 02:00:00"><n>NOMAD'S LAND - ETHIOPIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>With the label of &quot;cradle of humanity&quot;, Ethiopia is adorned with a legendary aura. It is here that the man was born, here he would have his first steps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 02:00:00" d="2019-08-18 03:00:00"><n>THE CHINESE WHITE GOLD</n><t>D</t>    <k>Chinese new middle class can now enjoy a sport they knew nothing about until recently: skiing. And they love it! This is not about trying some daredevil</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 03:00:00" d="2019-08-18 03:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - I (12)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Flight services specialists, Wilderness survival, In-flight oxygen, Three generations of flyers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 03:30:00" d="2019-08-18 04:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - I (13)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Young Eagles, Florida’s Sun ‘n Fun, Taking an intro flight, Royal Canadian Air Cadets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 04:00:00" d="2019-08-18 05:00:00"><n>CARSTANSZ - THE SEVENTH SUMMIT</n><t>D</t>    <k>Snowy Mountains rise high above the untouched jungle of New Guinea, breaking through heavy rain clouds. A limestone pyramid, known as the Carstensz</k>  </p>
</a>
