<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="35" t="2021-07-08 04:58:32"><p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 05:00:00" d="2021-07-13 06:00:00"><n>I HAVE SEEN THE EARTH CHANGE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Gerarda Moralčs is an Aymara Indian like half the population of Bolivia, and the president of a self-help charity network in the La region</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 06:00:00" d="2021-07-13 06:30:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES</n><t>D</t>    <k>Series 9 of Distant Shores follows Paul and Sheryl Shard on a diverse voyage from England through the inland waterways of France to the Mediterranean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 06:30:00" d="2021-07-13 07:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES</n><t>D</t>    <k>Series 9 of Distant Shores follows Paul and Sheryl Shard on a diverse voyage from England through the inland waterways of France to the Mediterranean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 07:00:00" d="2021-07-13 08:00:00"><n>ANCIENT CULTURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 08:00:00" d="2021-07-13 09:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>In this chapter, Claudio and his adventurous team decide to visit the tribe of the Datoga, an ancient tribe that lives across the Serengeti national paruqe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 09:00:00" d="2021-07-13 09:30:00"><n>TERRUA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Doctors recommend wine for its antioxidant properties and nutrients. We recommend it simply because it’s good. That’s why in Terruá, we invite you to learn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 09:30:00" d="2021-07-13 10:00:00"><n>TERRUA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Doctors recommend wine for its antioxidant properties and nutrients. We recommend it simply because it’s good. That’s why in Terruá, we invite you to learn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 10:00:00" d="2021-07-13 11:00:00"><n>NOMADS</n><t>D</t>    <k>The biggest stars of snowmobile head to the Rocky Mountains for an epic adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 11:00:00" d="2021-07-13 11:30:00"><n u="EVERYDAY ELEMENTS EP.">EVERYDAY ELEMENTS EP. 03</n><t>D</t>    <k>A series that puts chemistry in our everyday experience by showing the living connection we have with the chemicals and elements that make up our world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 11:30:00" d="2021-07-13 12:00:00"><n u="EVERYDAY ELEMENTS EP.">EVERYDAY ELEMENTS EP. 04</n><t>D</t>    <k>A series that puts chemistry in our everyday experience by showing the living connection we have with the chemicals and elements that make up our world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 12:00:00" d="2021-07-13 13:00:00"><n>LIVING JUNGLE</n><t>D</t>    <k>“Living Jungle” is an invitation to explore the most impressive biodiversity in the whole world: the Amazonian Forest. An experimented host starts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 13:00:00" d="2021-07-13 14:00:00"><n>FORCE OF THE SEA, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Power of the Sea is a documentary series that reveals the special features of each one of the wonderful seas of Chile, generating conscience</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 14:00:00" d="2021-07-13 15:00:00"><n>POSTCARD PERFECT</n><t>D</t>    <k>A small French island to the north of Guadeloupe, Saint Barthélémy is a very popular destination amongst the international elite. If the inhabitants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 15:00:00" d="2021-07-13 16:00:00"><n>MUNDO AD PORTAS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 16:00:00" d="2021-07-13 17:00:00"><n>SHARING THE EARTH EP. 09 MADAGASCAR</n><t>D</t>    <k>Veterinarian, biologist and adventurer Mannaďg de Kersauson travels the world in search of men and women who work to repair the damages inflicted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 17:00:00" d="2021-07-13 18:00:00"><n>SOAR</n><t>D</t>    <k>SOAR explores the evolving bond between two sisters: both are phenomenal dancers, one is a quadruple amputee from a childhood illness. Their art helps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 18:00:00" d="2021-07-13 18:30:00"><n>TRAVEL QUEST</n><t>D</t>    <k>Bill Ball breaks the rules and stereo types of travel shows as he ventures beyond the highlights. What do you do after you’ve lead groups</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 18:30:00" d="2021-07-13 19:00:00"><n>TRAVEL QUEST</n><t>D</t>    <k>Bill Ball breaks the rules and stereo types of travel shows as he ventures beyond the highlights. What do you do after you’ve lead groups</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 19:00:00" d="2021-07-13 19:30:00"><n u="AVIATORS S08 EP.">AVIATORS S08 EP. 03</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Aviators is a fast-paced, exciting TV series hosted and written by world re-nowned pilots. This unique series joins our aviation expert correspondents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 19:30:00" d="2021-07-13 20:00:00"><n u="AVIATORS S08 EP.">AVIATORS S08 EP. 04</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Aviators is a fast-paced, exciting TV series hosted and written by world re-nowned pilots. This unique series joins our aviation expert correspondents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 20:00:00" d="2021-07-13 20:30:00"><n>MUSIC VOYAGER</n><t>D</t>    <k>Music Voyager is a music and travel broadcast series (television/cable, broadband, in-flight and mobile) that invites viewers to discover the exciting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 20:30:00" d="2021-07-13 21:00:00"><n>WORLD MEDICINE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Embark on a world tour of ancestral medicinal practices with Bernard Fontanille - an emergency doctor used to operations in difficult conditions - through</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 21:00:00" d="2021-07-13 21:30:00"><n>WORLD MEDICINE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Embark on a world tour of ancestral medicinal practices with Bernard Fontanille - an emergency doctor used to operations in difficult conditions - through</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 21:30:00" d="2021-07-13 22:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF SOUTH AFRICA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Presenter Charlie Ottley explores some lesser known parts of the Western Cape from the townships to the desolate Cederberg Mountains. On his travels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 22:00:00" d="2021-07-13 23:00:00"><n>TRIBES OF THE HIMALAYAS</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the Indian region of Ladakh, in the heart of the Himalayas, a few thousands nomadic sheppperds still live with their herds at an altitude of 4500 meters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-13 23:00:00" d="2021-07-14 00:00:00"><n>BUDAPEST WILD</n><t>D</t>    <k>Most of us have very little to no idea how many species we are actually sharing our flats and houses with. Rest assured, it is an uncannily surprising number</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 00:00:00" d="2021-07-14 00:30:00"><n>WONDERFUL ITALY</n><t>D</t>    <k>Naples, the city that fascinates through its music, its thousand churches, its traditions and tastes. Between present and past the ancient origins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 00:30:00" d="2021-07-14 01:00:00"><n>WONDERFUL ITALY</n><t>D</t>    <k>Naples, the city that fascinates through its music, its thousand churches, its traditions and tastes. Between present and past the ancient origins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 01:00:00" d="2021-07-14 01:30:00"><n>GRAVEYARDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>A tour around the West graveyard, leads us to learn the story of Tucuman, its inhabitants and the funerary customs during each historic period</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 01:30:00" d="2021-07-14 02:00:00"><n>GRAVEYARDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>A visit to the two biggest and renewed graveyards of Buenos Aires: Recoleta and Chacarita. Both give us an idea of its architecture, customs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 02:00:00" d="2021-07-14 03:00:00"><n>TIMELESS TREASURES</n><t>D</t>    <k>A series celebrating the extraordinary preservation of human heritage. Discover the world’s most beautiful sites in an exceptional series of short programs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 03:00:00" d="2021-07-14 03:30:00"><n>AVIATORS, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Radial Engines: Anthony learns about the one-of a-kind sound and look of radial engines. Aerial Refueling: In-air refueling brings new meaning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 03:30:00" d="2021-07-14 04:00:00"><n>AVIATORS, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cobra: We take you aboard this two-bladed single engine attack helicopter formerly used by the United States Army. Team AeroDynamix:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 04:00:00" d="2021-07-14 04:30:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES</n><t>D</t>    <k>The next stops is the remote island of Saba where Paul and Sheryl experience the unique cultural attitudes of this small but independently-minded island</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 04:30:00" d="2021-07-14 05:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES</n><t>D</t>    <k>Montserrat and Guadeloupe have both suffered evacuations due to erupting volcanoes in the last few years. Paul and Sheryl visit these islands</k>  </p>
</a>
