<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="33" t="2020-05-12 04:32:48"><p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 05:00:00" d="2020-05-19 06:00:00"><n>I HAVE SEEN THE EARTH CHANGE - BOLIVIA: WHEN GLACIERS WEEP</n><t>D</t>    <k>Gerarda Moralčs is an Aymara Indian like half the population of Bolivia, and the president of a self-help charity network in the La region</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 06:00:00" d="2020-05-19 06:30:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - NORMANDY, FRANCE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Series 9 of Distant Shores follows Paul and Sheryl Shard on a diverse voyage from England through the inland waterways of France to the Mediterranean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 06:30:00" d="2020-05-19 07:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - PARIS, FRANCE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Series 9 of Distant Shores follows Paul and Sheryl Shard on a diverse voyage from England through the inland waterways of France to the Mediterranean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 07:00:00" d="2020-05-19 08:00:00"><n u="ANCIENT CULTURE -">ANCIENT CULTURE - (6)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 08:00:00" d="2020-05-19 09:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE - DATOGA</n><t>D</t>    <k>In this chapter, Claudio and his adventurous team decide to visit the tribe of the Datoga, an ancient tribe that lives across the Serengeti national paruqe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 09:00:00" d="2020-05-19 10:00:00"><n>CLOSE-UP ON WILDLIFE PHOTOGRAPHY</n><t>D</t>    <k>Europe still harbours a diversified wild animal life struggling to survive in the face of global urbanization. Approaching the more timid species</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 10:00:00" d="2020-05-19 11:00:00"><n>NOMADS - SNOWMOBILING THE ROCKY MOUNTAINS</n><t>D</t>    <k>The biggest stars of snowmobile head to the Rocky Mountains for an epic adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 11:00:00" d="2020-05-19 11:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - VI (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>FLYING AGAIN: Pilots return to the skies after extended absences only to realize that there’s a lot more rust to be removed than they might have expected</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 11:30:00" d="2020-05-19 12:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - VI (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>FORCES OF FLIGHT: Get ready for some learning as we explain the four forces that act on any object trying to essentially defy gravity. Sir Isaac would be proud! SKYTYPING: How to create messages in the sky that effective become the world’s largest billboard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 12:00:00" d="2020-05-19 12:30:00"><n u="GARONGA SAFARI -">GARONGA SAFARI - (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>This chapter shows how René must adjust to being without technology in the home. We will see a giraffe fighting in the outside of the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 12:30:00" d="2020-05-19 13:00:00"><n u="GARONGA SAFARI -">GARONGA SAFARI - (5)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Garonga Safari is a fun and educational show that showcases the African wilderness and the efforts to preserve it. Learn about the importance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 13:00:00" d="2020-05-19 14:00:00"><n>THE FORCE OF THE SEA - SOCIAL</n><t>D</t>    <k>Power of the Sea is a documentary series that reveals the special features of each one of the wonderful seas of Chile, generating conscience</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 14:00:00" d="2020-05-19 15:00:00"><n>POSTCARD PERFECT - ST. BARTH</n><t>D</t>    <k>A small French island to the north of Guadeloupe, Saint Barthélémy is a very popular destination amongst the international elite. If the inhabitants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 15:00:00" d="2020-05-19 16:00:00"><n u="MUNDO AD PORTAS -">MUNDO AD PORTAS - I (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 16:00:00" d="2020-05-19 17:00:00"><n u="LIVING JUNGLE -">LIVING JUNGLE - (14)</n><t>D</t>    <k>“Living Jungle” is an invitation to explore the most impressive biodiversity in the whole world: the Amazonian Forest. An experimented host starts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 17:00:00" d="2020-05-19 18:00:00"><n>TRIBES OF THE HIMALAYAS - NOMADS, THE GENERATION AFTER</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the Indian region of Ladakh, in the heart of the Himalayas, a few thousands nomadic sheppperds still live with their herds at an altitude of 4500 meters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 18:00:00" d="2020-05-19 19:00:00"><n>NOMADS - MOUNTAIN BIKING NEVADA</n><t>O</t>    <k>Pro mountain bikers test out their tricks in the dusty terrain of the Las Vegas dessert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 19:00:00" d="2020-05-19 20:30:00"><n>TEMPORADA DE ZOPILOTES</n><t>D</t>    <k>February of 1913. Mexico City is a nest of traitors that conspire against Francisco Madero, first president of the Mexican revolution</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 20:30:00" d="2020-05-19 21:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF SOUTH AFRICA - THE WESTERN CAPE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Presenter Charlie Ottley explores some lesser known parts of the Western Cape from the townships to the desolate Cederberg Mountains. On his travels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 21:00:00" d="2020-05-19 22:00:00"><n>GUSTAVE EIFFEL</n><t>D</t>    <k>Relying essentially on Gustave Eiffel's correspondence, and his descendants' testimonies, this filmed chronologically retraces his life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 22:00:00" d="2020-05-19 22:30:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - THE RED GOLD OF THE MEDITERRANEAN SEA">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - THE RED GOLD OF THE MEDITERRANEAN SEA (SARDEGNA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>It is in Sardinia that we discover the secrets of red coral, the underwater jewel of the Mediterranean Sea, where in Alghero you can find the centre</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 22:30:00" d="2020-05-19 23:00:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A SEA OF MARVELS!">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A SEA OF MARVELS! (CROAZIA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>An adventure in Croatia, to discover the Adriatic Sea but in apnoea. Together with Mike Maric, born in Rovigno d’Istria and world record holder in apnoea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-19 23:00:00" d="2020-05-20 00:00:00"><n>TECHNO-SCIENCE - DESASTRE NATURALES</n><t>D</t>    <k>Andrea Obaid and Cristián Campos visit two regions of our country, the Bío Bío Region and the Region of Araucanía to meet in two cities two significant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 00:00:00" d="2020-05-20 00:30:00"><n>WONDERFUL ITALY - CAMPANIA I – FROM ISCHIA TO CAPODIMONTE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Naples, the city that fascinates through its music, its thousand churches, its traditions and tastes. Between present and past the ancient origins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 00:30:00" d="2020-05-20 01:00:00"><n>WONDERFUL ITALY - CAMPANIA II – FROM CERTOSA DI SAN MARTINO TO CAPRI</n><t>D</t>    <k>Naples, the city that fascinates through its music, its thousand churches, its traditions and tastes. Between present and past the ancient origins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 01:00:00" d="2020-05-20 01:30:00"><n>GRAVEYARDS - TUCMAN GRAVEYARD</n><t>D</t>    <k>A tour around the West graveyard, leads us to learn the story of Tucuman, its inhabitants and the funerary customs during each historic period</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 01:30:00" d="2020-05-20 02:00:00"><n>GRAVEYARDS - RECOLETA &amp; CHARCARITA GRAVEYARD</n><t>D</t>    <k>A visit to the two biggest and renewed graveyards of Buenos Aires: Recoleta and Chacarita. Both give us an idea of its architecture, customs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 02:00:00" d="2020-05-20 02:30:00"><n>LOW COST - ROME</n><t>D</t>    <k>Each city is in its native language (ie. Parisis in French, Rome is in Italian, Berlin is in German, etc. with English Scripts) showing the viewer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 02:30:00" d="2020-05-20 03:00:00"><n>LOW COST - VALENCIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Each city is in its native language (ie. Parisis in French, Rome is in Italian, Berlin is in German, etc. with English Scripts) showing the viewer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 03:00:00" d="2020-05-20 03:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - IV (5)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Radial Engines: Anthony learns about the one-of a-kind sound and look of radial engines. Aerial Refueling: In-air refueling brings new meaning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 03:30:00" d="2020-05-20 04:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - IV (6)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Cobra: We take you aboard this two-bladed single engine attack helicopter formerly used by the United States Army. Team AeroDynamix:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 04:00:00" d="2020-05-20 04:30:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - SABA</n><t>D</t>    <k>The next stops is the remote island of Saba where Paul and Sheryl experience the unique cultural attitudes of this small but independently-minded island</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-20 04:30:00" d="2020-05-20 05:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - MONTSERRAT &amp; GUADELOUPE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Montserrat and Guadeloupe have both suffered evacuations due to erupting volcanoes in the last few years. Paul and Sheryl visit these islands</k>  </p>
</a>
