<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="32" t="2020-05-17 04:32:03"><p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 05:00:00" d="2020-05-24 06:00:00"><n>I HAVE SEEN THE EARTH CHANGE - JAPAN: LAND OF THE BURNING SUN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Katsuo Sasaki grows rice in Miyagi Province where the crop has a strong reputation. And yet, he is becoming impoverished since never before seen insects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 06:00:00" d="2020-05-24 07:00:00"><n>NEXOS - THE SHARED LANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Lebanon, Bosnia, Cyprus are countries without a predominance of one civilization or religion over the other and they live together in a maelstrom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 07:00:00" d="2020-05-24 07:30:00"><n u="ALL ABOUT ANIMALS -">ALL ABOUT ANIMALS - (15)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 07:30:00" d="2020-05-24 08:00:00"><n u="ALL ABOUT ANIMALS -">ALL ABOUT ANIMALS - (16)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 08:00:00" d="2020-05-24 09:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE - OVAMBO</n><t>D</t>    <k>A curious reporter, outdoor lover, will not rest until he shows us every mystery of the wild, black heart of Central Africa, discovering the stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 09:00:00" d="2020-05-24 10:00:00"><n u="ANCIENT CULTURE -">ANCIENT CULTURE - (11)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 10:00:00" d="2020-05-24 11:00:00"><n>RISE OF ECOLOGY</n><t>D</t>    <k>How did the whole green ecological phenomenon really start? Which are its main milestones? The film documents how environmental disasters have played</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 11:00:00" d="2020-05-24 11:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - III (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Training in a T-6: Kurtis earns his wings in a T-6 warbird. Journey of a Bag: Where does your bag go once it leaves your hands and heads down a conveyor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 11:30:00" d="2020-05-24 12:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - III (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Skydiving: Sara and Raeleen jump out of a perfectly good airplane! Rob Reider, Announcer: The famous voice of some of the largest air shows in the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 12:00:00" d="2020-05-24 13:00:00"><n>SEYCHELLES - TRIP TO PARADISE</n><t>D</t>    <k>White beaches, blue water and wonderful silence, the Seychelles are the garden eden. Consisting out of more than 100 isles, &quot;Seychelles - Trip to Paradise&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 13:00:00" d="2020-05-24 14:00:00"><n>ON THE HIGHWAYS OF HISTORY</n><t>D</t>    <k>The construction of a new highway near the city of Orleans has permitted to excave archaeological treasures and reveal exceptional information about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 14:00:00" d="2020-05-24 14:30:00"><n>PATHFINDERS - SURF PERUVIAN STYLE</n><t>D</t>    <k>It is no longer acceptable to use the world’s most beautiful locations as playgrounds without paying attention to the local people and their ecosystems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 14:30:00" d="2020-05-24 15:00:00"><n>PATHFINDERS - THE OTHER KENYA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Outdoor tourism has evolved beyond the landscape. Attention to local people and ecosystems while at the same time enjoying the world's most desirable</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 15:00:00" d="2020-05-24 16:00:00"><n u="MUNDO AD PORTAS -">MUNDO AD PORTAS - I (7)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 16:00:00" d="2020-05-24 17:00:00"><n>CLOSE-UP ON WILDLIFE PHOTOGRAPHY</n><t>D</t>    <k>Europe still harbours a diversified wild animal life struggling to survive in the face of global urbanization. Approaching the more timid species</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 17:00:00" d="2020-05-24 17:30:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - AFRICA-DORZE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 17:30:00" d="2020-05-24 18:00:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - FRANKFURT</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 18:00:00" d="2020-05-24 18:30:00"><n>THE NEXT ASIAN MIRACLE - AGRICULTURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Food security is becoming an increasingly contentious issue in South East Asia. Rising populations, climate change and higher commodity prices are placing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 18:30:00" d="2020-05-24 19:00:00"><n>THE NEXT ASIAN MIRACLE - INFLATION</n><t>D</t>    <k>South East Asia is embattled with sky rocketing inflation, threatening to wipe out the gains of economic growth made within the past decade</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 19:00:00" d="2020-05-24 20:00:00"><n>NOMADS - RESPECT-EXTREME BIG MOUNTAIN SKIING AROUND THE GLOBE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Respect is something all skiing athletes must have. Respect for different cultures, lifestyles and their environment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 20:00:00" d="2020-05-24 20:30:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - POLYNESIA, THE GODDESS OF NATURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>A visit to the Island of Tahiti together with a local called Alphonse who, as well as acquainting us with the famous canoe race Hawaiki Nui Va’a</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 20:30:00" d="2020-05-24 21:00:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - SOUTH SEA GIFTS</n><t>D</t>    <k>On board a catamaran, we discover several islands in the Society Island archipelago, in Polynesia. Of the Island of Raiatea, hilly and volcanic, we explore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 21:00:00" d="2020-05-24 22:00:00"><n>TECHNO-SCIENCE - IMPACTO DEL HOMBRE EN VESTIGIOS MILENARIOS</n><t>D</t>    <k>In this chapter, Andrea goes to San Vicente de Tagua Tagua to see a museum of natural history. Research shows that the sector Tagua Tagua million years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 22:00:00" d="2020-05-24 22:30:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - JAPAN'S HERBIVOROUS MAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Research shows that two out of five women say they wish to marry a man who earns at least 6 million yen a year — but such men make up only</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 22:30:00" d="2020-05-24 23:00:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - INDONESIA'S NEW ERA OF ENTREPRENEURSHIP</n><t>D</t>    <k>Indonesia’s economy was brought to its knees when the Asian Financial Crisis hit in 1997. A decade or so later, under the global downturn, the economy barely flinched</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-24 23:00:00" d="2020-05-25 00:00:00"><n>THE CHARRO</n><t>D</t>    <k>The &quot;charro&quot;, term that comes from military charreteras (Epaulettes) that horse riders use, is one of Mexico's national symbols. Their figure appeared</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-25 00:00:00" d="2020-05-25 01:00:00"><n>THE NEOLITHIC MOUNTAINS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel through Europe going back in time to the Neolithic era. Going to the France, England and Italy, discover more about the different plates that moved</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-25 01:00:00" d="2020-05-25 02:00:00"><n>CHINA UNCOVERED - A CITY TRANSFORMED</n><t>D</t>    <k>From the skyscrapers of Shanghai to the mountainous peaks of &quot;The Last Shangri-La&quot;, explore the breathtaking landscape of this incredible country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-25 02:00:00" d="2020-05-25 03:00:00"><n>RISE OF ECOLOGY</n><t>D</t>    <k>How did the whole green ecological phenomenon really start? Which are its main milestones? The film documents how environmental disasters have played</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-25 03:00:00" d="2020-05-25 04:00:00"><n>SEYCHELLES - TRIP TO PARADISE</n><t>D</t>    <k>White beaches, blue water and wonderful silence, the Seychelles are the garden eden. Consisting out of more than 100 isles, &quot;Seychelles - Trip to Paradise&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-25 04:00:00" d="2020-05-25 04:30:00"><n>LEGENDARY BEACHES - GOA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Goa is bordered by more than 20 beaches with enchanting names like Anjuna, Calangute, Candolim, Vagator, Benolim. Ruled by the Portuguese during</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-25 04:30:00" d="2020-05-25 05:00:00"><n u="GOING SOUTH -">GOING SOUTH - (6)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Going South: Cycling through the Americas an adventurous environmental cycling documentary. As the climate changes, an environmental crisis is proclaimed</k>  </p>
</a>
