<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="33" t="2020-05-28 04:35:18"><p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 05:00:00" d="2020-06-04 06:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE - MASAI MARA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra (conductor) part to Kenya to go into the Massai Mara National Park, one of the most beautiful nature reserves of Planet Earth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 06:00:00" d="2020-06-04 07:00:00"><n u="LIVING JUNGLE -">LIVING JUNGLE - (5)</n><t>D</t>    <k>“Living Jungle” is an invitation to explore the most impressive biodiversity in the whole world: the Amazonian Forest. An experimented host starts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 07:00:00" d="2020-06-04 07:30:00"><n>FISH LIFE - THE CORAL THEATRE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Coral reefs are reminiscent of the tower of Babel. Dating back over 200 million years ago, their structure seems part of a legend. All at once place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 07:30:00" d="2020-06-04 08:00:00"><n>FISH LIFE - HAZARDS OF THE SEA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Today still, the sea induces fear. In some people’s imagination, it is inhabited by sea monsters straight out of the depths. However, risk isn’t always</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 08:00:00" d="2020-06-04 08:30:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - CRUISING IN STYLE</n><t>D</t>    <k>At sea and in many of the worldwide ports Distant Shores sails to, Paul and Sheryl are in the company of luxurious cruise ships. In this episode</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 08:30:00" d="2020-06-04 09:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - CHESAPEAKE WEST</n><t>D</t>    <k>As hurricane season approaches, Paul and Sheryl leave the tropics and sail north to the Chesapeake Bay, the largest estuary in the United States, where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 09:00:00" d="2020-06-04 09:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - II (7)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Aircraft ownership: Exploring the varied costs and entry points of flying for everyone from the weekend warrior to the rich and famous. $100 Hamburger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 09:30:00" d="2020-06-04 10:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - II (8)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Airpark living: When your driveway is a runway, life is good! Water escape: Sara takes the plunge and learns how to survive a ditching. Jet truck race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 10:00:00" d="2020-06-04 10:30:00"><n>ANIMAL ALLIES - VET'S SCHOOL</n><t>D</t>    <k>In Animal Doctors, two vets are out to save Australia’s wildlife by setting up an operating theatre in the bush, while in the UK some abused chimpanzees</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 10:30:00" d="2020-06-04 11:00:00"><n>ANIMAL ALLIES - INFECTED FANG</n><t>D</t>    <k>In South Africa, a nervous Doc Rogers takes on a very precious patient; while in Australia Animal Helpers assist a group of whales as they struggle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 11:00:00" d="2020-06-04 12:00:00"><n u="ANCIENT CULTURE -">ANCIENT CULTURE - (15)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 12:00:00" d="2020-06-04 13:00:00"><n u="THE SOUTHERN FLOWER AT SEA - FLOWER IN BRAZIL - PART">THE SOUTHERN FLOWER AT SEA - FLOWER IN BRAZIL - PART 1</n><t>D</t>    <k>After 55 000 miles (105 000 km) traveled and well-deserved rest in Ushuaia, southern flower s' is now recovered from her adventures in Antarctica, ready</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 13:00:00" d="2020-06-04 13:30:00"><n u="TRAVEL PLAN - LONDON PART">TRAVEL PLAN - LONDON PART 1</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 13:30:00" d="2020-06-04 14:00:00"><n u="TRAVEL PLAN - LONDON PART">TRAVEL PLAN - LONDON PART 2</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 14:00:00" d="2020-06-04 15:00:00"><n u="CHINA, A TIMELESS COUNTRY - PART">CHINA, A TIMELESS COUNTRY - PART 1</n><t>D</t>    <k>This series goes through the most unknown places in the Republic of China, discovering at each step the marks that its history has left in the present</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 15:00:00" d="2020-06-04 16:00:00"><n>ANTARCTICA FLOWERS - HEADING SOUTH</n><t>D</t>    <k>The crew found his boat Flower Southern Tahiti, after six months of winter, unfortunately a bad surprise awaits. La Fleur was looted: cameras, navigation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 16:00:00" d="2020-06-04 17:00:00"><n>NOMADS - EXTREME FREESKIING SNOWBIRD, UTAH</n><t>D</t>    <k>Athletes from across the world are competing in skier cross and big mountain freeskiing for pride glory and big bucks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 17:00:00" d="2020-06-04 18:00:00"><n u="MANHATTAN">MANHATTAN 1609</n><t>D</t>    <k>Some four centuries ago, Protestants from Belgium and the North of France, chased from their region by war and religion, left to build</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 18:00:00" d="2020-06-04 19:00:00"><n u="LIVING JUNGLE -">LIVING JUNGLE - (11)</n><t>D</t>    <k>“Living Jungle” is an invitation to explore the most impressive biodiversity in the whole world: the Amazonian Forest. An experimented host starts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 19:00:00" d="2020-06-04 20:00:00"><n u="WIND QUEST -">WIND QUEST - (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Arthur de Kersauson, a young city-dweller hooked on extreme sports, and Antoine Auriol, World Champion in the Kiteboard Pro World Tour, set out in search</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 20:00:00" d="2020-06-04 21:30:00"><n>TEROS</n><t>D</t>    <k>TEROS is a documentary film that tells the story of Los Teros, the team that defends Uruguay national team, which is the only amateur team competed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 21:30:00" d="2020-06-04 22:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF SOUTH AFRICA - THE WINELANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>A viticultural romp around Capetown’s historic wine lands - presenter Charlie Ottley checks out the ultimate designer winery, the last word in chic hotels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 22:00:00" d="2020-06-04 22:30:00"><n>INSPIRING LIVES GLOBAL - BAHIA DE CARAQUEZ, ECUADOR</n><t>D</t>    <k>INSPIRING LIVES GLOBAL follows the journey of Tiamara Williams, social entrepreneur, TV host and life coach from New Zealand, around the developing world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 22:30:00" d="2020-06-04 23:00:00"><n>INSPIRING LIVES GLOBAL - RIO MUCHACHO, ECUADOR</n><t>D</t>    <k>INSPIRING LIVES GLOBAL follows the journey of Tiamara Williams, social entrepreneur, TV host and life coach from New Zealand, around the developing world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 23:00:00" d="2020-06-04 23:30:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - PHILIPPINES OFWs</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Philippines is one of the fastest growing economies among the ASEAN 5. And, in 2010, it showed such sterling results that the IMF even predicted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 23:30:00" d="2020-06-05 00:00:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - SHANGHAI'S TWO-CHILDREN POLICY</n><t>D</t>    <k>China, with a population of 1. 3 billion, would hardly be in need of a baby boom. However, Shanghai paints a starkly different picture. Ageing faster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 00:00:00" d="2020-06-05 00:30:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - FLYING OVER THE WATERWAYS">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - FLYING OVER THE WATERWAYS (VENEZUELA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>On board of the strangest Cessna in the whole of Venezuela. Vittorio, a man who feels that his personal space is more in the air rather than on the round</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 00:30:00" d="2020-06-05 01:00:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - BETWEEN THE SACRED AND THE PROFANE">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - BETWEEN THE SACRED AND THE PROFANE (CUBA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Our journey to Cuba begins in its capital city Havana, a city of architecture and sea. The sea that Ernest Hemingway loved so much, and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 01:00:00" d="2020-06-05 02:00:00"><n>SACRED CULTURE - DARJEELING</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra embarks on a trip to India and Nepal, to show the life of its inhabitants, their customs, the architecture of its temples and holy cities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 02:00:00" d="2020-06-05 03:00:00"><n>NOMADS - CRANKWORX MOUNTAIN BIKE FESTIVAL IN BRITISH COLUMBIA, CANADA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Top pros and riders meet up for five days of racing in Whistler ski resort for the Crankworx Mountain Bike Festival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 03:00:00" d="2020-06-05 03:30:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - ROME</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 03:30:00" d="2020-06-05 04:30:00"><n u="LIVING JUNGLE -">LIVING JUNGLE - (6)</n><t>D</t>    <k>“Living Jungle” is an invitation to explore the most impressive biodiversity in the whole world: the Amazonian Forest. An experimented host starts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 04:30:00" d="2020-06-05 05:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF COLOMBIA - HISTORIC COLOMBIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Charlie Ottley travels through time from Colombia's pre-Hispanic origins through its colonial era to the present day, encapsulated by the bustle</k>  </p>
</a>
