<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a><n>FLAVOURS OF COLOMBIA</n><g><o>https://gonet.cz/~tri65dnigalerie/zanr/600/c/c49bf832bb9e4f48bffc3d1cd1f2a8d0.jpg</o></g><o>https://gonet.cz/~tri65dnigalerie/zanr/250/c/c49bf832bb9e4f48bffc3d1cd1f2a8d0.jpg</o><s o="2021-07-20 04:00:00" d="2021-07-20 04:30:00" n="DocuBox HD" id_tv="733"></s><p><k>Flavours Of... sees gastronomer Charlie Ottley challenge his taste buds as he travels through some of the most exciting and unpredictable countries in the world, from South Africa to Scotland, Greece to Mexico, through to Colombia. Charlie travels the length of these countries in his quest for the best, packing in as much adventure as possible; from diving in Kalymnos to trekking through the Amazon to surviving the Day of the Dead festival. Prepared to risk life and limb in his quest for fun, fulfilment and a full stomach, Charlie experiences a mouth-watering trip where he samples the bizarre and wonderful dishes of these countries, and by the time he’s finished there are few flavours he hasn’t tasted! Charlie Ottley challenges his taste buds once more, this time by gallivanting around the magnificent but previously much maligned country of Colombia. Charlie undertakes an incredible journey from the Caribbean and Pacific coastlines, up over the high Andes, down to the depths of the jungle and onto the banks of the mighty Amazon. Colombia is synonymous with the magical coffee bean and Charlie learns the secret to the drink that has captured the world. It wouldn't be a culinary journey in the Charlie Ottley mould without the addition of a few bizarre dishes along the way and this time out Charlie does not disappoint as he tucks into some rodent stew and discovers how to cook a traditional pirate recipe. Looking down from the snow-clad volcanoes in the Los Nevados National Park, Charlie concludes that, for him, Colombia is not only safe to visit but also constitutes one of the last unspoilt destinations in Latin America. Charlie Ottley explores the stunning Pacific Region from the bleak and beautiful Isle of Gorgona to the great empty beaches of the South West. Along the way he visits the bustling city of Cali, birthplace of Colombian salsa, and discovers some of the best Latin American dancing in the world, as well as some of the worst.</k></p><i><t>Dokument</t><w>https://tv.sms.cz/televize/docubox-hd/20210720/1540228065-Flavours-of-colombia</w></i><x></x></a>
