<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="32" t="2020-05-27 04:33:52"><p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 05:00:00" d="2020-06-03 06:00:00"><n u="FRENCH SECRET SERVICES, A DECLASSIFIED HISTORY -">FRENCH SECRET SERVICES, A DECLASSIFIED HISTORY - (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Master Spies, secret Agents, assassins of the Republic, top Intel, infallibles: French intelligence agencies evoke superlatives, stereotypes, and paradoxes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 06:00:00" d="2020-06-03 07:00:00"><n>PROMISE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Despite 25 years of determined efforts made by the NHS to reduce the rate of breast cancer deaths and new breast cancer cases by detecting the disease</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 07:00:00" d="2020-06-03 07:30:00"><n u="RACING GREEN -">RACING GREEN - (8)</n><t>D</t>    <k>The border crossing into Chile happens in record time and the team is set to visit the European Southern observatory in the middle of the Atacama desert</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 07:30:00" d="2020-06-03 08:00:00"><n u="KUNG FU KITCHEN - FLYING ROTI CANAI">KUNG FU KITCHEN - FLYING ROTI CANAI (MALACCA, MALAYSIA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>The roti canai is a round flat pancake popular in Malaysia and Singapore. Of south Indian origin, the roti is fluffy inside, crisp outside. The original</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 08:00:00" d="2020-06-03 09:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE - HIMBA NOCHE</n><t>D</t>    <k>A curious reporter, outdoor lover, will not rest until he shows us every mystery of the wild, black heart of Central Africa, discovering the stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 09:00:00" d="2020-06-03 09:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - II (5)</n><t>D</t>    <k>AOPA Summit: The annual event of the Aircraft Owners and Pilots Association. LAPD: We take you inside the aerial unit of the Los Angeles Police Department</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 09:30:00" d="2020-06-03 10:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - II (6)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Airshows - Behind the scenes: An exclusive look at a day in the life of a major airshow from the perspective of a performer, an air traffic controller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 10:00:00" d="2020-06-03 11:00:00"><n>BIOTIFUL PLANET - CONGO</n><t>D</t>    <k>A nine-part series on the treasures of France’s overseas territories. The French overseas territories are a treasure trove of biodiversity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 11:00:00" d="2020-06-03 12:00:00"><n u="ANCIENT CULTURE -">ANCIENT CULTURE - (14)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 12:00:00" d="2020-06-03 12:30:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - ARC FINISH/ST. LUCIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Series 9 of Distant Shores follows Paul and Sheryl Shard on a diverse voyage from England through the inland waterways of France to the Mediterranean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 12:30:00" d="2020-06-03 13:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - BRITISH VIRGIN ISLANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Series 9 of Distant Shores follows Paul and Sheryl Shard on a diverse voyage from England through the inland waterways of France to the Mediterranean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 13:00:00" d="2020-06-03 13:30:00"><n u="GOING SOUTH -">GOING SOUTH - (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Going South: Cycling through the Americas an adventurous environmental cycling documentary. As the climate changes, an environmental crisis is proclaimed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 13:30:00" d="2020-06-03 14:00:00"><n u="GOING SOUTH -">GOING SOUTH - (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Going South: Cycling through the Americas an adventurous environmental cycling documentary. As the climate changes, an environmental crisis is proclaimed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 14:00:00" d="2020-06-03 14:30:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - MOSCOW</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 14:30:00" d="2020-06-03 15:00:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - MUMBAI</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 15:00:00" d="2020-06-03 16:00:00"><n u="MUNDO AD PORTAS -">MUNDO AD PORTAS - I (10)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 16:00:00" d="2020-06-03 17:00:00"><n>NOMADS - BASE JUMPING IN THE LAUTERBRUNNEN VALLEY-SWITZERLAND</n><t>D</t>    <k>Follow base jumping icon and ski base pioneer into the heart of Switzerland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 17:00:00" d="2020-06-03 18:00:00"><n u="LIVING JUNGLE -">LIVING JUNGLE - (10)</n><t>D</t>    <k>“Living Jungle” is an invitation to explore the most impressive biodiversity in the whole world: the Amazonian Forest. An experimented host starts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 18:00:00" d="2020-06-03 19:00:00"><n u="HAPPINESS IS ON THE PLATE -">HAPPINESS IS ON THE PLATE - (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>A tasty series blending travel, cooking, nature and civic sense, following the daily work of five &quot;green&quot; chefs fighting for eco-friendly cooking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 19:00:00" d="2020-06-03 20:00:00"><n u="PLANT SECRETS -">PLANT SECRETS - (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>To most of us, plants make up a familiar background decoration, albeit a beautiful one, but we don't really pay them that much attention</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 20:00:00" d="2020-06-03 21:30:00"><n>SILENCE IS GOLD</n><t>D</t>    <k>This feature documentary takes us through the twists and turns of judicial proceedings pitting Canadian mining companies Barrick Gold and Banro against</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 21:30:00" d="2020-06-03 22:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF SOUTH AFRICA - THE INTERIOR</n><t>D</t>    <k>From the savage Kruger National Park via Suweto to the oldest Baobab tree in the world, Charlie Ottley takes us on a breathless safari across South</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 22:00:00" d="2020-06-03 22:30:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - PHILIPPINES OFWs</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Philippines is one of the fastest growing economies among the ASEAN 5. And, in 2010, it showed such sterling results that the IMF even predicted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 22:30:00" d="2020-06-03 23:00:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - SHANGHAI'S TWO-CHILDREN POLICY</n><t>D</t>    <k>China, with a population of 1. 3 billion, would hardly be in need of a baby boom. However, Shanghai paints a starkly different picture. Ageing faster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-03 23:00:00" d="2020-06-04 00:00:00"><n u="MUNDO AD PORTAS -">MUNDO AD PORTAS - I (11)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 00:00:00" d="2020-06-04 00:30:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A DIVERS' PARADISE</n><t>D</t>    <k>In open sea, along the Venezuelan coastline, we fly over the biggest coral atoll of the Caribbean Sea to then dive into these beautiful waters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 00:30:00" d="2020-06-04 01:00:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - THE ROUTE TO LOS ROQUES</n><t>D</t>    <k>Our chosen route is the coral archipelago of Los Roques, our sail boat is pushed forward by the trade winds as we go to explore the small &quot;cayos&quot; in the region</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 01:00:00" d="2020-06-04 02:00:00"><n>NOMAD'S LAND - ETHIOPIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>With the label of &quot;cradle of humanity&quot;, Ethiopia is adorned with a legendary aura. It is here that the man was born, here he would have his first steps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 02:00:00" d="2020-06-04 03:00:00"><n>THE FORCE OF EARTH - LA FORMACION DE LA TIERRA</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Force of Earth is an educational documentary series of the journey of a Chilean scientist. In every episode we will learn about geography and geology</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 03:00:00" d="2020-06-04 04:00:00"><n u="MUNDO AD PORTAS -">MUNDO AD PORTAS - I (12)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 04:00:00" d="2020-06-04 04:30:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF SCOTLAND - THE BORDERS / LOWLANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Join Charlie for a gastronomic rummage through the Scottish Lowlands. Highlight include a visit to spectacular Floors Castle and the Roxburghe estate where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-04 04:30:00" d="2020-06-04 05:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF SCOTLAND - THE WEST COAST</n><t>D</t>    <k>Charlie takes a tour of Scotland’s wild west coast starting with the journey of a lifetime aboard the famous Royal Scotsman. Next we explore majestic</k>  </p>
</a>
