<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="36" t="2021-07-10 04:57:54"><p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 05:00:00" d="2021-07-17 06:00:00"><n>I HAVE SEEN THE EARTH CHANGE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Colleen Gregory (truck farmer, beekeeper and sheep breeder) lives in the San Juan Islands, off Seattle. Fed up with the city and its ongoing activity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 06:00:00" d="2021-07-17 07:00:00"><n>FORCE OF EARTH, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Force of Earth is an educational documentary series of the journey of a Chilean scientist. In every episode we will learn about geography and geology</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 07:00:00" d="2021-07-17 07:30:00"><n>ALL ABOUT ANIMALS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 07:30:00" d="2021-07-17 08:00:00"><n>ALL ABOUT ANIMALS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 08:00:00" d="2021-07-17 09:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>A curious reporter, outdoor lover, will not rest until he shows us every mystery of the wild, black heart of Central Africa, discovering the stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 09:00:00" d="2021-07-17 10:00:00"><n>ANCIENT CULTURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 10:00:00" d="2021-07-17 11:00:00"><n>JUNGWA, THE BROKEN BALANCE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Ladakh, a small region in the north of India, has suffered many years of terrible natural disasters, possibly the consequences of climate change, and which</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 11:00:00" d="2021-07-17 11:30:00"><n>TERRUA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Doctors recommend wine for its antioxidant properties and nutrients. We recommend it simply because it’s good. That’s why in Terruá, we invite you to learn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 11:30:00" d="2021-07-17 12:00:00"><n>TERRUA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Doctors recommend wine for its antioxidant properties and nutrients. We recommend it simply because it’s good. That’s why in Terruá, we invite you to learn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 12:00:00" d="2021-07-17 13:00:00"><n>SACRED CULTURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra embarks on a trip to India and Nepal, to show the life of its inhabitants, their customs, the architecture of its temples and holy cities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 13:00:00" d="2021-07-17 13:30:00"><n>TWENTY MASTERPIECES</n><t>D</t>    <k>Throughout the world, there are men and women who strive to protect the planet, rather than exploiting its resources. They know that man cannot exist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 13:30:00" d="2021-07-17 14:00:00"><n>TWENTY MASTERPIECES</n><t>D</t>    <k>Throughout the world, there are men and women who strive to protect the planet, rather than exploiting its resources. They know that man cannot exist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 14:00:00" d="2021-07-17 15:00:00"><n u="MANHATTAN">MANHATTAN 1609</n><t>D</t>    <k>Some four centuries ago, Protestants from Belgium and the North of France, chased from their region by war and religion, left to build</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 15:00:00" d="2021-07-17 15:30:00"><n>MUSIC VOYAGER S07 EP. 04: BAHAMAS - EXUMA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Music Voyager is a music and travel broadcast series (television/cable, broadband, in-flight and mobile) that invites viewers to discover the exciting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 15:30:00" d="2021-07-17 16:00:00"><n>MUSIC VOYAGER S07 EP. 05: BAHAMAS - ELEUTHERA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Music Voyager is a music and travel broadcast series (television/cable, broadband, in-flight and mobile) that invites viewers to discover the exciting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 16:00:00" d="2021-07-17 16:30:00"><n>WORLD MEDICINE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Embark on a world tour of ancestral medicinal practices with Bernard Fontanille - an emergency doctor used to operations in difficult conditions - through</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 16:30:00" d="2021-07-17 17:00:00"><n>WORLD MEDICINE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Embark on a world tour of ancestral medicinal practices with Bernard Fontanille - an emergency doctor used to operations in difficult conditions - through</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 17:00:00" d="2021-07-17 17:30:00"><n>EXPLORE TRAVEL</n><t>D</t>    <k>Japan. A place where you can certainly find heaven on earth and quickly escape the hassle and bustle of daily life. Here's a historical trail of a lifetime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 17:30:00" d="2021-07-17 18:00:00"><n>MARS RISING</n><t>D</t>    <k>The countdown has begun for the 21st century’s most heroic and potentially deadliest expedition - the first manned mission to Mars – and back. Produced by Galafilm Inc</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 18:00:00" d="2021-07-17 19:00:00"><n>WWII DOCUMENTARY FILMS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Award-winning documentary films produced to enlighten future generations about the personal stories of the WWII generations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 19:00:00" d="2021-07-17 19:30:00"><n>TRAVEL QUEST</n><t>D</t>    <k>Bill Ball breaks the rules and stereo types of travel shows as he ventures beyond the highlights. What do you do after you’ve lead groups</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 19:30:00" d="2021-07-17 20:00:00"><n>TRAVEL QUEST</n><t>D</t>    <k>Bill Ball breaks the rules and stereo types of travel shows as he ventures beyond the highlights. What do you do after you’ve lead groups</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 20:00:00" d="2021-07-17 20:30:00"><n>EUROPE'S COASTLINES FROM ABOVE</n><t>D</t>    <k>This series takes viewers across the 10.000 km long European coastlines from Cape North all the way down to the Mediterranean coasts and islands, including</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 20:30:00" d="2021-07-17 21:00:00"><n>EUROPE'S COASTLINES FROM ABOVE</n><t>D</t>    <k>This series takes viewers across the 10.000 km long European coastlines from Cape North all the way down to the Mediterranean coasts and islands, including</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 21:00:00" d="2021-07-17 22:00:00"><n>HAPPINESS IS ON THE PLATE</n><t>D</t>    <k>A tasty series blending travel, cooking, nature and civic sense, following the daily work of five &quot;green&quot; chefs fighting for eco-friendly cooking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 22:00:00" d="2021-07-17 22:30:00"><n>ASIAN CENTURY, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Having risen from the ashes of one of the poorest economies, India now is walking the road to becoming a superpower. Come the turn of the century</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 22:30:00" d="2021-07-17 23:00:00"><n>ASIAN CENTURY, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>South Korea boasts a population with one of the most highly educated youth in the world. However, with one in ten youth being unemployed, the nation’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-17 23:00:00" d="2021-07-18 00:00:00"><n>FORCE OF THE AIR, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Multidisciplinary documentary series that reveals some of the particular weather conditions of the Chilean territory and its evolution</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 00:00:00" d="2021-07-18 00:30:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES</n><t>D</t>    <k>Just south of Guadeloupe is a small group of islands known as &quot;The Saints&quot;. Paul and Sheryl discover a little bit of French heaven in the Caribbean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 00:30:00" d="2021-07-18 01:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES</n><t>D</t>    <k>A spring journey north through the lovely Bahamas! We sail first to Mayaguana, then Ragged and the Jumentos Cays before heading to the Exumas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 01:00:00" d="2021-07-18 02:00:00"><n>NOMAD'S LAND</n><t>D</t>    <k>With the label of &quot;cradle of humanity&quot;, Ethiopia is adorned with a legendary aura. It is here that the man was born, here he would have his first steps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 02:00:00" d="2021-07-18 02:30:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 02:30:00" d="2021-07-18 03:00:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 03:00:00" d="2021-07-18 03:30:00"><n>AVIATORS, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>BELL 407 HELICOPTER: If you didn't think there’s much of a difference between flying a helicopter and a fixed wing airplane watch as we put our training</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 03:30:00" d="2021-07-18 04:00:00"><n>AVIATORS, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>AIRCRAFT ENGINES: We take it back to basics when examining the components used to build aircraft engines so that they produce the kind of power needed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 04:00:00" d="2021-07-18 05:00:00"><n u="CARSTENSZ - THE SEVENTH SUMMIT">CARSTENSZ - THE SEVENTH SUMMIT (FAR BEYOND SENSATIONS)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Snowy Mountains rise high above the untouched jungle of New Guinea, breaking through heavy rain clouds. A limestone pyramid, known as the Carstensz</k>  </p>
</a>
