<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="36" t="2020-05-29 04:33:54"><p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 05:00:00" d="2020-06-05 06:00:00"><n>CARMEN, WHAT A STORY</n><t>D</t>    <k>Carmen, the femme fatale with a tragic destiny. The character, created by Prosper Mérimée in a novel published in 1847, acquired international</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 06:00:00" d="2020-06-05 07:00:00"><n>SCEPTICS - CLIMATE CHANGE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Humanity’s greatest challenge: global warming, the hole in the ozone layer, melting polar icecaps. Do we still have time to stop it? Are human beings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 07:00:00" d="2020-06-05 07:30:00"><n>FISH LIFE - THE RACE FOR SPACE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Reefs are magnificent edifices yet they still remain largely unknown. Even though it covers less than 1% of the sea floor, this ecosystem plays</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 07:30:00" d="2020-06-05 08:00:00"><n>FISH LIFE - THE INVISIBLES</n><t>D</t>    <k>Under the sea as on earth, sight is crucial for every simple act of life. The eyes allow to detect the danger, to flee or to attack. In this context, being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 08:00:00" d="2020-06-05 09:00:00"><n>CHINA UNCOVERED - THE NEED FOR SPEED</n><t>D</t>    <k>China runs on two gears as it moves millions of people around every day. A young driver of one of the world’s fastest trains and two seasoned pilots</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 09:00:00" d="2020-06-05 09:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - II (9)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Warbirds: Kurtis takes a walk back in time as he gets up close to a collection of historic aircraft that flew world-altering missions. iPad in the cockpit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 09:30:00" d="2020-06-05 10:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - II (10)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Wilderness survival: A well-known outdoorsman and pilot shows us how to spend the night in the remote wilderness while waiting for the weather to pass</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 10:00:00" d="2020-06-05 10:30:00"><n u="RACING GREEN -">RACING GREEN - (5)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Central America adds massive challenges to the Racing Green adventure. Security is a major worry and enormous tropical rain storms are pushing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 10:30:00" d="2020-06-05 11:00:00"><n u="RACING GREEN -">RACING GREEN - (6)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Colombia, at the start of South America looks bleak. Most low voltage cables of the SR-0 got burnt when the car caught fire in the harbour of Cartagena</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 11:00:00" d="2020-06-05 11:30:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - ROME</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 11:30:00" d="2020-06-05 12:00:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - KANCHANABURI</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 12:00:00" d="2020-06-05 12:30:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - ANATALYA&amp;KEMER</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 12:30:00" d="2020-06-05 13:00:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - ARBA MINCH</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 13:00:00" d="2020-06-05 13:30:00"><n u="GOING SOUTH -">GOING SOUTH - (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Going South: Cycling through the Americas an adventurous environmental cycling documentary. As the climate changes, an environmental crisis is proclaimed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 13:30:00" d="2020-06-05 14:00:00"><n u="GOING SOUTH -">GOING SOUTH - (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Going South: Cycling through the Americas an adventurous environmental cycling documentary. As the climate changes, an environmental crisis is proclaimed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 14:00:00" d="2020-06-05 15:00:00"><n>THE FORCE OF THE AIR - MIST IN FRAY JORGE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Multidisciplinary documentary series that reveals some of the particular weather conditions of the Chilean territory and its evolution</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 15:00:00" d="2020-06-05 15:30:00"><n u="TRAJECTORY -">TRAJECTORY - (10)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Today, although a cloud of satellites surrounds the planet, many records set during the early decades of space exploration remain unsurpassed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 15:30:00" d="2020-06-05 16:00:00"><n u="TRAJECTORY -">TRAJECTORY - (11)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Today, although a cloud of satellites surrounds the planet, many records set during the early decades of space exploration remain unsurpassed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 16:00:00" d="2020-06-05 16:30:00"><n>THE NEXT ASIAN MIRACLE - THE NEXT LAP FOR LABOUR</n><t>D</t>    <k>While the region’s economy surges forward, the labour market has not kept up with the pace of transformation. Despite strong economic growth, unemployment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 16:30:00" d="2020-06-05 17:00:00"><n>THE NEXT ASIAN MIRACLE - TECHNOLOGY, THE NEXT FRONTIER</n><t>D</t>    <k>More than ever before, science and technology have affected the shape and course of society so pervasively that the world is now on the threshold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 17:00:00" d="2020-06-05 18:00:00"><n>NOMADS - WHITEWATER KAYAKING REUNION ISLAND, INDIAN OCEAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>A group of international explorers for an adventure of Kayaking. A combination of canyoneering and kayaking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 18:00:00" d="2020-06-05 19:00:00"><n>THE BISHNOIS: INDIA'S ECO-WARRIORS</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Bishnois remain the first eco-friendly religious community in Historical records. Originating from the Thar Desert in Rajasthan, their guru Jimbaji</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 19:00:00" d="2020-06-05 20:00:00"><n>SOUTHERN FLOWER IN THE PACIFIC - ISLAND HOPPING</n><t>D</t>    <k>The adventure continues in the waters of the Pacific! After a quick break in Tahiti, Southern Flower repartt management Raiatea, Moorea, Thaha</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 20:00:00" d="2020-06-05 20:30:00"><n u="WORLD MEDICINE -">WORLD MEDICINE - I (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Embark on a world tour of ancestral medicinal practices with Bernard Fontanille - an emergency doctor used to operations in difficult conditions - through</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 20:30:00" d="2020-06-05 21:00:00"><n u="WORLD MEDICINE -">WORLD MEDICINE - I (12)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Embark on a world tour of ancestral medicinal practices with Bernard Fontanille - an emergency doctor used to operations in difficult conditions - through</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 21:00:00" d="2020-06-05 22:00:00"><n>BIOTIFUL PLANET - MOZAMBIQUE</n><t>D</t>    <k>A nine-part series on the treasures of France’s overseas territories. The French overseas territories are a treasure trove of biodiversity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 22:00:00" d="2020-06-05 22:30:00"><n>INSPIRING LIVES GLOBAL - CAPE TOWN, SOUTH AFRICA</n><t>D</t>    <k>INSPIRING LIVES GLOBAL follows the journey of Tiamara Williams, social entrepreneur, TV host and life coach from New Zealand, around the developing world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 22:30:00" d="2020-06-05 23:00:00"><n>INSPIRING LIVES GLOBAL - JOHANNESBURG, SOUTH AFRICA</n><t>D</t>    <k>INSPIRING LIVES GLOBAL follows the journey of Tiamara Williams, social entrepreneur, TV host and life coach from New Zealand, around the developing world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-05 23:00:00" d="2020-06-06 00:00:00"><n>BIATHLON, A TEAM AT THE TOP</n><t>D</t>    <k>Discover the universe of high competition by following the French biathlon team during the 2010-2011 world cup. Exclusive footage of behind-the-scenes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 00:00:00" d="2020-06-06 00:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - I (11)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Aviation and disaster relief, Women’s aviation museum, Balloon flying, Tiger Moth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 00:30:00" d="2020-06-06 01:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - I (12)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Flight services specialists, Wilderness survival, In-flight oxygen, Three generations of flyers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 01:00:00" d="2020-06-06 02:00:00"><n>SACRED CULTURE - MCLEOD GANJ</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra embarks on a trip to India and Nepal, to show the life of its inhabitants, their customs, the architecture of its temples and holy cities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 02:00:00" d="2020-06-06 03:00:00"><n>RIDERS IN THE LAND OF THE SETTING SUN</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Moussem of Tan- Tan, also known as the largest gathering of the Blue Men, is an annual research involving more than thirty Sahrawi tribes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 03:00:00" d="2020-06-06 04:00:00"><n u="TIMELESS TREASURES -">TIMELESS TREASURES - (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>A series celebrating the extraordinary preservation of human heritage. Discover the world’s most beautiful sites in an exceptional series of short programs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 04:00:00" d="2020-06-06 04:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - III (11)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Intro to Soaring: This is the only time missing the roar of the engine is intended to be a part of the experience! Learning to Fly: We hang out with Motley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-06 04:30:00" d="2020-06-06 05:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - III (12)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Balloons: Sara takes us to Battle Creek, Michigan for one of the largest balloon festivals in the world. Air Race Classic: We fly with hundreds of women</k>  </p>
</a>
