<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="32" t="2021-07-09 06:47:24"><p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 05:00:00" d="2021-07-14 06:00:00"><n>I HAVE SEEN THE EARTH CHANGE</n><t>D</t>    <k>A courageous and spirited Inuit woman, Ulaayu Pilurtuut lives in the heart of the Canadian Great North, where she teaches Inuktut, language of her people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 06:00:00" d="2021-07-14 07:00:00"><n>POSTCARD PERFECT</n><t>D</t>    <k>Reunion Island is a little corner of paradise to the east of Madagascar. But behind the bright white beaches, glittering sea and sunny skies hides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 07:00:00" d="2021-07-14 08:00:00"><n>SHARING THE EARTH - BRAZIL</n><t>D</t>    <k>Veterinarian, biologist and adventurer Mannaďg de Kersauson travels the world in search of men and women who work to repair the damages inflicted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 08:00:00" d="2021-07-14 09:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>In this chapter, Claudio and his team venture into Kenya to reach the villa inhabited by the Maasai tribe. Before heading to Kenya from Tanzania, Claudio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 09:00:00" d="2021-07-14 10:00:00"><n>ANCIENT CULTURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 10:00:00" d="2021-07-14 11:00:00"><n u="BEAUTIFUL MINDS">BEAUTIFUL MINDS (CANAL 13)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Albert Einstein said that the mind is like a parachute: it only works if we have it opened. Beautiful Minds is a documentary series that summarizes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 11:00:00" d="2021-07-14 12:00:00"><n>NOMAD'S LAND</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Great North. ‘up north’ as the Canadians say, is one of the most isolated regions in the world. Although the Great North occupies 40% of Canada’s total</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 12:00:00" d="2021-07-14 12:30:00"><n>RACING GREEN</n><t>D</t>    <k>RACING GREEN is a 3 hour long BBC World News TV series about an electric car world record established by 8 engineering graduates from London. They succeed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 12:30:00" d="2021-07-14 13:00:00"><n>RACING GREEN</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Racing Green expedition starts with a heavy rainstorm in Alaska - a serious challenge in an open top electric car packed with a 600 volt battery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 13:00:00" d="2021-07-14 13:30:00"><n>AVIATORS, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Aviators is a fast-paced, exciting TV series hosted and written by world-renowned pilots. This unique series joins our aviation expert correspondents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 13:30:00" d="2021-07-14 14:00:00"><n>AVIATORS, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Aviators is a fast-paced, exciting TV series hosted and written by world-renowned pilots. This unique series joins our aviation expert correspondents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 14:00:00" d="2021-07-14 15:00:00"><n>MEGALOPOLIS</n><t>D</t>    <k>As millions more people join the exodus from the countryside seeking a living in the big city, Alexandra Leroux, host of the series, investigates how these</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 15:00:00" d="2021-07-14 16:00:00"><n>MUNDO AD PORTAS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 16:00:00" d="2021-07-14 17:00:00"><n>NOMADS</n><t>D</t>    <k>A season accessing the front and back of Wasatch mountains from one of America’s best winter sport gems: Salt Lake City, Utah</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 17:00:00" d="2021-07-14 17:30:00"><n u="MUSIC VOYAGER EP.">MUSIC VOYAGER EP. 06</n><t>D</t>    <k>Music Voyager is a music and travel broadcast series (television/cable, broadband, in-flight and mobile) that invites viewers to discover the exciting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 17:30:00" d="2021-07-14 18:00:00"><n u="MUSIC VOYAGER EP.">MUSIC VOYAGER EP. 07</n><t>D</t>    <k>Music Voyager is a music and travel broadcast series (television/cable, broadband, in-flight and mobile) that invites viewers to discover the exciting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 18:00:00" d="2021-07-14 19:00:00"><n>WWII DOCUMENTARY FILMS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Award-winning documentary films produced to enlighten future generations about the personal stories of the WWII generations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 19:00:00" d="2021-07-14 19:30:00"><n>EUROPEAN ISLANDS EP. 03: TENERIFE</n><t>D</t>    <k>The European islands are renowned primarily for their hotel resorts. However, we will show you a completely different face of theirs: forests, beaches</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 19:30:00" d="2021-07-14 20:00:00"><n>EUROPEAN ISLANDS EP. 04: LANZAROTE</n><t>D</t>    <k>The European islands are renowned primarily for their hotel resorts. However, we will show you a completely different face of theirs: forests, beaches</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 20:00:00" d="2021-07-14 21:00:00"><n>BEAUTIFUL CHILE</n><t>D</t>    <k>The most arid desert in the world, millenary Patagonial ice fields, abundant forests lost in the heart of a mountain, are some of the geographical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 21:00:00" d="2021-07-14 22:00:00"><n>BIOTIFUL PLANET</n><t>D</t>    <k>A nine-part series on the treasures of France’s overseas territories. The French overseas territories are a treasure trove of biodiversity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 22:00:00" d="2021-07-14 22:30:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>On the Island of Boa Vista, in Cape Verde, along the coast and also inland to get acquainted with its many different faces. Together with Eliseu</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 22:30:00" d="2021-07-14 23:00:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>The smallest country in Africa, The Gambia, rises from and follows the river of the same name, but most of all it is a country surrounded by Senegal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-14 23:00:00" d="2021-07-15 00:00:00"><n u="ASSASINATION">ASSASINATION II</n><t>D</t>    <k>Assassination II, portrays the murder of Venustiano Carranza, Francisco Villa and Alvaro Obregon, occurred during the last years of the Mexican Revolution</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 00:00:00" d="2021-07-15 00:30:00"><n>ASIAN CENTURY, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>They are called the Strawberry Generation. Young Taiwanese, born in the 1980's who grew up as spoilt brats, raised by parents who made their fortunes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 00:30:00" d="2021-07-15 01:00:00"><n>ASIAN CENTURY, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>For the sake of development, Cambodians are finding themselves getting evicted out of their own homes, leaving the land as cash cows for foreign and local</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 01:00:00" d="2021-07-15 02:00:00"><n>NOMAD'S LAND</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Great North. ‘up north’ as the Canadians say, is one of the most isolated regions in the world. Although the Great North occupies 40% of Canada’s total</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 02:00:00" d="2021-07-15 02:30:00"><n>MINDWORKS</n><t>L</t>    <k>Understanding how we think and see by playing games with our brains. This factual entertainment series explores the way we see and interpret the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 02:30:00" d="2021-07-15 03:00:00"><n>MINDWORKS</n><t>L</t>    <k>Understanding how we think and see by playing games with our brains. This factual entertainment series explores the way we see and interpret the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 03:00:00" d="2021-07-15 03:30:00"><n>AVIATORS, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>PYROTECHNICS: We showcase Rich Gibson, the man behind some of the most explosive airshow spectacles. HANGAR FLYING 2: Kurtis, Sara, and Anthony debate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 03:30:00" d="2021-07-15 04:00:00"><n>AVIATORS, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>100 YEARS OF COMMERCIAL FLIGHT: The highs and the lows of an industry that has become an essential part of our lives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-15 04:00:00" d="2021-07-15 05:00:00"><n>ISLANDERS EP. 16: THE MALDIVES</n><t>D</t>    <k>Discovering some the world’s hidden treasures by revealing the hidden face of life and the inhabitants of the islands. Island folk are generally proud</k>  </p>
</a>
