<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2020-04-14 04:28:59"><p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 05:00:00" d="2020-04-21 05:30:00"><n>PASSPORT TO EXPLORE - PORTLAND</n><t>D</t>    <k>Passport to Explore is an internationallysyndicated half hour educational travel adventure series designed for 13-16 year olds. Syndicated on stations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 05:30:00" d="2020-04-21 06:00:00"><n>PASSPORT TO EXPLORE - PHILADELPHIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Passport to Explore is an internationallysyndicated half hour educational travel adventure series designed for 13-16 year olds. Syndicated on stations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 06:00:00" d="2020-04-21 07:00:00"><n>DON'T FORGET YOUR PASSPORT - SOUTH AFRICA</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Wilderness Route in South Africa is a visually stimulating environment where host Gordon Sivell samples the wine, has his first para-gliding flight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 07:00:00" d="2020-04-21 07:30:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A JOURNEY TO INFINITY - PART">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A JOURNEY TO INFINITY - PART 3 (PATAGONIA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>The third part of our expedition on board of our ship, that has taken us from Punta Arenas in Chile, takes us now to Ushuaia in Argentina, to cross</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 07:30:00" d="2020-04-21 08:00:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - CHAMPION OF BIODIVERSITY</n><t>D</t>    <k>On Providenciales Island, the entrance to the Turks &amp; Caicos archipelago, we begin our journey by discovering a farm where they grow the biggest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 08:00:00" d="2020-04-21 08:30:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - THE EGYPTIAN DESERT ROSE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Between the sea and the desert. That’s the fine line we travel on this trip to Egypt. To the south of Hurghada, on the Red Sea, there is a desert peninsula</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 08:30:00" d="2020-04-21 09:00:00"><n>THE GREAT JOURNEY - THE ANDES CROSSING</n><t>D</t>    <k>They manage to fly over the first hills of the Chilean mountain range, but fail and fall in a small town and must be rescued. Next to the pilot Cristian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 09:00:00" d="2020-04-21 10:00:00"><n>NEXOS - A SHARED FUTURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>The conclusion of this work in each of its facets will help to perceive the shape the future will take. What we have learned over the course of our journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 10:00:00" d="2020-04-21 10:30:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - ERIE CANAL TO NEW YORK</n><t>D</t>    <k>Beginning a voyage south from Canada, Paul and Sheryl cross Lake Ontario and enter the Oswego and Erie Canals where they transit historic locks, then visit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 10:30:00" d="2020-04-21 11:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - NORFOLK TO THE OUTER BANKS</n>    <k>The Atlantic Intracoastal Waterway is a 1,095 mile inland waterway running from Norfolk VA to Miami FL down the eastern coast of the USA</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 11:00:00" d="2020-04-21 12:00:00"><n>NOMAD'S LAND - AMAZONIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Brazilian state of Amazonas, a vast territory bordering Brazil, concentrate the beauty of the Amazon and an Eldorado for many travelers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 12:00:00" d="2020-04-21 12:30:00"><n>FISH LIFE - NIGHT LIFE</n><t>D</t>    <k>What happens to life underwater when darkness falls? Where do the diurnal fish go? Do nocturnal species exists? Is there a nightlife? In the underwater</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 12:30:00" d="2020-04-21 13:00:00"><n>FISH LIFE - INTO THE HEART OF THE REEF</n><t>D</t>    <k>Reefs always abound with life and a dazzling array of colors. The ballet of fish is infinite. Small and large fish twist and eddy in dreamlike decors</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 13:00:00" d="2020-04-21 13:30:00"><n>LOW COST - HELSINKI</n><t>D</t>    <k>Each city is in its native language (ie. Parisis in French, Rome is in Italian, Berlin is in German, etc. with English Scripts) showing the viewer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 13:30:00" d="2020-04-21 14:00:00"><n>LOW COST - LISBON</n><t>D</t>    <k>Each city is in its native language (ie. Parisis in French, Rome is in Italian, Berlin is in German, etc. with English Scripts) showing the viewer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 14:00:00" d="2020-04-21 15:00:00"><n>TRACK RIDER - INDE SUD</n><t>D</t>    <k>Let yourself be taken away to the heart of Russia, Australia, Thailand, Vietnam, Mexico or the United States, and discover along the tracks, colourful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 15:00:00" d="2020-04-21 15:30:00"><n>THE PATH IS THE GOAL - ANTARTICA 2008</n><t>D</t>    <k>Even if you have a complete climbing group, there are mountains that are not for beginners and sometimes not even for experts. The &quot;Path is the Goal&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 15:30:00" d="2020-04-21 16:00:00"><n>THE PATH IS THE GOAL - GROENLANDIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Even if you have a complete climbing group, there are mountains that are not for beginners and sometimes not even for experts. The &quot;Path is the Goal&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 16:00:00" d="2020-04-21 17:00:00" c="1"><n>RUDOLF NUREYEV</n><t>F</t>    <k>The film focuses on the frequent trips that the legendary Russian ballet dancer Rudolf Nureyev made to Turkey between 1980 and 1990, and explores</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 17:00:00" d="2020-04-21 18:00:00"><n>NOMADS - WINDSURFING MAUI-HAWAII</n>    <k>World Wave Sailing Champion's explore the beauty and mystique of Maui, as they prepare for the ‘Aloha Classic,’ the final stop on the World Wavesailing Tour</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 18:00:00" d="2020-04-21 18:30:00"><n u="TRAJECTORY -">TRAJECTORY - (7)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Today, although a cloud of satellites surrounds the planet, many records set during the early decades of space exploration remain unsurpassed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 18:30:00" d="2020-04-21 19:00:00"><n u="TRAJECTORY -">TRAJECTORY - (8)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Today, although a cloud of satellites surrounds the planet, many records set during the early decades of space exploration remain unsurpassed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 19:00:00" d="2020-04-21 20:00:00"><n>TRAVEL NOTEBOOKS - ARMENIE</n><t>D</t>    <k>This series invites the viewer to visit unusual countries, cities and places through the eye of a traveler-illustrator</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 20:00:00" d="2020-04-21 21:00:00"><n>THE WORLD'S GREATEST CARNIVALS - QUEBEC WINTER CARNIVAL</n><t>D</t>    <k>This 3D documentary special takes us to one of the most colourful and elaborate celebrations on earth where both human creativity and glorious cultures come together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 21:00:00" d="2020-04-21 22:00:00"><n u="INLAND ICE -">INLAND ICE - (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>We learn about the realities of camping out, taking pictures and how much food/water is enough. There is a new danger in the snow and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 22:00:00" d="2020-04-21 22:30:00"><n u="KUNG FU KITCHEN - HANDMADE NOODLES">KUNG FU KITCHEN - HANDMADE NOODLES (TAIYUAN, CHINA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>While many debate that the birthplace of noodles is in China, few can argue that when it comes to handmade noodles, the Chinese are the clear masters at it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 22:30:00" d="2020-04-21 23:00:00"><n u="KUNG FU KITCHEN - FLYING ROTI CANAI">KUNG FU KITCHEN - FLYING ROTI CANAI (MALACCA, MALAYSIA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>The roti canai is a round flat pancake popular in Malaysia and Singapore. Of south Indian origin, the roti is fluffy inside, crisp outside. The original</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 23:00:00" d="2020-04-21 23:30:00"><n>REBUILDING OUR ENVIRONMENT - BIOMASS</n><t>D</t>    <k>The use of organic materials and biomass. What it is, how it is produced and ways of using it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-21 23:30:00" d="2020-04-22 00:00:00"><n>REBUILDING OUR ENVIRONMENT - SEPARATION OF WASTE</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the recycling of urban waste, the separation of waste destined to be recycled is necessary. A visit to several cooperatives that collect and separate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 00:00:00" d="2020-04-22 01:00:00"><n>EPIGENETICS, THE HIDDEN LIFE OF OUR GENES</n><t>D</t>    <k>The consensus is building that the largest non-genetic contribution to most common diseases is going to be epigenetic, because that is the way every single</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 01:00:00" d="2020-04-22 02:00:00"><n>NOMADS - BIG MOUNTAIN HELI-SKIING IN HAINES, ALASKA</n><t>D</t>    <k>X games medalists take to the slopes of Haines, Alaska to experience the ultimate in heli-skiing; a challenge to even the best of the best</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 02:00:00" d="2020-04-22 03:00:00"><n>CHINA UNCOVERED - THE NEED FOR SPEED</n><t>D</t>    <k>China runs on two gears as it moves millions of people around every day. A young driver of one of the world’s fastest trains and two seasoned pilots</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 03:00:00" d="2020-04-22 04:00:00"><n>MAKE ME A LOG BOAT!</n><t>D</t>    <k>Around the Parandu lake, two groups of volunteers go about to make a logboat using antique tools and getting back in a 5,000 years journey while meeting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 04:00:00" d="2020-04-22 05:00:00"><n>THE NAZI NETWORK IN MEXICO</n><t>D</t>    <k>In 1985, had been released the documents about the nazis activities during the world War II in Mexico. But, what could be Hitler's interest in a country away from war? The answer that had remained hidden and generated legends, tries to be unveiled through this documentary that narrates and recreates Nazi activities in Mexico during World War II</k>  </p>
</a>
