<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="28" t="2020-04-10 04:31:28"><p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-17 05:00:00" d="2020-04-17 06:00:00"><n>I HAVE SEEN THE EARTH CHANGE - SPAIN: THE DESERT TO COME</n><t>D</t>    <k>At the heart of the Valencia Huerta, Antonio Gadčs watches worriedly the orange trees of his parcel wither away. This semi-arid region, true garden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-17 06:00:00" d="2020-04-17 07:00:00"><n>DIARIES OF BRAZIL</n><t>D</t>    <k>On 22 April 1500, a Portuguese ship captained by Cabral set foot in Brazil in a land populated by Indians This was the discovery of a New World that proved</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-17 07:00:00" d="2020-04-17 08:00:00"><n>IN CONCERT - JEFF KAVANDA</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jeff Kavanda’s group is multicultural and composed of artists from Congo, North Africa, Ghana and Belgium. The dominant style is Afro-Cuban</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-17 08:00:00" d="2020-04-17 09:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE - TRIBU MASAI</n><t>D</t>    <k>This chapter addresses Claudio Iturra Mara National Reserve Masai, located in southwestern Kenya, and one of the largest parks in the world, where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-17 09:00:00" d="2020-04-17 10:00:00"><n>SACRED CULTURE - CREAMTORIOS VARANASI</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra embarks on a trip to India and Nepal, to show the life of its inhabitants, their customs, the architecture of its temples and holy cities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-17 10:00:00" d="2020-04-17 11:00:00"><n>BEAUTIFUL MINDS - NIBALDO INESTROSA PHD</n><t>D</t>    <k>Albert Einstein said that the mind is like a parachute: it only works if we have it opened. Beautiful Minds is a documentary series that summarizes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-17 11:00:00" d="2020-04-17 11:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - VI (9)</n><t>D</t>    <k>AIR RALLY: Teams from all over North America compete in a race again time and each other to take the title of Air Rally Champion. SEARCH AND RESCUE</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-17 11:30:00" d="2020-04-17 12:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - VI (10)</n><t>D</t>    <k>FIGHTER INTERCEPT: What happens when a hapless Cessna flies someplace it shouldn’t? It gets up close and personal with Wisconsin Air National Guard fighter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-17 12:00:00" d="2020-04-17 13:00:00" c="1"><n>RUDOLF NUREYEV</n><t>F</t>    <k>The film focuses on the frequent trips that the legendary Russian ballet dancer Rudolf Nureyev made to Turkey between 1980 and 1990, and explores</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-17 13:00:00" d="2020-04-17 14:00:00"><n>DON'T FORGET YOUR PASSPORT - QUEENSLAND, AUSTRALIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Gordon Sivell travels the length of Queensland, Australia through dense tropical rainforest where he learns the secrets of Aboriginal artwork and early</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-17 14:00:00" d="2020-04-17 15:00:00"><n>NOMAD'S LAND MONGOLIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mongolia. Vast territory covered steppes and deserts. This is where Christophe Cousin goes - in search of nomads. There, he borrows not men with soles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-17 15:00:00" d="2020-04-17 16:00:00"><n u="MUNDO AD PORTAS -">MUNDO AD PORTAS - I (5)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-17 16:00:00" d="2020-04-17 17:00:00"><n>NOMADS - HELI-SKIING ADVENTURE IN BRITISH COLUMBIA-CANADA</n><t>D</t>    <k>A magnificent journey of cultural enrichment and hair raising heli-skiing in Beautiful British Columbia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-17 17:00:00" d="2020-04-17 18:00:00"><n u="WIND QUEST -">WIND QUEST - (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Arthur de Kersauson, a young city-dweller hooked on extreme sports, and Antoine Auriol, World Champion in the Kiteboard Pro World Tour, set out in search</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-17 18:00:00" d="2020-04-17 18:30:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - FRENCH RIVERS TO MED.</n><t>D</t>    <k>Series 9 of Distant Shores follows Paul and Sheryl Shard on a diverse voyage from England through the inland waterways of France to the Mediterranean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-17 18:30:00" d="2020-04-17 19:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - MOROCCO</n><t>D</t>    <k>Series 9 of Distant Shores follows Paul and Sheryl Shard on a diverse voyage from England through the inland waterways of France to the Mediterranean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-17 19:00:00" d="2020-04-17 20:00:00"><n>MISTS OF MANENGOUBA</n><t>D</t>    <k>The African continent still contains numerous unexplored regions. Recently, one of these lost worlds was discovered in Cameroon, by a British researcher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-17 20:00:00" d="2020-04-17 21:30:00"><n>THE ALAMO</n><t>D</t>    <k>1983: After more than 7 years of terror, the Argentineans recover the democracy. The reconstruction of a climate of timeand an event that amrked a point</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-17 21:30:00" d="2020-04-17 22:00:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - AYYATUYA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-17 22:00:00" d="2020-04-17 22:30:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - PARIS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-17 22:30:00" d="2020-04-17 23:00:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - PETER&amp;PAU LFORTRESS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-17 23:00:00" d="2020-04-18 00:00:00"><n>BOKASSA 1ST, THE LAST AFRICAN EMPEROR</n><t>D</t>    <k>Perish the thought of us falling into an angelical rehabiliatation of such a contestable and impugned dictator. It seemed impossible for</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 00:00:00" d="2020-04-18 01:00:00"><n>THE CHARRO</n><t>D</t>    <k>The &quot;charro&quot;, term that comes from military charreteras (Epaulettes) that horse riders use, is one of Mexico's national symbols. Their figure appeared</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 01:00:00" d="2020-04-18 02:00:00"><n>IN CONCERT - SERGIU POPA ENSEMBLE</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sergiu Popa is an acoustic quintet from Montreal, directed by accordionist Tzigane (Roma) Sergiu Popa. The group offers its own musical arrangements</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 02:00:00" d="2020-04-18 03:00:00"><n>NOMADS - WHITEWATER KAYAKING WITH THE JACKSON CLAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Jackson Family lead a very unique lifestyle, and are known for being at the very top of their sport, both in talent and accomplishments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 03:00:00" d="2020-04-18 03:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - V (10)</n><t>D</t>    <k>AIRSHOW RADIO CHATTER: Air shows are recognized as having great visual appeal. But when we take viewers inside the cockpit during an airshow performance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 03:30:00" d="2020-04-18 04:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - V (11)</n><t>D</t>    <k>CHALLENGER 605: We fly well above first class in the kind of super elite style experienced by only A-list celebrities, fortune 500 executives, and heads of state</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 04:00:00" d="2020-04-18 05:00:00"><n>EVITA</n><t>D</t>    <k>She was considered the most powerful woman of her time. Together with Juan Domingo Perón she formed a legendary partnership that was a mixture</k>  </p>
</a>
