<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="33" t="2019-08-15 22:36:43"><p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 05:00:00" d="2019-08-22 06:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE - MASAI MARA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra (conductor) part to Kenya to go into the Massai Mara National Park, one of the most beautiful nature reserves of Planet Earth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 06:00:00" d="2019-08-22 07:00:00"><n>GENIE IN THE LIGHT BULB, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Today, one billion six hundred thousand human beings have no access to electricity. This film tells the story of the arrival of electricity in Hathine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 07:00:00" d="2019-08-22 07:30:00"><n>FISH LIFE - THE CORAL THEATRE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Coral reefs are reminiscent of the tower of Babel. Dating back over 200 million years ago, their structure seems part of a legend. All at once place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 07:30:00" d="2019-08-22 08:00:00"><n>FISH LIFE - HAZARDS OF THE SEA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Today still, the sea induces fear. In some people’s imagination, it is inhabited by sea monsters straight out of the depths. However, risk isn’t always</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 08:00:00" d="2019-08-22 08:30:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - CRUISING IN STYLE</n><t>D</t>    <k>At sea and in many of the worldwide ports Distant Shores sails to, Paul and Sheryl are in the company of luxurious cruise ships. In this episode</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 08:30:00" d="2019-08-22 09:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - CHESAPEAKE WEST</n><t>D</t>    <k>As hurricane season approaches, Paul and Sheryl leave the tropics and sail north to the Chesapeake Bay, the largest estuary in the United States, where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 09:00:00" d="2019-08-22 09:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - II (7)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Aircraft ownership: Exploring the varied costs and entry points of flying for everyone from the weekend warrior to the rich and famous. $100 Hamburger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 09:30:00" d="2019-08-22 10:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - II (8)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Airpark living: When your driveway is a runway, life is good! Water escape: Sara takes the plunge and learns how to survive a ditching. Jet truck race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 10:00:00" d="2019-08-22 10:30:00"><n u="TAXI TO ASIA - INDIGENOUS CULTURE VS GOING COSMOPOLITAN">TAXI TO ASIA - INDIGENOUS CULTURE VS GOING COSMOPOLITAN (SINGAPORE VS SHANGHAI)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Taxi drivers are probably the first people you meet upon setting foot in a new country but also the most colorful and clued-in characters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 10:30:00" d="2019-08-22 11:00:00"><n u="TAXI TO ASIA - HARD LIFE VS HIGH LIFE">TAXI TO ASIA - HARD LIFE VS HIGH LIFE (MANILA VS MACAU)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Manila: Most of Manila’s cabbies, like Alejandro, slave 18-24 hours, live far away to cut down on accommodation and have to take refuge at gasoline stations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 11:00:00" d="2019-08-22 12:00:00"><n u="ANCIENT CULTURE -">ANCIENT CULTURE - (15)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 12:00:00" d="2019-08-22 13:00:00"><n>BETWEEN EARTH &amp; SKY II - PERU: SONS OF THE SUN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Sebastian travels the world in his balloon to visit traditional tribes. In exchange, he will show them their world from the sky! Episodes: Jordan, Peru</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 13:00:00" d="2019-08-22 14:00:00"><n>THE NAZI NETWORK IN MEXICO</n><t>D</t>    <k>In 1985, had been released the documents about the nazis activities during the world War II in Mexico. But, what could be Hitler's interest in a country away from war? The answer that had remained hidden and generated legends, tries to be unveiled through this documentary that narrates and recreates Nazi activities in Mexico during World War II</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 14:00:00" d="2019-08-22 15:00:00"><n u="CHINA, A TIMELESS COUNTRY - PART">CHINA, A TIMELESS COUNTRY - PART 1</n><t>D</t>    <k>This series goes through the most unknown places in the Republic of China, discovering at each step the marks that its history has left in the present</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 15:00:00" d="2019-08-22 16:00:00"><n u="MUNDO AD PORTAS -">MUNDO AD PORTAS - I (11)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 16:00:00" d="2019-08-22 16:30:00"><n>THE GREAT JOURNEY - THE ADVENTURE BEGINS</n><t>D</t>    <k>The crossing must be made from west to east, that is from Chile to Argentina. Installed in the Chilean capital a group of specialists finalize details for the trip</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 16:30:00" d="2019-08-22 17:00:00"><n>THE GREAT JOURNEY - EXPEDITION IN DANGER</n><t>D</t>    <k>The technician team can't make the right gas to raise the hot air balloon. In a chemical laboratory we will reproduce the gas production process</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 17:00:00" d="2019-08-22 18:00:00"><n>ANTARCTICA FLOWERS - HEADING SOUTH</n><t>D</t>    <k>The crew found his boat Flower Southern Tahiti, after six months of winter, unfortunately a bad surprise awaits. La Fleur was looted: cameras, navigation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 18:00:00" d="2019-08-22 19:00:00"><n>NOMADS - FREESTYLE MOTOCROSS UTAH</n><t>D</t>    <k>Follow some of the biggest names in freestyle motocross as they prepare for the ‘Dew Action Sports Tour,’ being held in Salt Lake City</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 19:00:00" d="2019-08-22 20:00:00"><n u="LEAVING JUNGLE -">LEAVING JUNGLE - (5)</n><t>D</t>    <k>“Living Jungle” is an invitation to explore the most impressive biodiversity in the whole world: the Amazonian Forest. An experimented host starts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 20:00:00" d="2019-08-22 21:30:00"><n>TEROS</n><t>D</t>    <k>TEROS is a documentary film that tells the story of Los Teros, the team that defends Uruguay national team, which is the only amateur team competed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 21:30:00" d="2019-08-22 22:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF SOUTH AFRICA - THE WINELANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>A viticultural romp around Capetown’s historic wine lands - presenter Charlie Ottley checks out the ultimate designer winery, the last word in chic hotels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 22:00:00" d="2019-08-22 22:30:00"><n>INSPIRING LIVES GLOBAL - BAHIA DE CARAQUEZ, ECUADOR</n><t>D</t>    <k>INSPIRING LIVES GLOBAL follows the journey of Tiamara Williams, social entrepreneur, TV host and life coach from New Zealand, around the developing world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 22:30:00" d="2019-08-22 23:00:00"><n>INSPIRING LIVES GLOBAL - RIO MUCHACHO, ECUADOR</n><t>D</t>    <k>INSPIRING LIVES GLOBAL follows the journey of Tiamara Williams, social entrepreneur, TV host and life coach from New Zealand, around the developing world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 23:00:00" d="2019-08-22 23:30:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - PHILIPPINES OFWs</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Philippines is one of the fastest growing economies among the ASEAN 5. And, in 2010, it showed such sterling results that the IMF even predicted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 23:30:00" d="2019-08-23 00:00:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - SHANGHAI'S TWO-CHILDREN POLICY</n><t>D</t>    <k>China, with a population of 1. 3 billion, would hardly be in need of a baby boom. However, Shanghai paints a starkly different picture. Ageing faster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-23 00:00:00" d="2019-08-23 00:30:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - FLYING OVER THE WATERWAYS">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - FLYING OVER THE WATERWAYS (VENEZUELA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>On board of the strangest Cessna in the whole of Venezuela. Vittorio, a man who feels that his personal space is more in the air rather than on the round</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-23 00:30:00" d="2019-08-23 01:00:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - BETWEEN THE SACRED AND THE PROFANE">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - BETWEEN THE SACRED AND THE PROFANE (CUBA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Our journey to Cuba begins in its capital city Havana, a city of architecture and sea. The sea that Ernest Hemingway loved so much, and</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-23 01:00:00" d="2019-08-23 02:00:00"><n>SACRED CULTURE - DARJEELING</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra embarks on a trip to India and Nepal, to show the life of its inhabitants, their customs, the architecture of its temples and holy cities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-23 02:00:00" d="2019-08-23 03:00:00"><n>NOMAD'S LAND MONGOLIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mongolia. Vast territory covered steppes and deserts. This is where Christophe Cousin goes - in search of nomads. There, he borrows not men with soles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-23 03:00:00" d="2019-08-23 04:00:00"><n>VIPERA LIFE</n><t>D</t>    <k>The viper. The word itself is able to fill up most people with dread. It calls to mind some kind of huge, ancient, writhing monster, lying on the floor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-23 04:00:00" d="2019-08-23 04:30:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF COLOMBIA - HISTORIC COLOMBIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Charlie Ottley travels through time from Colombia's pre-Hispanic origins through its colonial era to the present day, encapsulated by the bustle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-23 04:30:00" d="2019-08-23 05:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF COLOMBIA - IN AND AROUND CARTAGENA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Charlie Ottley checks out the famous and breathtaking Cartagena, host to the Hay Book Festival and one of the most historic cities in South America</k>  </p>
</a>
