<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2019-08-10 01:36:31"><p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 05:00:00" d="2019-08-16 06:00:00"><n>I HAVE SEEN THE EARTH CHANGE - SPAIN: THE DESERT TO COME</n><t>D</t>    <k>At the heart of the Valencia Huerta, Antonio Gadčs watches worriedly the orange trees of his parcel wither away. This semi-arid region, true garden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 06:00:00" d="2019-08-16 06:30:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - FRENCH RIVERS TO MED.</n><t>D</t>    <k>Series 9 of Distant Shores follows Paul and Sheryl Shard on a diverse voyage from England through the inland waterways of France to the Mediterranean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 06:30:00" d="2019-08-16 07:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - MOROCCO</n><t>D</t>    <k>Series 9 of Distant Shores follows Paul and Sheryl Shard on a diverse voyage from England through the inland waterways of France to the Mediterranean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 07:00:00" d="2019-08-16 08:00:00"><n>IN CONCERT - JEFF KAVANDA</n><t>M</t>    <k>Jeff Kavanda’s group is multicultural and composed of artists from Congo, North Africa, Ghana and Belgium. The dominant style is Afro-Cuban</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 08:00:00" d="2019-08-16 09:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE - TRIBU MASAI</n><t>D</t>    <k>This chapter addresses Claudio Iturra Mara National Reserve Masai, located in southwestern Kenya, and one of the largest parks in the world, where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 09:00:00" d="2019-08-16 10:00:00"><n>SACRED CULTURE - CREAMTORIOS VARANASI</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra embarks on a trip to India and Nepal, to show the life of its inhabitants, their customs, the architecture of its temples and holy cities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 10:00:00" d="2019-08-16 11:00:00"><n>BEAUTIFUL MINDS - NIBALDO INESTROSA PHD</n><t>D</t>    <k>Albert Einstein said that the mind is like a parachute: it only works if we have it opened. Beautiful Minds is a documentary series that summarizes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 11:00:00" d="2019-08-16 11:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - II (9)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Warbirds: Kurtis takes a walk back in time as he gets up close to a collection of historic aircraft that flew world-altering missions. iPad in the cockpit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 11:30:00" d="2019-08-16 12:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - II (10)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Wilderness survival: A well-known outdoorsman and pilot shows us how to spend the night in the remote wilderness while waiting for the weather to pass</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 12:00:00" d="2019-08-16 13:00:00" c="1"><n>RUDOLF NUREYEV</n><t>F</t>    <k>The film focuses on the frequent trips that the legendary Russian ballet dancer Rudolf Nureyev made to Turkey between 1980 and 1990, and explores</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 13:00:00" d="2019-08-16 14:00:00"><n>DON'T FORGET YOUR PASSPORT - QUEENSLAND, AUSTRALIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Gordon Sivell travels the length of Queensland, Australia through dense tropical rainforest where he learns the secrets of Aboriginal artwork and early</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 14:00:00" d="2019-08-16 15:00:00"><n>NOMAD'S LAND MONGOLIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mongolia. Vast territory covered steppes and deserts. This is where Christophe Cousin goes - in search of nomads. There, he borrows not men with soles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 15:00:00" d="2019-08-16 16:00:00"><n u="MUNDO AD PORTAS -">MUNDO AD PORTAS - I (5)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 16:00:00" d="2019-08-16 16:30:00"><n>THE NEXT ASIAN MIRACLE - THE ROLE OF THE STATE</n><t>D</t>    <k>THE NEXT ASIAN MIRACLE examines the prospects for the economies of South East Asia in light of the dramatic ascent of China and India. In this 8-part</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 16:30:00" d="2019-08-16 17:00:00"><n>THE NEXT ASIAN MIRACLE - MANUFACTURING - MOVING UP TO HIGHER VALUE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Manufacturing has been the traditional economic bedrock of South East Asian economies. In an increasingly globalized world, the region is opening</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 17:00:00" d="2019-08-16 18:00:00"><n>DIARIES OF BRAZIL</n><t>D</t>    <k>On 22 April 1500, a Portuguese ship captained by Cabral set foot in Brazil in a land populated by Indians This was the discovery of a New World that proved</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 18:00:00" d="2019-08-16 19:00:00"><n>NOMADS - HELI-SKIING ADVENTURE IN BRITISH COLUMBIA-CANADA</n><t>D</t>    <k>A magnificent journey of cultural enrichment and hair raising heli-skiing in Beautiful British Columbia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 19:00:00" d="2019-08-16 20:00:00"><n>THE HIMBAS ARE SHOOTING!</n><t>D</t>    <k>In Namibia, a group of Himbas men and women of all ages have decided to make a film showing who they are and what their life is like: incorporating</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 20:00:00" d="2019-08-16 21:00:00"><n>AFGHANISTAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Afghanistan is a region that plays a key role in ensuring stability and exerting influence in Asia. The interests of major world powers have converged in Afghanistan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 21:00:00" d="2019-08-16 22:00:00"><n>AFGHANISTAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Afghanistan is a region that plays a key role in ensuring stability and exerting influence in Asia. The interests of major world powers have converged in Afghanistan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 22:00:00" d="2019-08-16 22:30:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - VIETNAM'S YOUNG AND RESTLESS URBANITES</n><t>D</t>    <k>At the turn of the 21st century, all pundits were predicting the dawn f the so-called &quot;Asian Century&quot;. But even If no one today disputes the geopolitcal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 22:30:00" d="2019-08-16 23:00:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - SHANGHAI'S TWO-CHILDREN POLICY</n><t>D</t>    <k>China, with a population of 1. 3 billion, would hardly be in need of a baby boom. However, Shanghai paints a starkly different picture. Ageing faster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-16 23:00:00" d="2019-08-17 00:00:00"><n>IN THE LAND OF ENFLOWERED MEN</n><t>D</t>    <k>In Southern Saudi Arabia, at the heart of the mountain range of Tihama, which separates the Red Sea from the Rűb Al khalî desert, live the Enflowered-men</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 00:00:00" d="2019-08-17 01:00:00"><n>THE CHINESE WHITE GOLD</n><t>D</t>    <k>Chinese new middle class can now enjoy a sport they knew nothing about until recently: skiing. And they love it! This is not about trying some daredevil</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 01:00:00" d="2019-08-17 02:00:00"><n>NOMAD'S LAND - MEKONG</n><t>D</t>    <k>Continuing the theme of itinerancy, Christophe Cousin takes us on this new journey through two countries: Vietnam and Cambodia, on a river</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 02:00:00" d="2019-08-17 03:00:00"><n>SACRED CULTURE - CREAMTORIOS VARANASI</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra embarks on a trip to India and Nepal, to show the life of its inhabitants, their customs, the architecture of its temples and holy cities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 03:00:00" d="2019-08-17 03:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - I (11)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Aviation and disaster relief, Women’s aviation museum, Balloon flying, Tiger Moth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 03:30:00" d="2019-08-17 04:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - I (12)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Flight services specialists, Wilderness survival, In-flight oxygen, Three generations of flyers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-17 04:00:00" d="2019-08-17 05:00:00"><n>EVITA</n><t>D</t>    <k>She was considered the most powerful woman of her time. Together with Juan Domingo Perón she formed a legendary partnership that was a mixture</k>  </p>
</a>
