<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="33" t="2021-07-11 04:56:13"><p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 05:00:00" d="2021-07-18 06:00:00"><n>I HAVE SEEN THE EARTH CHANGE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Katsuo Sasaki grows rice in Miyagi Province where the crop has a strong reputation. And yet, he is becoming impoverished since never before seen insects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 06:00:00" d="2021-07-18 06:30:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF MEXICO</n><t>D</t>    <k>From hippie havens like Zipolite to the uber luxurious retreats of Careyes and El Tamarindo, we show you the Mexican Pacific like you’ve never seen it before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 06:30:00" d="2021-07-18 07:00:00"><n>ANIMAL ALLIES</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the UK, we meet our Animal Allies vet, Doctor Martin Andrews. Sparky the fox terrier has a hernia and Dr. Andrews prepares for what should be a routine operation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 07:00:00" d="2021-07-18 07:30:00"><n>ALL ABOUT ANIMALS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 07:30:00" d="2021-07-18 08:00:00"><n>ALL ABOUT ANIMALS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 08:00:00" d="2021-07-18 09:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>A curious reporter, outdoor lover, will not rest until he shows us every mystery of the wild, black heart of Central Africa, discovering the stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 09:00:00" d="2021-07-18 10:00:00"><n>ANCIENT CULTURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 10:00:00" d="2021-07-18 10:30:00"><n>EUROPE'S COASTLINES FROM ABOVE</n><t>D</t>    <k>This series takes viewers across the 10.000 km long European coastlines from Cape North all the way down to the Mediterranean coasts and islands, including</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 10:30:00" d="2021-07-18 11:00:00"><n>EUROPE'S COASTLINES FROM ABOVE</n><t>D</t>    <k>This series takes viewers across the 10.000 km long European coastlines from Cape North all the way down to the Mediterranean coasts and islands, including</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 11:00:00" d="2021-07-18 11:30:00"><n>AVIATORS, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Training in a T-6: Kurtis earns his wings in a T-6 warbird. Journey of a Bag: Where does your bag go once it leaves your hands and heads down a conveyor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 11:30:00" d="2021-07-18 12:00:00"><n>AVIATORS, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Skydiving: Sara and Raeleen jump out of a perfectly good airplane! Rob Reider, Announcer: The famous voice of some of the largest air shows in the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 12:00:00" d="2021-07-18 13:00:00"><n>NOMADS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Respect is something all skiing athletes must have. Respect for different cultures, lifestyles and their environment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 13:00:00" d="2021-07-18 14:00:00"><n>ON THE HIGHWAYS OF HISTORY</n><t>D</t>    <k>The construction of a new highway near the city of Orleans has permitted to excave archaeological treasures and reveal exceptional information about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 14:00:00" d="2021-07-18 15:00:00"><n>ISLANDERS, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Discovering some the world’s hidden treasures by revealing the hidden face of life and the inhabitants of the islands. Island folk are generally proud</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 15:00:00" d="2021-07-18 16:00:00"><n>MUNDO AD PORTAS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 16:00:00" d="2021-07-18 17:00:00"><n>CLOSE-UP ON WILDLIFE PHOTOGRAPHY</n><t>D</t>    <k>Europe still harbours a diversified wild animal life struggling to survive in the face of global urbanization. Approaching the more timid species</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 17:00:00" d="2021-07-18 17:30:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 17:30:00" d="2021-07-18 18:00:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 18:00:00" d="2021-07-18 19:00:00"><n>MEGALOPOLIS</n><t>D</t>    <k>As millions more people join the exodus from the countryside seeking a living in the big city, Alexandra Leroux, host of the series, investigates how these</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 19:00:00" d="2021-07-18 19:30:00"><n u="MUSIC VOYAGER EP.">MUSIC VOYAGER EP. 10</n><t>D</t>    <k>Music Voyager is a music and travel broadcast series (television/cable, broadband, in-flight and mobile) that invites viewers to discover the exciting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 19:30:00" d="2021-07-18 20:00:00"><n u="MUSIC VOYAGER EP.">MUSIC VOYAGER EP. 11</n><t>D</t>    <k>Music Voyager is a music and travel broadcast series (television/cable, broadband, in-flight and mobile) that invites viewers to discover the exciting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 20:00:00" d="2021-07-18 21:00:00"><n>BEAUTIFUL CHILE</n><t>D</t>    <k>The most arid desert in the world, millenary Patagonial ice fields, abundant forests lost in the heart of a mountain, are some of the geographical</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 21:00:00" d="2021-07-18 21:30:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>A visit to the Island of Tahiti together with a local called Alphonse who, as well as acquainting us with the famous canoe race Hawaiki Nui Va’a</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 21:30:00" d="2021-07-18 22:00:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>On board a catamaran, we discover several islands in the Society Island archipelago, in Polynesia. Of the Island of Raiatea, hilly and volcanic, we explore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 22:00:00" d="2021-07-18 22:30:00"><n>ASIAN CENTURY, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Research shows that two out of five women say they wish to marry a man who earns at least 6 million yen a year — but such men make up only</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 22:30:00" d="2021-07-18 23:00:00"><n>ASIAN CENTURY, THE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Indonesia’s economy was brought to its knees when the Asian Financial Crisis hit in 1997. A decade or so later, under the global downturn, the economy barely flinched</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-18 23:00:00" d="2021-07-19 00:00:00"><n>POPE FOR EVERYONE, A</n><t>D</t>    <k>In March 13, 2013, former Archibishop of Buenos Aires Jorge Mario Bergoglio, has turned to a beacon of hope for the world's catholic christian community</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-19 00:00:00" d="2021-07-19 00:30:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>It is in Santiago, Chile that we begin the extraordinary journey into the infinity that, place by place, will take us to South Patagonia, which</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-19 00:30:00" d="2021-07-19 01:00:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>The journey to the edge of the world in the icy waters of Tierra del Fuego continues. On board our expedition ship we arrive to Tucker island</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-19 01:00:00" d="2021-07-19 02:00:00"><n>SACRED CULTURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra embarks on a trip to India and Nepal, to show the life of its inhabitants, their customs, the architecture of its temples and holy cities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-19 02:00:00" d="2021-07-19 03:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>A curious reporter, outdoor lover, will not rest until he shows us every mystery of the wild, black heart of Central Africa, discovering the stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-19 03:00:00" d="2021-07-19 04:00:00"><n>IN CONCERT</n><t>M</t>    <k>Matsu Také was created in 2002 and is dedicated to promoting Japanese music. The group musicians play a wide variety of Japanese instruments: Koto (zither</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2021-07-19 04:00:00" d="2021-07-19 05:00:00"><n>WONDERS OF THE WORLD</n><t>D</t>    <k>In this episode Claudio visits the Galapagos Islands, a terrestrial paradise, insribed on the UNSECO World Heritage List due to local incredibile variety</k>  </p>
</a>
