<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="30" t="2019-08-15 22:36:36"><p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 05:00:00" d="2019-08-21 06:00:00"><n u="FRENCH SECRET SERVICES, A DECLASSIFIED HISTORY -">FRENCH SECRET SERVICES, A DECLASSIFIED HISTORY - (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Master Spies, secret Agents, assassins of the Republic, top Intel, infallibles: French intelligence agencies evoke superlatives, stereotypes, and paradoxes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 06:00:00" d="2019-08-21 07:30:00"><n>CARAPINTADAS</n><t>D</t>    <k>The carapintadas (Painted Face), were called like that because of their use of camouflage paint, they were rightmost military activists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 07:30:00" d="2019-08-21 08:00:00"><n u="KUNG FU KITCHEN - KUNG FU TEA">KUNG FU KITCHEN - KUNG FU TEA (HANGZHOU, CHINA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the kitchens of the Far East, the best cooks are Kung Fu Masters. Kung Fu Kitchen is an action-packed culinary adventure series delving into the highly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 08:00:00" d="2019-08-21 09:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE - HIMBA NOCHE</n><t>D</t>    <k>A curious reporter, outdoor lover, will not rest until he shows us every mystery of the wild, black heart of Central Africa, discovering the stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 09:00:00" d="2019-08-21 09:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - II (5)</n><t>D</t>    <k>AOPA Summit: The annual event of the Aircraft Owners and Pilots Association. LAPD: We take you inside the aerial unit of the Los Angeles Police Department</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 09:30:00" d="2019-08-21 10:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - II (6)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Airshows - Behind the scenes: An exclusive look at a day in the life of a major airshow from the perspective of a performer, an air traffic controller</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 10:00:00" d="2019-08-21 11:00:00"><n>BIOTIFUL PLANET - CONGO</n><t>D</t>    <k>A nine-part series on the treasures of France’s overseas territories. The French overseas territories are a treasure trove of biodiversity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 11:00:00" d="2019-08-21 12:00:00"><n u="ANCIENT CULTURE -">ANCIENT CULTURE - (14)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 12:00:00" d="2019-08-21 12:30:00"><n>PASSPORT TO EXPLORE - NASHVILLE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Passport to Explore is an internationallysyndicated half hour educational travel ad-venture series designed for 13-16 year olds. Syndicated on stations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 12:30:00" d="2019-08-21 13:00:00"><n>PASSPORT TO EXPLORE - NEW YORK CITY</n><t>D</t>    <k>Passport to Explore is an internationallysyndicated half hour educational travel ad-venture series designed for 13-16 year olds. Syndicated on stations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 13:00:00" d="2019-08-21 13:30:00"><n u="GOING SOUTH -">GOING SOUTH - (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Going South: Cycling through the Americas an adventurous environmental cycling documentary. As the climate changes, an environmental crisis is proclaimed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 13:30:00" d="2019-08-21 14:00:00"><n u="GOING SOUTH -">GOING SOUTH - (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Going South: Cycling through the Americas an adventurous environmental cycling documentary. As the climate changes, an environmental crisis is proclaimed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 14:00:00" d="2019-08-21 15:00:00"><n>SOUTHERN FLOWER IN THE PACIFIC - ISLAND HOPPING</n><t>D</t>    <k>The adventure continues in the waters of the Pacific! After a quick break in Tahiti, Southern Flower repartt management Raiatea, Moorea, Thaha</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 15:00:00" d="2019-08-21 16:00:00"><n u="MUNDO AD PORTAS -">MUNDO AD PORTAS - I (10)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 16:00:00" d="2019-08-21 17:00:00"><n>RIDERS IN THE LAND OF THE SETTING SUN</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Moussem of Tan- Tan, also known as the largest gathering of the Blue Men, is an annual research involving more than thirty Sahrawi tribes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 17:00:00" d="2019-08-21 18:00:00"><n>KIM JONG-IL: THE FORBIDDEN BIOGRAPHY</n><t>D</t>    <k>He was the most secretive political leader on earth. A grotesque dictator with a finger on the nuclear trigger. But since 2008, Kim Jong</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 18:00:00" d="2019-08-21 19:00:00"><n>NOMADS - GHOST TOWN-SKI &amp; SNOWMOBILE ADVENTURE IN BRALORNE, CANADA</n><t>D</t>    <k>A world-class group of skiers explore epic backcountry terrain around Bralorne, B.C., areas accessible only by snowmobiles, with Canadian sled super-heroes as their guides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 19:00:00" d="2019-08-21 20:00:00"><n>PROMISE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Despite 25 years of determined efforts made by the NHS to reduce the rate of breast cancer deaths and new breast cancer cases by detecting the disease</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 20:00:00" d="2019-08-21 21:30:00"><n>SILENCE IS GOLD</n><t>D</t>    <k>This feature documentary takes us through the twists and turns of judicial proceedings pitting Canadian mining companies Barrick Gold and Banro against</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 21:30:00" d="2019-08-21 22:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF SOUTH AFRICA - THE INTERIOR</n><t>D</t>    <k>From the savage Kruger National Park via Suweto to the oldest Baobab tree in the world, Charlie Ottley takes us on a breathless safari across South</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 22:00:00" d="2019-08-21 22:30:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - PHILIPPINES OFWs</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Philippines is one of the fastest growing economies among the ASEAN 5. And, in 2010, it showed such sterling results that the IMF even predicted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 22:30:00" d="2019-08-21 23:00:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - SHANGHAI'S TWO-CHILDREN POLICY</n><t>D</t>    <k>China, with a population of 1. 3 billion, would hardly be in need of a baby boom. However, Shanghai paints a starkly different picture. Ageing faster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-21 23:00:00" d="2019-08-22 00:00:00"><n u="BIG GAME">BIG GAME (ASIA, IN THE LAST INTERSECTION) - (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Big Game delves into the world of hidden wars involving diplomats, spies, military strategists, and hired assassins from Britain and Russia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 00:00:00" d="2019-08-22 00:30:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A DIVERS' PARADISE</n><t>D</t>    <k>In open sea, along the Venezuelan coastline, we fly over the biggest coral atoll of the Caribbean Sea to then dive into these beautiful waters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 00:30:00" d="2019-08-22 01:00:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - THE ROUTE TO LOS ROQUES</n><t>D</t>    <k>Our chosen route is the coral archipelago of Los Roques, our sail boat is pushed forward by the trade winds as we go to explore the small &quot;cayos&quot; in the region</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 01:00:00" d="2019-08-22 02:00:00"><n>NOMAD'S LAND - ETHIOPIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>With the label of &quot;cradle of humanity&quot;, Ethiopia is adorned with a legendary aura. It is here that the man was born, here he would have his first steps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 02:00:00" d="2019-08-22 03:00:00"><n>THE FORCE OF EARTH - LA FORMACION DE LA TIERRA</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Force of Earth is an educational documentary series of the journey of a Chilean scientist. In every episode we will learn about geography and geology</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 03:00:00" d="2019-08-22 04:00:00"><n>IN CONCERT - CORDES ORIENT</n><t>M</t>    <k>Cordes d'Orient is a group through which the richness of great Asian civilizations is revealed with finesse. Shen Qi (erhu) and Huu Bac Quach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 04:00:00" d="2019-08-22 04:30:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF SCOTLAND - THE BORDERS / LOWLANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Join Charlie for a gastronomic rummage through the Scottish Lowlands. Highlight include a visit to spectacular Floors Castle and the Roxburghe estate where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-22 04:30:00" d="2019-08-22 05:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF SCOTLAND - THE WEST COAST</n><t>D</t>    <k>Charlie takes a tour of Scotland’s wild west coast starting with the journey of a lifetime aboard the famous Royal Scotsman. Next we explore majestic</k>  </p>
</a>
