<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="30" t="2019-08-13 02:06:40"><p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 05:00:00" d="2019-08-18 06:00:00"><n>I HAVE SEEN THE EARTH CHANGE - JAPAN: LAND OF THE BURNING SUN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Katsuo Sasaki grows rice in Miyagi Province where the crop has a strong reputation. And yet, he is becoming impoverished since never before seen insects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 06:00:00" d="2019-08-18 07:00:00"><n>NEXOS - THE SHARED LANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Lebanon, Bosnia, Cyprus are countries without a predominance of one civilization or religion over the other and they live together in a maelstrom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 07:00:00" d="2019-08-18 07:30:00"><n u="ALL ABOUT ANIMALS -">ALL ABOUT ANIMALS - (15)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 07:30:00" d="2019-08-18 08:00:00"><n u="ALL ABOUT ANIMALS -">ALL ABOUT ANIMALS - (16)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 08:00:00" d="2019-08-18 09:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE - OVAMBO</n><t>D</t>    <k>A curious reporter, outdoor lover, will not rest until he shows us every mystery of the wild, black heart of Central Africa, discovering the stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 09:00:00" d="2019-08-18 10:00:00"><n u="ANCIENT CULTURE -">ANCIENT CULTURE - (11)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 10:00:00" d="2019-08-18 11:00:00"><n>RISE OF ECOLOGY</n><t>D</t>    <k>How did the whole green ecological phenomenon really start? Which are its main milestones? The film documents how environmental disasters have played</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 11:00:00" d="2019-08-18 11:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - III (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Training in a T-6: Kurtis earns his wings in a T-6 warbird. Journey of a Bag: Where does your bag go once it leaves your hands and heads down a conveyor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 11:30:00" d="2019-08-18 12:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - III (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Skydiving: Sara and Raeleen jump out of a perfectly good airplane! Rob Reider, Announcer: The famous voice of some of the largest air shows in the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 12:00:00" d="2019-08-18 13:00:00"><n>SEYCHELLES - TRIP TO PARADISE</n><t>D</t>    <k>White beaches, blue water and wonderful silence, the Seychelles are the garden eden. Consisting out of more than 100 isles, &quot;Seychelles - Trip to Paradise&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 13:00:00" d="2019-08-18 14:00:00"><n>ON THE HIGHWAYS OF HISTORY</n><t>D</t>    <k>The construction of a new highway near the city of Orleans has permitted to excave archaeological treasures and reveal exceptional information about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 14:00:00" d="2019-08-18 15:00:00"><n>THE DRAGON HOUSE</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Dragon House portrays the confrontation between tradition and modernity which the Kingdom of Bhutan is currently experiencing. This is done by means</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 15:00:00" d="2019-08-18 16:00:00"><n u="MUNDO AD PORTAS -">MUNDO AD PORTAS - I (7)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 16:00:00" d="2019-08-18 17:00:00"><n>CLOSE-UP ON WILDLIFE PHOTOGRAPHY</n><t>D</t>    <k>Europe still harbours a diversified wild animal life struggling to survive in the face of global urbanization. Approaching the more timid species</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 17:00:00" d="2019-08-18 17:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - VI (9)</n><t>D</t>    <k>AIR RALLY: Teams from all over North America compete in a race again time and each other to take the title of Air Rally Champion. SEARCH AND RESCUE</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 17:30:00" d="2019-08-18 18:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - VI (10)</n><t>D</t>    <k>FIGHTER INTERCEPT: What happens when a hapless Cessna flies someplace it shouldn’t? It gets up close and personal with Wisconsin Air National Guard fighter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 18:00:00" d="2019-08-18 18:30:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - POLYNESIA, THE GODDESS OF NATURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>A visit to the Island of Tahiti together with a local called Alphonse who, as well as acquainting us with the famous canoe race Hawaiki Nui Va’a</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 18:30:00" d="2019-08-18 19:00:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - SOUTH SEA GIFTS</n><t>D</t>    <k>On board a catamaran, we discover several islands in the Society Island archipelago, in Polynesia. Of the Island of Raiatea, hilly and volcanic, we explore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 19:00:00" d="2019-08-18 20:00:00"><n>ALIEN INVADERS!</n><t>D</t>    <k>Alien Invaders is a documentary special that throws three young, but experienced, hosts into the world of invasive species of animals, fish, birds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 20:00:00" d="2019-08-18 21:00:00"><n>THE MIND OF PLANTS</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Sinis protected marine area and the Island of Mal di Ventre is the subject of this documentary that takes place in the Eastern part of the Island of Sardinia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 21:00:00" d="2019-08-18 22:00:00"><n>TECHNO-SCIENCE - IMPACTO DEL HOMBRE EN VESTIGIOS MILENARIOS</n><t>D</t>    <k>In this chapter, Andrea goes to San Vicente de Tagua Tagua to see a museum of natural history. Research shows that the sector Tagua Tagua million years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 22:00:00" d="2019-08-18 22:30:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - JAPAN'S HERBIVOROUS MAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Research shows that two out of five women say they wish to marry a man who earns at least 6 million yen a year — but such men make up only</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 22:30:00" d="2019-08-18 23:00:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - INDONESIA'S NEW ERA OF ENTREPRENEURSHIP</n><t>D</t>    <k>Indonesia’s economy was brought to its knees when the Asian Financial Crisis hit in 1997. A decade or so later, under the global downturn, the economy barely flinched</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-18 23:00:00" d="2019-08-19 00:00:00"><n>A POPE FOR EVERYONE</n><t>D</t>    <k>In March 13, 2013, former Archibishop of Buenos Aires Jorge Mario Bergoglio, has turned to a beacon of hope for the world's catholic christian community</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-19 00:00:00" d="2019-08-19 00:30:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A JOURNEY TO INFINITY - PART">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A JOURNEY TO INFINITY - PART 1 (PATAGONIA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>It is in Santiago, Chile that we begin the extraordinary journey into the infinity that, place by place, will take us to South Patagonia, which</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-19 00:30:00" d="2019-08-19 01:00:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A JOURNEY TO INFINITY - PART">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A JOURNEY TO INFINITY - PART 2 (PATAGONIA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>The journey to the edge of the world in the icy waters of Tierra del Fuego continues. On board our expedition ship we arrive to Tucker island</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-19 01:00:00" d="2019-08-19 02:00:00"><n>SACRED CULTURE - JODPHUR</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra embarks on a trip to India and Nepal, to show the life of its inhabitants, their customs, the architecture of its temples and holy cities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-19 02:00:00" d="2019-08-19 03:00:00"><n>NOMAD'S LAND MONGOLIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Mongolia. Vast territory covered steppes and deserts. This is where Christophe Cousin goes - in search of nomads. There, he borrows not men with soles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-19 03:00:00" d="2019-08-19 04:00:00"><n>IN CONCERT - MATSU TAKE</n><t>M</t>    <k>Matsu Také was created in 2002 and is dedicated to promoting Japanese music. The group musicians play a wide variety of Japanese instruments: Koto (zither</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-08-19 04:00:00" d="2019-08-19 05:00:00"><n>THE NEOLITHIC MOUNTAINS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel through Europe going back in time to the Neolithic era. Going to the France, England and Italy, discover more about the different plates that moved</k>  </p>
</a>
