<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="32" t="2020-04-15 04:30:52"><p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 05:00:00" d="2020-04-22 05:30:00"><n>PASSPORT TO EXPLORE - SEATTLE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Passport to Explore is an internationallysyndicated half hour educational travel adventure series designed for 13-16 year olds. Syndicated on stations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 05:30:00" d="2020-04-22 06:00:00"><n>PASSPORT TO EXPLORE - SOUTH CAROLINA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Passport to Explore is an internationallysyndicated half hour educational travel adventure series designed for 13-16 year olds. Syndicated on stations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 06:00:00" d="2020-04-22 07:00:00"><n>DON'T FORGET YOUR PASSPORT - BRITISH COLUMBIA CANADA</n><t>D</t>    <k>The rugged Rocky Mountains in Western Canada with its glacial peaks and pristine lakes are the backdrop for Gordon Sivell’s tour of British Columbia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 07:00:00" d="2020-04-22 07:30:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - FULL IMMERSION IN THE SEA</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the middle of the Atlantic Ocean, about one hours flying time from Miami, we go to discover the Turks &amp; Caicos archipelago in the Caribbean Sea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 07:30:00" d="2020-04-22 08:00:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - LOS ROQUES, THE WINDY ARCHIPELAGO</n><t>D</t>    <k>We fly over the waters that separate the Venezuelan coast from Los Roques, we are going to visit this archipelago together with Francesca and her father</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 08:00:00" d="2020-04-22 08:30:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - NORMANDY, FRANCE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Series 9 of Distant Shores follows Paul and Sheryl Shard on a diverse voyage from England through the inland waterways of France to the Mediterranean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 08:30:00" d="2020-04-22 09:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - PARIS, FRANCE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Series 9 of Distant Shores follows Paul and Sheryl Shard on a diverse voyage from England through the inland waterways of France to the Mediterranean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 09:00:00" d="2020-04-22 10:00:00"><n>NEXOS - THE PILLARS OF HERCULES</n><t>D</t>    <k>In this episode we will visit the countries of the Maghreb and the south of Europe. Its’ history, the Hafsides, Marinids, Zayyanids and others</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 10:00:00" d="2020-04-22 10:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - VI (6)</n><t>D</t>    <k>ANATOMY OF A DEPARTURE: Get up and go? Not quite. The process of just leaving the airport sometimes involves talking to a half a dozen separate air traffic controllers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 10:30:00" d="2020-04-22 11:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - VI (7)</n><t>D</t>    <k>WWI History: Soon after the invention of the aircraft, military uses for the new flying machine came into being. Then with the dawn of the Great</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 11:00:00" d="2020-04-22 12:00:00"><n>NOMAD'S LAND - MEKONG</n><t>D</t>    <k>Continuing the theme of itinerancy, Christophe Cousin takes us on this new journey through two countries: Vietnam and Cambodia, on a river</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 12:00:00" d="2020-04-22 12:30:00"><n>GRAVEYARDS - AZUL GRAVEYARDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>A program that scours around the famous and the unknown graveyards. The exquisite architectural designs mixed with the whims of their inhabitants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 12:30:00" d="2020-04-22 13:00:00"><n>GRAVEYARDS - URQUIZA GRAVEYARD</n><t>D</t>    <k>Villa Urquiza is a little but amazing village of the Entre Rios Province, Argentina that has four graveyards spite its only 2000 inhabitants</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 13:00:00" d="2020-04-22 13:30:00"><n>LOW COST - MADRID</n><t>D</t>    <k>Each city is in its native language (ie. Parisis in French, Rome is in Italian, Berlin is in German, etc. with English Scripts) showing the viewer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 13:30:00" d="2020-04-22 14:00:00"><n>LOW COST - NAPLES</n><t>D</t>    <k>Each city is in its native language (ie. Parisis in French, Rome is in Italian, Berlin is in German, etc. with English Scripts) showing the viewer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 14:00:00" d="2020-04-22 14:30:00"><n u="TRAJECTORY -">TRAJECTORY - (9)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Today, although a cloud of satellites surrounds the planet, many records set during the early decades of space exploration remain unsurpassed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 14:30:00" d="2020-04-22 15:00:00"><n u="GARONGA SAFARI -">GARONGA SAFARI - (14)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Garonga Safari is a fun and educational show that showcases the African wilderness and the efforts to preserve it. Learn about the importance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 15:00:00" d="2020-04-22 16:00:00"><n>POSTCARD PERFECT - GUYANA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Bordering Suriname and Brazil, Guyana is France’s biggest region. With its surface being 96% covered by an impenetrable jungle, it is the location</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 16:00:00" d="2020-04-22 17:00:00"><n>BETWEEN EARTH &amp; SKY II - JORDANIA: THE LAST BEDOUINS OF ARABIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Sebastian travels the world in his balloon to visit traditional tribes. In exchange, he will show them their world from the sky! Episodes: Jordan, Peru</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 17:00:00" d="2020-04-22 18:00:00"><n>TRAVEL NOTEBOOKS - CAMBODGE</n><t>D</t>    <k>This series invites the viewer to visit unusual countries, cities and places through the eye of a traveler-illustrator</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 18:00:00" d="2020-04-22 20:00:00"><n>FRANCE BETWEEN EARTH AND SKY</n><t>D</t>    <k>A riveting 3D journey along 5500 kms of coasts and 3 different seas. From the coast of Belgium to Normandy, from Brittany to the Pyrennees, along</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 20:00:00" d="2020-04-22 21:00:00"><n>NOMADS - FREESKIING JAPAN BACKCOUNTRY</n><t>D</t>    <k>First people to free ski big mountain lines in Japan. Long travel times to Japan and ski opportunities were not the only obstacles on their way to explore</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 21:00:00" d="2020-04-22 22:00:00"><n>THE ENCHANTED FOREST</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the heart of France in Auvergne lies a long forgotten forest, la Foręt de la Comté, legacy of La Reine Margot who dedicated the nearby castle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 22:00:00" d="2020-04-22 22:30:00"><n u="KUNG FU KITCHEN - PEKING DUCK">KUNG FU KITCHEN - PEKING DUCK (BEIJING, CHNIA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Peking duck is a famous duck dish from Beijing that is considered one of China's national treasure. The dish is prized for the thin, crispy skin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 22:30:00" d="2020-04-22 23:00:00"><n u="KUNG FU KITCHEN - TEPPANYAKI">KUNG FU KITCHEN - TEPPANYAKI (KOBE, JAPAN)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Teppanyaki, meaning &quot;grilled or fried on iron plate&quot;, is a popular style of Japanese cuisine that uses an iron griddle to cook food. The flashing tools</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-22 23:00:00" d="2020-04-23 00:00:00"><n>MALICE OR MUTINY</n><t>D</t>    <k>The conflict, struggles and adventures that took place on a remote beach in 1942 have been called Australia’s only mutiny for 400 years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 00:00:00" d="2020-04-23 01:00:00"><n>SCEPTICS - HOMEOPATHY</n><t>D</t>    <k>The most popular and profitable alternative therapy of them all: homeopathy. Is it really effective? We will explain what it is and what it is based on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 01:00:00" d="2020-04-23 01:30:00"><n>REBUILDING OUR ENVIRONMENT - PERMACULTURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Permaculture is an energy, fuel and material-saving system that allows construction with eco-friendly materials. A visit to community village</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 01:30:00" d="2020-04-23 02:00:00"><n>REBUILDING OUR ENVIRONMENT - SUSTAINABLE HOUSING</n><t>D</t>    <k>Sustainable housing saves energy and materials and improves the quality of life. A visit to the construction sites of houses through sustainable architecture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 02:00:00" d="2020-04-23 03:00:00"><n>GREAT AMERICAN FESTIVALS - STURGIS MOTORCYCLE RALLY</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Sturgis Motorcycle Rally is the oldest, largest and greatest motorcycle event in the United States. Enthusiasts are drawn to the unique combination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 03:00:00" d="2020-04-23 04:00:00"><n u="ANCIENT CULTURE -">ANCIENT CULTURE - (15)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 04:00:00" d="2020-04-23 05:00:00"><n>IN CONCERT - CORDES ORIENT</n><t>M</t>    <k>Cordes d'Orient is a group through which the richness of great Asian civilizations is revealed with finesse. Shen Qi (erhu) and Huu Bac Quach</k>  </p>
</a>
