<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2020-06-01 04:32:16"><p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 05:00:00" d="2020-06-08 05:30:00"><n>TECHNO-SCIENCE - TECNOLOGIAS PARA MEJORAR LA AGRICULTURA</n><t>D</t>    <k>In this chapter we will see how Cristián Campos travels to San Francisco de Mostazal where knows the work being done with drones in the agricultural sector</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 05:30:00" d="2020-06-08 06:00:00"><n>TECHNO-SCIENCE - ASTRONOMIA AL SERVICIO DE LA EDUCACION Y EL TURISMO</n><t>D</t>    <k>This chapter Cristián visit the region of Antofagasta and goes to Yungay where it has just opened the first state observatory that anyone can learn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 06:00:00" d="2020-06-08 07:00:00"><n>TRAVEL NOTEBOOKS - GUATEMALA</n><t>D</t>    <k>This series invites the viewer to visit unusual countries, cities and places through the eye of a traveler-illustrator</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 07:00:00" d="2020-06-08 08:00:00"><n u="LIQUID EDGE -">LIQUID EDGE - (8)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Liquid Edge is a fast paced series highlighting action sports water adventures from around the globe. We showcase the visually stunning awe-freaking sports</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 08:00:00" d="2020-06-08 08:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - II (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Aviation 101: An explanation of some of the very basics of aviation. Host profiles: A closer look as some of the hosts of The Aviators including Sara</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 08:30:00" d="2020-06-08 09:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - II (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>ATC gibberish: Breaking down and simplifying all that complex sounding radio chatter. Hot air balloons: Up, up and away! Condor Squadron:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 09:00:00" d="2020-06-08 09:30:00"><n u="GOING SOUTH -">GOING SOUTH - (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Going South: Cycling through the Americas an adventurous environmental cycling documentary. As the climate changes, an environmental crisis is proclaimed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 09:30:00" d="2020-06-08 10:00:00"><n u="GOING SOUTH -">GOING SOUTH - (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Going South: Cycling through the Americas an adventurous environmental cycling documentary. As the climate changes, an environmental crisis is proclaimed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 10:00:00" d="2020-06-08 11:00:00"><n u="ANCIENT CULTURE -">ANCIENT CULTURE - (16)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 11:00:00" d="2020-06-08 11:30:00"><n u="TAXI TO ASIA - MIDNIGHT COWBOYS">TAXI TO ASIA - MIDNIGHT COWBOYS (HO CHI MINH VS TOKYO)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Ho Chi Minh: This post-communist city is trying to rival Bangkok and won’t let anything stand in the way of its accelerating economy. Our taxi driver</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 11:30:00" d="2020-06-08 12:00:00"><n u="TAXI TO ASIA - HERITAGE CABS">TAXI TO ASIA - HERITAGE CABS (JAKARTA VS KOLKATA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jakarta: Often referred to as unofficial F1 road racers, the 3-wheeler auto rickshaw Bajaj taxis are banned from major roads and some districts because</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 12:00:00" d="2020-06-08 12:30:00"><n u="ANIMAL ALLIES -">ANIMAL ALLIES - II (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animal Allies first travels to Hampshire in the UK for the rough and tough - but necessary - job of de-horning cows. It’s not for the faint-hearted</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 12:30:00" d="2020-06-08 13:00:00"><n u="ANIMAL ALLIES -">ANIMAL ALLIES - II (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>In Animal Allies this week, we travel to South Africa on the trail of an ailing elephant. This youngster has come off second best in a hassle with a hippo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 13:00:00" d="2020-06-08 13:30:00"><n>ANIMAL ALLIES - DR. DARIO</n><t>D</t>    <k>In Australia Dr Dario takes on a herd of pregnant cows and takes his student through the steps of dealing with the rather smelly procedure, while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 13:30:00" d="2020-06-08 14:00:00"><n>ANIMAL ALLIES - LONDON'S CAT OVERPOPULATION</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the UK, Animal Doctor Justine Braun performs routine but extremely delicate operations on two cats and tells us why these procedures are so important</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 14:00:00" d="2020-06-08 15:00:00"><n u="LIVING JUNGLE -">LIVING JUNGLE - (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>“Living Jungle” is an invitation to explore the most impressive biodiversity in the whole world: the Amazonian Forest. An experimented host starts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 15:00:00" d="2020-06-08 16:00:00"><n>WONDERS OF THE WORLD - SRI LANKA</n><t>D</t>    <k>In this episode Claudio Iturra visits Sri Lanka. He climbs 5000 steps up to the Adam’s Peak, or Pico de Adán in Spanish. Then he admires natural wonders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 16:00:00" d="2020-06-08 17:00:00"><n>NOMADS - FREERIDE MOUNTAIN BIKING BRITISH COLUMBIA, CANADA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Behind the scenes of a mountain bike action movie with the top riders in the world hitting new stunts and tricks that will elevate the sport of freeride mountain biking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 17:00:00" d="2020-06-08 17:30:00"><n u="EUROPE'S COASTLINES FROM ABOVE -">EUROPE'S COASTLINES FROM ABOVE - (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>This series takes viewers across the 10.000 km long European coastlines from Cape North all the way down to the Mediterranean coasts and islands, including</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 17:30:00" d="2020-06-08 18:00:00"><n u="EUROPE'S COASTLINES FROM ABOVE -">EUROPE'S COASTLINES FROM ABOVE - (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>This series takes viewers across the 10.000 km long European coastlines from Cape North all the way down to the Mediterranean coasts and islands, including</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 18:00:00" d="2020-06-08 19:00:00"><n>GREEN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Her name is Green, she is alone in a world that doesn't belong to her anymore. She is a female orangutan, victim of deforestation and resource exploitation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 19:00:00" d="2020-06-08 20:00:00"><n u="WIND QUEST -">WIND QUEST - (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Arthur de Kersauson, a young city-dweller hooked on extreme sports, and Antoine Auriol, World Champion in the Kiteboard Pro World Tour, set out in search</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 20:00:00" d="2020-06-08 22:00:00"><n>THE TREASURES OF MEXICO</n><t>D</t>    <k>A great highlight on the historical and architectural splendors of Mexico It illustrates the strong commitment of Mexico towards the protection</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 22:00:00" d="2020-06-08 22:30:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A JOURNEY TO INFINITY - PART">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A JOURNEY TO INFINITY - PART 1 (PATAGONIA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>It is in Santiago, Chile that we begin the extraordinary journey into the infinity that, place by place, will take us to South Patagonia, which</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 22:30:00" d="2020-06-08 23:00:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A JOURNEY TO INFINITY - PART">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A JOURNEY TO INFINITY - PART 2 (PATAGONIA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>The journey to the edge of the world in the icy waters of Tierra del Fuego continues. On board our expedition ship we arrive to Tucker island</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-08 23:00:00" d="2020-06-09 00:00:00"><n>I HAVE SEEN THE EARTH CHANGE - NETHERLANDS: A COUNTRY BENEATH THE SEA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Global warming causes the icecap to melt which induces a rise in sea level. A nightmare for the Dutch since 60% of their territory lies below</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-09 00:00:00" d="2020-06-09 00:30:00"><n>INSPIRING LIVES GLOBAL - PORT ELIZABETH, SOUTH AFRICA</n><t>D</t>    <k>INSPIRING LIVES GLOBAL follows the journey of Tiamara Williams, social entrepreneur, TV host and life coach from New Zealand, around the developing world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-09 00:30:00" d="2020-06-09 01:00:00"><n>INSPIRING LIVES GLOBAL - YANGSHUO, CHINA</n><t>D</t>    <k>INSPIRING LIVES GLOBAL follows the journey of Tiamara Williams, social entrepreneur, TV host and life coach from New Zealand, around the developing world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-09 01:00:00" d="2020-06-09 02:00:00"><n>POSTCARD PERFECT - TAHITI</n><t>D</t>    <k>French Polynesia. lying 18,000km away from France, this overseas territory in the South Pacific is made up of 118 islands, and half of its population</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-09 02:00:00" d="2020-06-09 02:30:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF GREECE - ATHENS, THE CYCLADES AND KALYMNOS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Starting in the capital city of Athens, Charlie checks out the new Acropolis museum before heading out to the Cyclades and Sporades Islands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-09 02:30:00" d="2020-06-09 03:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF GREECE - CENTRAL GREECE</n><t>D</t>    <k>In this episode we take you on an adrenalin fuelled foray through central Greece. First off Charlie gets up close and vertical with the famous pinnacles of Meteora</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-09 03:00:00" d="2020-06-09 04:00:00"><n>WONDERS OF THE WORLD - GALÁPAGOS</n><t>D</t>    <k>In this episode Claudio visits the Galapagos Islands, a terrestrial paradise, insribed on the UNSECO World Heritage List due to local incredibile variety</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-09 04:00:00" d="2020-06-09 04:30:00"><n u="TRAVEL PLAN - BARCELONA - PART">TRAVEL PLAN - BARCELONA - PART 2</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-09 04:30:00" d="2020-06-09 05:00:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - ADDIS ABEBBA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
</a>
