<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="30" t="2020-05-25 04:46:48"><p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-01 05:00:00" d="2020-06-01 06:00:00"><n u="FRENCH SECRET SERVICES, A DECLASSIFIED HISTORY -">FRENCH SECRET SERVICES, A DECLASSIFIED HISTORY - (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Master Spies, secret Agents, assassins of the Republic, top Intel, infallibles: French intelligence agencies evoke superlatives, stereotypes, and paradoxes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-01 06:00:00" d="2020-06-01 07:00:00"><n u="INTO THE ARCTIC -">INTO THE ARCTIC - (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>For years, artists Cory Trepanier has explored some of the wildest places in the North. Few have walked in these landscapes and even fewer have captures them on canvas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-01 07:00:00" d="2020-06-01 07:30:00"><n>FISH LIFE - MOTION</n><t>D</t>    <k>The ocean has its stars: dolphins, sharks, Manta rays, whales; and then there are the others, the humble and the discreet, which can only get the limelight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-01 07:30:00" d="2020-06-01 08:00:00"><n>FISH LIFE - SEA DESERTS</n><t>D</t>    <k>On the beach or underwater, sand is rarely considered a place teeming with life. Yet, encounters are possible, sometimes multiple, or astonishing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-01 08:00:00" d="2020-06-01 09:00:00"><n>DON'T FORGET YOUR PASSPORT - MALAYSIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Adventure traveler Gordon Sivell tours an old Japanese Prisoner of War Camp in the jungles of Malaysia, and just off the coast of southern Thailand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-01 09:00:00" d="2020-06-01 09:30:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - GENEVA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-01 09:30:00" d="2020-06-01 10:00:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - GOA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-01 10:00:00" d="2020-06-01 11:00:00"><n>DESTINATION WILDERNESS - ARCTIC, SEPENTRION</n><t>D</t>    <k>I’m about to take you across the Great North, from Denmark to Greenland via Iceland, in the footsteps of the conquering Vikings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-01 11:00:00" d="2020-06-01 12:00:00"><n u="ANCIENT CULTURE -">ANCIENT CULTURE - (12)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-01 12:00:00" d="2020-06-01 13:00:00"><n>LUCIEN BONAPARTE, THE REBELLIOUS BROTHER</n><t>D</t>    <k>This documentary retraces the life of Napoleon Bonaparte’s brother through the world of art, his preferred field. The little-known rebel prince</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-01 13:00:00" d="2020-06-01 14:00:00"><n>THE FORCE OF THE SEA - ENERGIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Power of the Sea is a documentary series that reveals the special features of each one of the wonderful seas of Chile, generating conscience</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-01 14:00:00" d="2020-06-01 15:00:00"><n>SOUTHERN FLOWER IN THE PACIFIC - SOUTH OF THE BORDER</n><t>D</t>    <k>A 3 year sailing expedition accross the Oceans with Philippe Poupon - French skipper, his wife Geraldine Danon and their four children to decipher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-01 15:00:00" d="2020-06-01 16:00:00"><n u="MUNDO AD PORTAS -">MUNDO AD PORTAS - I (8)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-01 16:00:00" d="2020-06-01 17:00:00"><n>NOMADS - TANNER HALL-FREESKIING LEGEND</n><t>D</t>    <k>Tanner Hall is today’s most influential skier. He has won every contest, he knows every trick and there is seemingly nothing he cannot do</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-01 17:00:00" d="2020-06-01 18:00:00"><n u="TIMELESS TREASURES -">TIMELESS TREASURES - (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>A series celebrating the extraordinary preservation of human heritage. Discover the world’s most beautiful sites in an exceptional series of short programs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-01 18:00:00" d="2020-06-01 18:30:00"><n u="GARONGA SAFARI -">GARONGA SAFARI - (12)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Garonga Safari is a fun and educational show that showcases the African wilderness and the efforts to preserve it. Learn about the importance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-01 18:30:00" d="2020-06-01 19:00:00"><n u="GARONGA SAFARI -">GARONGA SAFARI - (13)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Garonga Safari is a fun and educational show that showcases the African wilderness and the efforts to preserve it. Learn about the importance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-01 19:00:00" d="2020-06-01 20:00:00"><n>I HAVE SEEN THE EARTH CHANGE - MALI: THE LAKE OF SAND</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the North of Mali, Khissa lives along the banks of Lake Faguibine. A location erstwhile « blessed by Gods ». An area of exchange for nomad breeders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-01 20:00:00" d="2020-06-01 22:00:00"><n>TREASURES OF THE LOST PHARAOHS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Discover three dimensions of the Egyptian history: the Old Kingdom - the golden age of the Pharaonic civilization, the end of ancient Egypt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-01 22:00:00" d="2020-06-01 22:30:00"><n u="ANIMAL ALLIES -">ANIMAL ALLIES - II (13)</n><t>D</t>    <k>We’ll take you Perth Zoo, in Western Australia, for a family re-union this week in Animal Allies. Phil the Gibbon and family are starting a whole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-01 22:30:00" d="2020-06-01 23:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF MEXICO - ADVENTURES IN &amp; AROUND MEXICO CITY</n><t>D</t>    <k>Charlie embarks on an urban safari in one of the world’s largest capitals, meeting top celebrity chef Enrique Olvera and visiting the largest food market</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-01 23:00:00" d="2020-06-02 00:00:00"><n>THE DRAGON HOUSE</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Dragon House portrays the confrontation between tradition and modernity which the Kingdom of Bhutan is currently experiencing. This is done by means</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 00:00:00" d="2020-06-02 00:30:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A JOURNEY TO INFINITY - PART">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A JOURNEY TO INFINITY - PART 3 (PATAGONIA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>The third part of our expedition on board of our ship, that has taken us from Punta Arenas in Chile, takes us now to Ushuaia in Argentina, to cross</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 00:30:00" d="2020-06-02 01:00:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - CHAMPION OF BIODIVERSITY</n><t>D</t>    <k>On Providenciales Island, the entrance to the Turks &amp; Caicos archipelago, we begin our journey by discovering a farm where they grow the biggest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 01:00:00" d="2020-06-02 01:30:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - VOYAGE TO ABACOS</n><t>D</t>    <k>A spring journey north through the lovely Bahamas! We sail first to Mayaguana, then Ragged and the Jumentos Cays before heading to the Exumas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 01:30:00" d="2020-06-02 02:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - CRUISING IN STYLE</n><t>D</t>    <k>At sea and in many of the worldwide ports Distant Shores sails to, Paul and Sheryl are in the company of luxurious cruise ships. In this episode</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 02:00:00" d="2020-06-02 03:00:00"><n>UBUNTU SOUTH AFRICA: LE GRAND PARDON</n><t>D</t>    <k>In May 1994, Nelson Mandela made the promise that in South Africa a new society should rise up that would make the world proud The film is a on whether</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 03:00:00" d="2020-06-02 04:00:00"><n>NOMADS - BIG MOUNTAIN EXTREME SKIING IN LAS LENAS, ARGENTINA</n><t>D</t>    <k>A group of pro skiers travel a tough journey to South America in the hopes of experiencing the world-renown ski terrain Las Lenas, Argentina</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 04:00:00" d="2020-06-02 04:30:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF COLOMBIA - THE PACIFIC</n><t>D</t>    <k>Flavours Of. sees gastronomer Charlie Ottley challenge his taste buds as he travels through some of the most exciting and unpredictable countries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-06-02 04:30:00" d="2020-06-02 05:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF COLOMBIA - THE LOWLANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Charlie Ottley explores the Lowlands starting in the heart of the Colombian Amazon, where he mingles with local tribes, sleeps rough in the jungle</k>  </p>
</a>
