<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2019-07-11 00:20:31"><p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-15 05:00:00" d="2019-07-15 06:00:00"><n u="FRENCH SECRET SERVICES, A DECLASSIFIED HISTORY -">FRENCH SECRET SERVICES, A DECLASSIFIED HISTORY - (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Master Spies, secret Agents, assassins of the Republic, top Intel, infallibles: French intelligence agencies evoke superlatives, stereotypes, and paradoxes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-15 06:00:00" d="2019-07-15 07:00:00"><n u="INTO THE ARCTIC -">INTO THE ARCTIC - (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>For years, artists Cory Trepanier has explored some of the wildest places in the North. Few have walked in these landscapes and even fewer have captures them on canvas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-15 07:00:00" d="2019-07-15 07:30:00"><n>FISH LIFE - MOTION</n><t>D</t>    <k>The ocean has its stars: dolphins, sharks, Manta rays, whales; and then there are the others, the humble and the discreet, which can only get the limelight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-15 07:30:00" d="2019-07-15 08:00:00"><n>FISH LIFE - SEA DESERTS</n><t>D</t>    <k>On the beach or underwater, sand is rarely considered a place teeming with life. Yet, encounters are possible, sometimes multiple, or astonishing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-15 08:00:00" d="2019-07-15 09:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE - ETOSHA</n><t>D</t>    <k>A curious reporter, outdoor lover, will not rest until he shows us every mystery of the wild, black heart of Central Africa, discovering the stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-15 09:00:00" d="2019-07-15 09:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - II (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Aviation 101: An explanation of some of the very basics of aviation. Host profiles: A closer look as some of the hosts of The Aviators including Sara</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-15 09:30:00" d="2019-07-15 10:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - II (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>ATC gibberish: Breaking down and simplifying all that complex sounding radio chatter. Hot air balloons: Up, up and away! Condor Squadron:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-15 10:00:00" d="2019-07-15 11:00:00"><n>DESTINATION WILDERNESS - ARCTIC, SEPENTRION</n><t>D</t>    <k>I’m about to take you across the Great North, from Denmark to Greenland via Iceland, in the footsteps of the conquering Vikings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-15 11:00:00" d="2019-07-15 12:00:00"><n u="ANCIENT CULTURE -">ANCIENT CULTURE - (12)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-15 12:00:00" d="2019-07-15 13:00:00"><n>LUCIEN BONAPARTE, THE REBELLIOUS BROTHER</n><t>D</t>    <k>This documentary retraces the life of Napoleon Bonaparte’s brother through the world of art, his preferred field. The little-known rebel prince</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-15 13:00:00" d="2019-07-15 14:00:00"><n>THE FORCE OF THE SEA - ENERGIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Power of the Sea is a documentary series that reveals the special features of each one of the wonderful seas of Chile, generating conscience</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-15 14:00:00" d="2019-07-15 15:00:00"><n>SOUTHERN FLOWER IN THE PACIFIC - SOUTH OF THE BORDER</n><t>D</t>    <k>A 3 year sailing expedition accross the Oceans with Philippe Poupon - French skipper, his wife Geraldine Danon and their four children to decipher</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-15 15:00:00" d="2019-07-15 16:00:00"><n u="MUNDO AD PORTAS -">MUNDO AD PORTAS - I (8)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-15 16:00:00" d="2019-07-15 17:00:00"><n>IMMORTAL LIFE: MEDICINE OF THE FUTURE</n><t>D</t>    <k>During the Paleolithic Area, 300,000 years ago, the average lifespan was 17 years. An elder citizen in Ancient Rome would have died by the age of 30, while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-15 17:00:00" d="2019-07-15 18:00:00"><n>WONDERS OF THE WORLD - GALÁPAGOS</n><t>D</t>    <k>In this episode Claudio visits the Galapagos Islands, a terrestrial paradise, insribed on the UNSECO World Heritage List due to local incredibile variety</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-15 18:00:00" d="2019-07-15 19:00:00"><n>NOMADS - WHITEWATER KAYAKING WITH THE JACKSON CLAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Jackson Family lead a very unique lifestyle, and are known for being at the very top of their sport, both in talent and accomplishments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-15 19:00:00" d="2019-07-15 20:00:00"><n>I HAVE SEEN THE EARTH CHANGE - MALI: THE LAKE OF SAND</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the North of Mali, Khissa lives along the banks of Lake Faguibine. A location erstwhile « blessed by Gods ». An area of exchange for nomad breeders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-15 20:00:00" d="2019-07-15 22:00:00"><n>TREASURES OF THE LOST PHARAOHS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Discover three dimensions of the Egyptian history: the Old Kingdom - the golden age of the Pharaonic civilization, the end of ancient Egypt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-15 22:00:00" d="2019-07-15 22:30:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - TAIWAN'S STRAWBERRY GENERATION GROWS UP</n><t>D</t>    <k>They are called the Strawberry Generation. Young Taiwanese, born in the 1980's who grew up as spoilt brats, raised by parents who made their fortunes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-15 22:30:00" d="2019-07-15 23:00:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - CAMBODIA'S LAND GRABS</n><t>D</t>    <k>For the sake of development, Cambodians are finding themselves getting evicted out of their own homes, leaving the land as cash cows for foreign and local</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-15 23:00:00" d="2019-07-16 00:00:00"><n>VIPERA LIFE</n><t>D</t>    <k>The viper. The word itself is able to fill up most people with dread. It calls to mind some kind of huge, ancient, writhing monster, lying on the floor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-16 00:00:00" d="2019-07-16 00:30:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A JOURNEY TO INFINITY - PART">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A JOURNEY TO INFINITY - PART 3 (PATAGONIA)</n><t>D</t>    <k>The third part of our expedition on board of our ship, that has taken us from Punta Arenas in Chile, takes us now to Ushuaia in Argentina, to cross</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-16 00:30:00" d="2019-07-16 01:00:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - CHAMPION OF BIODIVERSITY</n><t>D</t>    <k>On Providenciales Island, the entrance to the Turks &amp; Caicos archipelago, we begin our journey by discovering a farm where they grow the biggest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-16 01:00:00" d="2019-07-16 01:30:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - VOYAGE TO ABACOS</n><t>D</t>    <k>A spring journey north through the lovely Bahamas! We sail first to Mayaguana, then Ragged and the Jumentos Cays before heading to the Exumas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-16 01:30:00" d="2019-07-16 02:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - CRUISING IN STYLE</n><t>D</t>    <k>At sea and in many of the worldwide ports Distant Shores sails to, Paul and Sheryl are in the company of luxurious cruise ships. In this episode</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-16 02:00:00" d="2019-07-16 03:00:00"><n>UBUNTU SOUTH AFRICA: LE GRAND PARDON</n><t>D</t>    <k>In May 1994, Nelson Mandela made the promise that in South Africa a new society should rise up that would make the world proud The film is a on whether</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-16 03:00:00" d="2019-07-16 04:00:00"><n>IN CONCERT - SERGIU POPA ENSEMBLE</n><t>M</t>    <k>Sergiu Popa is an acoustic quintet from Montreal, directed by accordionist Tzigane (Roma) Sergiu Popa. The group offers its own musical arrangements</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-16 04:00:00" d="2019-07-16 04:30:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF COLOMBIA - THE PACIFIC</n><t>D</t>    <k>Flavours Of. sees gastronomer Charlie Ottley challenge his taste buds as he travels through some of the most exciting and unpredictable countries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2019-07-16 04:30:00" d="2019-07-16 05:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF COLOMBIA - THE LOWLANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Charlie Ottley explores the Lowlands starting in the heart of the Colombian Amazon, where he mingles with local tribes, sleeps rough in the jungle</k>  </p>
</a>
