<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="32" t="2020-05-14 04:49:49"><p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 05:00:00" d="2020-05-21 06:00:00"><n>I HAVE SEEN THE EARTH CHANGE - EGYPT: THE PHARAOH WITH DRENCHED FEET</n><t>D</t>    <k>Abid'allah Quanwati, a fisherman, and Tarek Al-Cheikh, a farmer, are childhood friends. They live in Rosetta, which is located in the mouth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 06:00:00" d="2020-05-21 07:00:00"><n>NOMADS - FLYING HIGH-PARAGLIDING IN TENERIFE-CANARY ISLANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Three paragliders explore the flight opportunities in Tenerife, a volcanic region of Mt. Teide, in the Canary Islands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 07:00:00" d="2020-05-21 08:00:00"><n>SCEPTICS - OCCULT SCIENCES</n><t>D</t>    <k>We will attempt to decipher &quot;the mysteries of the occult&quot;: the powers of the mind, contact with the dead and being possessed by demons</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 08:00:00" d="2020-05-21 09:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE - SERENGUETI</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra, with his team, is directed to the Serengeti National Park in Tanzania, Africa. During their journey, they encounter an African celebration</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 09:00:00" d="2020-05-21 10:00:00"><n u="ANCIENT CULTURE -">ANCIENT CULTURE - (8)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 10:00:00" d="2020-05-21 11:00:00"><n>BEAUTIFUL MINDS - FERNANDO MONCKEBERG</n><t>D</t>    <k>Albert Einstein said that the mind is like a parachute: it only works if we have it opened. Beautiful Minds is a documentary series that summarizes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 11:00:00" d="2020-05-21 11:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - VI (7)</n><t>D</t>    <k>WWI History: Soon after the invention of the aircraft, military uses for the new flying machine came into being. Then with the dawn of the Great</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 11:30:00" d="2020-05-21 12:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - VI (8)</n><t>D</t>    <k>COMMON AEROBATIC MOVES: All air show maneuvers can almost be broken down to one of a handful of common moves that we’ll explain. SUB SONEX: A homebuilt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 12:00:00" d="2020-05-21 12:30:00"><n u="GOING SOUTH -">GOING SOUTH - (7)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Going South: Cycling through the Americas an adventurous environmental cycling documentary. As the climate changes, an environmental crisis is proclaimed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 12:30:00" d="2020-05-21 13:00:00"><n u="GOING SOUTH -">GOING SOUTH - (8)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Going South: Cycling through the Americas an adventurous environmental cycling documentary. As the climate changes, an environmental crisis is proclaimed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 13:00:00" d="2020-05-21 14:00:00"><n>DON'T FORGET YOUR PASSPORT - VICTORIA, AUSTRALIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Host Gordon Sivell takes in the colorful ANZAC parade in Melbourne, Australia and then tours the wine region of Yarra Valley after touring a unique</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 14:00:00" d="2020-05-21 15:00:00"><n>BUDAPEST WILD</n><t>D</t>    <k>Most of us have very little to no idea how many species we are actually sharing our flats and houses with. Rest assured, it is an uncannily surprising number</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 15:00:00" d="2020-05-21 16:00:00"><n u="MUNDO AD PORTAS -">MUNDO AD PORTAS - I (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 16:00:00" d="2020-05-21 16:30:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - TAIWAN'S STRAWBERRY GENERATION GROWS UP</n><t>D</t>    <k>They are called the Strawberry Generation. Young Taiwanese, born in the 1980's who grew up as spoilt brats, raised by parents who made their fortunes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 16:30:00" d="2020-05-21 17:00:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - CAMBODIA'S LAND GRABS</n><t>D</t>    <k>For the sake of development, Cambodians are finding themselves getting evicted out of their own homes, leaving the land as cash cows for foreign and local</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 17:00:00" d="2020-05-21 18:00:00"><n>TRIBES OF THE HIMALAYAS - THE MESSENGERS OF ZANSKAR: A MARRIAGE IN THE HIMALAYAS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Likden is a trekking guide living in Skaagam located 3700 meters high in the Himalayan valley of Zanskar. After four long years of negotiation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 18:00:00" d="2020-05-21 19:00:00"><n>NOMADS - WAITING GAME - FREESKIING THE WORLD'S BEST POWDER</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Waiting is the hardest part. The anticipation of the next face shot, of an uncut heli run, and of an approaching storm is enough to drive this group</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 19:00:00" d="2020-05-21 20:30:00"><n>PACHO VILLA HERE AND THERE</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Centaur of the North, bandit for some, revolutionary leader for the others. The life, the character and the fights of one of the greatest symbols</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 20:30:00" d="2020-05-21 21:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF SOUTH AFRICA - THE INTERIOR</n><t>D</t>    <k>From the savage Kruger National Park via Suweto to the oldest Baobab tree in the world, Charlie Ottley takes us on a breathless safari across South</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 21:00:00" d="2020-05-21 22:00:00"><n>POSTCARD PERFECT - NEW CALEDONIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>New Caledonia is desperately seeking tourists. Unlike its neighbours, New Caledonia has seen tourist visits stagnate at around 100,000 visitors a year</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 22:00:00" d="2020-05-21 22:30:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - UNINHABITED PARADISE">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - UNINHABITED PARADISE (FANJOVE)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Adventures in Tanzania. On board of a little Cessna plane, we reach the Songo Songo archipelago, 50 km south from Mafia. It’s from here that, after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 22:30:00" d="2020-05-21 23:00:00"><n u="AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - BETWEEN NATURE AND TRADITION">AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - BETWEEN NATURE AND TRADITION (GREECE)</n><t>D</t>    <k>We’re in Messinia, looking out over the Mediterranean Sea. Here we find the beautiful Navarino Coast, with its’ rich vegetation, historically important</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-21 23:00:00" d="2020-05-22 00:00:00"><n u="ANCIENT CULTURE -">ANCIENT CULTURE - (9)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-22 00:00:00" d="2020-05-22 00:30:00"><n>RAMESSES II THE GREAT JOURNEY</n><t>D</t>    <k>3200 years ago, Egypt is living the final hours of its golden age under the reign of Ramesses II. After ruling the country for 67 years, the great pharaoh</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-22 00:30:00" d="2020-05-22 01:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF SCOTLAND - THE ISLANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Take a trip to bonny Scotland, as you’ve never seen it before. Join Charlie Ottley as he sets off through the highlands and lowlands in search</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-22 01:00:00" d="2020-05-22 01:30:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF SCOTLAND - THE ISLANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Take a trip to bonny Scotland, as you’ve never seen it before. Join Charlie Ottley as he sets off through the highlands and lowlands in search</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-22 01:30:00" d="2020-05-22 02:00:00"><n>FLAVOURS OF SCOTLAND - THE HIGHLANDS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Charlie explores the breath-taking Scottish highlands from the Michelin starred Summer Isles Hotel in Achiltibuie to a remote glen where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-22 02:00:00" d="2020-05-22 02:30:00"><n>LOW COST - VIENNA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Each city is in its native language (ie. Parisis in French, Rome is in Italian, Berlin is in German, etc. with English Scripts) showing the viewer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-22 02:30:00" d="2020-05-22 03:00:00"><n>LOW COST - PRAGUE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Each city is in its native language (ie. Parisis in French, Rome is in Italian, Berlin is in German, etc. with English Scripts) showing the viewer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-22 03:00:00" d="2020-05-22 03:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - V (8)</n><t>D</t>    <k>EPIC AIRCRAFT: Surprise! Anthony gets an unexpected opportunity to fly a brand new turboprop driven aircraft. JET TRUCK: 3 jet engines, 48,000 horsepower</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-22 03:30:00" d="2020-05-22 04:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - V (9)</n><t>D</t>    <k>AIRCRAFT TIRES: Tires are one of the most overlooked parts of an aircraft so we highlight the importance of a plane’s rubber. CONTROL TOWER:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-05-22 04:00:00" d="2020-05-22 05:00:00"><n>IMMORTAL SHADOWS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animation is one of today’s most popular forms of entertainment which makes great use of ever evolving technologies. However its origin goes way back</k>  </p>
</a>
