<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="32" t="2020-04-16 04:31:13"><p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 05:00:00" d="2020-04-23 05:30:00"><n>PASSPORT TO EXPLORE - ST LOUIS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Passport to Explore is an internationallysyndicated half hour educational travel adventure series designed for 13-16 year olds. Syndicated on stations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 05:30:00" d="2020-04-23 06:00:00"><n>PASSPORT TO EXPLORE - TAMPA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Passport to Explore is an internationallysyndicated half hour educational travel adventure series designed for 13-16 year olds. Syndicated on stations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 06:00:00" d="2020-04-23 07:00:00"><n>DON'T FORGET YOUR PASSPORT - VIETNAM</n><t>D</t>    <k>Vietnam may be on the move economically but the ‘Communist Manifesto’ still lingers at the Ho Chi Minh Mausoleum and Lenin Square in the frenzied city of Hanoi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 07:00:00" d="2020-04-23 07:30:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - A DIVERS' PARADISE</n><t>D</t>    <k>In open sea, along the Venezuelan coastline, we fly over the biggest coral atoll of the Caribbean Sea to then dive into these beautiful waters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 07:30:00" d="2020-04-23 08:00:00"><n>AROUND THE WORLD IN 80 ISLANDS - THE ROUTE TO LOS ROQUES</n><t>D</t>    <k>Our chosen route is the coral archipelago of Los Roques, our sail boat is pushed forward by the trade winds as we go to explore the small &quot;cayos&quot; in the region</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 08:00:00" d="2020-04-23 09:00:00"><n>IMMORTAL SHADOWS</n><t>D</t>    <k>Animation is one of today’s most popular forms of entertainment which makes great use of ever evolving technologies. However its origin goes way back</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 09:00:00" d="2020-04-23 10:00:00"><n>NEXOS - IN NORTH AMERICA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Many Muslims think of the USA as the enemy, the embodiment of Evil, ignoring perhaps, that it is the home of large numbers of their brothers, Muslims</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 10:00:00" d="2020-04-23 10:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - VI (8)</n><t>D</t>    <k>COMMON AEROBATIC MOVES: All air show maneuvers can almost be broken down to one of a handful of common moves that we’ll explain. SUB SONEX: A homebuilt</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 10:30:00" d="2020-04-23 11:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - VI (9)</n><t>D</t>    <k>AIR RALLY: Teams from all over North America compete in a race again time and each other to take the title of Air Rally Champion. SEARCH AND RESCUE</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 11:00:00" d="2020-04-23 12:00:00"><n>TRACKING THE BLUE DIAMOND</n><t>D</t>    <k>Could HOPE, the most famous diamond in the world exposed at the Smithsonian museum in Washington be the mythical Blue Diamond of the French Crown, which</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 12:00:00" d="2020-04-23 12:30:00"><n>FISH LIFE - MOTION</n><t>D</t>    <k>The ocean has its stars: dolphins, sharks, Manta rays, whales; and then there are the others, the humble and the discreet, which can only get the limelight</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 12:30:00" d="2020-04-23 13:00:00"><n>FISH LIFE - SEA DESERTS</n><t>D</t>    <k>On the beach or underwater, sand is rarely considered a place teeming with life. Yet, encounters are possible, sometimes multiple, or astonishing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 13:00:00" d="2020-04-23 14:00:00"><n u="FRENCH SECRET SERVICES, A DECLASSIFIED HISTORY -">FRENCH SECRET SERVICES, A DECLASSIFIED HISTORY - (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Master Spies, secret Agents, assassins of the Republic, top Intel, infallibles: French intelligence agencies evoke superlatives, stereotypes, and paradoxes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 14:00:00" d="2020-04-23 15:00:00"><n>TRACK RIDER - ARGENTINA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Let yourself be taken away to the heart of Russia, Australia, Thailand, Vietnam, Mexico or the United States, and discover along the tracks, colourful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 15:00:00" d="2020-04-23 16:00:00"><n u="MUNDO AD PORTAS -">MUNDO AD PORTAS - I (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 16:00:00" d="2020-04-23 17:00:00"><n>CHINA UNCOVERED - THE COST OF BEAUTY RISING</n><t>D</t>    <k>Fashion designer Ji Cheng has shown her designs at London fashion week and, like beauty stylist A Zhi, is beginning to challenge the monopoly of Western brands in China</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 17:00:00" d="2020-04-23 17:30:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - AYYATUYA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 17:30:00" d="2020-04-23 18:00:00"><n>TRAVEL PLAN - BAHIR DAR</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 18:00:00" d="2020-04-23 19:00:00"><n u="LIVING JUNGLE -">LIVING JUNGLE - (9)</n><t>D</t>    <k>“Living Jungle” is an invitation to explore the most impressive biodiversity in the whole world: the Amazonian Forest. An experimented host starts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 19:00:00" d="2020-04-23 20:00:00"><n>NOMADS - WHITEWATER KAYAKING THE ZAMBEZI IN AFRICA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Several of the world’s best kayakers are led by South African legend, Steve Fisher, on a trip down one of the most difficult rivers in the world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 20:00:00" d="2020-04-23 20:30:00"><n u="GARONGA SAFARI -">GARONGA SAFARI - (15)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Garonga Safari is a fun and educational show that showcases the African wilderness and the efforts to preserve it. Learn about the importance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 20:30:00" d="2020-04-23 21:00:00"><n u="GARONGA SAFARI -">GARONGA SAFARI - (16)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Garonga Safari is a fun and educational show that showcases the African wilderness and the efforts to preserve it. Learn about the importance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 21:00:00" d="2020-04-23 22:00:00"><n>I HAVE SEEN THE EARTH CHANGE - GREECE: HONEY AND ASHES</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the last 10 years, Greece has endured the worst fires in the Mediterranean bassin of this era. Beyond the climatic factors at stake in this tragedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 22:00:00" d="2020-04-23 23:00:00"><n u="FRENCH SECRET SERVICES, A DECLASSIFIED HISTORY -">FRENCH SECRET SERVICES, A DECLASSIFIED HISTORY - (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Master Spies, secret Agents, assassins of the Republic, top Intel, infallibles: French intelligence agencies evoke superlatives, stereotypes, and paradoxes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 23:00:00" d="2020-04-23 23:30:00"><n>KITCHEN RUSH - AMSTERDAM - RESTAURANTS BRIDG &amp; DE ROODE LEEUW</n><t>D</t>    <k>A journey to some of the best restaurants around the globe. We're going to try everything from sushi to steak tartare. Surprise some of the great Chefs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-23 23:30:00" d="2020-04-24 00:00:00"><n>KITCHEN RUSH - AMSTERDAM - RESTAURANTS SILK ROAD &amp; NEVY</n><t>D</t>    <k>A journey to some of the best restaurants around the globe. We're going to try everything from sushi to steak tartare. Surprise some of the great Chefs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-24 00:00:00" d="2020-04-24 01:00:00"><n>THE DESCENT</n><t>D</t>    <k>Is it possible to travel through time? By digging deep into caves and rocks, let's travel through time to the latest Ice Age</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-24 01:00:00" d="2020-04-24 02:00:00"><n>EARTH: CRACKS OF RAGE HEART OF THE FIRE</n><t>D</t>    <k>Rescuers testify about their involvement, specialists explain to us how these catastrophes come to life and how they evolve Victims explain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-24 02:00:00" d="2020-04-24 03:00:00"><n>POSTCARD PERFECT - REUNION ISLAND</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the tropical climate of Reunion, marijuana grows very easily. And although it hasn’t yet inundated the mainland, zamal - local marijuana - has found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-24 03:00:00" d="2020-04-24 03:30:00"><n>EXPLORE TRAVEL - GENTLE GIANTS OF THAILAND</n><t>D</t>    <k>Elephants are the major icon of Thailand. Explore Travel took unique footage of Thai elephant preserves in Pattaya and Ayutthaya. These magnificent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-24 03:30:00" d="2020-04-24 04:00:00"><n u="EXPLORE TRAVEL - TRAILS OF A LEGEND - PART">EXPLORE TRAVEL - TRAILS OF A LEGEND - PART 1</n><t>D</t>    <k>This special provides a fascinating insight into the migratory patterns of animals and people. At the heart of the story are the Ponies of Lampang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-24 04:00:00" d="2020-04-24 05:00:00"><n>NOMADS - GHOST TOWN-SKI &amp; SNOWMOBILE ADVENTURE IN BRALORNE, CANADA</n><t>D</t>    <k>A world-class group of skiers explore epic backcountry terrain around Bralorne, B.C., areas accessible only by snowmobiles, with Canadian sled super-heroes as their guides</k>  </p>
</a>
