<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="33" t="2020-04-11 04:30:29"><p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 05:00:00" d="2020-04-18 06:00:00"><n>I HAVE SEEN THE EARTH CHANGE - UNITED STATES: FAHRENHEIT 1,5</n><t>D</t>    <k>Colleen Gregory (truck farmer, beekeeper and sheep breeder) lives in the San Juan Islands, off Seattle. Fed up with the city and its ongoing activity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 06:00:00" d="2020-04-18 06:30:00"><n>GUIDES &amp; GURUS - ARIZONA</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Navajo way tradition and way of life is vastly different from the one many people live in this modern world. Henry Walters, a teacher and medicine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 06:30:00" d="2020-04-18 07:00:00"><n>GUIDES &amp; GURUS - SRI LANKA</n><t>D</t>    <k>Veddha people, of Sri Lanka, have a magical link with the jungle and a tradition of elaborate rituals to placate angry gods as well as amazing medicinal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 07:00:00" d="2020-04-18 07:30:00"><n u="ALL ABOUT ANIMALS -">ALL ABOUT ANIMALS - (13)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 07:30:00" d="2020-04-18 08:00:00"><n u="ALL ABOUT ANIMALS -">ALL ABOUT ANIMALS - (14)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Accompanied by her witty and charming 16-year-old brother, Jake, award-winning animal lover and 10-year-old host, Olivia Todd, visits a wide range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 08:00:00" d="2020-04-18 09:00:00"><n>WILD CULTURE - BUSHMAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>A curious reporter, outdoor lover, will not rest until he shows us every mystery of the wild, black heart of Central Africa, discovering the stories</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 09:00:00" d="2020-04-18 10:00:00"><n u="ANCIENT CULTURE -">ANCIENT CULTURE - (10)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra takes viewers on a journey to the world’s most astonishing areas. Each episode of this fascinating documentary series shows a new place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 10:00:00" d="2020-04-18 11:00:00"><n>BEAUTIFUL MINDS - PABLO VALENZUELA PHD</n><t>D</t>    <k>Albert Einstein said that the mind is like a parachute: it only works if we have it opened. Beautiful Minds is a documentary series that summarizes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 11:00:00" d="2020-04-18 11:30:00"><n>TERRUA - MISTRAL VINEYARD</n><t>D</t>    <k>Doctors recommend wine for its antioxidant properties and nutrients. We recommend it simply because it’s good. That’s why in Terruá, we invite you to learn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 11:30:00" d="2020-04-18 12:00:00"><n>TERRUA - TAMAYA VINEYARD</n><t>D</t>    <k>Doctors recommend wine for its antioxidant properties and nutrients. We recommend it simply because it’s good. That’s why in Terruá, we invite you to learn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 12:00:00" d="2020-04-18 13:00:00"><n>SACRED CULTURE - CREAMTORIOS VARANASI</n><t>D</t>    <k>Claudio Iturra embarks on a trip to India and Nepal, to show the life of its inhabitants, their customs, the architecture of its temples and holy cities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 13:00:00" d="2020-04-18 14:00:00"><n>THE FORCE OF EARTH - VOLCANES</n><t>D</t>    <k>The Force of Earth is an educational documentary series of the journey of a Chilean scientist. In every episode we will learn about geography and geology</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 14:00:00" d="2020-04-18 15:00:00"><n u="MANHATTAN">MANHATTAN 1609</n><t>D</t>    <k>Some four centuries ago, Protestants from Belgium and the North of France, chased from their region by war and religion, left to build</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 15:00:00" d="2020-04-18 16:00:00"><n u="MUNDO AD PORTAS -">MUNDO AD PORTAS - I (6)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Why travelling makes us so happy? Is it because it makes us remember what we are capable of creating? In &quot;Mundo Ad Portas&quot; we closely follow the journey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 16:00:00" d="2020-04-18 16:30:00"><n>THE GREAT JOURNEY - EXPEDITION IN DANGER</n><t>D</t>    <k>The technician team can't make the right gas to raise the hot air balloon. In a chemical laboratory we will reproduce the gas production process</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 16:30:00" d="2020-04-18 17:00:00"><n>THE GREAT JOURNEY - FLYING TO THE ANDES</n><t>D</t>    <k>They manage to fly over the first hills of the Chilean mountain range, but fail and fall in a small town and must be rescued. Next to the pilot Cristian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 17:00:00" d="2020-04-18 17:30:00"><n>EXPLORE TRAVEL - TOKYO, JAPAN</n><t>D</t>    <k>Japan. A place where you can certainly find heaven on earth and quickly escape the hassle and bustle of daily life. Here's a historical trail of a lifetime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 17:30:00" d="2020-04-18 18:00:00"><n u="EXPLORE TRAVEL - TRAILS OF A LEGEND - PART">EXPLORE TRAVEL - TRAILS OF A LEGEND - PART 1</n><t>D</t>    <k>This special provides a fascinating insight into the migratory patterns of animals and people. At the heart of the story are the Ponies of Lampang</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 18:00:00" d="2020-04-18 19:00:00"><n u="HAPPINESS IS ON THE PLATE -">HAPPINESS IS ON THE PLATE - (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>A tasty series blending travel, cooking, nature and civic sense, following the daily work of five &quot;green&quot; chefs fighting for eco-friendly cooking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 19:00:00" d="2020-04-18 20:00:00"><n>NOMADS - WAKEBOARDING</n><t>D</t>    <k>This episode of Nomads provides a sneak peek at life as a professional wakeboarder, what the sport is, and the east coast world of wakeboarding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 20:00:00" d="2020-04-18 20:30:00"><n u="TRAVEL PLAN - THILAND-PHUKET PART">TRAVEL PLAN - THILAND-PHUKET PART 1</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 20:30:00" d="2020-04-18 21:00:00"><n u="TRAVEL PLAN - THILAND-PHUKET PART">TRAVEL PLAN - THILAND-PHUKET PART 2</n><t>D</t>    <k>Travel to Amazing Places all over the world. From Paris to Petra. From New York to Cambodia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 21:00:00" d="2020-04-18 22:00:00"><n>SMALL CAMS, BIG BEASTS</n><t>D</t>    <k>25 years ago in wildlife filmmaking, it took about four people to carry camera and lighting equipment. Back then celluloid was loaded into cameras</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 22:00:00" d="2020-04-18 22:30:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - INDIA'S RETURNING NRIs</n><t>D</t>    <k>Having risen from the ashes of one of the poorest economies, India now is walking the road to becoming a superpower. Come the turn of the century</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 22:30:00" d="2020-04-18 23:00:00"><n>THE ASIAN CENTURY - KOREA'S YOUTH EMPLOYMENT</n><t>D</t>    <k>South Korea boasts a population with one of the most highly educated youth in the world. However, with one in ten youth being unemployed, the nation’s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-18 23:00:00" d="2020-04-19 00:00:00"><n>THE FORCE OF THE AIR - INTRODUCTION TO METEOROLOGY</n><t>D</t>    <k>Multidisciplinary documentary series that reveals some of the particular weather conditions of the Chilean territory and its evolution</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-19 00:00:00" d="2020-04-19 00:30:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - THE SAINTES</n><t>D</t>    <k>Just south of Guadeloupe is a small group of islands known as &quot;The Saints&quot;. Paul and Sheryl discover a little bit of French heaven in the Caribbean</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-19 00:30:00" d="2020-04-19 01:00:00"><n>DISTANT SHORES - VOYAGE TO ELEUTHERA</n><t>D</t>    <k>A spring journey north through the lovely Bahamas! We sail first to Mayaguana, then Ragged and the Jumentos Cays before heading to the Exumas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-19 01:00:00" d="2020-04-19 02:00:00"><n>NOMAD'S LAND - ETHIOPIA</n><t>D</t>    <k>With the label of &quot;cradle of humanity&quot;, Ethiopia is adorned with a legendary aura. It is here that the man was born, here he would have his first steps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-19 02:00:00" d="2020-04-19 03:00:00"><n>ALIEN INVADERS!</n><t>D</t>    <k>Alien Invaders is a documentary special that throws three young, but experienced, hosts into the world of invasive species of animals, fish, birds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-19 03:00:00" d="2020-04-19 03:30:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - V (12)</n><t>D</t>    <k>BELL 407 HELICOPTER: If you didn't think there’s much of a difference between flying a helicopter and a fixed wing airplane watch as we put our training</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-19 03:30:00" d="2020-04-19 04:00:00"><n u="THE AVIATORS -">THE AVIATORS - V (13)</n><t>D</t>    <k>AIRCRAFT ENGINES: We take it back to basics when examining the components used to build aircraft engines so that they produce the kind of power needed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="733" o="2020-04-19 04:00:00" d="2020-04-19 05:00:00"><n>CARSTANSZ - THE SEVENTH SUMMIT</n><t>D</t>    <k>Snowy Mountains rise high above the untouched jungle of New Guinea, breaking through heavy rain clouds. A limestone pyramid, known as the Carstensz</k>  </p>
</a>
