<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="63" t="2021-07-09 07:43:36"><p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 05:20:00" d="2021-07-16 05:45:00"><n>Anal Lovers: Liona &amp; Vega</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A realistic porn scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 05:45:00" d="2021-07-16 06:09:00"><n>Breakfast for Two</n>    <k>These girlfriends just wanna have fun. With each other. Especially while having a sleepover. A female friendly porn production by Dusk porn-TV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 06:09:00" d="2021-07-16 06:32:00"><n>Love Lust Longing: Jessica Drake &amp; Kurt Lockwood</n>    <k>Love Lust &amp; Longing takes place in a seemingly innocent Bed &amp; Breakfast. Rachel a prostitute who has set up shop in the master bedroom falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 06:32:00" d="2021-07-16 06:48:00"><n>I found your mother on tinder</n><t>S</t>    <k>The legendary Mrs. Robinson brought to life by the most modern of dating apps. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 06:48:00" d="2021-07-16 07:14:00"><n>Dirty Secerts: Brenda James &amp; Casey Stone</n>    <k>Dirty Secrets is the sultry sexy tale of two worlds colliding when an inhibited divorcee Lana (Brenda James) rents out her home to an adult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 07:14:00" d="2021-07-16 07:36:00"><n>Cum Inside Me 2: Alina Blond &amp; Leo Dee</n><t>L</t>    <k>Watch and learn as Desire Media shows you how to have a strong, respectful and happy sex life with your loved one. Porn for couples by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 07:36:00" d="2021-07-16 07:59:00"><n>Confessions Of A Sound Girl: Roleplay</n>    <k>Ever wondered what porn performers would actually get up to on set if they were in charge? Happy-go-lucky sound girl Ru gets a front row seat behind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 07:59:00" d="2021-07-16 08:16:00"><n>Pure Sexual Attraction 2: Natasha White &amp; Johnny Castle</n>    <k>Embark on an exciting journey of pure sexual attraction as five breathtaking girls are captured in five scenes that set the standard for high definition erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 08:16:00" d="2021-07-16 08:37:00"><n>Fit: Jasmine Aruba &amp; Sienna Day</n>    <k>You are running on the beach, bathed in the beautiful sunshine. You feel alive and energized ? what could be better? Get outside. Get active</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 08:37:00" d="2021-07-16 09:03:00"><n>Sex In White: Silvia Rubi &amp; Zayas</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us with her female friendly porn production: &quot;Sex In White&quot;, where sexual encounters take place in a pure and white scenery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 09:03:00" d="2021-07-16 09:18:00"><n>Never Forgotten: Ella Nova &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>Robert can’t stop thinking about Elizabeth, his first love during the 1940’s. An argument teared the perfect couple apart and decades later Robert is still</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 09:18:00" d="2021-07-16 09:28:00"><n>Chicazo</n><t>S</t>    <k>Luna Corazón will expose herself entirely for this show - only to dress herself again once it's all over. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 09:28:00" d="2021-07-16 09:47:00"><n>Close To The Bone: Anya Olsen &amp; Loren Minardi</n>    <k>Two immortal lovers are feeling the three-hundred-year-itch. As night falls the city becomes a playground for Jonus and Bryana, both seeking to quench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 09:47:00" d="2021-07-16 10:15:00"><n>My Love For you: Claudia Macc &amp; Nick Ross</n>    <k>Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la presents: Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 10:15:00" d="2021-07-16 10:45:00"><n>Sex Sinners and Saints: Nathaly Cherie &amp; Steve</n>    <k>Not only is the church the perfect place to confess your sins, it's also the perfect location to have sensational sex. These couples sin in church, moaning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 10:45:00" d="2021-07-16 11:13:00"><n>My Daughters Boyfriend 10: Keisha Grey &amp; Tommy Gunn</n>    <k>A free spirited skateboarder wants to get more serious with her boyfriend, but he?s resisting. For one, he?s just met an uber-hot, elegant woman at the office</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 11:13:00" d="2021-07-16 11:42:00"><n>Chance Encounters: Alice March &amp; Jordan Ash</n>    <k>Several couples encounter love, affairs, sex and romance at a hotel. A Intimate Encounters film by J. Crawford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 11:42:00" d="2021-07-16 12:09:00"><n>In the limelight 2: Denisa Heaven &amp; Denis Reed</n>    <k>These beautiful pornstars surpass your wildest dreams to fulfill their sexual desires. A romantic female friendly porn film by Daring! Pure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 12:09:00" d="2021-07-16 12:20:00"><n>Off limits: Krissy Lynn &amp; Small Hands</n>    <k>Jesse is the quintessential bad boy. His band is the next big thing in Los Angeles and he is on a fast track to stardom. He then meets Caitlyn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 12:20:00" d="2021-07-16 12:41:00"><n>Delilahs Top Tips: Marc Rose &amp; Sicilia</n>    <k>Delilah is the nation's naughtiest agony aunt dedicated to solving the nation's more. ntimate dilemmas. A naughty female friendly porn scene by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 12:41:00" d="2021-07-16 12:54:00"><n>Late night out</n>    <k>From XConfessions 3: When that little bit too much makes you uncontrollably horny! In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 12:54:00" d="2021-07-16 13:34:00"><n>Nymphomaniac Diaries: Daydreaming</n>    <k>The blond Katerina loves sex so much that her dreams are filled with kinky stuff, but her sexual fantasies with men and women become even better</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 13:34:00" d="2021-07-16 13:56:00"><n>Confessions Of A Sound Girl: Assume The Position</n>    <k>Ever wondered what porn performers would actually get up to on set if they were in charge? Happy-go-lucky sound girl Ru gets a front row seat behind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 13:56:00" d="2021-07-16 14:25:00"><n>Beauty Of Nature: Anabelle &amp; Adam Black</n><t>L</t>    <k>Wondering what it take to have that fantastic sex that you will remmeber for the rest of your life? Watch and learn as Desire Media show you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 14:25:00" d="2021-07-16 14:41:00"><n>Apolonia's Musical Fantasies 4: Deep Inside Me</n>    <k>Apolonia Lapiedra is a beautiful Spanish pornstar who is a classic example of good girl gone bad. In this scene, a gorgeous couple, Apolonia and Juan Lucho</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 14:41:00" d="2021-07-16 15:01:00"><n>Trouble X 2: Abigai Max &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>On his first day back in the dating game, Nick meets not one but TWO beautiful women. Olivia (Abigail Mac) is hot, sexy, and confident. Jenny (Cherie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 15:01:00" d="2021-07-16 15:26:00"><n>Very Beautiful Lips</n><t>L</t>    <k>Starting with a shower, performers Apolonia Lapiedra and Alberto Blanco waste no time in exploring their lust for one another. As they move</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 15:26:00" d="2021-07-16 15:46:00"><n>The Invitation: Sienna Day, Alexei Jackson, Max Deeds &amp; Emma Leigh</n>    <k>Jane and Tom decide to pack the kids off and book a romantic weekend away. When their car unexpectedly breaks down late at night they find themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 15:46:00" d="2021-07-16 16:14:00"><n>Confessions Of A Sinner: Dorian Del Isla &amp; Cassie Del Isla</n>    <k>This beautiful couple relishes each others body with sensual hand and mouth massages by candlelight. Another visual and erotic porn for women film by Studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 16:14:00" d="2021-07-16 16:33:00"><n>Sex in white: Zayas, Xavi &amp; Didac</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us with her &quot;Sex In White&quot; productions, where sexual encounters take place in a pure and light scenery. Starring Zayas, Xavi and Didac</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 16:33:00" d="2021-07-16 16:44:00"><n>Make some time for us</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: Samantha Bentley and Franck Franco make a gorgeous couple in this confession about sex when you're a parent. In XConfessions, people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 16:44:00" d="2021-07-16 17:03:00"><n>Pure Milf 5: Johnny Castle &amp; Capri Cavanni</n><t>L</t>    <k>These pure MILFs always get what they want as you will see in these five tantalizing scenes. These sexy ladies show you the true meaning of seduction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 17:03:00" d="2021-07-16 17:20:00"><n u="Ages of Sex: Sex at">Ages of Sex: Sex at (50)</n>    <k>The Ages of Sex is a porn for women film by Thagson. 4 Well known directors will direct a short which represents a woman?s sexual reality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 17:20:00" d="2021-07-16 17:51:00"><n>Sexy Massage Fantasies: A Touch of Oil</n>    <k>A beautiful sensual film by Roma Amor for SinfulXXX. In this scene oil is key when exploring and touching each other's body. Sexual massages are hot!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 17:51:00" d="2021-07-16 18:10:00"><n>Housemates 2: Luke Hotrod &amp; Samantha Bentley</n>    <k>New house. New rules. Artist James moves to the UK in search of his ex-girlfriend (Dalush) and finds himself sharing a house with four incredibly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 18:10:00" d="2021-07-16 18:37:00"><n>Gentle Loving: Katarina &amp; Vega</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A female friendly porn scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 18:37:00" d="2021-07-16 19:06:00"><n>Forbidden Affairs 4: India Summer &amp; Erik Everhard</n>    <k>He is astounded by the drop-dead gorgeous girlfriend of his son. When she starts to flirt with him he can no longer resist the temptation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 19:06:00" d="2021-07-16 19:22:00"><n>From The First Moment: Alexa Grace &amp; Lucas Frost</n><t>L</t>    <k>What happens at the ranch, stays at the ranch. Unless wicked pictures show up to shoot the hottest porn for women featuring cowboys we can imagine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 19:22:00" d="2021-07-16 19:46:00"><n>Mother Daughter affair: Jodi Taylor &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>Eric has an interesting dilemma. He?s going with a smoking hot woman who has an over-sexed erotic devilish daughter, he just can?t resist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 19:46:00" d="2021-07-16 20:01:00"><n>Fräulein O</n><t>S</t>    <k>The unbearable August Spanish heat. who wouldn't be seduced by the local boy with a bucket full of ice! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 20:01:00" d="2021-07-16 20:32:00"><n>Lesbian Riding School: Jay Taylor &amp; Sinn Sage</n>    <k>To be the best lesbian horse rider you gotta practice eating pussy! Cowgirl Up! A Filly film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 20:32:00" d="2021-07-16 20:52:00"><n>Love is Blind: All the Feels</n>    <k>Starting to lose her sight teaches Julie how to use her other senses to take her to new erotic realms. With her newly heightened perception the sound</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 20:52:00" d="2021-07-16 21:15:00"><n>Room 208: Penelope Cum &amp; Salva Da Silva</n>    <k>A female friendly sex video by Lara Tinelli for Dusk TV. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 21:15:00" d="2021-07-16 21:49:00"><n>Sexy Massage Fantasies: Smooth Seduction</n>    <k>A beautiful sensual film by Roma Amor for SinfulXXX. In this scene the combination of a blindfold and lots of oil prove to be the perfect ingredients</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 21:49:00" d="2021-07-16 22:11:00"><n>Milk</n>    <k>What kind of Milk are you drinking today? A romantic porn video featuring pornstar Julia Roca by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 22:11:00" d="2021-07-16 22:22:00"><n>Be A Hero</n><t>S</t>    <k>Anneke woke up horny and spotted her boyfriend's go pro lying around. What will she do with it? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 22:22:00" d="2021-07-16 22:45:00"><n>Perfect &amp; Pure 2: Ariel &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive, four sultry sirens kiss their lovers whilst soft hands caress strong backs, firm gluts and erect manhoods</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 22:45:00" d="2021-07-16 23:05:00"><n>Afternoon Love: Lexi Dona &amp; Thomas Reed</n>    <k>A realistic couple with realistic sex. A romantic porn for women film by Dusk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 23:05:00" d="2021-07-16 23:23:00"><n>HouseMates: Sicilia &amp; Sean</n>    <k>After a painful break up Jess flees to the city and is thrown into a world where hiding away is not an option. Her new housemates Ollie and Saskia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 23:23:00" d="2021-07-16 23:47:00"><n>Pure Passion: Mia Manarote &amp; Thomas</n>    <k>With the intensity at its highest level you will feel the Passion marked by those indistinct moans and body shivers of your partner who is experiencing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 23:47:00" d="2021-07-17 00:09:00"><n>Rosa: Angell Summers &amp; Danny D</n>    <k>Aspiring novelist Rosa dreams of writing a masterpiece. It is not likely to happen when she keeps being distracted by men. Romantic porn by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 00:09:00" d="2021-07-17 00:27:00"><n>Cabaret Desire: Sofia Prada, Saskia Condal &amp; Toni Fontana</n>    <k>Welcome to nightclub Cabaret Desire indulge yourself with poets and their erotic tales filled with passion and temptation. Porn for women by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 00:27:00" d="2021-07-17 00:57:00"><n>A Touch of Nature: Jenny Simons &amp; Dennis Reed</n>    <k>The heat of the sun guides hands and fingers to touch your deepest soul. Ecstasy, passion and sexual arousal. Having sex outdoors is every womens fantasy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 00:57:00" d="2021-07-17 01:18:00"><n>In The Limelight 1: Chris Johnson &amp; Lexi Belle</n><t>L</t>    <k>This female friendly porn film shows a spectacular selection of nine of their best scenes. In this scene the most beautiful couple surpasses your wildest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 01:18:00" d="2021-07-17 01:42:00"><n>Pleasure Professionals: The Timid Bookworm</n>    <k>Do you harbour special sexual desires? Hire a professional and let them make your naughtiest dreams come true. Scene from a film by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 01:42:00" d="2021-07-17 02:08:00"><n>Afternoon Love</n>    <k>Alexander Theodor is a young Dutch director who saw a challenge in making real Porna.He set to work using the Dusk! panel?s comments.This</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 02:08:00" d="2021-07-17 02:34:00"><n>Her Desire: Ladies Night</n>    <k>Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion. A pleasure to all the senses representing realistic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 02:34:00" d="2021-07-17 02:53:00"><n>Quartet: The Teacher</n>    <k>Penelope boards a plane from London to Budapest, eager to perform with her three best friends from music academy. Reunited, the foursome soon remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 02:53:00" d="2021-07-17 03:19:00"><n>Anal Adventure: Lola &amp; Joe T</n>    <k>Wondering what it takes to have that fantastic sex that you will remember for the rest of your life? These beautiful desirable couples are highly confident</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 03:19:00" d="2021-07-17 03:42:00"><n>After Forever: Alexa Grace &amp; Ryan Mclane</n>    <k>When Derrick plans a romantic weekend in his vacation house he soon finds out that his ex Penny had the same idea with her new partner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 03:42:00" d="2021-07-17 04:13:00"><n>Laguna Passionata: Cindy Shine &amp; Max Dior</n>    <k>In the light of the moon amid a secluded lagoon, beautiful bodies love each other from head to toe. A sinful production</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 04:13:00" d="2021-07-17 04:42:00"><n>Chance Encounters: Capri Anderson &amp; Anthony Rosano</n>    <k>Several couples encounter love, affairs, sex and romance at a hotel. A Intimate Encounters film by J. Crawford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 04:42:00" d="2021-07-17 05:04:00"><n>Apolonia's Musical Fantasies 2: Remembering You</n>    <k>Apolonia Lapiedra is a beautiful Spanish pornstar who is a classic example of good girl gone bad. In this scene, a gorgeous couple, Apolonia and Juan Lucho</k>  </p>
</a>
