<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="61" t="2021-07-10 05:07:37"><p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 05:04:00" d="2021-07-17 05:28:00"><n>He Loves To Watch: India Summer &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>This couple has found a unique way to keep the spark in their marriage. Passionate sex and powerful orgasms for everybody!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 05:28:00" d="2021-07-17 05:44:00"><n>Memory Files of You</n><t>S</t>    <k>A deeply moving ode to loves lost, and irrevocable, unobtainable desires through Virtual Reality. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 05:44:00" d="2021-07-17 06:05:00"><n>Secret Sex Society 2: Calling the Shots</n>    <k>A mysterious invitation gives Emmy the chance to live out her fantasies. In The Game you can be anyone you want, with whoever you want but where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 06:05:00" d="2021-07-17 06:41:00"><n>Exploring Couples 2: Sofi Goldfinger &amp; Vincent Vega</n>    <k>These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A beautiful porn for women scene from Exploring Couples 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 06:41:00" d="2021-07-17 07:13:00"><n>Special Moments: The Apple</n>    <k>A truly romantic sex scene by Dusk TV's own porn for women label: &quot;Ooh la la&quot;. Passionate, realistic lovemaking for women whom enjoy romantic sex scenes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 07:13:00" d="2021-07-17 07:28:00"><n>From Beyond: Aaliyah Love &amp; Jay Smooth</n><t>L</t>    <k>Romantic porn scene with a young couple fully in love. Let the beautiful Aaliyah Love &amp; Jay Smooth show you how they take care of eachothers needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 07:28:00" d="2021-07-17 07:42:00"><n>Art of Spanking</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: after reading The Art of Spanking by renowned erotic artist Milo Manara, a man begins to obsess about this realm of pleasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 07:42:00" d="2021-07-17 08:05:00"><n>Chance Encounters Natalia Starr &amp; Karlo Karerra</n>    <k>Several couples encounter love, affairs, sex and romance at a hotel. A Intimate Encounters film by J. Crawford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 08:05:00" d="2021-07-17 08:31:00"><n>Cum Inside Me 2: Emily Red &amp; Joe T</n><t>L</t>    <k>Watch and learn as Desire Media shows you how to have a strong, respectful and happy sex life with your loved one. Porn for couples by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 08:31:00" d="2021-07-17 08:52:00"><n>Ball Control: Victoria Summers &amp; Ryan Ryder</n>    <k>They say that football is a man’s world, but there’s one woman on this pitch with all the power. Watch pornstar Ryan Ryder en Milf Victoria Summers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 08:52:00" d="2021-07-17 09:20:00"><n>A Beautiful Solo 2: Lilly Evans</n>    <k>Tonight, these ladies are flying solo! Join them in their scenes of sweet female masturbation. Get ready to indulge in the art of self-pleasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 09:20:00" d="2021-07-17 09:38:00"><n>Quartet: Inspiration</n>    <k>Penelope boards a plane from London to Budapest, eager to perform with her three best friends from music academy. Reunited, the foursome soon remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 09:38:00" d="2021-07-17 09:56:00"><n>Apolonia's Musical Fantasies 3: Savage Beauty</n>    <k>Nog toe te voegen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 09:56:00" d="2021-07-17 10:19:00"><n>Hollywood Ending: Karlee Grey &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>Childhood lovers Rebecca and Tommy are finally getting the acting success they always wanted. But their love is put to the test when fame, fortune</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 10:19:00" d="2021-07-17 10:32:00"><n>Hunt Me Catch Me Eat Me</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: A fox hunts for the rabbit, devouring her in all her beauty in the end. In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 10:32:00" d="2021-07-17 10:55:00"><n>Everyday Turn-Ons: Oral Fixation</n><t>L</t>    <k>Nelson loves the taste of Jackie?s body, but since her last boyfriend never went down on her, she?s become shy and self-conscious about oral sex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 10:55:00" d="2021-07-17 11:19:00"><n>Her Desire: The Couch</n>    <k>A great scene by AlexanFilm for Dusk's Porn for women label: Ooh la la. Explicit erotic films for women and couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 11:19:00" d="2021-07-17 11:53:00"><n>Body 2 Body: Lexi Dona &amp; Victoria Pure</n>    <k>Artistic romantic porn from Roma Amor (suitable for watching together or alone) that proves that porn can really be WONDERFUL. Pure pleasure:</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 11:53:00" d="2021-07-17 12:23:00"><n>My Girlfriends Mother 10: Ariella Ferrera &amp; Steven St. Croix</n>    <k>Jordan hopes the handsome young man she met while running will help her forget her troubled marriage. But she doesn?t know that the hot guy is already</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 12:23:00" d="2021-07-17 12:53:00"><n>Infidelity: Lily Cade &amp; Tilly McReese</n>    <k>They wanted a normal life in suburbia! Gina and Annie are a long term lesbian couple with a 2008 vintage marriage, a cute house, good jobs? and a sex life that is a thing of the past. But what happens when a young lesbian couple moves in next door? Lesbian porn for women by Filly film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 12:53:00" d="2021-07-17 13:16:00"><n>All For You: Ella Hughes &amp; Max Deeds</n>    <k>When every thought is focused on one special person, thoughts quickly turn into fantasy. Memories of special moments become the seed of a sexual encounter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 13:16:00" d="2021-07-17 13:37:00"><n>Friends And Lovers: Brett Rossi &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Caroline and Matt have been best friends since college. Through break-ups they've been there for each other. But they have yet to find true love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 13:37:00" d="2021-07-17 14:01:00"><n>Sun stroke: Stephanie</n>    <k>When international DJ Cosmo needs a secluded escape, his boss, sun-kissed Spanish villa is the perfect location. The unannounced arrival of Chloe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 14:01:00" d="2021-07-17 14:16:00"><n>Public Submission</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sometimes you find the most thrilling encounters where you least expect. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 14:16:00" d="2021-07-17 14:40:00"><n>Sexual Bliss: Claudia &amp; Nic</n>    <k>Four passionate couples in a Sinful XXX film by Roma Amor. Beautiful, Arty and very sexy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 14:40:00" d="2021-07-17 15:01:00"><n>Confessions Of A Sound Girl: Instant Attraction</n>    <k>Ever wondered what porn performers would actually get up to on set if they were in charge? Happy-go-lucky sound girl Ru gets a front row seat behind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 15:01:00" d="2021-07-17 15:32:00"><n>Soft And Sweet 2: Vanessa Decker &amp; Dean</n><t>L</t>    <k>These young couples show you their most intimate experiences, see the excitement they both have to endure when they tease each other by kissing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 15:32:00" d="2021-07-17 15:52:00"><n>Apolonia's Musical Fantasies 4: On A Hot Summers Day</n>    <k>Apolonia Lapiedra is a beautiful Spanish pornstar who is a classic example of good girl gone bad. In this scene, two gorgeous girls, Apolonia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 15:52:00" d="2021-07-17 16:21:00"><n>Ilove: Alex is Fawx &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>Tech nerd Tommy (Tommy Pistol) has created a revolutionary algorithm for connecting people and has enlisted his best friend and gaming partner Lina (Alexis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 16:21:00" d="2021-07-17 16:36:00"><n>Thr3e</n>    <k>The threesome has always been a recurring fantasy in the imaginary of erotica. Sharing the pleasure with two other people, discovering their bodies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 16:36:00" d="2021-07-17 16:59:00"><n>Everyday Turn-Ons: Restricted Behaviour</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sometimes we don?t choose our fetishes; they find us in the night. Gavin wakes up to find Mary has stolen the covers and is cocooned inside the sheets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 16:59:00" d="2021-07-17 17:31:00"><n>Sweat On: Max Deeds &amp; Stacy Cruz</n>    <k>A Roma Amor sex film (suitable for watching together or alone) that proves that porn can really be BEAUTIFUL. Pure pleasure, beautiful, passionate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 17:31:00" d="2021-07-17 17:36:00"><n>Bad Sometimes: Didac Duran</n><t>L</t>    <k>After the acclaimed success of his first film, Lara Tinelli surprises us with a completely different and transgressive film while staying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 17:36:00" d="2021-07-17 17:57:00"><n>The Ski Instructor</n><t>S</t>    <k>Baby, it's cold outside. Who doesn't want to sleep with their ski instructor? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 17:57:00" d="2021-07-17 18:17:00"><n>Pure Sexual Attraction: Emily Grey &amp; Dylan Snow</n>    <k>Embark on an exciting journey of pure sexual attraction as five breathtaking girls are captured in five scenes that set the standard for high definition erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 18:17:00" d="2021-07-17 18:35:00"><n>Apolonia's Musical Fantasies 5: The Biker</n>    <k>Apolonia Lapiedra is a beautiful Spanish pornstar who is a classic example of good girl gone bad. In this scene, a gorgeous couple, Apolonia and Emilio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 18:35:00" d="2021-07-17 19:17:00"><n>Light my Fire: Max Deeds &amp; Angel Wicky</n>    <k>This beautiful couple relishes each others body with sensual hand and mouth massages by candlelight. Another visual and erotic jewel by Studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 19:17:00" d="2021-07-17 19:38:00"><n>Slutish: Anticipation</n>    <k>Dharma is fucking a guy in an open relationship, so when he's out of town she likes to find herself a new hookup. She enjoys the preparation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 19:38:00" d="2021-07-17 20:02:00"><n>Cum Inside Me 2: Katty West &amp; Joe T</n><t>L</t>    <k>Watch and learn as Desire Media shows you how to have a strong, respectful and happy sex life with your loved one. Porn for couples by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 20:02:00" d="2021-07-17 20:37:00"><n>My Girlfriends Mother 6: Chloe Foster &amp; James Deen</n>    <k>Robbie dreaded meeting his girlfriend's mother, but when he finally does, he's taken back as how friendly, alluring and sensual she really is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 20:37:00" d="2021-07-17 21:04:00"><n>Friends And Lovers: AJ Applegate, Blair Williams &amp; Small Hands</n>    <k>Caroline and Matt have been best friends since college. Through break-ups they've been there for each other. But they have yet to find true love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 21:04:00" d="2021-07-17 21:35:00"><n>A love triangle 2: Dana DeArmond &amp; Danny Mountain</n>    <k>It?s time for yoga class! Sensuous Dana DeArmond leads the star studded class flaunting her sexual appetite for both men and women. A Mile High film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 21:35:00" d="2021-07-17 21:47:00"><n>That Guy At The Nudist Beach</n><t>S</t>    <k>Julia Roca and Bel Gris play a gorgeous Spanish couple, seducing each other on a deserted beach. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 21:47:00" d="2021-07-17 22:15:00"><n>My Wife's First Girlfriend: Dana Vespoli &amp; Melissa Moore</n>    <k>Jenna?s secret desires become unleashed when her husband catches her masturbating to lesbian porn. When Jimmy notices a growing attraction between</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 22:15:00" d="2021-07-17 22:37:00"><n>Love is Blind: Spoken Word</n>    <k>Starting to lose her sight teaches Julie how to use her other senses to take her to new erotic realms. With her newly heightened perception the sound</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 22:37:00" d="2021-07-17 23:00:00"><n>Tenderness: Alexis Crystal &amp; George Lee</n>    <k>A romantic sex scene by Dusk TV's own female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Romantic porn films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 23:00:00" d="2021-07-17 23:28:00"><n>Massage Room: Nikolas &amp; Avery</n>    <k>Please lay down, make yourself comfortable and make sure you are totally relaxed. Once the masseur starts their job, you only can think of one thing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 23:28:00" d="2021-07-17 23:52:00"><n>Blondes Have All The Fun: Melanie &amp; Thomas</n>    <k>Some say blondes have more fun. Let's watch and find out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-17 23:52:00" d="2021-07-18 00:18:00"><n>Deep: Ariana &amp; Edward</n>    <k>Gorgeous, hot looking couples who just love sex, that is all what you will find in this 2020 Vision masterpiece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-18 00:18:00" d="2021-07-18 00:46:00"><n>Her Desire: Shy Guy</n>    <k>Romantic porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion. A pleasure to all the senses representing realistic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-18 00:46:00" d="2021-07-18 01:06:00"><n>Sun stroke: Michelle And Jade</n>    <k>These girls are trying to beat the spanish summer heat at their beautiful summerhouse in the woods. But cooling down appears to be a major challenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-18 01:06:00" d="2021-07-18 01:30:00"><n>Perfect &amp; Pure 2: Lola &amp; Vincent</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive, four sultry sirens kiss their lovers whilst soft hands caress strong backs, firm gluts and erect manhoods</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-18 01:30:00" d="2021-07-18 01:56:00" c="1"><n>The Possession Of Mrs Hyde: Seth Gamble, Kenna James &amp; Victoria Voxxx</n><t>F</t>    <k>The Possession of Mrs. Hyde is Axel Braun's first non-parody feature in 15 years and his most ambitious movie to date. Shot entirely in Black and White</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-18 01:56:00" d="2021-07-18 02:26:00"><n>Wet!: A Wet Suprise</n>    <k>Sinful couples enjoy having seks when it pours? What's on your bucket list? A SinfulXXX film by Roma Amor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-18 02:26:00" d="2021-07-18 03:06:00"><n>Black And Blue: Jade Nila &amp; James Deen</n><t>L</t>    <k>In this tale of submission and dominance, wealthy businessman Patrick introduces young Alison to the world of BDSM. When they fall in lover it shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-18 03:06:00" d="2021-07-18 03:19:00"><n>Bad Sometimes: Amarna Miller &amp; Miguel Zayas</n><t>L</t>    <k>After the acclaimed success of his first film, Lara Tinelli surprises us with a completely different and transgressive film while staying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-18 03:19:00" d="2021-07-18 03:41:00"><n>Upon Further Reflection: Brittney Amber &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>Fiction writer, James Wharton (Ryan Mclane), is suffering from writers block and a drinking problem. His ex-wife is making his life a living</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-18 03:41:00" d="2021-07-18 03:53:00"><n>Come Fly With Me</n><t>S</t>    <k>Luke Hotrod and Carolina Abril play a couple caught in between angst and lust, all up in the air. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-18 03:53:00" d="2021-07-18 04:13:00"><n>Housemates 2 : Alexei Jackson, Stella Cox &amp; Amber Nevada</n>    <k>New house. New rules. Artist James moves to the UK in search of his ex-girlfriend and finds himself sharing a house with four incredibly attractive women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-18 04:13:00" d="2021-07-18 04:48:00"><n>Beauty Of Nature: Alex Black &amp; Nick Ross</n><t>L</t>    <k>Wondering what it takes to have fantastic sex that you will remmeber for the rest of your life? Watch and learn as Desire Media show you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-18 04:48:00" d="2021-07-18 05:19:00"><n>Not to Innocent: Ally &amp; Max D</n>    <k>A sensuous sex video depicting real excitement and passion. A pleasure to all the senses representing realistic sex full of intimacy, laughter, chemistry</k>  </p>
</a>
