<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="59" t="2020-05-31 04:38:14"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 05:22:00" d="2020-06-07 05:41:00"><n>Naked Desire</n>    <k>An exciting porn for women video by Dusk TV's own female friendly porn label. Watch this beautiful young woman having sex with her tattooed, big dick boyfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 05:41:00" d="2020-06-07 05:56:00"><n>Never Forgotten: Ella Nova &amp; Robby Echo</n>    <k>Robert can’t stop thinking about Elizabeth, his first love during the 1940’s. An argument teared the perfect couple apart and decades later Robert is still</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 05:56:00" d="2020-06-07 06:10:00"><n>Art of Spanking</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: after reading The Art of Spanking by renowned erotic artist Milo Manara, a man begins to obsess about this realm of pleasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 06:10:00" d="2020-06-07 06:41:00"><n>My Hotwife's Lover: The Seduction Game</n>    <k>Kristin's (Karla Kush) forbidden attraction to her husband's best friend reaches a breaking point when he arranges a private get-together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 06:41:00" d="2020-06-07 07:05:00"><n>Exploring Couples 2: Lila West &amp; Johnny</n>    <k>These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A romatic porn scene from Exploring Couples 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 07:05:00" d="2020-06-07 07:23:00"><n>Delilahs Top Tips: Jess West &amp; Danielle Ashlea Maye</n><t>L</t>    <k>Delilah is the nation's naughtiest agony aunt dedicated to solving the nation's more. ntimate dilemmas. She shows a pretty young teacher how to get closer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 07:23:00" d="2020-06-07 07:40:00"><n>Pure Sexual Attraction 2: Natasha White &amp; Johnny Castle</n>    <k>Embark on an exciting journey of pure sexual attraction as five breathtaking girls are captured in five scenes that set the standard for high definition erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 07:40:00" d="2020-06-07 07:58:00"><n>Thr3e</n>    <k>The threesome has always been a recurring fantasy in the imaginary of erotica. Sharing the pleasure with two other people, discovering their bodies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 07:58:00" d="2020-06-07 08:24:00"><n>Connections: Kara Dasha &amp; Devon</n>    <k>Connections, celebrates all that?s great about sex: passion, laughter, teasing, giving, receiving, &amp; experiencing real pleasure. For this real life couple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 08:24:00" d="2020-06-07 08:51:00"><n>Sexual Situations: Friends with Benefits Sex</n>    <k>&quot;Wanna have sex?&quot; Gorgeous Gina Valentina takes the viewer through 5 sexy scenarios illustrating the various ways that people hook up -- Casual sex, kinky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 08:51:00" d="2020-06-07 09:04:00"><n>Cinema X Pigalle</n><t>S</t>    <k>The piano goes on as an old porn movie is projected just for their own private arousal. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 09:04:00" d="2020-06-07 09:22:00"><n>Everyday Turn-Ons: Close To The Edge</n>    <k>Like most modern couples, Shan and Mark struggle to fit sex into their busy lives along with family, friends and work. Snatching a few precious moments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 09:22:00" d="2020-06-07 09:58:00"><n>Not to Innocent: Bella Jordan &amp; Fernando</n>    <k>A scene by Dawn for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 09:58:00" d="2020-06-07 10:38:00"><n>Light my Fire: Daphne Klyde &amp; Steve Q</n>    <k>This beautiful couple relishes each others body with sensual hand and mouth massages by candlelight. Another visual and erotic jewel by Studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 10:38:00" d="2020-06-07 11:06:00"><n>Mother Daughter Affair 2: Sara Luvv &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>Chloe just can?t forgive her mom for leaving her dad for a young hot guy, but a visit to the sexy older psychiatrist seems to help in many ways</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 11:06:00" d="2020-06-07 11:25:00"><n>Oasis: Christie Stevens &amp; Giovanni Franceso</n>    <k>A secluded oasis with design furniture appears to be the perfect place to have passionate sex. A scene from an Intimate Encounters film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 11:25:00" d="2020-06-07 11:46:00"><n>A Girls' Getaway: Lucia Love &amp; Stella Cox</n>    <k>Girls weekend out! The girls go away together each year for a relaxing weekend to the English countryside. But what happens when the girls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 11:46:00" d="2020-06-07 12:05:00"><n>Love and Loss: Chad White &amp; AJ Applegate</n>    <k>With more twists and turns than the German autobahn, Love and Loss follows the story of Lanie and Alex, an ex-cop involved in the shooting of Lanie's ex-lover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 12:05:00" d="2020-06-07 12:27:00"><n>Inside: Kali Sudhra &amp; Miguel Zayas</n>    <k>Welcome to The Retreat: where curious minds come to play. Plug in and turn on to explore a virtual reality experience where you can be anyone, go anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 12:27:00" d="2020-06-07 12:45:00"><n>If the Apocalypse Comes, Fuck Me</n><t>S</t>    <k>Maria Riot is lost and thirsty in an apocalyptical world. Luke seems to be the only man alive. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 12:45:00" d="2020-06-07 13:10:00"><n>Raw: Denisa &amp; Radek</n>    <k>Beautiful images of sexual tenderness in its pure but raw way. Close-ups of gorgeous toned bodies and horny sweat. One of Sinful?s most beautiful productions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 13:10:00" d="2020-06-07 13:33:00"><n>Taste: Jasmine Jae &amp; Ryan Ryder</n>    <k>Audrey is a talented and beautiful chef with a gift. She has the power to make her unsuspecting diners feel overwhelmingly amorous. She is one mouthful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 13:33:00" d="2020-06-07 14:02:00"><n>I Will Share My Friend With You: Laveina Lux &amp; Sofi Goldfinger &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. Is a threesome your ulitimate sexual experience? A passionate erotic video by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 14:02:00" d="2020-06-07 14:20:00"><n>From The First Moment: Alana Cruise &amp; Damon Dice</n>    <k>Kira (Alix Lynx) is about to marry her handsome movie star boyfriend James except he gets cold feet and leaves her at the wedding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 14:20:00" d="2020-06-07 14:38:00"><n>Strip Chess</n>    <k>Are you up for a chess game? Join Silvia Rubi and Gabe Romero in this intimate scene full of chemistry, where the game (and the increasing lack of clothes)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 14:38:00" d="2020-06-07 15:06:00"><n>Secret Sex Society: Cintia Shapiro &amp; Bel Gris</n>    <k>When colourful people meet and share their colourful fantasies. Starring the hot blooded Spanish beauty Julia Roca</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 15:06:00" d="2020-06-07 15:36:00"><n>The Artist: Max Deeds &amp; Misha Cross</n>    <k>Another beautiful production by Studio Sinful, containing lots of close-ups, artistic lighting and delicious performers. In The Artist a man is sensually</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 15:36:00" d="2020-06-07 16:03:00"><n>Real And Molly</n>    <k>A new scene for Dusk Academy from Michelle Flynn. A different couple, a different style, a different setting. But 100% porna</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 16:03:00" d="2020-06-07 16:17:00"><n>Garden of Eden</n>    <k>From XConfessions 3: Ever thought about a fresh fuck in the middle of nature, covered in the fruit of mother natures creation? In XConfessions, people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 16:17:00" d="2020-06-07 16:42:00"><n>Blindfolded Passion</n>    <k>When Uma steps through the gate at Nick's home he's waiting for her with a plan in mind and a blindfold in hand. A bathtub, kisses, teasing and lovemaking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 16:42:00" d="2020-06-07 17:11:00"><n>My Love For you: Vinna Reed &amp; Lutro</n>    <k>A sex film by Roma Woodcock for Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 17:11:00" d="2020-06-07 17:37:00"><n>Raw: Fanni &amp; Ivan</n>    <k>Beautiful images of sexual tenderness in its pure but raw way. Close-ups of gorgeous toned bodies and horny sweat. One of Sinful?s most beautiful productions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 17:37:00" d="2020-06-07 18:01:00"><n>Housemates 2: Ava Dalush &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Romantic porn with pornstars: Ava Dalush &amp; Tyler Nixon. Artist James moves to the UK in search of his ex-girlfriend (Dalush) and finds himself sharing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 18:01:00" d="2020-06-07 18:26:00"><n>Daytime Desires: Amily &amp; Henderson</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A female friendly porn scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 18:26:00" d="2020-06-07 19:01:00"><n>Guide To Kinky Sex For Couples: Asa Akira &amp; Derrick Pierce</n>    <k>Kink expert Tristan Taormino gives sexlessons to discuss, explore and finally act out your wildest fantasies, with your partner! 4 Hot couples demonstrate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 19:01:00" d="2020-06-07 19:18:00"><n>Trouble X 2: Abigail Mac &amp; Damon Dice</n>    <k>On his first day back in the dating game, Nick meets not one but TWO beautiful women. Olivia (Abigail Mac) is hot, sexy, and confident. Jenny (Cherie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 19:18:00" d="2020-06-07 19:51:00"><n>Forbidden Affairs 4: Jade Nile &amp; Steven St. Croix</n>    <k>He is astounded by the drop-dead gorgeous girlfriend of his son. When she starts to flirt with him he can no longer resist the temptation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 19:51:00" d="2020-06-07 20:06:00"><n>Boat Buddies With Benefits</n>    <k>From XConfessions 3: Warning: mixing business with pleasure has orgasmic effects! In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 20:06:00" d="2020-06-07 20:37:00"><n>The Exes And Ohhs: Richie Calhoun &amp; Casey Calvert</n>    <k>While helping friends plan a wedding, Jade and Michael?s lingering feelings ignite a passionate conversation about what went wrong in their relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 20:37:00" d="2020-06-07 20:57:00"><n>Housemates 2: Satine Spark &amp; Seth Strong</n>    <k>New house. New rules. Artist James moves to the UK in search of his ex-girlfriend (Dalush) and finds himself sharing a house with four incredibly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 20:57:00" d="2020-06-07 21:25:00"><n>Come Closer: Sunday Morning</n>    <k>Having a lazy sunday? This couple is enjoying each other and making their time together worthwhile. A real life couple with real life sex. A romantic sex film by Dusk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 21:25:00" d="2020-06-07 21:55:00"><n>Sex Sinners and Saints: Jan Seidl &amp; Michaela Mangova</n>    <k>Not only is the church the perfect place to confess your sins, it's also the perfect location to have sensational sex. These couples sin in church, moaning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 21:55:00" d="2020-06-07 22:13:00"><n>Arousal</n>    <k>If you ever wondered why everybody wants to make threesomes with these two? Super sexy porn for women by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 22:13:00" d="2020-06-07 22:27:00"><n>Eat with me</n><t>S</t>    <k>Be fed all your deepest and most delicious desires by a gorgeous celeb chef. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 22:27:00" d="2020-06-07 22:54:00"><n>I Love You: Blanche Bradburry &amp; Nick Ross</n>    <k>These beautiful desireable men and women are highly confident and have all the experience to bring you in a state of trance. A erotic porn film by Desire media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 22:54:00" d="2020-06-07 23:09:00"><n>Unbridled: Stormy Daniels &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>To save her family’s ranch, city girl Avery has to return to Texas and face her demons and her old flame horse trainer Grant. Stormy Daniels stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 23:09:00" d="2020-06-07 23:33:00"><n>Sweet Memories: Together</n>    <k>A short erotic story by Lara Tinelli for female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting realistic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 23:33:00" d="2020-06-07 23:55:00"><n>Tease: Amber Nevada &amp; Billy King</n>    <k>If according to Shakespeare, clothes make the man, then without doubt lingerie make the woman. Skyler is the gorgeous young owner and head designer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 23:55:00" d="2020-06-08 00:36:00"><n>Couples Massage: Vanessa Decker &amp; Ricky</n>    <k>A crackling fire, relaxing music and a lot of warm oil for a total body massage. Delicious. These beautiful couples can’t get enough of it too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 00:36:00" d="2020-06-08 00:53:00"><n>Perfect timing: Veronica Avluv &amp; Eric Masterson</n>    <k>Christina has a dilemma. She was swept off her feet by a much older man, but now things have cooled. She then meets a charming guy and very soon sparks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 00:53:00" d="2020-06-08 01:31:00"><n>Light my Fire: Dominica Phoenix &amp; Kristof Cale</n>    <k>This beautiful couple relishes each others body with sensual hand and mouth massages by candlelight. Another visual and erotic jewel by Studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 01:31:00" d="2020-06-08 02:02:00"><n>Lesbian Riding School: Jay Taylor &amp; Sinn Sage</n>    <k>To be the best lesbian horse rider you gotta practice eating pussy! Cowgirl Up! A Filly film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 02:02:00" d="2020-06-08 02:13:00"><n>Tease</n>    <k>&quot;Tease&quot; is an erotic video shot from an straight female perspective, exploring the idea of playfulness in relationships. A porn for women film by Louise Lush</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 02:13:00" d="2020-06-08 02:41:00"><n>Facade: Keira Nicole &amp; James Deen</n>    <k>Amber and her friend Lindsay are average college students?who happen to moonlight as sexy webcam models. This complicates things when they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 02:41:00" d="2020-06-08 03:28:00"><n>Feminist &amp; Submissive</n><t>S</t>    <k>Can you be a feminist and submissive? A round table discussion accompanies a sensual BDSM scene. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 03:28:00" d="2020-06-08 03:49:00"><n>Quartet: Controlled</n>    <k>Penelope boards a plane from London to Budapest, eager to perform with her three best friends from music academy. Reunited, the foursome soon remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 03:49:00" d="2020-06-08 04:14:00"><n>In the limelight 2: Iwia &amp; Jay Dee</n>    <k>The most beautiful couples surpass your wildest dreams to fulfill their sexual desires. A sensual romantic erotic film by Daring! Pure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 04:14:00" d="2020-06-08 04:48:00"><n>Not to Innocent: Angel Piaf &amp; Max D</n>    <k>This scene is a true pleasure to all the senses representing natural sex full of intimacy, romance, chemistry and lots of naughtiness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 04:48:00" d="2020-06-08 05:04:00"><n>When it Comes to you: Hope Howell &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>When It Comes To You is a captivating and scintillating story of a woman torn between two men who both profess great love. Directed by Stormy Daniels</k>  </p>
</a>
