<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="60" t="2020-04-11 04:38:11"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 05:07:00" d="2020-04-18 05:32:00"><n>With Love</n>    <k>Lucy stands in the bathroom brushing her teeth. Her lover, William, watches, entranced, from the hallway before stepping into the room and joining</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 05:32:00" d="2020-04-18 06:01:00"><n>Couples Massage: Daphne &amp; Andrew Truck</n>    <k>A crackling fire, relaxing music and a lot of warm oil for a total body massage. Delicious. These beautiful couples can’t get enough of it too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 06:01:00" d="2020-04-18 06:29:00"><n>Tenderness: Violette Pink &amp; Angelo Godshack</n>    <k>A erotic video by Dusk TV. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion. A pleasure to all the senses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 06:29:00" d="2020-04-18 07:09:00"><n>Light my Fire: Daphne Klyde &amp; Steve Q</n>    <k>This beautiful couple relishes each others body with sensual hand and mouth massages by candlelight. Another visual and erotic jewel by Studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 07:09:00" d="2020-04-18 07:29:00"><n>The Invitation: Luke Hotrod, Ava Austen &amp; Carly Rae</n>    <k>Jane and Tom decide to pack the kids off and book a romantic weekend away. When their car unexpectedly breaks down late at night they find themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 07:29:00" d="2020-04-18 07:41:00"><n>Win A Date With Sofia Blake: Bianca Breeze &amp; Jake Jace</n>    <k>A-list Hollywood actress Sofia Blake (Olivia Austin) is having the worst day of her life and the paparazzi have made sure to plaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 07:41:00" d="2020-04-18 08:06:00"><n>Two Girls Sofa</n>    <k>Two girls on a sofa, what else is there to do on a Sunday when you have nothing planned? These girls decide to explore each other's bodies? A lesbian porn for women scene byVerso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 08:06:00" d="2020-04-18 08:40:00"><n>The Teacher 4: Katie St. Ives &amp; Manuel Ferrara</n>    <k>Physicist Manuel Ferrara is on the verge of solving physics? biggest mysteries, and smitten young students treat him like a rock star. Obsessive young</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 08:40:00" d="2020-04-18 09:07:00"><n>Tenderness: Ria Sunn &amp; Jayden Cox</n>    <k>A erotic massage scene by Dusk TV's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Romantic porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 09:07:00" d="2020-04-18 09:48:00"><n>Guide to Bondage For Couples: Skin Diamond &amp; Derrick Pierce</n>    <k>If Fifty Shades of Grey intrigued and inspired you, then get ready for Tristan Taormino's Guide to Bondage for Couples, an educational film for couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 09:48:00" d="2020-04-18 10:02:00"><n>Cinema X Pigalle</n><t>S</t>    <k>The piano goes on as an old porn movie is projected just for their own private arousal. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 10:02:00" d="2020-04-18 10:29:00"><n>Spicing up the Marriage: Jillian Janson &amp; Chad White</n>    <k>When work and responsibility begin to pull a young couple apart, they find out working out becomes the ultimate foreplay. Romantic porn for couples by New Sensations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 10:29:00" d="2020-04-18 10:42:00"><n>Getting Cozy: Scarlet Red &amp; Ryan McLane</n>    <k>Recently single Marisa is unwillingly sent on a blind date by her best friend. After a few cocktails things get out of hand and Marisa wakes up in his bed? Due to an ice storm she cannot leave his appartment, and spends the weekend. A film from Wicked Pictures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 10:42:00" d="2020-04-18 11:05:00"><n>Breathless: Jillian Janson &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>I get so breathless, when you call my name, I've often wondered, do you feel the same? There's a chemistry, energy, a synchronicity. Two lovers having</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 11:05:00" d="2020-04-18 11:23:00"><n>Matchmaker: Satine Spark &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>Casey Collins is the Matchmaker. She can find anyone the perfect partner. The ultimate professional, Casey always puts her clients first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 11:23:00" d="2020-04-18 11:35:00"><n>Titty Titty Bang Bang</n><t>S</t>    <k>Miriam Prado is feeling like dancing. Breasts will jiggle and sparks will fly. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 11:35:00" d="2020-04-18 11:58:00"><n>After Forever: Britney Amber &amp; Chadalva</n>    <k>When Derrick plans a romantic weekend in his vacation house he soon finds out that his ex Penny had the same idea with her new partner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 11:58:00" d="2020-04-18 12:24:00"><n>My Cam Model</n>    <k>The Portuguese Jesus sees his dreams come true when his favorite hot webcam girl invites him to comeÂ. t her house. A naughty porn for women film, watch if you like big dick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 12:24:00" d="2020-04-18 12:35:00"><n>Obsessed</n>    <k>A scene from Xconfessions by Erika Lust. In this porn for women movie she films the 'sneaky' fantasies of her fans. Have you ever fantasized about a former lover?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 12:35:00" d="2020-04-18 13:31:00"><n>A Mothers Secret: Kasey Warner, Ingrid Mouth &amp; Jelena Jensen</n>    <k>When her student daughter comes home for winter break she brings home a mysterious brunette. The mom discovers her daughter is erotically involved</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 13:31:00" d="2020-04-18 13:53:00"><n>Everyday Turn-Ons: Touchy-Feeley</n>    <k>Alone in her bedroom, Nora hears her neighbours fucking next door - and it's seriously hot. Pressing her ear to the wall, she begins to touch herself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 13:53:00" d="2020-04-18 14:26:00"><n>True Intensions: Bentley &amp; Max Deeds</n>    <k>From director Anjali Kara comes True Intentions, romantic passion and beautiful sex. Watch the palpable chemistry between partners as they climax together onscreen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 14:26:00" d="2020-04-18 14:54:00"><n>My Love For you: Claudia Macc &amp; Nick Ross</n>    <k>Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la presents: Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 14:54:00" d="2020-04-18 15:01:00"><n>Slo Blo Mo Job</n><t>S</t>    <k>The longest, most intense blow job imaginable. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual confessions of her viewers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 15:01:00" d="2020-04-18 15:24:00"><n>All For You: Ella Hughes &amp; Max Deeds</n>    <k>When every thought is focused on one special person, thoughts quickly turn into fantasy. Memories of special moments become the seed of a sexual encounter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 15:24:00" d="2020-04-18 15:51:00"><n>The Passionate Three: Gina Gerson, Nick Gill &amp; Adam Black</n>    <k>Sinful trinity's enjoying a triad of erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 15:51:00" d="2020-04-18 16:19:00"><n>I Love You: Antonia Sainz &amp; Ricky</n>    <k>These beautiful desireable men and women are highly confident and have all the experience to bring you in a state of trance. A female friendly porn film by Desire media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 16:19:00" d="2020-04-18 16:44:00"><n>Love is in the Air: Jenna J Ross &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>When her fiance gets sucked into never-ending conversation at a friend's party, a woman lures him to the bedroom for a passionate sexual encounter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 16:44:00" d="2020-04-18 17:04:00"><n>Ouija</n>    <k>My girlfriend asked me to play with a Ouija board tonight. I?m dying to have some wild sex here on the floor. Let?s ask the ghosts what they think about it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 17:04:00" d="2020-04-18 17:22:00"><n>Sun stroke: Crowd control</n>    <k>When international DJ Cosmo needs a secluded escape, his boss? sun-kissed Spanish villa is the perfect location. Romantic outdoor pon for women by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 17:22:00" d="2020-04-18 17:33:00"><n>He Was First In My Ass</n><t>S</t>    <k>Tiffany gets inspired by an erotic book on anal sex, and decides that it's time for sexual liberty. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 17:33:00" d="2020-04-18 18:02:00"><n>Special Moments: Reading</n>    <k>Female friendly porn by Dusk TV's own label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. A pleasure to all the senses representing romantic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 18:02:00" d="2020-04-18 18:19:00"><n>From The First Moment: Alix Lynx &amp; Robby Echo</n>    <k>Kira (Alix Lynx) is about to marry her handsome movie star boyfriend James except he gets cold feet and leaves her at the wedding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 18:19:00" d="2020-04-18 18:44:00"><n>Brothers and Sisters 2: Ava Taylor &amp; Erik Everhard</n>    <k>Keisha Grey has the biggest crush on her step brother (Christian). She likes to play with herself in hoping that her step brother (Christian) walks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 18:44:00" d="2020-04-18 19:04:00"><n>Unwrap Me</n>    <k>Put the music on. And let yourself go wrapped in glossy vinyl bandages. Red and bright, that?s what excites me. Take them off quickly and fuck me</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 19:04:00" d="2020-04-18 19:26:00"><n>Quartet: The Quartet</n>    <k>Penelope boards a plane from London to Budapest, eager to perform with her three best friends from music academy. Reunited, the foursome soon remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 19:26:00" d="2020-04-18 19:43:00"><n>Memory Files of You</n><t>S</t>    <k>A deeply moving ode to loves lost, and irrevocable, unobtainable desires through Virtual Reality. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 19:43:00" d="2020-04-18 20:15:00"><n>Playful passion</n><t>L</t>    <k>A porn for women scene by former Playmate of the World, Zimra Geurts, for Dusk TV's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Jane von Detta has an exciting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 20:15:00" d="2020-04-18 20:46:00"><n>So Wet Beside Her: Vinna Reed &amp; Jennifer Jane</n>    <k>These girls love, lust, lick, becoming almost one in this sensual piece of erotica. Sinful Studio making art again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 20:46:00" d="2020-04-18 21:34:00"><n>Feminist &amp; Submissive</n><t>S</t>    <k>Can you be a feminist and submissive? A round table discussion accompanies a sensual BDSM scene. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 21:34:00" d="2020-04-18 21:52:00"><n>Love and Loss: Penny Pax &amp; Ramon Nomar</n>    <k>With more twists and turns than the German autobahn, Love and Loss follows the story of Lanie and Alex, an ex-cop involved in the shooting of Lanie's ex-lover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 21:52:00" d="2020-04-18 22:23:00"><n>Guide to Bondage For Couples: James Deen &amp; Adrianna Luna</n>    <k>If Fifty Shades of Grey intrigued and inspired you, then get ready for Tristan Taormino's Guide to Bondage for Couples, an educational film for couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 22:23:00" d="2020-04-18 22:53:00"><n>Remy Loves Girls: Sovereign Syre &amp; Remy LaCroix</n>    <k>Sweetheart proudly presents Performer of the year Remy La Croix. In the tradition of this title, Remy has chosen four of her favorite girls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 22:53:00" d="2020-04-18 23:25:00"><n>Suspicious Minds: Steve Q &amp; Katy Rose</n>    <k>Max Deeds Is A Private Detective Caught In A World Of Suspicious Minds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 23:25:00" d="2020-04-18 23:41:00"><n>Momentum 2: Voyeur</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Momentum Volume. 2 lives up to it's predecessor, taking us back from the beach to the lazy Australian suburbs. Director Michelle Flynn retains the retro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 23:41:00" d="2020-04-19 00:06:00"><n>Momentum 1: Before dinner</n>    <k>Australian film maker Michelle Flynn has the most distinctive style within the alternative porn genre. Her debut film Momentum is a cinematic intimacy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 00:06:00" d="2020-04-19 00:35:00"><n>Sweat On: Tina Kay &amp; Emilio Ardana</n>    <k>A Roma Amor sex film (suitable for watching together or alone) that proves that porn can really be BEAUTIFUL. Pure pleasure, beautiful, passionate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 00:35:00" d="2020-04-19 00:48:00"><n>Red Light: Lea Lexis &amp; Derrick Pierce</n>    <k>Red Light is like a waking dream set in the streets of Los Angeles. It's the story of a woman's transformation into her true self, and a wild chase</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 00:48:00" d="2020-04-19 01:07:00"><n u="Ages of Sex: Sex at">Ages of Sex: Sex at (40)</n>    <k>The Ages of Sex is a porn for women film by Thagson. 4 Well known directors will direct a short which represents a woman?s sexual reality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 01:07:00" d="2020-04-19 01:26:00"><n>Fit: Jasmine Aruba &amp; Sienna Day</n>    <k>You are running on the beach, bathed in the beautiful sunshine. You feel alive and energized ? what could be better? Get outside. Get active</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 01:26:00" d="2020-04-19 01:55:00"><n>Black Sweat</n>    <k>Sinful interracial couples enjoy colorful erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 01:55:00" d="2020-04-19 02:20:00" c="1"><n>The Possession Of Mrs Hyde: Seth Gamble, Kenna James &amp; Victoria Voxxx</n><t>F</t>    <k>The Possession of Mrs. Hyde is Axel Braun's first non-parody feature in 15 years and his most ambitious movie to date. Shot entirely in Black and White</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 02:20:00" d="2020-04-19 02:45:00"><n>Sweet Petite Girls: Timea &amp; Kristof Cale</n>    <k>These young beauties are starting to discover their sexuality, exploring their bodies and seek new limits. Director Roman Sluka captured these teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 02:45:00" d="2020-04-19 03:04:00"><n>Room 208: Sara May &amp; Juan Lucho</n>    <k>A romantic sex film by Lara Tinelli for Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 03:04:00" d="2020-04-19 03:24:00"><n>Tease: Ava Austen &amp; Luke Hardy</n>    <k>If according to Shakespeare, clothes make the man, then without doubt lingerie make the woman. Skyler is the gorgeous young owner and head designer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 03:24:00" d="2020-04-19 03:53:00"><n>Oasis: Anissa Kate &amp; Karlos Karrera</n>    <k>A secluded oasis with design furniture appears to be the perfect place to have passionate sex. A scene from an Intimate Encounters film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 03:53:00" d="2020-04-19 04:06:00"><n>The Couchsurfer</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: Making the most of your house guests has never been so sexy. In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 04:06:00" d="2020-04-19 04:24:00"><n>Close To The Bone: Anya Olsen &amp; Loren Minardi</n>    <k>Two immortal lovers are feeling the three-hundred-year-itch. As night falls the city becomes a playground for Jonus and Bryana, both seeking to quench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 04:24:00" d="2020-04-19 04:38:00"><n>Lust Unleashed 3: Dani Daniels &amp; Johnny Castle</n>    <k>Erotic passions are allowed to run rampant in this collection scenes where Lust is Unleashed. This movie was filmed in the highest quality, giving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 04:38:00" d="2020-04-19 05:03:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies: Liona &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Sexy beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A porn for women scene from Favorite Fantasies by Desire Media</k>  </p>
</a>
