<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="64" t="2020-05-10 04:38:47"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 05:11:00" d="2020-05-17 05:35:00"><n>I Am All Yours: Eveline Neil &amp; Marcel Lee</n>    <k>A romantic film by Dawn for Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 05:35:00" d="2020-05-17 05:47:00"><n>Off limits: Keira Nicole &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>Jesse is the quintessential bad boy. His band is the next big thing in Los Angeles and he is on a fast track to stardom. He then meets Caitlyn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 05:47:00" d="2020-05-17 05:57:00"><n>Magic Magnus</n><t>S</t>    <k>There's nothing like a man who dares to do a bit of dancing in order to spice things up, right? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 05:57:00" d="2020-05-17 06:22:00"><n>My Wife's First Girlfriend: Karlie Montana &amp; Abigail Mac</n>    <k>Jenna?s secret desires become unleashed when her husband catches her masturbating to lesbian porn. When Jimmy notices a growing attraction between</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 06:22:00" d="2020-05-17 06:45:00"><n>Gentle Loving 2: Lana &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also super passionate. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A romantic sex scene from Gentle Loving 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 06:45:00" d="2020-05-17 07:07:00"><n>Quartet: The Quartet</n>    <k>Penelope boards a plane from London to Budapest, eager to perform with her three best friends from music academy. Reunited, the foursome soon remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 07:07:00" d="2020-05-17 07:34:00"><n>Homecomming</n>    <k>This is quite obviously a joyous reunion as the couple fly into one another's arms the emotional impact of the scene. What is perhaps most notable about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 07:34:00" d="2020-05-17 07:50:00"><n>Going Bananas</n>    <k>Stand up and pick up a banana, read the instructions carefully, follow the rules. Wait for me lying on our big white bed, I?ll come</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 07:50:00" d="2020-05-17 08:13:00"><n>Momentum 2: Language of lust</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Momentum Volume. 2 lives up to it's predecessor, taking us back from the beach to the lazy Australian suburbs. Director Michelle Flynn retains the retro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 08:13:00" d="2020-05-17 08:24:00"><n>Girlfriends: Casey Calvert &amp; AJ Applegate</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Small town girl Jamie (Casey Calvert) has made the difficult decision to tell her parents that she is in a same sex relationship. Unfortunately her family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 08:24:00" d="2020-05-17 08:43:00"><n>I wish I was a lesbian</n><t>S</t>    <k>Maria's deepest fantasies come true when she finds herself being hosted by a hot and sweet lesbian couple. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 08:43:00" d="2020-05-17 09:05:00"><n>Housemates 2: Tyler Nixon &amp; Samatha Bentley</n>    <k>Artist James moves to the UK in search of his ex-girlfriend (Dalush) and finds himself sharing a house with four incredibly attractive women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 09:05:00" d="2020-05-17 09:28:00"><n>The Party</n>    <k>A breasty Spanish beauty can’t get any sleep because of the loud party next door. But when she sees her attractive neighbor her angry feelings fade away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 09:28:00" d="2020-05-17 10:00:00"><n>So Wet Beside Her: Tina Kay &amp; Timea Bella</n>    <k>These girls love, lust, lick, becoming almost one in this sensual piece of erotica. Sinful Studio making art again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 10:00:00" d="2020-05-17 10:25:00"><n>My Girlfriends Mother 7: Marcus London &amp; Dana deArmond</n>    <k>An ambitious young man, with a nave mother and a philandering father, returns home from college to discover that the girl next door has grown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 10:25:00" d="2020-05-17 10:58:00"><n>I Love My Hotwife: Romi Rain, Toni Ribas &amp; Otto Bauer</n>    <k>Four segments on the sexual fantasies of husbands and wives. A married couple hires a sexy male escort, Siri let?s her husband listen to her sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 10:58:00" d="2020-05-17 11:23:00"><n>Fading Memories: Francys Belle &amp; Alberto Blanco</n>    <k>From a collection of four scenes of women having vivid memories about former lovers, especially about the fantastic sex they used to have with their big dick guys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 11:23:00" d="2020-05-17 11:35:00"><n>Getting Cozy: Scarlet Red &amp; Ryan McLane</n>    <k>Recently single Marisa is unwillingly sent on a blind date by her best friend. After a few cocktails things get out of hand and Marisa wakes up in his bed? Due to an ice storm she cannot leave his appartment, and spends the weekend. A film from Wicked Pictures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 11:35:00" d="2020-05-17 12:00:00"><n>Sun stroke: The Final Song</n>    <k>When international DJ Cosmo needs a secluded escape, his boss? sun-kissed Spanish villa is the perfect location. Chloe soon becomes an intense distraction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 12:00:00" d="2020-05-17 12:12:00"><n>Madmen Porn</n><t>S</t>    <k>Have you ever wondered what Don Draper's cock might be like? Find out in this fan fiction inspired short! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 12:12:00" d="2020-05-17 12:42:00"><n>Hot Water: Francys Belle &amp; Steve Q</n>    <k>Licking, sucking, kissing, thrusting, touching, stroking, becoming one with each other in hot water. A sexual and visual delight by Studio Sinfull</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 12:42:00" d="2020-05-17 13:01:00"><n>Corporate Bonding: Tamara Grace &amp; Max Deeds</n>    <k>Good teamwork can lead to surprising situations. Rookie lawyer Leyla organises a team-building weekend by the beach for her and her firm of London lawyers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 13:01:00" d="2020-05-17 13:25:00"><n>Exploring Couples 2: Lila West &amp; Johnny</n>    <k>These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A romatic porn scene from Exploring Couples 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 13:25:00" d="2020-05-17 13:45:00"><n>Love Lust Longing: Allie Haze &amp; Jake Jace</n>    <k>Love Lust &amp; Longing takes place in a seemingly innocent Bed &amp; Breakfast. Rachel a prostitute who has set up shop in the master bedroom falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 13:45:00" d="2020-05-17 14:00:00"><n>Belle Dame Sans Merci</n>    <k>I met a lady in the meads, full beautiful - a faery's child, her hair was long, her foot was light, and her eyes were wild. Porn for women by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 14:00:00" d="2020-05-17 14:20:00"><n>Ball Control: Sienna Day &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>They say that football is a man’s world, but there’s one woman on this pitch with all the power. Physio Eva puts her massage skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 14:20:00" d="2020-05-17 14:46:00"><n>Once In A Blue Moon: Nikky Dream &amp; Lupro</n>    <k>In the blue light of the moon various couples love all parts of each other?s bodies on quiet spots in alleys, on rooftops and in fields. A Sinful production</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 14:46:00" d="2020-05-17 15:28:00"><n>Guide to Bondage For Couples: Skin Diamond &amp; Derrick Pierce</n>    <k>If Fifty Shades of Grey intrigued and inspired you, then get ready for Tristan Taormino's Guide to Bondage for Couples, an educational film for couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 15:28:00" d="2020-05-17 15:37:00"><n>Cybersex</n><t>S</t>    <k>Can cybersex be more stimulating than the real thing? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual confessions of her viewers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 15:37:00" d="2020-05-17 16:00:00"><n>Pure Sexual Attraction: Skylar Green &amp; Johnny Castle</n>    <k>Embark on an exciting journey of pure sexual attraction as five breathtaking girls are captured in five scenes that set the standard for high definition erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 16:00:00" d="2020-05-17 16:32:00"><n>Not to Innocent: Ally &amp; Max D</n>    <k>A sensuous sex video depicting real excitement and passion. A pleasure to all the senses representing realistic sex full of intimacy, laughter, chemistry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 16:32:00" d="2020-05-17 17:10:00"><n>Blind Date Swingers Club: Tina Kay &amp; Lutro</n>    <k>Everyone is getting their fuck on! Swinging couples going wild!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 17:10:00" d="2020-05-17 17:30:00"><n>Delilahs Top Tips: Victoria Summers &amp; Ryan Ryder</n><t>O</t>    <k>Delilah is the nation's naughtiest agony aunt dedicated to solving the nation's more. ntimate dilemmas. She whips two city workers into a frenzy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 17:30:00" d="2020-05-17 17:57:00"><n>True Intensions: Victoria Summers &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>From director Anjali Kara comes True Intentions, romantic passion and beautiful sex. Watch the palpable chemistry between partners as they climax together onscreen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 17:57:00" d="2020-05-17 18:04:00"><n>Momentum 1: A day at the beach</n>    <k>Australian film maker Michelle Flynn has the most distinctive style within the alternative porn genre. Her debut film Momentum is a cinematic intimacy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 18:04:00" d="2020-05-17 18:23:00"><n>Trouble X 2: Abigai Max &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>On his first day back in the dating game, Nick meets not one but TWO beautiful women. Olivia (Abigail Mac) is hot, sexy, and confident. Jenny (Cherie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 18:23:00" d="2020-05-17 18:55:00"><n>The Swinger Vol 5: Casey Calvert &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>You're neglecting your sexy rich wife because you're having a heated affair with a blonde nymphet who has just given you an ultimatum - leave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 18:55:00" d="2020-05-17 19:07:00"><n>A Talk Too Dirty</n><t>S</t>    <k>The power of dirty talk is a wonderful thing. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual confessions of her viewers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 19:07:00" d="2020-05-17 19:28:00"><n>The Temptation Of Eve: Remy LaCroix &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>Thrust into an uncomfortable circumstance, Eve (Remy LaCroix) finds herself living under the same roof as Brandon (the man she shared the most intense</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 19:28:00" d="2020-05-17 19:47:00"><n>Fit: Luke Hardy &amp; Jasmine Jae</n>    <k>You are running on the beach, bathed in the beautiful sunshine. You feel alive and energized ? what could be better? Get outside. Get active</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 19:47:00" d="2020-05-17 20:10:00"><n>Seven Days</n>    <k>This couple can have dramatic fights, but when they make up, it?s nothing but passion, lust and a bit of rough sex. An erotic sex scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 20:10:00" d="2020-05-17 20:36:00"><n>Home Coming: Mile High Hostess</n>    <k>Oh, home sweet home. These couples experience that there's no place like home to come back to, especially since orgasms are awaiting them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 20:36:00" d="2020-05-17 20:59:00"><n>Blind</n>    <k>Open your eyes wide for this one! Gorgeous Spanish beauty Apolonia Lapiedra and Pablo Ferrari get steamy in this short film with another classic scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 20:59:00" d="2020-05-17 21:22:00"><n>The Ski Instructor</n><t>S</t>    <k>Baby, it's cold outside. Who doesn't want to sleep with their ski instructor? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 21:22:00" d="2020-05-17 21:45:00"><n>Romeo &amp; Juliet: Anthony Rosano &amp; Andy San Dimas</n>    <k>Directed by Lee Roy Myers, this porn for women film by DreamZone Entertainment features tragic lovers trapped within a web of love, lies and loyalties</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 21:45:00" d="2020-05-17 22:10:00"><n>Facade: Cassidy Klein &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>Amber and her friend Lindsay are average college students?who happen to moonlight as sexy webcam models. This complicates things when they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 22:10:00" d="2020-05-17 22:31:00"><n>Housemates 2: Ava Dalush &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Romantic porn with pornstars: Ava Dalush &amp; Tyler Nixon. Artist James moves to the UK in search of his ex-girlfriend (Dalush) and finds himself sharing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 22:31:00" d="2020-05-17 22:43:00"><n>Some never awaken</n><t>S</t>    <k>Experience a sexual awakening through dance, movement, and passionate sex. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 22:43:00" d="2020-05-17 23:00:00"><n>Momentum 4: Car</n>    <k>The fourth final and most epic adult film. The Volume 4 stage is set in the Australian desert - an aesthetic overthrow from the previous films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 23:00:00" d="2020-05-17 23:28:00"><n>Afternoon Love: Bella Jordan &amp; Fernando</n>    <k>These real-life lovers are in a romantic and passionate relationship. Through the art of blowjob, pussy licking and loving intercourse, they reach their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 23:28:00" d="2020-05-17 23:52:00"><n>Sexual Bliss: Alexis &amp; Jayden</n>    <k>Four passionate couples in a Sinful XXX film by Roma Amor. Beautiful, Arty and very sexy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-17 23:52:00" d="2020-05-18 00:15:00"><n>While You're Sleeping</n><t>L</t>    <k>A man secretly watches porn when he thinks his wife is asleep. But she know?s what he is doing and shows him that he doesn?t have to watch tv when he wants good porn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 00:15:00" d="2020-05-18 00:35:00"><n>Secret Sex Society: Julia Roca &amp; Julia De Lucia</n>    <k>When colourful people meet and share their colourful fantasies. Starring the hot blooded Spanish beauty Julia Roca</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 00:35:00" d="2020-05-18 01:03:00"><n>I Will Share My Friend With You: Laveina Lux &amp; Sofi Goldfinger &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. Is a threesome your ulitimate sexual experience? A passionate erotic video by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 01:03:00" d="2020-05-18 01:25:00"><n>Hollywood Ending: Karlee Grey &amp; Derrick Pierce</n>    <k>Childhood lovers Rebecca and Tommy are finally getting the acting success they always wanted. But their love is put to the test when fame, fortune</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 01:25:00" d="2020-05-18 01:59:00"><n>Jungleicious: Aaron Rock &amp; Antonia Saintz</n>    <k>Together alone, in a dense forest, Stacy treats her date to a dinner with a view</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 01:59:00" d="2020-05-18 02:38:00"><n>Summer Lovers: Carla Coz</n>    <k>When it's summer the temperature rises, you wear less clothes and get aroused much easier. Is there anything hotter than having outdoor sex surrounded by nature? A scene from an Intimate Encounters film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 02:38:00" d="2020-05-18 03:09:00"><n>Guide to Bondage For Couples: James Deen &amp; Adrianna Luna</n>    <k>If Fifty Shades of Grey intrigued and inspired you, then get ready for Tristan Taormino's Guide to Bondage for Couples, an educational film for couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 03:09:00" d="2020-05-18 03:33:00"><n>Girlfriends: August Ames &amp; Lily Cade</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Small town girl Jamie (Casey Calvert) has made the difficult decision to tell her parents that she is in a same sex relationship. Unfortunately her family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 03:33:00" d="2020-05-18 03:41:00"><n>Carnival Hustlers</n><t>S</t>    <k>Two rival thieves take advantage of a Carnival to sneak around a Fifth Avenue inspired party, in disguise. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 03:41:00" d="2020-05-18 04:02:00"><n>Ball Control: Rebecca More &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>They say that football is a man’s world, but there’s one Milf on this pitch with all the power. Physio Eva puts her massage skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 04:02:00" d="2020-05-18 04:33:00"><n>Lovers Tryst: Victoria Summers &amp; Max Deeds</n>    <k>5 Erotic scenes featuring the genuine sexual pleasure that real couples achieved when they have truly learned their way around each other's sensitive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 04:33:00" d="2020-05-18 04:57:00"><n>Sweet Memories: Take Me Now</n>    <k>A hot romantic porn for women scene by Lara Tinelli for women who love rough sex with a guy who has a a big dick. A female friendly porn video by Dusk TV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 04:57:00" d="2020-05-18 05:13:00"><n>Red Light: Chanel Preston &amp; Damon Dice</n>    <k>Red Light is like a waking dream set in the streets of Los Angeles. It's the story of a woman's transformation into her true self, and a wild chase</k>  </p>
</a>
