<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="54" t="2020-05-13 04:38:32"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 05:17:00" d="2020-05-20 05:36:00"><n>Fit: Marc Rose &amp; Lucia Love</n>    <k>You are running on the beach, bathed in the beautiful sunshine. You feel alive and energized ? what could be better? Get outside. Get active</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 05:36:00" d="2020-05-20 06:00:00"><n>Erotic Massage Stories 3: Ella Milano &amp; Billy Hart</n><t>L</t>    <k>So relaxing as you watch five sensuous massage fantasies that will overwhelm you. Every delicate curve and touch has been captured</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 06:00:00" d="2020-05-20 06:25:00"><n>Very Beautiful Lips</n><t>L</t>    <k>Starting with a shower, performers Apolonia Lapiedra and Alberto Blanco waste no time in exploring their lust for one another. As they move</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 06:25:00" d="2020-05-20 06:42:00"><n>Momentum 1: Backseat lovers</n>    <k>Australian film maker Michelle Flynn has the most distinctive style within the alternative porn genre. Her debut film Momentum is a cinematic intimacy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 06:42:00" d="2020-05-20 07:03:00"><n>When it Comes to you: Karlie Montana &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>When It Comes To You is a captivating and scintillating story of a woman torn between two men who both profess great love. Directed by Stormy Daniels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 07:03:00" d="2020-05-20 07:31:00"><n>I'm Obsessed with Owen Gray</n><t>S</t>    <k>What would happen if your first time having sex on screen was with a pornstar you were totally obsessed with? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 07:31:00" d="2020-05-20 07:51:00"><n>Everyday Turn-Ons: Boyfriend's Clothes</n>    <k>When Mark's away for work, Shan misses everything about him; from the way he smells to the weight of his body on hers. Breathing in his scent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 07:51:00" d="2020-05-20 08:22:00"><n>Come Closer: Friday Night</n>    <k>A real life straight couple with real life sex. A romantic porn video by Dusk TV's own porn for women label</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 08:22:00" d="2020-05-20 08:54:00"><n>Girls Crush: Ildiko Sarang &amp; Simona Opavova</n>    <k>These girls love, lust, lick, becoming almost one in this sensual piece of erotica. Sinful Studio making art again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 08:54:00" d="2020-05-20 09:26:00"><n>My Daughters Boyfriend 11: Sara Luvv &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>Kelsey?s confused. Her daughter Sara and her best friend?s son Seth have grown up together just like brother and sister in the same house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 09:26:00" d="2020-05-20 09:51:00"><n>Brothers and Sisters 2: Ava Taylor &amp; Erik Everhard</n>    <k>Keisha Grey has the biggest crush on her step brother (Christian). She likes to play with herself in hoping that her step brother (Christian) walks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 09:51:00" d="2020-05-20 10:17:00"><n>First Summer Love 2: Radek Chigsantor &amp; Samantha Joons</n><t>L</t>    <k>The temperature is not the only thing that rises. Love is in the air. The passion these couples show you is as warm as the sun - it's their &quot;first summer love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 10:17:00" d="2020-05-20 10:31:00"><n>Red Light: Lea Lexis &amp; Derrick Pierce</n>    <k>Red Light is like a waking dream set in the streets of Los Angeles. It's the story of a woman's transformation into her true self, and a wild chase</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 10:31:00" d="2020-05-20 10:48:00"><n>Delilahs Top Tips: Emma Leigh &amp; Alexei Jackson</n><t>O</t>    <k>Delilah is the nation's naughtiest agony aunt dedicated to solving the nation's more. ntimate dilemmas. She whips two city workers into a frenzy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 10:48:00" d="2020-05-20 11:00:00"><n>Late night out</n>    <k>From XConfessions 3: When that little bit too much makes you uncontrollably horny! In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 11:00:00" d="2020-05-20 11:34:00"><n>The Artist: Max Deeds &amp; Eveline Dellai</n>    <k>Another beautiful production by Studio Sinful, containing lots of close-ups, artistic lighting and delicious performers. In The Artist a man is sensually</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 11:34:00" d="2020-05-20 11:55:00"><n>Inside: Sicilia &amp; Juan Lucho</n>    <k>Welcome to The Retreat: where curious minds come to play. Plug in and turn on to explore a virtual reality experience where you can be anyone, go anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 11:55:00" d="2020-05-20 12:20:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies: Liona &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Sexy beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A porn for women scene from Favorite Fantasies by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 12:20:00" d="2020-05-20 12:35:00"><n>Never Forgotten: Ella Nova &amp; Robby Echo</n>    <k>Robert can’t stop thinking about Elizabeth, his first love during the 1940’s. An argument teared the perfect couple apart and decades later Robert is still</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 12:35:00" d="2020-05-20 12:55:00"><n>Ouija</n>    <k>My girlfriend asked me to play with a Ouija board tonight. I?m dying to have some wild sex here on the floor. Let?s ask the ghosts what they think about it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 12:55:00" d="2020-05-20 13:15:00"><n>Quartet: Tenderley</n>    <k>Penelope boards a plane from London to Budapest, eager to perform with her three best friends from music academy. Reunited, the foursome soon remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 13:15:00" d="2020-05-20 13:46:00"><n>A Touch Of Lust: Dance D'amour</n>    <k>In this scene an intimate dance ends up in sultry sex on the kitchen table. A cinematic feast for the eyes by Roma Amor for SinfulXXX</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 13:46:00" d="2020-05-20 14:13:00"><n>Guide to Bondage For Couples: Samantha Ryan &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>If Fifty Shades of Grey intrigued and inspired you, then get ready for Tristan Taormino's Guide to Bondage for Couples, an educational film for couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 14:13:00" d="2020-05-20 14:25:00"><n>My moaning neighbor</n><t>S</t>    <k>Your neighbor is always moaning out of pleasure, and quite loudly. What would you do? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 14:25:00" d="2020-05-20 14:52:00"><n>Spicing up the Marriage: Jade Nile &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>When work and responsibility begin to pull a young couple apart, an inhibited woman transforms into an insatiable sex goddess when she allows her husband</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 14:52:00" d="2020-05-20 15:20:00"><n>Special Moments: Reading</n>    <k>Female friendly porn by Dusk TV's own label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. A pleasure to all the senses representing romantic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 15:20:00" d="2020-05-20 15:53:00"><n>A Touch Of Lust: Romantic Suprise</n>    <k>In this scene an intimate dance ends up in sultry sex on the kitchen table. A cinematic feast for the eyes by Roma Amor for SinfulXXX</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 15:53:00" d="2020-05-20 16:18:00"><n>Secret Sex Society: Cintia Shapiro &amp; Bel Gris</n>    <k>When colourful people meet and share their colourful fantasies. Starring the hot blooded Spanish beauty Julia Roca</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 16:18:00" d="2020-05-20 16:45:00"><n>Beauty Of Nature: Cayla Lions &amp; Nick Larsen</n><t>L</t>    <k>Wondering what it take to have fantastic sex that you will remmeber for the rest of your life? Watch and learn as Desire Media shows you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 16:45:00" d="2020-05-20 16:55:00"><n>Momentum 2: Gardenwork</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Momentum Volume. 2 lives up to it's predecessor, taking us back from the beach to the lazy Australian suburbs. Director Michelle Flynn retains the retro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 16:55:00" d="2020-05-20 17:20:00"><n>He Loves To Watch: Penny Pax &amp; Van Wyle</n>    <k>This couple has found a unique way to keep the spark in their marriage. Passionate sex and powerful orgasms for everybody! Cuckolding porn with focus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 17:20:00" d="2020-05-20 17:44:00"><n>Mother Daughter affair: Jodi Taylor &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>Eric has an interesting dilemma. He?s going with a smoking hot woman who has an over-sexed erotic devilish daughter, he just can?t resist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 17:44:00" d="2020-05-20 18:09:00"><n>Sweet but Psycho</n><t>S</t>    <k>Four of the hottest and most popular performers on the scene create a hilarious and erotic film. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 18:09:00" d="2020-05-20 18:32:00"><n>Afternoon Delight: Julia Ann &amp; Billy Hart</n>    <k>Attractive people that have sex on gorgeous locations. A scene from an Intimate Encounters film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 18:32:00" d="2020-05-20 18:53:00"><n>Close To The Bone: Cherry Kiss &amp; Matt Bird</n>    <k>Two immortal lovers are feeling the three-hundred-year-itch. As night falls the city becomes a playground for Jonus and Bryana, both seeking to quench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 18:53:00" d="2020-05-20 19:20:00"><n>Tenderness: Ria Sunn &amp; Jayden Cox</n>    <k>A erotic massage scene by Dusk TV's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Romantic porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 19:20:00" d="2020-05-20 19:50:00"><n>Desire For Sex: Diner D'amour</n>    <k>A beautiful film by Roma Amor for SinfulXXX. In this scene a couple enjoys a delicious dinner. But when it's time for desert they themselves take place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 19:50:00" d="2020-05-20 20:08:00"><n>Arousal</n>    <k>If you ever wondered why everybody wants to make threesomes with these two? Super sexy porn for women by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 20:08:00" d="2020-05-20 20:19:00"><n>Obsessed</n>    <k>A scene from Xconfessions by Erika Lust. In this porn for women movie she films the 'sneaky' fantasies of her fans. Have you ever fantasized about a former lover?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 20:19:00" d="2020-05-20 20:44:00"><n>Our Sexual Secrets 2: Dolce Vita &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A porn for women scene from Our Sexual Secrets 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 20:44:00" d="2020-05-20 21:08:00"><n>Hollywood Ending: Aaliyah Love &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>Childhood lovers Rebecca and Tommy are finally getting the acting success they always wanted. But their love is put to the test when fame, fortune</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 21:08:00" d="2020-05-20 21:29:00"><n>Delilahs Top Tips: Marc Rose &amp; Sicilia</n>    <k>Delilah is the nation's naughtiest agony aunt dedicated to solving the nation's more. ntimate dilemmas. A naughty female friendly porn scene by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 21:29:00" d="2020-05-20 21:50:00"><n>Dacrifilia</n><t>S</t>    <k>An artist brings a man to tears to fulfil her fetish - dacryphilia. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 21:50:00" d="2020-05-20 22:15:00"><n>Momentum 1: Before dinner</n>    <k>Australian film maker Michelle Flynn has the most distinctive style within the alternative porn genre. Her debut film Momentum is a cinematic intimacy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 22:15:00" d="2020-05-20 22:43:00"><n>Special Moments: The Second Date</n>    <k>What happens after the second date? Find out in this new romantic sex scene by AlexanFilm for Dusk TV's own female friendly porn label: Ooh la la</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 22:43:00" d="2020-05-20 23:12:00"><n>Desire For Sex: Piano Sonata</n>    <k>A beautiful film by Roma Amor for SinfulXXX. In this scene a couple enjoys a delicious dinner. But when it's time for desert they themselves take place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 23:12:00" d="2020-05-21 00:39:00"><n>Liberte Sexuelle</n>    <k>Een kijkje in het seksuele leven van ruimdenkende mensen laat zien hoe divers we allemaal zijn, gefilmd door Ovidie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 00:39:00" d="2020-05-21 02:57:00"><n>Dirty Secerts</n>    <k>Dirty Secrets is the sultry sexy tale of two worlds colliding when an inhibited divorcee Lana (Brenda James) rents out her home to an adult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 02:57:00" d="2020-05-21 03:20:00"><n>Tenderness: Alexis Crystal &amp; George Lee</n>    <k>A romantic sex scene by Dusk TV's own female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Romantic porn films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 03:20:00" d="2020-05-21 03:41:00"><n>Tease: Tyler Nixon &amp; Stella Cox</n>    <k>If according to Shakespeare, clothes make the man, then without doubt lingerie make the woman. Naught porn for women by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 03:41:00" d="2020-05-21 04:06:00"><n>Anal Lovers: Esparansa &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A romantic sex scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 04:06:00" d="2020-05-21 04:21:00"><n>Red Light: Kleio Valentien &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>Red Light is like a waking dream set in the streets of Los Angeles. It's the story of a woman's transformation into her true self, and a wild chase</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 04:21:00" d="2020-05-21 04:52:00"><n>So Wet Beside Her: Vinna Reed &amp; Jennifer Jane</n>    <k>These girls love, lust, lick, becoming almost one in this sensual piece of erotica. Sinful Studio making art again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 04:52:00" d="2020-05-21 05:22:00"><n>Tales from the Heart: Carter Cruise &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>Love is in the air. specially on your Anniversary. A trip down memory lane is just the spark Michelle and Andy need to reignite the lustful feelings</k>  </p>
</a>
