<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="65" t="2019-07-21 01:28:33"><p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 05:17:00" d="2019-07-27 05:42:00"><n>Inside: Frida Sante &amp; Alberta Blanco</n>    <k>Welcome to The Retreat: where curious minds come to play. Plug in and turn on to explore a virtual reality experience where you can be anyone, go anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 05:42:00" d="2019-07-27 06:04:00"><n u="The Submission of Emma Marx: Penny Pax &amp; Richie Calhoun">The Submission of Emma Marx: Penny Pax &amp; Richie Calhoun (2)</n>    <k>By all accounts, Emma Marx is a beautiful, confident, well-adjusted woman. Unfortunately when it comes to love and romance, she has found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 06:04:00" d="2019-07-27 06:15:00"><n>Car Sex Generation</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 06:15:00" d="2019-07-27 06:34:00"><n>Corporate Bonding: Amber Nevada &amp; Amarna Miller</n>    <k>Good teamwork can lead to surprising situations. Rookie lawyer Leyla organises a team-building weekend by the beach for her and her firm of London lawyers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 06:34:00" d="2019-07-27 06:59:00"><n>Chef</n>    <k>After lessons in slicing, spicing, dicing, and sautéing, the class concludes with glasses of sparkling wine. They quickly make it clear that they're hungry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 06:59:00" d="2019-07-27 07:18:00"><n>A Girls' Getaway: Dan Lucia Love &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>Girls weekend out! The girls used to go away together each year, but it has already been 5 years. Amy organized another girly weekend after a desperate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 07:18:00" d="2019-07-27 07:45:00"><n>My Cam Model</n>    <k>The Portuguese Jesus sees his dreams come true when his favorite hot webcamgirl invites him to come?at her house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 07:45:00" d="2019-07-27 08:16:00"><n>Private Spa: Carlo Minaldi &amp; Rebecca Volpetti</n>    <k>This beautiful couple enjoys every bit of their private spa. We like it that hot! A delightful video by studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 08:16:00" d="2019-07-27 08:41:00"><n>Riot Girls: Jasmine Jae, Jess West &amp; Satine Spark</n>    <k>The Riot Girls are Jenna, Bett and Karma. An all-girl rock band touring the world and loving the Rock 'N Roll lifestyle. They are best friends and nothing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 08:41:00" d="2019-07-27 08:59:00"><n>When it Comes to you: Karlie Montana &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>When It Comes To You is a captivating and scintillating story of a woman torn between two men who both profess great love. Directed by Stormy Daniels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 08:59:00" d="2019-07-27 09:22:00"><n>Potter In Love</n>    <k>Let's get dirty with clay! A Verso Cinema film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 09:22:00" d="2019-07-27 09:55:00"><n>Forbidden Affairs: My Wife's Sister 2: Veruca James &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Two sisters are in love with the same man. The older sister lets her career get in the way, and lets him go. Years later, when he returns married</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 09:55:00" d="2019-07-27 10:20:00"><n>Afternoon Love: Angel Piaf &amp; Max D</n>    <k>What are you going to do when all of a suddon both of you are at home and have nothing to do? Exactly, enjoy each other and make your time together worthwhile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 10:20:00" d="2019-07-27 10:39:00"><n u="Ages of Sex: Sex at">Ages of Sex: Sex at (40)</n>    <k>The Ages of Sex is a Thagson Digital Media project. 4 well known directors will direct a short which represents a woman?s sexual reality in her 30s, 40s and 50s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 10:39:00" d="2019-07-27 10:47:00"><n>Hold me so tight it hurts</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 10:47:00" d="2019-07-27 11:08:00"><n>Erotic Massage Stories 3: Bruce Venture &amp; Lizz Tayler</n><t>L</t>    <k>So relaxing as you watch five sensuous massage fantasies that will overwhelm you. Every delicate curve and touch has been captured</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 11:08:00" d="2019-07-27 11:20:00"><n>Romance Bullshit</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 11:20:00" d="2019-07-27 11:49:00"><n>A Touch of Nature: Jenny Simons &amp; Dennis Reed</n>    <k>You can taste the love in the air. The heat of the sun guides hands and fingers to touch your deepest soul. Ecstasy, passion and sexual arousal, ?A Touch Of Nature? from Daring! brings it all</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 11:49:00" d="2019-07-27 12:15:00"><n>Sexology: Mira, Choky Ice &amp; Tifanny Naylor</n>    <k>For her graduation project, sexology student Tess researches how the female orgasm works. What do women really want in bed? Scene from a film by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 12:15:00" d="2019-07-27 12:28:00"><n>Some never awaken</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 12:28:00" d="2019-07-27 12:39:00"><n>Girlfriends: Casey Calvert &amp; AJ Applegate</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Small town girl Jamie (Casey Calvert) has made the difficult decision to tell her parents that she is in a same sex relationship. Unfortunately her family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 12:39:00" d="2019-07-27 13:02:00"><n>Tenderness: Alexis Crystal &amp; George Lee</n>    <k>A new scene by Roma Woodcock for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 13:02:00" d="2019-07-27 13:12:00"><n>Cybersex</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 13:12:00" d="2019-07-27 13:46:00"><n>Dani Loves Girls: Dani Daniels &amp; Natasha Nice</n><t>L</t>    <k>Sweetheart Video presents the beautiful Dani Daniels in her own movie. Dani showcases her sensuality and voracious appetite in four scenes;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 13:46:00" d="2019-07-27 14:05:00"><n>Fit: Marc Rose &amp; Lucia Love</n>    <k>You are running on the beach, bathed in the beautiful sunshine. You feel alive and energized ? what could be better? Get outside. Get active</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 14:05:00" d="2019-07-27 14:32:00"><n>Soft And Sweet 2: Ornella Morgen &amp; Nic Vargas</n><t>L</t>    <k>Did you ever notice the softness of your lovers skin, the sweet taste when you move your tongue over her well formed sensual body? These young couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 14:32:00" d="2019-07-27 14:55:00"><n>Come Closer: Summer Love</n>    <k>What are you going to do when all of a suddon both of you are at home and have nothing to do? Exactly, enjoy each other and make your time together worthwhile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 14:55:00" d="2019-07-27 15:07:00"><n>My moaning neighbor</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 15:07:00" d="2019-07-27 15:26:00"><n>Only women can: Denisa Heaven &amp; Abigaile</n>    <k>Porna award-nominated director Kendo portrays the world of latex with a beautiful, filmic dark side and incredibly attractive women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 15:26:00" d="2019-07-27 15:54:00"><n>Sexy And She Knows It: Lutro, Dorian Del Isla &amp; Anna Polina</n>    <k>Sinful trinity's enjoying a triad of erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 15:54:00" d="2019-07-27 16:20:00"><n>My Love For you: Chrissy Fox &amp; Nic Vargas</n>    <k>A new scene by Roma Woodcock for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 16:20:00" d="2019-07-27 16:50:00"><n>Oasis: Anissa Kate &amp; Karlos Karrera</n>    <k>A secluded oasis with design furniture appears to be the perfect place to have passionate sex. A scene from an Intimate Encounters film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 16:50:00" d="2019-07-27 17:09:00"><n>Heavy Contact</n>    <k>That feeling when you have a lot of contact with someone and the connection gets even heavier when you meet in real life? Yes, that's passion to the max</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 17:09:00" d="2019-07-27 17:35:00"><n>Sexology: Tiffany Naylor &amp; Seth Strong</n>    <k>For her graduation project, sexology student Tess researches how the female orgasm works. What do women really want in bed? Scene from a film by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 17:35:00" d="2019-07-27 17:51:00"><n>An Appointment With My Master</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 17:51:00" d="2019-07-27 18:22:00"><n>Not to Innocent: Ally &amp; Max D</n>    <k>A new scene by Dawn for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 18:22:00" d="2019-07-27 18:41:00"><n>Camera Angle: Ivy Labelle &amp; Roman Nomar</n>    <k>Fiction and reality seem to blend when Hollywood actor Peter gets a concussion. His visions of heart-racing, sweat inducing sex seem very real though.</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 18:41:00" d="2019-07-27 19:08:00"><n>All In Your Head: Casey Calvert &amp; Bill Bailey</n><t>O</t>    <k>All In Your Head transcends expectations with its striking imagery and brilliant creative direction. There is something for everyone's perverted minds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 19:08:00" d="2019-07-27 19:31:00"><n>Blind</n>    <k>Open your eyes wide for this one! Gorgeous Spanish beauty Apolonia Lapiedra and Pablo Ferrari get steamy in this short film with another classic scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 19:31:00" d="2019-07-27 19:53:00"><n>Positions: Fourth</n>    <k>While finding inspiration at a dancer?s retreat, the ballet dancer Florence soon realises she?s not the only one who could do with practising some new positions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 19:53:00" d="2019-07-27 20:04:00"><n>Come Fly With Me</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 20:04:00" d="2019-07-27 20:39:00"><n>I Am All Yours: Daphne Klyde &amp; Nick Ross</n>    <k>A new scene by Dawn for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 20:39:00" d="2019-07-27 21:14:00"><n>Wet!: Shower Me With Love</n><t>L</t>    <k>Sinful couples enjoy having seks when it pours? What's on your bucket list? A SinfulXXX film by Roma Amor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 21:14:00" d="2019-07-27 21:32:00"><n>Dacrifilia</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 21:32:00" d="2019-07-27 21:47:00"><n>Girlfriends: Casey Calvert &amp; Scarlet Red</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Small town girl Jamie (Casey Calvert) has made the difficult decision to tell her parents that she is in a same sex relationship. Unfortunately her family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 21:47:00" d="2019-07-27 22:08:00"><n>The Temptation Of Eve: India Summer &amp; Xander Corvus</n>    <k>Thrust into an uncomfortable circumstance, Eve (Remy LaCroix) finds herself living under the same roof as Brandon (the man she shared the most intense</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 22:08:00" d="2019-07-27 22:34:00"><n>Intimate Moments: Leona &amp; Peter</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A scene from Intimate Moments by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 22:34:00" d="2019-07-27 22:57:00"><n>Question</n>    <k>Thomas stands on the street. When Ferrera joins him we soon learn what he was anticipating. He drops to one knee, holds up a shiny little box, and after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 22:57:00" d="2019-07-27 23:12:00"><n>Never Forgotten: Casey Calvert &amp; Robby Echo</n>    <k>Robert can’t stop thinking about Elizabeth, his first love during the 1940’s. An argument teared the perfect couple apart and decades later Robert is still</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 23:12:00" d="2019-07-27 23:34:00"><n>He Loves To Watch: Nina Elle &amp; Bill Bailey</n>    <k>This couple has found a unique way to keep the spark in their marriage. Passionate sex and powerful orgasms for everybody!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 23:34:00" d="2019-07-27 23:58:00"><n>Exploring Couples 2: Lila West &amp; Johnny</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A scene from Exploring Couples 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-27 23:58:00" d="2019-07-28 00:24:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies: Liona &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A scene from Favorite Fantasies by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-28 00:24:00" d="2019-07-28 00:48:00"><n>Love Me Forever: Lily Cat &amp; Vega</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A scene from Love Me Forever by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-28 00:48:00" d="2019-07-28 01:08:00"><n>Exploring Couples: Sheri Vi &amp; Nicolas</n>    <k>When the moment is right, it's time to take your romantic interests to the next level of passion by exploring the options. See what these couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-28 01:08:00" d="2019-07-28 01:30:00"><n>Gentle Loving 2: Lana &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A scene from Gentle Loving 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-28 01:30:00" d="2019-07-28 01:55:00"><n>Gentle Loving: Katarina &amp; Vega</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A scene from Gentle Loving by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-28 01:55:00" d="2019-07-28 02:20:00"><n>Gentle Loving 2: Tequila &amp; Vincent Vega</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A scene from Gentle Loving 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-28 02:20:00" d="2019-07-28 02:45:00"><n>Making Ends Meet: Gia Paige &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>A suburbian family is in destress over money, but sex seems to really heal the wounds. Scorching hot sex and sharp comedy blend perfectly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-28 02:45:00" d="2019-07-28 02:57:00"><n>Do You Find My Feet Suckable?</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-28 02:57:00" d="2019-07-28 03:16:00"><n>The Guesthouse: Julia Roca &amp; Sicilia</n>    <k>Nestled in the Spanish countryside, there?s a Guesthouse where visitors enjoy more than just the sunshine on their bodies. Come alone, come with a friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-28 03:16:00" d="2019-07-28 03:48:00"><n>Girls Crush: Constanze Berankova &amp; Nicole Dandova</n>    <k>These girls love, lust, lick, becoming almost one in this sensual piece of erotica. Sinful Studio making art again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-28 03:48:00" d="2019-07-28 03:59:00"><n>The fate of love: Ash Hollywood &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>After a heart transplant, Caroline has problems getting her life back on track. Then she falls for John, but does fate really have love in store for them? Film by Wicked</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-28 03:59:00" d="2019-07-28 04:22:00"><n>A Sensual Touch: Hanna Shaw &amp; Ben Kelly</n>    <k>Intimate lovers escape the stresses of every day life and spend some relaxing time together. Couples pamper each other with erotic massage and intense sexual pleasure. From Daring! Pure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-28 04:22:00" d="2019-07-28 04:45:00"><n>Her Desire: The Couch</n>    <k>A new scene by AlexanFilm for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-28 04:45:00" d="2019-07-28 05:05:00"><n>Close To The Bone: Anya Olsen &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Two immortal lovers are feeling the three-hundred-year-itch. As night falls the city becomes a playground for Jonus and Bryana, both seeking to quench</k>  </p>
</a>
