<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="62" t="2019-08-11 01:42:49"><p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 05:14:00" d="2019-08-17 06:03:00"><n>Lesbian Surrender: Nikita Bellucci &amp; Sovereign Syre</n>    <k>Watch as tattooed angel Ela Darling realizes her taboo fantasies, how French stunner Nikita Bellucci barely speaks English and how blond bombshell Aaliyah</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 06:03:00" d="2019-08-17 06:13:00"><n>Dear Brother In Law</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 06:13:00" d="2019-08-17 06:31:00"><n>Delilahs Top Tips: Jess West &amp; Danielle Ashlea Maye</n><t>O</t>    <k>Delilah is the nation's naughtiest agony aunt dedicated to solving the nation's more. ntimate dilemmas. She whips two city workers into a frenzy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 06:31:00" d="2019-08-17 06:51:00"><n>Our Time</n>    <k>Forget the concerns of the outside world. Occupations, responsibilities, social commitments ? those are for another day, another time, some other place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 06:51:00" d="2019-08-17 07:19:00"><n>Picture Perfect: Ryan Ryder &amp; Anny Aurora</n>    <k>Daring presents Picture Perfect. In an age of social media, FaceTime and mobile communication, couples now have the ultimate sex toy at their disposal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 07:19:00" d="2019-08-17 07:44:00"><n>Sweet Memories: Take Me Now</n>    <k>4 small erotic stories by Lara Tinelli for Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 07:44:00" d="2019-08-17 08:05:00"><n>Passion Noir: Lexi &amp; Jason</n>    <k>Four passionate couples in a Sinful XXX film by Roma Amor. Beautiful, Arty and very sexy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 08:05:00" d="2019-08-17 08:26:00"><n>Tease: Tyler Nixon &amp; Stella Cox</n>    <k>If according to Shakespeare, clothes make the man, then without doubt lingerie make the woman. Skyler is the gorgeous young owner and head designer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 08:26:00" d="2019-08-17 08:47:00"><n>If You Only Knew: Logan Pierce &amp; Allie Haze</n>    <k>For many years, the loyal and hardworking Kellie has been Mark?s assistant, and in love with him. Mark, however, is oblivious to this</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 08:47:00" d="2019-08-17 09:07:00"><n>Ouija</n>    <k>My girlfriend asked me to play with a Ouija board tonight. I?m dying to have some wild sex here on the floor. Let?s ask the ghosts what they think about it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 09:07:00" d="2019-08-17 09:44:00"><n>Mother Daughter Affair 2: Tomi Taylor &amp; Steven St. Croix</n>    <k>Chloe just can?t forgive her mom for leaving her dad for a young hot guy, but a visit to the sexy older psychiatrist seems to help in many ways</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 09:44:00" d="2019-08-17 10:07:00"><n>Room 208: Penelope Cum &amp; Salva Da Silva</n>    <k>A new scene by Award Winning director Lara Tinelli for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 10:07:00" d="2019-08-17 10:41:00"><n>Guide To Kinky Sex For Couples: Lyla Storm &amp; Danny Wylde</n>    <k>Kink expert Tristan Taormino gives how-to's to discuss, explore and finally act out your wildest fantasies, with your partner! 4 Hot couples demonstrate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 10:41:00" d="2019-08-17 10:56:00"><n>Boat Buddies With Benefits</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 10:56:00" d="2019-08-17 11:13:00"><n>Lust Unleashed 3: Billy Hart &amp; Dani Jensen</n>    <k>Erotic passions are allowed to run rampant in this collection scenes where Lust is Unleashed. This movie was filmed in the highest quality, giving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 11:13:00" d="2019-08-17 11:32:00"><n>Cabaret Desire: Sofia Prada, Saskia Condal &amp; Toni Fontana</n>    <k>Welcome to nightclub Cabaret Desire ? indulge yourself with poets and their erotic tales filled with passion and temptation. A film by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 11:32:00" d="2019-08-17 11:59:00"><n>Office Love Affairs: Alexis Crystal &amp; Dante White</n>    <k>At four different workplaces there are four attractive ladies that are bored with work. They find a little distraction playing with themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 11:59:00" d="2019-08-17 12:21:00"><n>Positions: Fourth</n>    <k>While finding inspiration at a dancer?s retreat, the ballet dancer Florence soon realises she?s not the only one who could do with practising some new positions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 12:21:00" d="2019-08-17 12:35:00"><n>Public Submission</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 12:35:00" d="2019-08-17 12:57:00"><n>Camera Angle: Casey Calvert &amp; Jay Smooth</n>    <k>Fiction and reality seem to blend when Hollywood actor Peter gets a concussion. His visions of heart-racing, sweat inducing sex seem very real though.</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 12:57:00" d="2019-08-17 13:25:00"><n>Her Desire: Shy Guy</n>    <k>A new scene by AlexanFilm for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 13:25:00" d="2019-08-17 13:42:00"><n>Cabaret Desire: Liandra Dahl and Matisse</n>    <k>Welcome to nightclub Cabaret Desire ? indulge yourself with poets and their erotic tales filled with passion and temptation. A film by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 13:42:00" d="2019-08-17 14:04:00"><n>Jessie Loves Girls: Jodi Taylor &amp; Jessie Andrews</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sweetheart Video's celebrated showcase series presents Jessie Andrews, in four unique scenes with four of her favorite girls. Beautiful, sexy and intriguing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 14:04:00" d="2019-08-17 14:24:00"><n>Pleasure Professionals 2: Samantha Bentley &amp; Alexei Jackson</n>    <k>A high quality couple's film from Joybear. Every summer Mrs ERC bolts to the countryside to relax and unwind. A secluded hotel provides the perfect getaway</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 14:24:00" d="2019-08-17 14:44:00"><n>Exploring Couples: Sheri Vi &amp; Nicolas</n>    <k>When the moment is right, it's time to take your romantic interests to the next level of passion by exploring the options. See what these couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 14:44:00" d="2019-08-17 15:10:00"><n>Tenderness: Ria Sunn &amp; Jayden Cox</n>    <k>A new scene by Roma Woodcock for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 15:10:00" d="2019-08-17 15:23:00"><n>The Ultimate Kink</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 15:23:00" d="2019-08-17 15:43:00"><n>Kendo's Brunettes: Anina Silk &amp; Zack</n>    <k>The Brunette. The classy, sexy alternative to the blonde. The lust filled mystery contained within thefemale character in each scene unfolds in intricate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 15:43:00" d="2019-08-17 16:10:00"><n>Once In A Blue Moon: Nicole Love &amp; Pavlos</n>    <k>In the blue light of the moon various couples love all parts of each other?s bodies on quiet spots in alleys, on rooftops and in fields. A Sinful production</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 16:10:00" d="2019-08-17 16:36:00"><n>My Cam Model</n>    <k>The Portuguese Jesus sees his dreams come true when his favorite hot webcamgirl invites him to come?at her house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 16:36:00" d="2019-08-17 17:06:00"><n>Hair Down There: Nadine Sage &amp; Bruce Venture</n><t>L</t>    <k>She's got hair down there, and yes, we love that natural look! Let Mia Malkova, Nadine Sage, Tracey Sweet, and Anastasia Morna show you how their naturally</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 17:06:00" d="2019-08-17 17:31:00"><n>Very Beautiful Lips</n><t>L</t>    <k>Tarting with a shower scene, performers Apolonia Lapiedra and Alberto Blanco waste no time in exploring their lust for one another</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 17:31:00" d="2019-08-17 17:50:00"><n>HouseMates: Chessie Kay &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>After a painful break up Jess flees to the city and is thrown into a world where hiding away is not an option. Her new housemates Ollie and Saskia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 17:50:00" d="2019-08-17 18:04:00"><n>La Reine Des Culottes</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 18:04:00" d="2019-08-17 18:25:00"><n>Special Moments: The Shower</n><t>L</t>    <k>A new scene by AlexanFilm for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 18:25:00" d="2019-08-17 18:41:00"><n>It's Complicated: Gracie Glam &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>Shauna (Gracie Glam) has been having casual sex with her handsome friend Will, biding her time until she can finally make a move on her long time crush Brandon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 18:41:00" d="2019-08-17 19:05:00"><n>A Lesbian Romance: Shyla Jennings &amp; Mia Malkova</n>    <k>When feelings develop after a one-night-stand, Kenna puts her heart on the line and fights for the woman she wants. Penny?s secret attraction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 19:05:00" d="2019-08-17 19:16:00"><n>Hit Me With Your Best Shot</n>    <k>Every time he grabs it he feels so strong, as if his virility depended on it. It starts to annoy me when he?s been shooting at cans for an</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 19:16:00" d="2019-08-17 19:36:00"><n>Fit: Marc Rose &amp; Lucia Love</n>    <k>You are running on the beach, bathed in the beautiful sunshine. You feel alive and energized ? what could be better? Get outside. Get active</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 19:36:00" d="2019-08-17 19:48:00"><n>Car Sex Generation</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 19:48:00" d="2019-08-17 20:08:00"><n>Afternoon Love: Lexi Dona &amp; Thomas Reed</n>    <k>What are you going to do when all of a suddon both of you are at home and have nothing to do? Exactly, enjoy each other and make your time together worthwhile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 20:08:00" d="2019-08-17 20:45:00"><n>Light my Fire: Dominica Phoenix &amp; Kristof Cale</n>    <k>This beautiful couple relishes each others body with sensual hand and mouth massages by candlelight. Another visual and erotic jewel by Studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 20:45:00" d="2019-08-17 20:57:00"><n>Dominate Me</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 20:57:00" d="2019-08-17 21:09:00"><n>Love and Loss: Brendon Miller &amp; Maddy O Reilly</n>    <k>With more twists and turns than the German autobahn, Love and Loss follows the story of Lanie and Alex, an ex-cop involved in the shooting of Lanie's ex-lover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 21:09:00" d="2019-08-17 21:38:00"><n u="The Submission Of Emma Marx: Penny Pax &amp; Richie Calhoun">The Submission Of Emma Marx: Penny Pax &amp; Richie Calhoun (5)</n>    <k>When a new contract is drafted up defining the parameters of their BDSM relationship, Emma realizes that Mr. Frederick is anything but predictable</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 21:38:00" d="2019-08-17 22:06:00"><n>I Will Share My Friend With You: Laveina Lux &amp; Sofi Goldfinger &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A scene from I Will Share My Friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 22:06:00" d="2019-08-17 22:26:00"><n>Second Chances: Allie Haze &amp; Chad White</n>    <k>During her Freshman year of college, Madison thought she'd met the love of her life when she starting dating handsome football player, Josh. This didn't work out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 22:26:00" d="2019-08-17 22:41:00"><n>Never Forgotten: Ella Nova &amp; Robby Echo</n>    <k>Robert can’t stop thinking about Elizabeth, his first love during the 1940’s. An argument teared the perfect couple apart and decades later Robert is still</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 22:41:00" d="2019-08-17 23:01:00"><n>Tender Love And Care: Lola &amp; Tommy Deer</n>    <k>Attractive young people having sultry, passionate sex, and beautifully filmed to boot! A scene from a film by Yourope Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 23:01:00" d="2019-08-17 23:31:00"><n>Escort No.5: Tina Kay, Wicky Angel &amp; Steve Q</n>    <k>Sinful trinity's enjoying a triad of erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 23:31:00" d="2019-08-17 23:54:00"><n>Exploring Couples 2: Lila West &amp; Johnny</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A scene from Exploring Couples 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-17 23:54:00" d="2019-08-18 00:19:00"><n>Cum Inside Me: Rebeccca &amp; Andrew</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A scene from Cum Inside Me by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 00:19:00" d="2019-08-18 00:42:00"><n>Gentle Loving 2: Lana &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A scene from Gentle Loving 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 00:42:00" d="2019-08-18 01:12:00"><n>Confessions Of A Sinner: Dorian Del Isla &amp; Simony Diamond</n>    <k>This beautiful couple relishes each others body with sensual hand and mouth massages by candlelight. Another visual and erotic jewel by Studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 01:12:00" d="2019-08-18 01:42:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies: Dolce Vita &amp; Vega</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A scene from Favorite Fantasies by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 01:42:00" d="2019-08-18 02:12:00"><n>Our Sexual Secrets: Katarina &amp; Vega</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A scene from Our Sexual Secrets by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 02:12:00" d="2019-08-18 02:34:00"><n>Camera Angle: Ryan Keely &amp; Ryan Mclane</n>    <k>Fiction and reality seem to blend when Hollywood actor Peter gets a concussion. His visions of heart-racing, sweat inducing sex seem very real though.</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 02:34:00" d="2019-08-18 03:21:00"><n>Feminist &amp; Submissive</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 03:21:00" d="2019-08-18 03:47:00"><n>Riot Girls: Ava Dalush &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>The Riot Girls are Jenna, Bett and Karma. An all-girl rock band touring the world and loving the Rock 'N Roll lifestyle. They are best friends and nothing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 03:47:00" d="2019-08-18 04:13:00"><n>Raw: Fanni &amp; Ivan</n>    <k>Beautiful images of sexual tenderness in its pure but raw way. Close-ups of gorgeous toned bodies and horny sweat. One of Sinful?s most beautiful productions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 04:13:00" d="2019-08-18 04:45:00"><n>The Escort 2: Lilly Love, Dana DeArmond &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>When a beautiful young woman enters the escorting profession, she's put off by her first client. But under the tutelage of a smart and capable madam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 04:45:00" d="2019-08-18 05:09:00"><n>After Midnight: Denisa Heaven &amp; Wein Lewis</n>    <k>The most beautiful and hottest meetings take place as the world slowly grows quiet after midnight. Scene from a film by Daring</k>  </p>
</a>
