<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="61" t="2020-05-16 05:02:02"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 05:16:00" d="2020-05-23 05:43:00"><n>Friends And Lovers: Angela White &amp; Donny Rock</n>    <k>Caroline and Matt have been best friends since college. Through break-ups they've been there for each other. But they have yet to find true love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 05:43:00" d="2020-05-23 05:53:00"><n>Make some time for us</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: Samantha Bentley and Franck Franco make a gorgeous couple in this confession about sex when you're a parent. In XConfessions, people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 05:53:00" d="2020-05-23 06:25:00"><n>All In Your Head: Keira Nicole &amp; Ryan McClane</n><t>O</t>    <k>All In Your Head transcends expectations with its striking imagery and brilliant creative direction. There is something for everyone's perverted minds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 06:25:00" d="2020-05-23 06:39:00"><n>Romeo &amp; Juliet: Chanel Preston &amp; Marie Rios</n>    <k>Romeo &amp; Juliet, maybe the most well known romantic couple. A sexy and spicy version of the traditional narrative. A porn for women flic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 06:39:00" d="2020-05-23 06:58:00"><n>Sun stroke: Stephanie</n>    <k>When international DJ Cosmo needs a secluded escape, his boss? sun-kissed Spanish villa is the perfect location. The unannounced arrival of Chloe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 06:58:00" d="2020-05-23 07:21:00"><n>Pure Sexual Attraction: Emily Grey &amp; Dylan Snow</n>    <k>Embark on an exciting journey of pure sexual attraction as five breathtaking girls are captured in five scenes that set the standard for high definition erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 07:21:00" d="2020-05-23 07:38:00"><n>Thr3e</n>    <k>The threesome has always been a recurring fantasy in the imaginary of erotica. Sharing the pleasure with two other people, discovering their bodies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 07:38:00" d="2020-05-23 07:57:00"><n>Sex in white: Amirah Adara &amp; Adrian Yuyu</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us with her female friendly porn production: ?Sex In White?, where sexual encounters take place in a pure and white scenery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 07:57:00" d="2020-05-23 08:23:00" c="1"><n>The Possession Of Mrs Hyde: Seth Gamble, Kenna James &amp; Victoria Voxxx</n><t>F</t>    <k>The Possession of Mrs. Hyde is Axel Braun's first non-parody feature in 15 years and his most ambitious movie to date. Shot entirely in Black and White</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 08:23:00" d="2020-05-23 08:39:00"><n>Hello Pool Boy</n>    <k>From XConfessions 3: “I clean your pool. Easy going, good hearted, always horny.” In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 08:39:00" d="2020-05-23 09:00:00"><n>Tease: Amber Nevada &amp; Billy King</n>    <k>If according to Shakespeare, clothes make the man, then without doubt lingerie make the woman. Skyler is the gorgeous young owner and head designer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 09:00:00" d="2020-05-23 09:25:00"><n>Her Desire: Ladies Night</n>    <k>Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion. A pleasure to all the senses representing realistic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 09:25:00" d="2020-05-23 09:55:00"><n>Blind Date Swingers Club: Ricky Raskal &amp; Nikky Dream</n>    <k>Everyone is getting their fuck on! Swinging couples going wild!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 09:55:00" d="2020-05-23 10:28:00"><n>Mother Daughter Affair 2: Sara Luvv &amp; James Deen</n>    <k>Chloe just can?t forgive her mom for leaving her dad for a young hot guy, but a visit to the sexy older psychiatrist seems to help in many ways</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 10:28:00" d="2020-05-23 11:08:00"><n>Restraint: Persley Hart &amp; Ryan Mclane</n>    <k>Hoping to invigorate their predictable sex life, married couple, Logan and Ashlyn, dabble in beginner BDSM sex with the help of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 11:08:00" d="2020-05-23 11:29:00"><n>Anticipation: Sensi &amp; Lea Guerlin</n>    <k>Anticipation is the latest cinematic adult movie directed by DiSanto for Daring Sex. Romantic porn for women with a focus on female pleasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 11:29:00" d="2020-05-23 11:53:00"><n>After Forever: Alexa Grace &amp; Derrick Pierce</n>    <k>When Derrick plans a romantic weekend in his vacation house he soon finds out that his ex Penny had the same idea with her new partner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 11:53:00" d="2020-05-23 12:11:00"><n>Matchmaker: Ava Dalush &amp; Jess West</n>    <k>Casey Collins is the Matchmaker. She can find anyone the perfect partner. The ultimate professional, Casey always puts her clients first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 12:11:00" d="2020-05-23 12:27:00"><n>I found your mother on tinder</n><t>S</t>    <k>The legendary Mrs. Robinson brought to life by the most modern of dating apps. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 12:27:00" d="2020-05-23 12:54:00"><n>Raw: Fanni &amp; Ivan</n>    <k>Beautiful images of sexual tenderness in its pure but raw way. Close-ups of gorgeous toned bodies and horny sweat. One of Sinful?s most beautiful productions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 12:54:00" d="2020-05-23 13:15:00"><n>Close To The Bone: Anya Olsen &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Two immortal lovers are feeling the three-hundred-year-itch. As night falls the city becomes a playground for Jonus and Bryana, both seeking to quench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 13:15:00" d="2020-05-23 13:38:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies 2: Miranda &amp; Joe T</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A female friendly porn scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 13:38:00" d="2020-05-23 13:53:00"><n>Never Forgotten: Ella Nova &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>Robert can’t stop thinking about Elizabeth, his first love during the 1940’s. An argument teared the perfect couple apart and decades later Robert is still</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 13:53:00" d="2020-05-23 14:12:00"><n>Stair Love</n>    <k>Yet another cinematic Spanish female friendly porn scene from Verso Cinema featuring the super popular and multiply awarded Carolina Abril. Don't miss this encounter!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 14:12:00" d="2020-05-23 14:32:00"><n>Ball Control: Victoria Summers &amp; Ryan Ryder</n>    <k>They say that football is a man’s world, but there’s one woman on this pitch with all the power. Watch pornstar Ryan Ryder en Milf Victoria Summers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 14:32:00" d="2020-05-23 15:04:00"><n>The Passionate Three: Evelyn Dellai, Jean, Angel Piaff</n>    <k>Sinful trinity's enjoying a triad of erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 15:04:00" d="2020-05-23 15:38:00"><n>Guide To Kinky Sex For Couples: Lyla Storm &amp; Danny Wylde</n>    <k>Kink expert Tristan Taormino gives how-to's to discuss, explore and finally act out your wildest fantasies, with your partner! 4 Hot couples demonstrate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 15:38:00" d="2020-05-23 15:49:00"><n>Car Sex Generation</n><t>S</t>    <k>Juan Lucho and Julia Roca show exactly why sex in a car is so exciting. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 15:49:00" d="2020-05-23 16:05:00"><n>Fantastico</n>    <k>They chat, they laugh, they joke, confide, and reveal, and in the process they move ever closer to physical union. The tender kisses and warm smiles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 16:05:00" d="2020-05-23 16:28:00"><n>Her Desire: The Couch</n>    <k>A great scene by AlexanFilm for Dusk's Porn for women label: Ooh la la. Explicit erotic films for women and couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 16:28:00" d="2020-05-23 16:58:00"><n>Surreal Encounters: Aaron Rock &amp; Stacy Cruz</n>    <k>All Space &amp;Time Is Lost When Mysterious Lovers Meet. First there seems to be someone behind the mirror, then he's gone. Stacy looks closer and steps into an erotic dream</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 16:58:00" d="2020-05-23 17:22:00"><n>Close To The Bone: Azazie Skymm &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Two immortal lovers are feeling the three-hundred-year-itch. As night falls the city becomes a playground for Jonus and Bryana, both seeking to quench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 17:22:00" d="2020-05-23 17:56:00"><n>Beauty Of Nature: Alex Black &amp; Nick Ross</n><t>L</t>    <k>Wondering what it takes to have fantastic sex that you will remmeber for the rest of your life? Watch and learn as Desire Media show you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 17:56:00" d="2020-05-23 18:15:00"><n>Girls Sex Tricks: Ana Marco &amp; Fenix Santos</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us on her first porn for women film as director for Thagson with a vibrant story which will take place in the streets of Barcelona</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 18:15:00" d="2020-05-23 18:30:00"><n>From Beyond: Aaliyah Love &amp; Jay Smooth</n><t>L</t>    <k>Romantic porn scene with a young couple fully in love. Let the beautiful Aaliyah Love &amp; Jay Smooth show you how they take care of eachothers needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 18:30:00" d="2020-05-23 18:56:00"><n>My Girlfriends Mother 8: Karla Kush &amp; Daniel Hunter</n>    <k>When she gets caught in a compromising position with her professor, Sandi escapes with her boyfriend to her artistic free-spirit mother, Moon-Rose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 18:56:00" d="2020-05-23 19:44:00"><n>Feminist &amp; Submissive</n><t>S</t>    <k>Can you be a feminist and submissive? A round table discussion accompanies a sensual BDSM scene. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 19:44:00" d="2020-05-23 20:13:00"><n>Infidelity: Lily Cade &amp; Tilly McReese</n>    <k>They wanted a normal life in suburbia! Gina and Annie are a long term lesbian couple with a 2008 vintage marriage, a cute house, good jobs? and a sex life that is a thing of the past. But what happens when a young lesbian couple moves in next door? Lesbian porn for women by Filly film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 20:13:00" d="2020-05-23 20:36:00"><n>Exposure: Touch Me</n>    <k>In a world where couples would rather play with their phones than each other, one woman uses her technology skills for good, nudging distracted lovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 20:36:00" d="2020-05-23 20:54:00"><n>Naked Desire</n>    <k>An exciting porn for women video by Dusk TV's own female friendly porn label. Watch this beautiful young woman having sex with her tattooed, big dick boyfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 20:54:00" d="2020-05-23 21:29:00"><n>Private Spa: Carlo Minaldi &amp; Rebecca Volpetti</n>    <k>This beautiful couple enjoys every bit of their private spa. We like it that hot! A delightful video by studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 21:29:00" d="2020-05-23 21:54:00"><n>Two Girls Sofa</n>    <k>Two girls on a sofa, what else is there to do on a Sunday when you have nothing planned? These girls decide to explore each other's bodies? A lesbian porn for women scene byVerso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 21:54:00" d="2020-05-23 22:07:00"><n>Chicazo</n><t>S</t>    <k>Luna Corazón will expose herself entirely for this show - only to dress herself again once it's all over. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 22:07:00" d="2020-05-23 22:27:00"><n>Romeo &amp; Juliet: India Summer &amp; Tom Byron</n>    <k>Directed by Lee Roy Myers, this female friendly porn film by DreamZone Entertainment features tragic lovers trapped within a web of love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 22:27:00" d="2020-05-23 22:51:00"><n>He Loves To Watch: Aaliyah Love &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>This couple has found a unique way to keep the spark in their marriage. Passionate sex and powerful orgasms for everybody! Cuckold porn for women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 22:51:00" d="2020-05-23 23:12:00"><n>Corporate Bonding: Hannah Shaw &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>Good teamwork can lead to surprising situations. Rookie lawyer Leyla organises a team-building weekend by the beach for her and her firm of London lawyers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 23:12:00" d="2020-05-23 23:23:00"><n>Momentum 2: Gardenwork</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Momentum Volume. 2 lives up to it's predecessor, taking us back from the beach to the lazy Australian suburbs. Director Michelle Flynn retains the retro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 23:23:00" d="2020-05-23 23:45:00"><n>Housemates 3: Decoupled</n>    <k>Synopsis not available</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 23:45:00" d="2020-05-24 00:20:00"><n>Paparazzi: Tiffany Doll &amp; Angelo Godshack</n>    <k>Brandi Love, Paparazzi, a Scandalous Red Carpet Tale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 00:20:00" d="2020-05-24 00:52:00"><n>Everyday Turn-Ons: Restricted Behaviour</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sometimes we don?t choose our fetishes; they find us in the night. Gavin wakes up to find Mary has stolen the covers and is cocooned inside the sheets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 00:52:00" d="2020-05-24 01:15:00"><n>Girls Fight Club</n><t>S</t>    <k>What's the first rule of girls fight club? Only women allowed. An homage to David Fincher’s classic dystopian film, this time with lesbians</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 01:15:00" d="2020-05-24 01:51:00"><n>Exploring Couples 2: Sofi Goldfinger &amp; Vincent Vega</n>    <k>These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A beautiful porn for women scene from Exploring Couples 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 01:51:00" d="2020-05-24 02:01:00"><n>Off limits: Krissy Lynn &amp; Small Hands</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 02:01:00" d="2020-05-24 02:33:00"><n>Home Coming: Home for Diner</n>    <k>Oh, home sweet home. These couples experience that there's no place like home to come back to, especially since orgasms are awaiting them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 02:33:00" d="2020-05-24 03:10:00"><n u="The Submission Of Emma Marx: Riley Reid &amp; Van Wylde">The Submission Of Emma Marx: Riley Reid &amp; Van Wylde (2)</n>    <k>When a new contract is drafted up defining the parameters of their BDSM relationship, Emma realizes that Mr. Frederick is anything but predictable</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 03:10:00" d="2020-05-24 03:19:00"><n>Diet Of Sex: The Beach</n>    <k>Diet of Sex is an experience, is a love story between Ágata and Marc told through sex. A culinary, sexual adventure through a variety of flavours</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 03:19:00" d="2020-05-24 03:34:00"><n>Win A Date With Sofia Blake: Charlotte Cross &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>A-list Hollywood actress Sofia Blake (Olivia Austin) is having the worst day of her life and the paparazzi have made sure to plaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 03:34:00" d="2020-05-24 03:48:00"><n>Latex Sessions</n><t>S</t>    <k>Parker Marx and Amarna Miller feature in this steamy homage to latex and the psychology of fetishism. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 03:48:00" d="2020-05-24 04:10:00"><n>The Invitation: Lola Gatsby &amp; Dean Van Damme</n>    <k>Jane and Tom's car unexpectedly breaks down late at night they find themselves knocking on a stranger?s door only to be presented with an invitation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 04:10:00" d="2020-05-24 04:36:00"><n>Picture Perfect: Freddy Fox &amp; Taylor Sands</n>    <k>In an age of social media, FaceTime and mobile communication, couples now have the ultimate sextoy at their disposal. They can tease each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 04:36:00" d="2020-05-24 05:04:00"><n>Come Closer: Sunday Morning</n>    <k>Having a lazy sunday? This couple is enjoying each other and making their time together worthwhile. A real life couple with real life sex. A romantic sex film by Dusk</k>  </p>
</a>
