<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="65" t="2019-08-13 02:38:39"><p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 05:09:00" d="2019-08-18 05:28:00"><n>Room 208: Pamela Sanchez &amp; Sasha blonnde</n>    <k>A new scene by Award Winning director Lara Tinelli for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 05:28:00" d="2019-08-18 05:48:00"><n>Secret Sex Society: Julia Roca &amp; Julia De Lucia</n>    <k>When colourful people meet and share their colourful fantasies. Starring the hot blooded Spanish beauty Julia Roca</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 05:48:00" d="2019-08-18 06:25:00"><n>Almost Relatives: Scarlet Red &amp; Steven St. Croix</n>    <k>Things become heated between a bride and the best man when their explosive attraction to one another makes them question their loyalty to the groom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 06:25:00" d="2019-08-18 06:35:00"><n>Garden of Eden</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 06:35:00" d="2019-08-18 06:57:00"><n>Positions: Fifth</n>    <k>While finding inspiration at a dancer?s retreat, the ballet dancer Florence soon realises she?s not the only one who could do with practising some new positions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 06:57:00" d="2019-08-18 07:18:00"><n>In Motion</n>    <k>A man enters a dimly lit room. He presses &quot;play&quot; on a reel-to-reel tape recorder and starts dancing until his dancepartner walks into the room</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 07:18:00" d="2019-08-18 07:45:00"><n>Wellness: Iwa &amp; Johnny</n>    <k>Massages, manicures and 100% 'me time'. Ultra relaxing and satisfying! Scene from the film Wellness, by Daring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 07:45:00" d="2019-08-18 08:08:00"><n>While You're Sleeping</n><t>L</t>    <k>A man secretly watches porn when he thinks his wife is asleep. But she know?s what he is doing and shows him that he doesn?t have to watch tv when he wants good porn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 08:08:00" d="2019-08-18 08:37:00"><n>Sexual Bliss: Keira &amp; Chriss</n>    <k>Four passionate couples in a Sinful XXX film by Roma Amor. Beautiful, Arty and very sexy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 08:37:00" d="2019-08-18 09:03:00"><n>Sexology: Mira, Choky Ice &amp; Tifanny Naylor</n>    <k>For her graduation project, sexology student Tess researches how the female orgasm works. What do women really want in bed? Scene from a film by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 09:03:00" d="2019-08-18 09:20:00"><n>When it Comes to you: Hope Howell &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>When It Comes To You is a captivating and scintillating story of a woman torn between two men who both profess great love. Directed by Stormy Daniels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 09:20:00" d="2019-08-18 09:42:00"><n>Blind</n>    <k>Open your eyes wide for this one! Gorgeous Spanish beauty Apolonia Lapiedra and Pablo Ferrari get steamy in this short film with another classic scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 09:42:00" d="2019-08-18 10:06:00"><n>Mother Daughter affair: Jodi Taylor &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>Eric has an interesting dilemma. He?s going with a smoking hot woman who has an over-sexed erotic devilish daughter, he just can?t resist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 10:06:00" d="2019-08-18 10:29:00"><n>Sweet Memories: Together</n>    <k>4 small erotic stories by Lara Tinelli for Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 10:29:00" d="2019-08-18 10:56:00"><n>Guide to Bondage For Couples: Samantha Ryan &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>If Fifty Shades of Grey intrigued and inspired you, then get ready for Tristan Taormino's Guide to Bondage for Couples, an educational film for couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 10:56:00" d="2019-08-18 11:09:00"><n>Some never awaken</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 11:09:00" d="2019-08-18 11:23:00"><n>Lust Unleashed 3: Dani Daniels &amp; Johnny Castle</n>    <k>Erotic passions are allowed to run rampant in this collection scenes where Lust is Unleashed. This movie was filmed in the highest quality, giving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 11:23:00" d="2019-08-18 11:34:00"><n>Romance Bullshit</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 11:34:00" d="2019-08-18 11:59:00"><n>Fading Memories: Francys Belle &amp; Alberto Blanco</n>    <k>A collection of four scenes of women having vivid memories about former lovers, especially about the fantastic sex they used to have with their handsome guys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 11:59:00" d="2019-08-18 12:17:00"><n>Delilahs Top Tips: Lynna Nilsson &amp; Clarke Kent</n><t>O</t>    <k>Delilah is the nation's naughtiest agony aunt dedicated to solving the nation's more. ntimate dilemmas. She whips two city workers into a frenzy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 12:17:00" d="2019-08-18 12:29:00"><n>Ibiza Splash Crush</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 12:29:00" d="2019-08-18 12:58:00"><n>Friends And Lovers: Chanel Preston &amp; Bill Bailey</n>    <k>Caroline and Matt (Aaliyah Love and Tommy Pistol) have been best friends since college. Through break-ups they've been there for each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 12:58:00" d="2019-08-18 13:30:00"><n>Special Moments: The Apple</n>    <k>A new scene by AlexanFilm for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 13:30:00" d="2019-08-18 13:45:00"><n>An Appointment With My Master</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 13:45:00" d="2019-08-18 14:24:00"><n>A love triangle 2: Maddy O' Reilly &amp; Erik Everhard</n>    <k>It?s time for yoga class! Sensuous Dana DeArmond leads the star studded class flaunting her sexual appetite for both men and women. A Mile High film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 14:24:00" d="2019-08-18 14:46:00"><n>Close To The Bone: Cherry Kiss &amp; Matt Bird</n>    <k>Two immortal lovers are feeling the three-hundred-year-itch. As night falls the city becomes a playground for Jonus and Bryana, both seeking to quench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 14:46:00" d="2019-08-18 15:17:00"><n>True Intensions: Stella Cox &amp; Max Deeds</n>    <k>Een zeer gewaardeerde film van Erotikara. Natuurlijk mooi en intiem spelen de koppels met elkaar vol overgave. Liefde, lust, passie en fantastische orgasmes!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 15:17:00" d="2019-08-18 15:40:00"><n>Sweet Memories: Lovers</n>    <k>4 small erotic stories by Lara Tinelli for Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 15:40:00" d="2019-08-18 15:54:00"><n>Fräulein O</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 15:54:00" d="2019-08-18 16:30:00"><n>In the limelight 2: Caprice &amp; Marry Queen</n><t>L</t>    <k>Daring! Pure in the limelight shows you a spectacular selection of nine of our best scenes. The most beautiful girls surpass your wildest dreams to fulfill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 16:30:00" d="2019-08-18 17:00:00"><n>Desire For Sex: Piano Sonata</n>    <k>A beautiful film by Roma Amor for SinfulXXX. In this scene a couple enjoys a delicious dinner. But when it's time for desert they themselves take place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 17:00:00" d="2019-08-18 17:28:00"><n>My Love For you: Vinna Reed &amp; Lutro</n>    <k>A new scene by Roma Woodcock for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 17:28:00" d="2019-08-18 18:04:00"><n>Restraint: Ashlyn Molloy &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>Hoping to invigorate their predictable sex life, married couple, Logan and Ashlyn, dabble in beginner BDSM sex with the help of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 18:04:00" d="2019-08-18 18:22:00"><n>Arousal</n>    <k>If you ever wondered why everybody wants to make threesomes with these two? A Verso Cinema film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 18:22:00" d="2019-08-18 18:40:00"><n>Close To The Bone: Anya Olsen &amp; Loren Minardi</n>    <k>Two immortal lovers are feeling the three-hundred-year-itch. As night falls the city becomes a playground for Jonus and Bryana, both seeking to quench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 18:40:00" d="2019-08-18 18:54:00"><n>Latex Sessions</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 18:54:00" d="2019-08-18 19:20:00"><n>Afternoon Love: Angel Piaf &amp; Max D</n>    <k>What are you going to do when all of a suddon both of you are at home and have nothing to do? Exactly, enjoy each other and make your time together worthwhile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 19:20:00" d="2019-08-18 19:39:00"><n>If You Only Knew: Penny Pax &amp; Aaron Wilcox</n>    <k>For many years, the loyal and hardworking Kellie has been Mark?s assistant, and in love with him. Mark, however, is oblivious to this</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 19:39:00" d="2019-08-18 20:11:00"><n>I Love My Hotwife: Romi Rain, Toni Ribas &amp; Otto Bauer</n>    <k>Four segments on the sexual fantasies of husbands and wives. A married couple hires a sexy male escort, Siri let?s her husband listen to her sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 20:11:00" d="2019-08-18 20:34:00"><n>Potter In Love</n>    <k>Let's get dirty with clay! A Verso Cinema film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 20:34:00" d="2019-08-18 20:53:00"><n>Corporate Bonding: Amber Nevada &amp; Amarna Miller</n>    <k>Good teamwork can lead to surprising situations. Rookie lawyer Leyla organises a team-building weekend by the beach for her and her firm of London lawyers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 20:53:00" d="2019-08-18 21:02:00"><n>Cybersex</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 21:02:00" d="2019-08-18 21:31:00"><n>Special Moments: Reading</n>    <k>A new scene by AlexanFilm for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 21:31:00" d="2019-08-18 22:06:00"><n>The Artist: Max Deeds, Anna Rose &amp; Cherry Kiss</n>    <k>Another beautiful production by Studio Sinful, containing lots of close-ups, artistic lighting and delicious performers. In The Artist a man is sensually</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 22:06:00" d="2019-08-18 22:15:00"><n>Can Vampires Smell My Period?</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 22:15:00" d="2019-08-18 22:27:00"><n>Win A Date With Sofia Blake: Olivia Austin &amp; Ryan Mclean</n>    <k>A-list Hollywood actress Sofia Blake (Olivia Austin) is having the worst day of her life and the paparazzi have made sure to plaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 22:27:00" d="2019-08-18 22:48:00"><n>Dirty Secerts: Odette Delacroix &amp; Zoey Holloway</n>    <k>Dirty Secrets is the sultry sexy tale of two worlds colliding when an inhibited divorcee Lana (Brenda James) rents out her home to an adult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 22:48:00" d="2019-08-18 23:07:00"><n>Soft And Sweet: Victoria Blaze &amp; Thomas</n>    <k>Attractive young people having sultry, passionate sex, and beautifully filmed to boot! A scene from a film by Yourope Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 23:07:00" d="2019-08-18 23:33:00"><n>Give Me More</n>    <k>Alone in the serenity and privacy of her bedroom Sophie indulges her appetite, caressing her body, touching and teasing. When Thomas unexpectedly appears</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 23:33:00" d="2019-08-18 23:48:00"><n>Win A Date With Sofia Blake: Charlotte Cross &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>A-list Hollywood actress Sofia Blake (Olivia Austin) is having the worst day of her life and the paparazzi have made sure to plaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-18 23:48:00" d="2019-08-19 00:10:00"><n>Hollywood Ending: Karlee Grey &amp; Derrick Pierce</n>    <k>Childhood lovers Rebecca and Tommy are finally getting the acting success they always wanted. But their love is put to the test when fame, fortune</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-19 00:10:00" d="2019-08-19 00:26:00"><n>Cabaret Desire: Didac Duran and Samia Duarte</n>    <k>Welcome to nightclub Cabaret Desire ? indulge yourself with poets and their erotic tales filled with passion and temptation. A film by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-19 00:26:00" d="2019-08-19 00:45:00"><n>Quartet: The Teacher</n>    <k>Penelope boards a plane from London to Budapest, eager to perform with her three best friends from music academy. Reunited, the foursome soon remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-19 00:45:00" d="2019-08-19 01:21:00"><n>Private Spa: Renato &amp; Simony Diamond</n>    <k>This beautiful couple enjoys every bit of their private spa. We like it that hot! A delightful video by studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-19 01:21:00" d="2019-08-19 01:45:00"><n>Love Blossoms: Heather Starlet &amp; Ryan Mclane</n>    <k>Jane?s life is perfect, until a car accident causes her to lose her memory. Gardener Brian is the only one who is able to understand her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-19 01:45:00" d="2019-08-19 02:09:00"><n>Milf Affairs: Luke Hotrod &amp; Candi Coxx</n>    <k>Five erotic vignettes featuring hot wives and their sexual adventures with younger guys. Female director Anjali Kara delivers a cinematic adult movie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-19 02:09:00" d="2019-08-19 02:28:00"><n>4 Passionate Women: My Friend Ana</n>    <k>A new scene by Award Winning director Lara Tinelli for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-19 02:28:00" d="2019-08-19 02:48:00"><n>Fit: Alexei Jackson &amp; Amarna Miller</n>    <k>You are running on the beach, bathed in the beautiful sunshine. You feel alive and energized ? what could be better? Get outside. Get active</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-19 02:48:00" d="2019-08-19 03:17:00"><n>Brave Hearts: Abigaile Johnson &amp; George Uhl</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sarah (Faye Regan), the most famous Romance Novelist in the world, is writing the final book in her series of best-selling love stories. Admired by women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-19 03:17:00" d="2019-08-19 03:29:00"><n>My moaning neighbor</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-19 03:29:00" d="2019-08-19 03:49:00"><n>Pleasure Professionals 2: Lexi Lowe &amp; Ryan Ryder</n>    <k>A high quality couple's film from Joybear. Every summer Mrs ERC bolts to the countryside to relax and unwind. A secluded hotel provides the perfect getaway</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-19 03:49:00" d="2019-08-19 04:07:00"><n>True Love</n>    <k>The new day has dawned, breakfast is on the table, and two lovers are enjoying a leisurely meal. The loving looks, the gestures, feeding each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-19 04:07:00" d="2019-08-19 04:28:00"><n>Bedtime Stories II: Gettin Cute &amp; Jaydee</n>    <k>Breathtaking moments of sweltering passion and arousal, like your first love. Sentiments that will keep you focused on the screen for hours. Wonderful film by Daring! Pure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-19 04:28:00" d="2019-08-19 04:54:00"><n>Sensuous Seduction: Sweet</n>    <k>A new scene by Award Winning director Lara Tinelli for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-19 04:54:00" d="2019-08-19 05:27:00"><n>Home Coming: Burning Desire</n>    <k>Oh, home sweet home. These couples experience that there's no place like home to come back to, especially since orgasms are awaiting them</k>  </p>
</a>
