<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="67" t="2020-04-13 04:35:21"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 05:23:00" d="2020-04-20 05:42:00"><n>Girls Sex Tricks: Marta La Croft &amp; Xavi Tralla</n><t>L</t>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us on her first film as director for Thagson with a vibrant female friendly porn story which will take place in the streets of Barcelona</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 05:42:00" d="2020-04-20 05:56:00"><n>Art of Spanking</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: after reading The Art of Spanking by renowned erotic artist Milo Manara, a man begins to obsess about this realm of pleasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 05:56:00" d="2020-04-20 06:18:00"><n>Sex is for Lovers: Denise &amp; Renato</n>    <k>Indulge yourself in female friendly porn with an emphasis on passion, lovers, and true romance. Their inspiration is not found in anonymous encounters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 06:18:00" d="2020-04-20 06:31:00"><n>It's Complicated: Brooke &amp; Small Hands</n>    <k>Shauna (Gracie Glam) has been having casual sex with her handsome friend Will, biding her time until she can finally make a move on her long time crush Brandon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 06:31:00" d="2020-04-20 06:59:00"><n>Coming Out: Candy Sweet &amp; Sandra</n>    <k>In uncertainty about their sexual orientation these young women finally no longer conceal their sexual preference, and revealing their gender identity completely</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 06:59:00" d="2020-04-20 07:18:00"><n>Fit: Marc Rose &amp; Lucia Love</n>    <k>You are running on the beach, bathed in the beautiful sunshine. You feel alive and energized ? what could be better? Get outside. Get active</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 07:18:00" d="2020-04-20 07:28:00"><n>Garden of Eden</n>    <k>From XConfessions 3: Ever thought about a fresh fuck in the middle of nature, covered in the fruit of mother natures creation? In XConfessions, people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 07:28:00" d="2020-04-20 07:45:00"><n>When it Comes to you: Hope Howell &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>When It Comes To You is a captivating and scintillating story of a woman torn between two men who both profess great love. Directed by Stormy Daniels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 07:45:00" d="2020-04-20 08:16:00"><n>Come Closer: Friday Night</n>    <k>A real life straight couple with real life sex. A romantic porn video by Dusk TV's own porn for women label</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 08:16:00" d="2020-04-20 08:31:00"><n>Coming of age</n><t>S</t>    <k>A coming of age tale of young lust, farewells and new encounters. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 08:31:00" d="2020-04-20 08:51:00"><n>My Girlfriends Mother 3: Nica Noelle &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>Stay-at-home mom Inari isn't so sure she approves of her daughter getting involved in a serious relationship, but Alyssa convinces her mom to invite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 08:51:00" d="2020-04-20 09:14:00"><n>Positions: First</n>    <k>While finding inspiration at a dancer?s retreat, the ballet dancer Florence soon realises she?s not the only one who could do with practising</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 09:14:00" d="2020-04-20 09:40:00"><n>Intimate Moments: Leona &amp; Peter</n>    <k>Intimate moments for beautiful couples while exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A porn for women scene from Intimate Moments by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 09:40:00" d="2020-04-20 10:05:00"><n>Not to Innocent: Naomi Nevena &amp; Thomas Reed</n>    <k>A romantic sex film by Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous sex films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 10:05:00" d="2020-04-20 10:28:00"><n>Dude Looks Like A Lady</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: A girl gets a kick from dressing her boyfriend up as a lady. In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 10:28:00" d="2020-04-20 10:50:00"><n>Picture Perfect: Billy King &amp; Julia De Lucia</n>    <k>Even pornstars the age of social media, FaceTime and mobile communication, now have the ultimate sex toy at their disposal. They can tease each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 10:50:00" d="2020-04-20 11:23:00"><n>Sexy Massage Fantasies: Smooth Seduction</n>    <k>A beautiful sensual film by Roma Amor for SinfulXXX. In this scene the combination of a blindfold and lots of oil prove to be the perfect ingredients</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 11:23:00" d="2020-04-20 11:47:00"><n>Cum Inside Me: Rebeccca &amp; Andrew</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A porn for women scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 11:47:00" d="2020-04-20 12:14:00"><n>Afternoon Delight: Alyssa Branch &amp; Giovanni Francesco</n>    <k>Attractive people that have sex on gorgeous locations. A scene from an Intimate Encounters film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 12:14:00" d="2020-04-20 12:34:00"><n>Hard Rain</n><t>L</t>    <k>Showering, always better in company! A super sensual sex scene with a leading roll for pornstar Juan Lucho. Porn for women by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 12:34:00" d="2020-04-20 12:54:00"><n>Close To The Bone: Anya Olsen &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Two immortal lovers are feeling the three-hundred-year-itch. As night falls the city becomes a playground for Jonus and Bryana, both seeking to quench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 12:54:00" d="2020-04-20 13:17:00"><n>Horngry</n><t>S</t>    <k>Food and sex combine in a delicious foursome from Erika Lust's XConfessions series! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 13:17:00" d="2020-04-20 13:38:00"><n>Sensuous Seduction: The Imaginary Boyfriend</n>    <k>Who is your imaginary boyfriend? A sex scene by Lara Tinelli for Dusk TV's' female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 13:38:00" d="2020-04-20 13:49:00"><n>Unbridled: Lyra Law &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>To save her family’s ranch, city girl Avery has to return to Texas and face her demons and her old flame horse trainer Grant. Stormy Daniels stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 13:49:00" d="2020-04-20 14:20:00"><n>I Love My Hotwife: Siri &amp; Chad White</n>    <k>Four segments on the sexual fantasies of husbands and wives. A married couple hires a sexy male escort, Siri let?s her husband listen to her sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 14:20:00" d="2020-04-20 14:34:00"><n>Candles</n>    <k>Candles always set the tone for a romantic evening with your partner. Sometimes some candles more than others? Romantic porn for women by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 14:34:00" d="2020-04-20 14:58:00"><n>Sex With Friends: Freedom</n>    <k>When old college friends meet again they take the time to rekindle and explore each other?s bodies and sexual boundries. A reunion you don?t want to miss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 14:58:00" d="2020-04-20 15:10:00"><n>Dominate Me</n><t>S</t>    <k>This beautiful and intense film explores the intimacy of BDSM, carefully capturing every little detail. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 15:10:00" d="2020-04-20 15:28:00"><n>Naked Desire</n>    <k>An exciting porn for women video by Dusk TV's own female friendly porn label. Watch this beautiful young woman having sex with her tattooed, big dick boyfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 15:28:00" d="2020-04-20 16:05:00"><n>The Passionate Three: Vanessa Decker, Jayden &amp; Pavlos</n>    <k>Sinful trinity's enjoying a triad of erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 16:05:00" d="2020-04-20 16:17:00"><n>Do You Find My Feet Suckable?</n>    <k>“Do You Find My Feet Suckable” is an erotic short film inspired by one the anonymous sex confessions submitted to XConfessions. In XConfessions, people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 16:17:00" d="2020-04-20 16:38:00"><n>Camera Angle: Casey Calvert &amp; Jay Smooth</n>    <k>Fiction and reality seem to blend when Hollywood actor Peter gets a concussion. His visions of heart-racing, sweat inducing sex seem very real though</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 16:38:00" d="2020-04-20 16:44:00"><n>Momentum 1: A day at the beach</n>    <k>Australian film maker Michelle Flynn has the most distinctive style within the alternative porn genre. Her debut film Momentum is a cinematic intimacy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 16:44:00" d="2020-04-20 17:15:00"><n>True Intensions: Stella Cox &amp; Max Deeds</n>    <k>From director Anjali Kara comes True Intentions, romantic passion and beautiful sex. Watch the palpable chemistry between partners as they climax together onscreen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 17:15:00" d="2020-04-20 17:33:00"><n>Just Touch Me</n>    <k>A playful vignette involving two shared lollipops is about as far removed from the film's opening sequence as possible, but with all the unexpected</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 17:33:00" d="2020-04-20 17:50:00"><n>Perfect timing: Veronica Avluv &amp; Eric Masterson</n>    <k>Christina has a dilemma. She was swept off her feet by a much older man, but now things have cooled. She then meets a charming guy and very soon sparks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 17:50:00" d="2020-04-20 18:17:00"><n>Facade: Keira Nicole &amp; James Deen</n>    <k>Amber and her friend Lindsay are average college students?who happen to moonlight as sexy webcam models. This complicates things when they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 18:17:00" d="2020-04-20 18:26:00"><n>Momentum 4: Sun on our skin</n>    <k>The fourth final and most epic adult film. The Volume 4 stage is set in the Australian desert - an aesthetic overthrow from the previous films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 18:26:00" d="2020-04-20 18:44:00"><n>HouseMates: Sicilia &amp; Satine Spark</n>    <k>After a painful break up Jess flees to the city and is thrown into a world where hiding away is not an option. Her new housemates Ollie and Saskia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 18:44:00" d="2020-04-20 19:15:00"><n>The Artist: Max Deeds &amp; Eveline Dellai</n>    <k>Another beautiful production by Studio Sinful, containing lots of close-ups, artistic lighting and delicious performers. In The Artist a man is sensually</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 19:15:00" d="2020-04-20 19:38:00"><n>He Loves To Watch: India Summer &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>This couple has found a unique way to keep the spark in their marriage. Passionate sex and powerful orgasms for everybody!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 19:38:00" d="2020-04-20 20:08:00"><n>Sexual Ecstasy: Thomas Reed &amp; Naomi Nevena</n>    <k>Sexual Ecstasy is always perfect because it's full of love, and they are going to share as much love as they possibly can. All you have</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 20:08:00" d="2020-04-20 20:39:00"><n>Special Moments: The Apple</n>    <k>A truly romantic sex scene by Dusk TV's own porn for women label: &quot;Ooh la la&quot;. Passionate, realistic lovemaking for women whom enjoy romantic sex scenes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 20:39:00" d="2020-04-20 21:03:00"><n>Inside: Julia Roca &amp; Anneke Necro</n>    <k>Welcome to The Retreat: where curious minds come to play. Plug in and turn on to explore a virtual reality experience where you can be anyone, go anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 21:03:00" d="2020-04-20 21:45:00"><n>Bound For Sex: Samantha Hayes &amp; Richie Calhoun</n>    <k>For over 2 hrs. 40 mins., watch Jillian Janson, Sara Luvv, Samantha Hayes and Dahlia Sky get their share of blindfolds, silk ropes and hard cocks! These sex freaks can't wait to be tied up tight and fucked just right. We hope you?re ready, because tonight, we're all bound for sex!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 21:45:00" d="2020-04-20 22:01:00"><n>Birthday Surprise</n><t>S</t>    <k>It's Danny's birthday and Poppy has a big surprise prepared - he just needs to enjoy the show! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 22:01:00" d="2020-04-20 22:21:00"><n>Ball Control: Sienna Day &amp; Jess West</n>    <k>They say that football is a man’s world, but these two women on this pitch hold all the power. A romantic lesbian porn scene by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 22:21:00" d="2020-04-20 22:37:00"><n>Fantastico</n>    <k>They chat, they laugh, they joke, confide, and reveal, and in the process they move ever closer to physical union. The tender kisses and warm smiles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 22:37:00" d="2020-04-20 22:59:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies 2: Rebeccca &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. This beautiful couple is exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A erotic sex scene from Favorite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 22:59:00" d="2020-04-20 23:24:00"><n>Her Desire: Ladies Night</n>    <k>Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion. A pleasure to all the senses representing realistic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 23:24:00" d="2020-04-20 23:53:00"><n>Jungleicious: Stacy Cruz &amp; Mugur</n>    <k>In a dream, Antonia goes out in the woods. She finds her love, sleeping and waiting for her to touch him. First softly, then firm</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 23:53:00" d="2020-04-21 00:15:00"><n>Quartet: Controlled</n>    <k>Penelope boards a plane from London to Budapest, eager to perform with her three best friends from music academy. Reunited, the foursome soon remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 00:15:00" d="2020-04-21 00:29:00"><n>From The First Moment: Alix Lynx &amp; Damon Dice</n>    <k>Kira (Alix Lynx) is about to marry her handsome movie star boyfriend James except he gets cold feet and leaves her at the wedding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 00:29:00" d="2020-04-21 00:48:00"><n>Heavy Contact</n>    <k>That feeling when you have a lot of contact with someone and the connection gets even heavier when you meet in real life? Yes, that's passion to the max</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 00:48:00" d="2020-04-21 01:20:00"><n>My daughters boyfriend 8: Chastity Lynn &amp; James Deen</n>    <k>When a girl brings her gorgeous boyfriend home to meet her mother, the mother suddenly realizes that she had a completely wrong impression of the young man</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 01:20:00" d="2020-04-21 01:46:00"><n>Afternoon Love: Angel Piaf &amp; Max D</n>    <k>Watch this straight couple enjoy each other and make their time together worthwhile. A real life couple having realistic sex. A porn for women film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 01:46:00" d="2020-04-21 02:08:00"><n>Momentum 2: Language of lust</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Momentum Volume. 2 lives up to it's predecessor, taking us back from the beach to the lazy Australian suburbs. Director Michelle Flynn retains the retro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 02:08:00" d="2020-04-21 02:19:00"><n>Make some time for us</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: Samantha Bentley and Franck Franco make a gorgeous couple in this confession about sex when you're a parent. In XConfessions, people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 02:19:00" d="2020-04-21 02:43:00"><n>Girl Next Door Likes It Dirty: Dillion Harper &amp; Ryan McClane</n>    <k>All of these next door girls are young, free, and secretly wild who love it dirty! They all get their pussies passionately pulverized over the course</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 02:43:00" d="2020-04-21 02:58:00"><n>It's Complicated: Yhivi &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>Shauna (Gracie Glam) has been having casual sex with her handsome friend Will, biding her time until she can finally make a move on her long time crush Brandon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 02:58:00" d="2020-04-21 03:23:00"><n>Pure Thoughts: Chris Hollander &amp; Violette Pink</n>    <k>Welcome to ?Pure Thoughts?, Daring! Pure?s newest female friendly porn installment, which reveals the depths, passion and boundaries of loving couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 03:23:00" d="2020-04-21 03:44:00"><n>Quartet: Tenderley</n>    <k>Penelope boards a plane from London to Budapest, eager to perform with her three best friends from music academy. Reunited, the foursome soon remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 03:44:00" d="2020-04-21 03:54:00"><n>Be A Hero</n><t>S</t>    <k>Anneke woke up horny and spotted her boyfriend's go pro lying around. What will she do with it? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 03:54:00" d="2020-04-21 04:09:00"><n>Never Forgotten: Ella Nova &amp; Robby Echo</n>    <k>Robert can’t stop thinking about Elizabeth, his first love during the 1940’s. An argument teared the perfect couple apart and decades later Robert is still</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 04:09:00" d="2020-04-21 04:37:00"><n>My Love For you: Ana Rose &amp; Figi</n>    <k>A romantic film from Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 04:37:00" d="2020-04-21 04:49:00"><n>Car Sex Generation</n><t>S</t>    <k>Juan Lucho and Julia Roca show exactly why sex in a car is so exciting. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 04:49:00" d="2020-04-21 05:26:00"><n>The Neighbours 2: Lily Labaue &amp; Xander Corvus</n>    <k>Jessica and Dick live together in a sweet love filled house until the house next door becomes invaded by the wild young couple Rachel and frank</k>  </p>
</a>
