<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="58" t="2021-07-13 05:08:10"><p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 05:14:00" d="2021-07-20 05:37:00"><n>Corporate Bonding: Sienna Day &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Good teamwork can lead to surprising situations. Rookie lawyer Leyla organises a team-building weekend by the beach for her and her firm of London lawyers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 05:37:00" d="2021-07-20 05:59:00"><n>Special Moments: The Shower</n><t>L</t>    <k>Watch how this couple shares a steamy shower. A romantic sex scene by Dusk TV's Porn for women label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women, sensuous films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 05:59:00" d="2021-07-20 06:27:00"><n>Black Obsession</n>    <k>Sinful interracial couples enjoy colorful erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 06:27:00" d="2021-07-20 06:53:00"><n>My Girlfriends Mother 6: Logan Pierce &amp; Veronica Radke</n>    <k>Robbie dreaded meeting his girlfriend's mother, but when he finally does, he's taken back as how friendly, alluring and sensual she really is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 06:53:00" d="2021-07-20 07:27:00"><n>My Hotwife's Lover: My Wife, The Sex Lover</n>    <k>Kristin's (Karla Kush) forbidden attraction to her husband's best friend reaches a breaking point when he arranges a private get-together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 07:27:00" d="2021-07-20 07:55:00"><n>Lovers Tryst: Rob Dean &amp; Lucia Love</n>    <k>Real mature couples have truly learned their way around each other's sensitive and aroused bodies. All that is needed to stimulate your senses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 07:55:00" d="2021-07-20 08:10:00"><n>Summer Loving: Misty Stone &amp; Ryan Mclane</n>    <k>The attractive Keiko is bored in the tiny village where she grew up and longs for some excitement. Until a stranger arrives in the village</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 08:10:00" d="2021-07-20 08:30:00"><n>Love is Blind: Sweet Smell</n>    <k>Starting to lose her sight teaches Julie how to use her other senses to take her to new erotic realms. With her newly heightened perception the sound</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 08:30:00" d="2021-07-20 08:45:00"><n>La Reine Des Culottes</n><t>S</t>    <k>A woman's lingerie can say a lot about her - and about her neighbour. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 08:45:00" d="2021-07-20 09:16:00"><n>Confessions Of A Sinner: Dorian Del Isla &amp; Simony Diamond</n>    <k>This beautiful couple relishes each others body with sensual hand and mouth massages by candlelight. Another visual and erotic female friendly porn film by Studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 09:16:00" d="2021-07-20 09:38:00"><n>The Guesthouse: Clea Gaultier &amp; Anthony Gaultier</n>    <k>Nestled in the Spanish countryside, there?s a Guesthouse where visitors enjoy more than just the sunshine on their bodies. Come alone, come with a friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 09:38:00" d="2021-07-20 10:07:00"><n>Soft And Sweet 2: Vinna Reed &amp; Nick Ross</n>    <k>Did you ever notice the softness of your lovers skin, the sweet taste when you move your tongue over her well formed sensual body? A porn for women film by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 10:07:00" d="2021-07-20 10:29:00"><n>Apolonia's Musical Fantasies 1: Girlfriends</n>    <k>Apolonia Lapiedra is a beautiful Spanish spinner who is a classic example of good girl gone bad. In this scene, two gorgeous girls, Apolonia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 10:29:00" d="2021-07-20 10:52:00"><n>Facade: Layla Price &amp; Damon Dice</n>    <k>Amber and her friend Lindsay are average college students?who happen to moonlight as sexy webcam models. This complicates things when they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 10:52:00" d="2021-07-20 11:11:00"><n>Stair Love</n>    <k>Yet another cinematic Spanish female friendly porn scene from Verso Cinema featuring the super popular and multiply awarded Carolina Abril. Don't miss this encounter!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 11:11:00" d="2021-07-20 11:32:00"><n>Ball Control: Sienna Day &amp; Jess West</n>    <k>They say that football is a man’s world, but these two women on this pitch hold all the power. A romantic lesbian porn scene by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 11:32:00" d="2021-07-20 12:07:00"><n>Blind Date Swingers Club: Tina Kay &amp; Lutro</n>    <k>Everyone is getting their fuck on! Swinging couples going wild!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 12:07:00" d="2021-07-20 12:45:00"><n>First Love Sensual Sex</n><t>L</t>    <k>Always wanted to know how to get started with a new lover? This film shows how nice it can be</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 12:45:00" d="2021-07-20 13:08:00"><n>Sweet but Psycho</n><t>S</t>    <k>Four of the hottest and most popular performers on the scene create a hilarious and erotic film. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 13:08:00" d="2021-07-20 13:29:00"><n u="Possessione">Possessione (2)</n>    <k>Alexa takes on the role of submissive to Franck Franco's dominant. There is a clever mix of the sinister with the sweet, the ominous with the innocent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 13:29:00" d="2021-07-20 13:46:00"><n>Apolonia's Musical Fantasies 4: Deep Inside Me</n>    <k>Apolonia Lapiedra is a beautiful Spanish pornstar who is a classic example of good girl gone bad. In this scene, a gorgeous couple, Apolonia and Juan Lucho</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 13:46:00" d="2021-07-20 14:21:00"><n>The Artist: Max Deeds, Anna Rose &amp; Cherry Kiss</n>    <k>Another beautiful production by Studio Sinful, containing lots of close-ups, artistic lighting and delicious performers. In The Artist a man is sensually</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 14:21:00" d="2021-07-20 14:42:00"><n>Housemates 2: Ava Dalush &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Romantic porn with pornstars: Ava Dalush &amp; Tyler Nixon. Artist James moves to the UK in search of his ex-girlfriend (Dalush) and finds himself sharing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 14:42:00" d="2021-07-20 15:20:00"><n>Perfect And Pure: Mary Dee &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Romantic and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A romantic porn scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 15:20:00" d="2021-07-20 15:48:00"><n>My Girlfriends Mother 11: Marley Brinx &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>When Tylers sexy but demanding girlfriend Marley cheats on him, he takes solace in the arms and incredible hot body of Marley?s mom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 15:48:00" d="2021-07-20 16:06:00"><n>Win A Date With Sofia Blake: Mia Li &amp; Derrick Pierce</n>    <k>A-list Hollywood actress Sofia Blake (Olivia Austin) is having the worst day of her life and the paparazzi have made sure to plaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 16:06:00" d="2021-07-20 16:39:00"><n>Shades Of Kink 2: Logan Pierce &amp; Penny Pax</n>    <k>A young man is attracted to a seemingly innocent, sweet young woman, but when he discovers that she moonlights as an infamous dominatrix by night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 16:39:00" d="2021-07-20 16:52:00"><n>Some never awaken</n><t>S</t>    <k>Experience a sexual awakening through dance, movement, and passionate sex. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 16:52:00" d="2021-07-20 17:29:00"><n>Trying New Things: Alison Rey &amp; Robby Echo</n>    <k>Passions explode when a sexually frustrated Alison asks her fiancé to take her virginity two weeks before their wedding day. Sara discovers that adult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 17:29:00" d="2021-07-20 17:49:00"><n>The Invitation: Amber Nevada &amp; Ryan Ryder</n>    <k>Jane and Tom decide to pack the kids off and book a romantic weekend away. When their car unexpectedly breaks down late at night they find themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 17:49:00" d="2021-07-20 18:17:00"><n>Come Closer: Sunday Morning</n>    <k>Having a lazy sunday? This couple is enjoying each other and making their time together worthwhile. A real life couple with real life sex. A romantic sex film by Dusk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 18:17:00" d="2021-07-20 18:49:00"><n>The Passionate Three: Evelyn Dellai, Jean, Angel Piaff</n>    <k>Sinful trinity's enjoying a triad of erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 18:49:00" d="2021-07-20 19:12:00"><n>Blind</n>    <k>Open your eyes wide for this one! Gorgeous Spanish beauty Apolonia Lapiedra and Pablo Ferrari get steamy in this short film with another classic scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 19:12:00" d="2021-07-20 19:25:00"><n>Car Sex Generation</n><t>S</t>    <k>Juan Lucho and Julia Roca show exactly why sex in a car is so exciting. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 19:25:00" d="2021-07-20 19:49:00"><n>Anal Adventure: Dolce Vita &amp; Vincent Vega</n>    <k>Wondering what it takes to have that fantastic sex that you will remember for the rest of your life? These beautiful desirable couples are highly confident</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 19:49:00" d="2021-07-20 20:17:00"><n>My Love For you: Ana Rose &amp; Figi</n>    <k>A romantic film from Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 20:17:00" d="2021-07-20 20:47:00"><n>Our Summer of Love: Sienna Day &amp; Mugur</n>    <k>A hot couple travels abroad and adores the new country, but they enjoy each other even more and especially the new sexy people they meet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 20:47:00" d="2021-07-20 20:57:00"><n>Hysterical Piano Concert</n><t>S</t>    <k>A pianist's ultimate sexual fantasy is played out in an intimate concert that hits an exquisite note! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 20:57:00" d="2021-07-20 21:33:00"><n>I Am All Yours: Daphne Klyde &amp; Nick Ross</n>    <k>A film by Dawn for Dusk's Porn for women label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting realistic excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 21:33:00" d="2021-07-20 21:52:00"><n>Corporate Bonding: Amber Nevada &amp; Amarna Miller</n>    <k>Good teamwork can lead to surprising situations. Rookie lawyer Leyla organises a team-building weekend by the beach for her and her firm of London lawyers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 21:52:00" d="2021-07-20 22:31:00"><n>Couples Massage: Vanessa Decker &amp; Ricky</n>    <k>A crackling fire, relaxing music and a lot of warm oil for a total body massage. Delicious. These beautiful couples can’t get enough of it too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 22:31:00" d="2021-07-20 22:58:00"><n>Faithless: Lacy Lennon &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>&quot;Laura (Whitney Wright) is an aspiring actress from small town America who made her way to LA with stars in her eyes. Her boyfriend waits patiently</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 22:58:00" d="2021-07-20 23:20:00"><n>Sexual Bliss: Nico &amp; Vanessa</n>    <k>Four passionate couples in a Sinful XXX film by Roma Amor. Beautiful, Arty and very sexy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-20 23:20:00" d="2021-07-21 00:02:00"><n>Bound For Sex: Samantha Hayes &amp; Richie Calhoun</n>    <k>For over 2 hrs. 40 mins., watch Jillian Janson, Sara Luvv, Samantha Hayes and Dahlia Sky get their share of blindfolds, silk ropes and hard cocks! These sex freaks can't wait to be tied up tight and fucked just right. We hope you?re ready, because tonight, we're all bound for sex!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-21 00:02:00" d="2021-07-21 00:21:00"><n>Apolonia's Musical Fantasies 3: She</n>    <k>Apolonia Lapiedra is a beautiful Spanish pornstar who is a classic example of good girl gone bad. In this scene, a gorgeous Threesome, Apolonia, Emilio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-21 00:21:00" d="2021-07-21 00:38:00"><n>Red Light: Bree Daniels &amp; Skin Diamond</n>    <k>Red Light is like a waking dream set in the streets of Los Angeles. It's the story of a woman's transformation into her true self, and a wild chase</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-21 00:38:00" d="2021-07-21 00:50:00"><n>Romance Bullshit</n>    <k>From XConfessions 3: Every writer in the room types frantically, but she is just not inspired. Until she sees him. In XConfessions, people from all around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-21 00:50:00" d="2021-07-21 01:12:00"><n>Housemates 3: Good Company</n>    <k>Synopsis not available</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-21 01:12:00" d="2021-07-21 01:41:00"><n>Couples Massage: Daphne &amp; Andrew Truck</n>    <k>A crackling fire, relaxing music and a lot of warm oil for a total body massage. Delicious. These beautiful couples can’t get enough of it too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-21 01:41:00" d="2021-07-21 02:12:00"><n>Sensuous Seduction: Messaging</n>    <k>A sensual massage is the gateway to your partners naughtiness and desires. Watch how this sexy couple is physically expressing their love to each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-21 02:12:00" d="2021-07-21 02:30:00"><n>From The First Moment: Alana Cruise &amp; Damon Dice</n>    <k>Kira (Alix Lynx) is about to marry her handsome movie star boyfriend James except he gets cold feet and leaves her at the wedding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-21 02:30:00" d="2021-07-21 02:42:00"><n>Obsessed</n>    <k>A scene from Xconfessions by Erika Lust. In this porn for women movie she films the 'sneaky' fantasies of her fans. Have you ever fantasized about a former lover?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-21 02:42:00" d="2021-07-21 03:15:00"><n>Restraint 2: Ryan Driller &amp; Valentina Nappi</n>    <k>After placing an ad in search of a dominant man, Valentina finds herself blindfolded and restrained in the home of a mysterious stranger. Although Aria?s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-21 03:15:00" d="2021-07-21 03:42:00"><n>Soft And Sweet 2: Ornella Morgen &amp; Nic Vargas</n><t>L</t>    <k>These young couples show you their most intimate experiences, see the excitement they both have to endure when they tease each other by kissing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-21 03:42:00" d="2021-07-21 04:07:00"><n>Inside: Frida Sante &amp; Alberta Blanco</n>    <k>Welcome to The Retreat: where curious minds come to play. Plug in and turn on to explore a virtual reality experience where you can be anyone, go anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-21 04:07:00" d="2021-07-21 04:28:00"><n>Que Es La Pasion</n>    <k>A couple, clearly in love, kissing and indulging in a brief bit of spontaneous sex. While there is affection and romance in the air, there's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-21 04:28:00" d="2021-07-21 04:53:00"><n>Inside: Julia Roca &amp; Anneke Necro</n>    <k>Welcome to The Retreat: where curious minds come to play. Plug in and turn on to explore a virtual reality experience where you can be anyone, go anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-21 04:53:00" d="2021-07-21 05:26:00"><n>Rob And Marina</n>    <k>For Dusk Academy, Michelle Flynn produced a few scenes with tips, tricks and ideas from the Dusk panel. This scene features Rob and Marina, a real life couple</k>  </p>
</a>
