<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="67" t="2021-07-09 07:43:13"><p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 05:02:00" d="2021-07-15 05:23:00"><n>Dirty Secerts: Odette Delacroix &amp; Zoey Holloway</n>    <k>Dirty Secrets is the sultry sexy tale of two worlds colliding when an inhibited divorcee Lana (Brenda James) rents out her home to an adult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 05:23:00" d="2021-07-15 05:34:00"><n>Bad Sometimes: Sausage</n><t>L</t>    <k>After the acclaimed success of his first film, Lara Tinelli surprises us with a completely different and transgressive film while staying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 05:34:00" d="2021-07-15 05:50:00"><n>Unbridled: Stormy Daniels &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>To save her family’s ranch, city girl Avery has to return to Texas and face her demons and her old flame horse trainer Grant. Stormy Daniels stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 05:50:00" d="2021-07-15 06:00:00"><n>Parallel Universe</n><t>S</t>    <k>There is another world out there, a world where you can exist purely as a piece of furniture. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 06:00:00" d="2021-07-15 06:19:00"><n>Slutish: Adventureland</n>    <k>Bea never misses an opportunity when it comes knocking. While it can take Kylie ages to make a connection with someone, with Bea it's instant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 06:19:00" d="2021-07-15 06:41:00"><n>Perfect &amp; Pure 2: Loveini Lux &amp; Antony</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive, four sultry sirens kiss their lovers whilst soft hands caress strong backs, firm gluts and erect manhoods</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 06:41:00" d="2021-07-15 07:01:00"><n>Room 208: Sara May &amp; Juan Lucho</n>    <k>A romantic sex film by Lara Tinelli for Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 07:01:00" d="2021-07-15 07:17:00"><n>It's Complicated: Gracie Glam &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>Shauna (Gracie Glam) has been having casual sex with her handsome friend Will, biding her time until she can finally make a move on her long time crush Brandon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 07:17:00" d="2021-07-15 07:37:00"><n>I wish I was a lesbian</n><t>S</t>    <k>Maria's deepest fantasies come true when she finds herself being hosted by a hot and sweet lesbian couple. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 07:37:00" d="2021-07-15 08:17:00"><n>Restraint: Persley Hart &amp; Ryan Mclane</n>    <k>Hoping to invigorate their predictable sex life, married couple, Logan and Ashlyn, dabble in beginner BDSM sex with the help of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 08:17:00" d="2021-07-15 08:55:00"><n>Couples Massage: Vanessa Decker &amp; Ricky</n>    <k>A crackling fire, relaxing music and a lot of warm oil for a total body massage. Delicious. These beautiful couples can’t get enough of it too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 08:55:00" d="2021-07-15 09:17:00"><n>Tease: Tyler Nixon &amp; Stella Cox</n>    <k>If according to Shakespeare, clothes make the man, then without doubt lingerie make the woman. Naught porn for women by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 09:17:00" d="2021-07-15 09:33:00"><n>I'm Here For Love</n>    <k>I'm Here for Love is all about two lovers, sharing love, making love, and completely submitting to their love. The contact, the caring, this unexpectedly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 09:33:00" d="2021-07-15 09:55:00"><n>Housemates 3: Morning Sex</n>    <k>Synopsis not available</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 09:55:00" d="2021-07-15 10:06:00"><n>Momentum 2: Gardenwork</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Momentum Volume. 2 lives up to it's predecessor, taking us back from the beach to the lazy Australian suburbs. Director Michelle Flynn retains the retro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 10:06:00" d="2021-07-15 10:23:00"><n>Red Light: Casey Calvert &amp; Damon Dice</n>    <k>Red Light is like a waking dream set in the streets of Los Angeles. It's the story of a woman's transformation into her true self, and a wild chase</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 10:23:00" d="2021-07-15 10:36:00"><n>The Ultimate Kink</n><t>S</t>    <k>An adventure with a female couple who have tried it all when it comes to sex - except for a man. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, kinky female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 10:36:00" d="2021-07-15 11:02:00"><n>Sun stroke: The Final Song</n>    <k>When international DJ Cosmo needs a secluded escape, a sun-kissed Spanish villa is the perfect location. Chloe soon becomes an intense distraction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 11:02:00" d="2021-07-15 11:20:00"><n>4 Passionate Women: First Time</n>    <k>Dusk-tv presents: explicit porn for women and couples by Lara Tinelli. A pleasure to all the senses representing real-life sex full of intimacy, laughter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 11:20:00" d="2021-07-15 11:49:00"><n>Jungleicious: Stacy Cruz &amp; Mugur</n>    <k>In a dream, Antonia goes out in the woods. She finds her love, sleeping and waiting for her to touch him. First softly, then firm</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 11:49:00" d="2021-07-15 12:16:00"><n>Forbidden Affairs: My Wife's Sister 2: Kimber Day &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Two sisters are in love with the same man. The older sister lets her career get in the way, and lets him go. Years later, when he returns married</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 12:16:00" d="2021-07-15 12:53:00"><n>Restraint 2: Aria Alexander &amp; Erik Everhard</n>    <k>After placing an ad in search of a dominant man, Valentina finds herself blindfolded and restrained in the home of a mysterious stranger. Although Aria?s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 12:53:00" d="2021-07-15 13:17:00"><n>In the limelight 2: Raduschka &amp; Marco</n><t>L</t>    <k>Simply a beautiful romantic sex scene. These lovers are showing you what a sensual lovemaking session is all about. Porn for women by Daring! Pure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 13:17:00" d="2021-07-15 13:27:00"><n u="From Beyond: Chanel Preston &amp; Ryan Mclane">From Beyond: Chanel Preston &amp; Ryan Mclane (2)</n>    <k>Sofia is mourning her beloved husband, but still feels him everywhere in their house. Is he haunting her for a reason? Her best friend helps Sofia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 13:27:00" d="2021-07-15 13:47:00"><n>The Guesthouse: Julia Roca &amp; Sicilia</n>    <k>Nestled in the Spanish countryside, there's a Guesthouse where visitors enjoy more than just the sunshine on their bodies. Come alone, come with a friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 13:47:00" d="2021-07-15 14:14:00"><n>Multiorgasmic Brunch</n><t>S</t>    <k>An explosive exploration of the possibilities for female pleasure; where the orgasms just never end. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 14:14:00" d="2021-07-15 14:39:00"><n>Passion Noir: Nick &amp; Karol</n>    <k>A fantastic new romantic porn film from Roma Amor for Sinful XXX. The naked body as an art form and sex as a masterpiece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 14:39:00" d="2021-07-15 14:58:00"><n>Close To The Bone: Loren Minard &amp; Sabby</n>    <k>Two immortal lovers are feeling the three-hundred-year-itch. As night falls the city becomes a playground for Jonus and Bryana, both seeking to quench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 14:58:00" d="2021-07-15 15:22:00"><n>Cum Inside Me: Rebeccca &amp; Andrew</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A porn for women scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 15:22:00" d="2021-07-15 15:37:00"><n>Bad Sometimes: Didac Duran &amp; Erica Fontes</n><t>L</t>    <k>After the acclaimed success of his first film, Lara Tinelli surprises us with a completely different and transgressive film while staying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 15:37:00" d="2021-07-15 16:02:00"><n>Hollywood Ending: Aaliyah Love &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>Childhood lovers Rebecca and Tommy are finally getting the acting success they always wanted. But their love is put to the test when fame, fortune</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 16:02:00" d="2021-07-15 16:27:00"><n>Two Girls Sofa</n>    <k>Two girls on a sofa, what else is there to do on a Sunday when you have nothing planned? These girls decide to explore each other's bodies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 16:27:00" d="2021-07-15 16:49:00"><n>Quartet: Controlled</n>    <k>Penelope boards a plane from London to Budapest, eager to perform with her three best friends from music academy. Reunited, the foursome soon remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 16:49:00" d="2021-07-15 17:18:00"><n>Surreal Encounters: Florane Russell &amp; Mugur</n>    <k>All Space &amp;Time Is Lost When Mysterious Lovers Meet. The three girls feel the wet sheets tickle their beautiful skin as they are waiting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 17:18:00" d="2021-07-15 17:27:00"><n>Momentum 4: Sun on our skin</n>    <k>The fourth final and most epic adult film. The Volume 4 stage is set in the Australian desert - an aesthetic overthrow from the previous films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 17:27:00" d="2021-07-15 17:41:00"><n>Cinema X Pigalle</n><t>S</t>    <k>The piano goes on as an old porn movie is projected just for their own private arousal. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 17:41:00" d="2021-07-15 18:04:00"><n>Love Beats</n>    <k>Victoria lounges on the pillows piled on a wooden sofa listening to music on a set of headphones. She slides a hand into her denim short-shorts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 18:04:00" d="2021-07-15 18:22:00"><n>Girls Sex Tricks: Ana Marco &amp; Fenix Santos</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us on her first porn for women film as director for Thagson with a vibrant story which will take place in the streets of Barcelona</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 18:22:00" d="2021-07-15 18:48:00"><n>Raw: Denisa &amp; Radek</n>    <k>Beautiful images of sexual tenderness in its pure but raw way. Close-ups of gorgeous toned bodies and horny sweat. One of Sinful?s most beautiful productions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 18:48:00" d="2021-07-15 19:08:00"><n>Sex With Friends: Experience</n>    <k>When old college friends meet again they take the time to rekindle and explore each other?s bodies and sexual boundries. A reunion you don?t want to miss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 19:08:00" d="2021-07-15 19:31:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies 2: Rebeccca &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. This beautiful couple is exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A erotic sex scene from Favorite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 19:31:00" d="2021-07-15 20:04:00"><n>The Stepmother 14: Dana DeArmond &amp; Damon Dice</n>    <k>Andrew is mad at his dad when he misses out on important stuff to take care of his step-mother who broke her leg. Until he realizes how hot and sensual she is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 20:04:00" d="2021-07-15 20:29:00"><n>He Loves To Watch: Penny Pax &amp; Van Wyle</n>    <k>This couple has found a unique way to keep the spark in their marriage. Passionate sex and powerful orgasms for everybody! Cuckolding porn with focus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 20:29:00" d="2021-07-15 20:57:00"><n>Forbidden Affairs 4: Logan Pierce &amp; Jade Nile</n>    <k>He is astounded by the drop-dead gorgeous girlfriend of his son. When she starts to flirt with him he can no longer resist the temptation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 20:57:00" d="2021-07-15 21:08:00"><n>Dear Brother In Law</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lana is the perfect bourgeois wife who ends up feeling attracted by her messy brother-in-law. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 21:08:00" d="2021-07-15 21:35:00"><n>Afternoon Delight: Alyssa Branch &amp; Giovanni Francesco</n>    <k>Attractive people that have sex on gorgeous locations. A scene from an Intimate Encounters film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 21:35:00" d="2021-07-15 21:57:00"><n>Secret Sex Society 2: Keep the Lights On</n>    <k>A mysterious invitation gives Emmy the chance to live out her fantasies. In The Game you can be anyone you want, with whoever you want but where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 21:57:00" d="2021-07-15 22:22:00"><n>Sweet Memories: Take Me Now</n>    <k>A hot romantic porn for women scene by Lara Tinelli for women who love rough sex with a guy who has a a big dick. A female friendly porn video by Dusk TV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 22:22:00" d="2021-07-15 22:51:00"><n>Sexy And She Knows It: Lutro, Dorian Del Isla &amp; Anna Polina</n>    <k>Sinful trinity's enjoying a triad of erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 22:51:00" d="2021-07-15 23:15:00"><n>Apple</n>    <k>Who knew slicing an apple could be so sensual? For this couple it’s the perfect foreplay for delicious sex in the kitchen. Hot and sexy porn for women by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 23:15:00" d="2021-07-15 23:27:00"><n>Madmen Porn</n><t>S</t>    <k>Have you ever wondered what Don Draper's cock might be like? Find out in this fan fiction inspired short! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 23:27:00" d="2021-07-15 23:58:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies: Dolce Vita &amp; Vega</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. A romantic porn video from Favorite Fantasies by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 23:58:00" d="2021-07-16 00:21:00"><n>Sweet Memories: Lovers</n>    <k>A hot erotic video by Lara Tinelli for female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples who like big dick. Romantic sex films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 00:21:00" d="2021-07-16 00:56:00"><n>Our Summer of Love: Mugur, Renator &amp; Sienna Day</n>    <k>A hot couple travels abroad and adores the new country, but they enjoy each other even more and especially the new sexy people they meet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 00:56:00" d="2021-07-16 01:09:00"><n>Do You Find My Feet Suckable?</n>    <k>“Do You Find My Feet Suckable” is an erotic short film inspired by one the anonymous sex confessions submitted to XConfessions. In XConfessions, people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 01:09:00" d="2021-07-16 01:26:00"><n>Everyday Turn-Ons: Close To The Edge</n>    <k>Like most modern couples, Shan and Mark struggle to fit sex into their busy lives along with family, friends and work. Snatching a few precious moments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 01:26:00" d="2021-07-16 01:48:00"><n>Camera Angle: Casey Calvert &amp; Jay Smooth</n>    <k>Fiction and reality seem to blend when Hollywood actor Peter gets a concussion. His visions of heart-racing, sweat inducing sex seem very real though</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 01:48:00" d="2021-07-16 02:11:00"><n>The Party</n>    <k>A breasty Spanish beauty can’t get any sleep because of the loud party next door. But when she sees her attractive neighbor her angry feelings fade away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 02:11:00" d="2021-07-16 02:32:00"><n>Close To The Bone: Anya Olsen &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Two immortal lovers are feeling the three-hundred-year-itch. As night falls the city becomes a playground for Jonus and Bryana, both seeking to quench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 02:32:00" d="2021-07-16 02:57:00"><n>Gentle Loving 2: Tequila &amp; Vincent Vega</n>    <k>These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. An erotic sex scene from Favorite Fantasies 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 02:57:00" d="2021-07-16 03:23:00"><n>After Forever: Kenzie Taylor &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>When Derrick plans a romantic weekend in his vacation house he soon finds out that his ex Penny had the same idea with her new partner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 03:23:00" d="2021-07-16 03:49:00"><n>Once In A Blue Moon: Nicole Love &amp; Pavlos</n>    <k>In the blue light of the moon various couples love all parts of each other?s bodies on quiet spots in alleys, on rooftops and in fields. A Sinful production</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 03:49:00" d="2021-07-16 04:09:00"><n>Recipe for Romance: Gracie Glam &amp; Levi Cash</n>    <k>Love is cooking in Carolina's kitchen, and it's wonderfully delicious! Carolina is a passionate cook who is patiently waiting for Mr. Right. But what if Mr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 04:09:00" d="2021-07-16 04:28:00"><n>Apolonia's Musical Fantasies 3: She</n>    <k>Apolonia Lapiedra is a beautiful Spanish pornstar who is a classic example of good girl gone bad. In this scene, a gorgeous Threesome, Apolonia, Emilio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 04:28:00" d="2021-07-16 04:43:00"><n>Never Forgotten: Katana &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>Robert can’t stop thinking about Elizabeth, his first love during the 1940’s. An argument teared the perfect couple apart and decades later Robert is still</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 04:43:00" d="2021-07-16 04:59:00"><n>An Appointment With My Master</n><t>S</t>    <k>The honest and truthful relationship between a dominant and a submissive. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, kinky female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-16 04:59:00" d="2021-07-16 05:20:00"><n>Inside: Sicilia &amp; Juan Lucho</n>    <k>Welcome to The Retreat: where curious minds come to play. Plug in and turn on to explore a virtual reality experience where you can be anyone, go anywhere</k>  </p>
</a>
