<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="66" t="2019-07-12 01:09:57"><p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 05:03:00" d="2019-07-18 05:35:00"><n>I Love My Hotwife: Romi Rain, Toni Ribas &amp; Otto Bauer</n>    <k>Four segments on the sexual fantasies of husbands and wives. A married couple hires a sexy male escort, Siri let?s her husband listen to her sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 05:35:00" d="2019-07-18 05:54:00"><n>If the Apocalypse Comes, Fuck Me</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 05:54:00" d="2019-07-18 06:14:00"><n>Delilahs Top Tips: Victoria Summers &amp; Ryan Ryder</n><t>O</t>    <k>Delilah is the nation's naughtiest agony aunt dedicated to solving the nation's more. ntimate dilemmas. She whips two city workers into a frenzy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 06:14:00" d="2019-07-18 06:30:00"><n>I'm Here For Love</n>    <k>I'm Here for Love is all about two lovers, sharing love, making love, and completely submitting to their love. The contact, the caring, this unexpectedly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 06:30:00" d="2019-07-18 06:49:00"><n>A Girls' Getaway: Ella Hughes</n>    <k>Girls weekend out! The girls used to go away together each year, but it has already been 5 years. Amy organized another girly weekend after a desperate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 06:49:00" d="2019-07-18 07:23:00"><n>I Am All Yours: Daphne Klyde &amp; Nick Ross</n>    <k>A new scene by Dawn for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 07:23:00" d="2019-07-18 07:56:00"><n>Girls Crush: Ildiko Sarang &amp; Simona Opavova</n>    <k>These girls love, lust, lick, becoming almost one in this sensual piece of erotica. Sinful Studio making art again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 07:56:00" d="2019-07-18 08:16:00"><n>Housemates 2 : Alexei Jackson, Stella Cox &amp; Amber Nevada</n>    <k>New house. New rules. Artist James moves to the UK in search of his ex-girlfriend (Dalush) and finds himself sharing a house with four incredibly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 08:16:00" d="2019-07-18 08:37:00"><n>BFF's: Nicole Aniston &amp; Xander Corvus</n>    <k>John and Julia are best friends. John wants more but he once told Julia that he fancies men? will she be able to forgive him his lies?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 08:37:00" d="2019-07-18 08:56:00"><n>Stair Love</n>    <k>Yet another cinematic Spanish scene from Verso Cinema featuring the super popular and multiply awarded Carolina Abril. Don't miss this encounter!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 08:56:00" d="2019-07-18 09:23:00"><n>My Girlfriends Mother 6: Julia Ann &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>Robbie dreaded meeting his girlfriend's mother, but when he finally does, he's taken back as how friendly, alluring and sensual she really is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 09:23:00" d="2019-07-18 09:41:00"><n>Naked Desire</n>    <k>This girl likes to play with her own beautiful body, but let?s her sexy tattooed boyfriend enjoy her luscious body too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 09:41:00" d="2019-07-18 10:04:00"><n>Connections: Kara Dasha &amp; Devon</n>    <k>Connections, celebrates all that?s great about sex: passion, laughter, teasing, giving, receiving, &amp; experiencing real pleasure. It?s about the connection</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 10:04:00" d="2019-07-18 10:15:00"><n>Be A Hero</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 10:15:00" d="2019-07-18 10:34:00"><n>Pure Milf 5: Johnny Castle &amp; Capri Cavanni</n><t>L</t>    <k>These pure MILFs always get what they want as you will see in these five tantalizing scenes. These sexy ladies show you the true meaning of seduction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 10:34:00" d="2019-07-18 10:48:00"><n>Let me see your ponytail swing, I Want a Viking Warrior</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 10:48:00" d="2019-07-18 11:16:00"><n>Wellness: Iwa &amp; Johnny</n>    <k>Massages, manicures and 100% 'me time'. Ultra relaxing and satisfying! Scene from the film Wellness, by Daring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 11:16:00" d="2019-07-18 11:36:00"><n>Ball Control: Marc Rose, Anissa Kate &amp; Tina Kay</n>    <k>They say that football is a man’s world, but there’s one woman on this pitch with all the power. Physio Eva puts her massage skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 11:36:00" d="2019-07-18 11:50:00"><n>I'm a Very Bad Secretary</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 11:50:00" d="2019-07-18 12:13:00"><n>Hollywood Ending: Aaliyah Love &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>Childhood lovers Rebecca and Tommy are finally getting the acting success they always wanted. But their love is put to the test when fame, fortune</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 12:13:00" d="2019-07-18 12:44:00"><n>Sensuous Seduction: Messaging</n>    <k>A new scene by Award Winning director Lara Tinelli for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 12:44:00" d="2019-07-18 13:00:00"><n>Hello Pool Boy</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 13:00:00" d="2019-07-18 13:27:00"><n>My Daughters Boyfriend 10: Keisha Grey &amp; Tommy Gunn</n>    <k>A free spirited skateboarder wants to get more serious with her boyfriend, but he?s resisting. For one, he?s just met an uber-hot, elegant woman at the office</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 13:27:00" d="2019-07-18 13:47:00"><n>The Invitation: Amber Nevada &amp; Ryan Ryder</n>    <k>Jane and Tom decide to pack the kids off and book a romantic weekend away. When their car unexpectedly breaks down late at night they find themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 13:47:00" d="2019-07-18 14:15:00"><n>Soft And Sweet 2: Lady Dee &amp; Max D</n><t>L</t>    <k>Did you ever notice the softness of your lovers skin, the sweet taste when you move your tongue over her well formed sensual body? These young couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 14:15:00" d="2019-07-18 14:37:00"><n>4 Passionate Woman: Feeling Hot</n>    <k>A new scene by Award Winning director Lara Tinelli for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 14:37:00" d="2019-07-18 14:49:00"><n>Do You Find My Feet Suckable?</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 14:49:00" d="2019-07-18 15:13:00"><n>Office Love Affairs: Gina Gerson &amp; Marc Rose</n>    <k>At four different workplaces there are four attractive ladies that are bored with work. They find a little distraction playing with themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 15:13:00" d="2019-07-18 15:49:00"><n>The Passionate Three: Vanessa Decker, Jayden &amp; Pavlos</n>    <k>Sinful trinity's enjoying a triad of erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 15:49:00" d="2019-07-18 16:17:00"><n>Come Closer: Sunday Morning</n>    <k>What are you going to do when all of a suddon both of you are at home and have nothing to do? Exactly, enjoy each other and make your time together worthwhile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 16:17:00" d="2019-07-18 16:43:00"><n>Brave Hearts: Samantha Jolie &amp; Mark Zicha</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sarah (Faye Regan), the most famous Romance Novelist in the world, is writing the final book in her series of best-selling love stories. Admired by women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 16:43:00" d="2019-07-18 17:08:00"><n>Very Beautiful Lips</n><t>L</t>    <k>Tarting with a shower scene, performers Apolonia Lapiedra and Alberto Blanco waste no time in exploring their lust for one another</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 17:08:00" d="2019-07-18 17:34:00"><n>Pleasure Professionals: Samantha Bentley &amp; Tiffany Doll</n>    <k>Do you harbour special sexual desires? Hire a professional and let them make your naughtiest dreams come true. Scene from a film by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 17:34:00" d="2019-07-18 17:45:00"><n>Mother Fucker</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 17:45:00" d="2019-07-18 18:07:00"><n>Elevator Dreams</n>    <k>When a guy meets an attractive girl in an elevator, she ignores him. But in his dreams all she want to do is to pleasure him sexually</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 18:07:00" d="2019-07-18 18:30:00"><n>She's the one: Carolyn Reese &amp; Ryan Mclane</n>    <k>It is clear to everyone that Ryan and Rachel fancy each other, but not to themselves. Will it ever come to something between these two?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 18:30:00" d="2019-07-18 18:59:00"><n>Almost Relatives: Brandi Love &amp; Chad White</n>    <k>Things become heated between a bride and the best man when their explosive attraction to one another makes them question their loyalty to the groom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 18:59:00" d="2019-07-18 19:14:00"><n>Belle Dame Sans Merci</n>    <k>I met a lady in the meads, full beautiful - a faery?s child, her hair was long, her foot was light, and her eyes were wild. A Verso Cinema film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 19:14:00" d="2019-07-18 19:39:00"><n>Secret Sex Society: Julia De Lucia &amp; Bishop Black</n>    <k>When colourful people meet and share their colourful fantasies. Starring the hot blooded Spanish beauty Julia Roca</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 19:39:00" d="2019-07-18 19:54:00"><n>Art of Spanking</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 19:54:00" d="2019-07-18 20:14:00"><n>Special Moments: The Shower</n><t>L</t>    <k>A new scene by AlexanFilm for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 20:14:00" d="2019-07-18 20:41:00"><n>Confessions Of A Sinner: Dorian Del Isla &amp; Cassie Del Isla</n>    <k>This beautiful couple relishes each others body with sensual hand and mouth massages by candlelight. Another visual and erotic jewel by Studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 20:41:00" d="2019-07-18 20:51:00"><n>Chicazo</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 20:51:00" d="2019-07-18 21:13:00"><n>Haunted Hearts: Michael Vegas &amp; Dana DeArmond</n>    <k>When a distant aunt dies her nice guy nephew inherits her estate. While settling into his palatial mansion he discovers sexual temptation family rivalry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 21:13:00" d="2019-07-18 21:40:00"><n>Restraint: Sarah Luvv &amp; Xander Crovus</n>    <k>Hoping to invigorate their predictable sex life, married couple, Logan and Ashlyn, dabble in beginner BDSM sex with the help of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 21:40:00" d="2019-07-18 22:00:00"><n>Tender Love And Care: Lola &amp; Tommy Deer</n>    <k>Attractive young people having sultry, passionate sex, and beautifully filmed to boot! A scene from a film by Yourope Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 22:00:00" d="2019-07-18 22:17:00"><n>Erotic Massage Stories 3: Bambi Wolfe &amp; Bill Bailey</n><t>L</t>    <k>So relaxing as you watch five sensuous massage fantasies that will overwhelm you. Every delicate curve and touch has been captured</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 22:17:00" d="2019-07-18 22:32:00"><n>It's Complicated: Yhivi &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>Shauna (Gracie Glam) has been having casual sex with her handsome friend Will, biding her time until she can finally make a move on her long time crush Brandon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 22:32:00" d="2019-07-18 22:46:00"><n>Getting Cozy: AJ Applegate &amp; Daniel Hunter</n>    <k>Recently single Marisa is unwillingly sent on a blind date by her best friend. After a few cocktails things get out of hand and Marisa wakes up in his bed? Due to an ice storm she cannot leave his appartment, and spends the weekend. A film from Wicked Pictures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 22:46:00" d="2019-07-18 23:00:00"><n>La Reine Des Culottes</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 23:00:00" d="2019-07-18 23:21:00"><n>Ball Control: Sienna Day &amp; Jess West</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 23:21:00" d="2019-07-18 23:46:00"><n>Once In A Blue Moon: Nikky Dream &amp; Lupro</n>    <k>In the blue light of the moon various couples love all parts of each other?s bodies on quiet spots in alleys, on rooftops and in fields. A Sinful production</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-18 23:46:00" d="2019-07-19 00:12:00"><n>The Escort 2: Presley Hart &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>When a beautiful young woman enters the escorting profession, she's put off by her first client. But under the tutelage of a smart and capable madam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-19 00:12:00" d="2019-07-19 00:41:00"><n>The Bedroom Chronicles: Chris Hollander &amp; Chelsy Sun</n>    <k>As women we all exactly know what kind of sex we want, need and prefer: 'sexy', 'sensual' and 'sophisticated' are the keywords as a prelude for great sex! These Chronicles from Daring! Pure are exactly as we want it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-19 00:41:00" d="2019-07-19 01:09:00"><n>Special Moments: Reading</n>    <k>A new scene by AlexanFilm for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-19 01:09:00" d="2019-07-19 01:29:00"><n>HouseMates: Chessie Kay &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>After a painful break up Jess flees to the city and is thrown into a world where hiding away is not an option. Her new housemates Ollie and Saskia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-19 01:29:00" d="2019-07-19 01:58:00"><n>Infidelity: Lily Cade &amp; Tilly McReese</n>    <k>They wanted a normal life in suburbia! Gina and Annie are a long term lesbian couple with a 2008 vintage marriage, a cute house, good jobs? and a sex life that is a thing of the past. Annie starts having an affair with her 19 year old assistant and a threesome follows. A Filly film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-19 01:58:00" d="2019-07-19 02:05:00"><n>Slo Blo Mo Job</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-19 02:05:00" d="2019-07-19 02:27:00"><n>Tease: Amber Nevada &amp; Billy King</n>    <k>If according to Shakespeare, clothes make the man, then without doubt lingerie make the woman. Skyler is the gorgeous young owner and head designer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-19 02:27:00" d="2019-07-19 02:51:00"><n>Weekend: Katy Rose, Lexi Dona &amp; Dominica Phoenix</n>    <k>Shot in Portugal, episode 4 of The Weekend, &quot;Time for Love,&quot; begins with a new day. As Lutro and Dominika prepare breakfast, Lexie and Jason are enjoying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-19 02:51:00" d="2019-07-19 03:15:00"><n>Milf Affairs: Luke Hotrod &amp; Candi Coxx</n>    <k>Five erotic vignettes featuring hot wives and their sexual adventures with younger guys. Female director Anjali Kara delivers a cinematic adult movie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-19 03:15:00" d="2019-07-19 03:40:00"><n>My Love For you: Chrissy Fox &amp; Nic Vargas</n>    <k>A new scene by Roma Woodcock for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-19 03:40:00" d="2019-07-19 04:11:00"><n>A Touch Of Lust: The Book of Love</n>    <k>In this scene an intimate dance ends up in sultry sex on the kitchen table. A cinematic feast for the eyes by Roma Amor for SinfulXXX</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-19 04:11:00" d="2019-07-19 04:31:00"><n>Close To The Bone: Anya Olsen &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Two immortal lovers are feeling the three-hundred-year-itch. As night falls the city becomes a playground for Jonus and Bryana, both seeking to quench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-19 04:31:00" d="2019-07-19 04:46:00"><n>Win A Date With Sofia Blake: Charlotte Cross &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>A-list Hollywood actress Sofia Blake (Olivia Austin) is having the worst day of her life and the paparazzi have made sure to plaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-19 04:46:00" d="2019-07-19 05:02:00"><n>Going Bananas</n>    <k>Stand up and pick up a banana, read the instructions carefully, follow the rules. Wait for me lying on our big white bed, I?ll come</k>  </p>
</a>
