<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="63" t="2020-05-11 04:37:35"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 05:13:00" d="2020-05-18 05:24:00"><n>Eat with me</n><t>S</t>    <k>Be fed all your deepest and most delicious desires by a gorgeous celeb chef. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 05:24:00" d="2020-05-18 05:51:00"><n>Trying New Things: Kasey Warner &amp; Richie Calhoun</n>    <k>Passions explode when a sexually frustrated Alison asks her fiancé to take her virginity two weeks before their wedding day. Sara discovers that adult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 05:51:00" d="2020-05-18 06:18:00"><n>Sexy and Sensual: Sheri Vee &amp; Nikolas</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. A porn for women scene from Sexy and Sensual by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 06:18:00" d="2020-05-18 06:38:00"><n>The Guesthouse: Julia De Lucia &amp; Emilio Adrana</n>    <k>Nestled in the Spanish countryside, there?s a Guesthouse where visitors enjoy more than just the sunshine on their bodies. Come alone, come with a friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 06:38:00" d="2020-05-18 06:59:00"><n>Pure Sexual Attraction: Chase Ryder &amp; Johnny Castle</n>    <k>Embark on an exciting journey of pure sexual attraction as five breathtaking girls are captured in five scenes that set the standard for high definition erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 06:59:00" d="2020-05-18 07:13:00"><n>Hit Me With Your Best Shot</n>    <k>Every time he grabs it he feels so strong, as if his virility depended on it. It starts to annoy me when he's been shooting at cans for an</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 07:13:00" d="2020-05-18 07:47:00"><n>Rob And Marina</n>    <k>For Dusk Academy, Michelle Flynn produced a few scenes with tips, tricks and ideas from the Dusk panel. This scene features Rob and Marina, a real life couple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 07:47:00" d="2020-05-18 08:05:00"><n>Trouble X 2: Cherie Deville &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>On his first day back in the dating game, Nick meets not one but TWO beautiful women. Olivia (Abigail Mac) is hot, sexy, and confident. Jenny (Cherie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 08:05:00" d="2020-05-18 08:20:00"><n>Boat Buddies With Benefits</n>    <k>From XConfessions 3: Warning: mixing business with pleasure has orgasmic effects! In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 08:20:00" d="2020-05-18 08:41:00"><n>The Guesthouse: Clea Gaultier &amp; Anthony Gaultier</n>    <k>Nestled in the Spanish countryside, there?s a Guesthouse where visitors enjoy more than just the sunshine on their bodies. Come alone, come with a friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 08:41:00" d="2020-05-18 09:06:00"><n>Sweet Memories: Touch me</n>    <k>A sex scene by Lara Tinelli for female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. An erotic video for women who are into guys with a big dick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 09:06:00" d="2020-05-18 09:34:00"><n>Sex Sinners and Saints: Nathaly Cherie &amp; Steve</n>    <k>Not only is the church the perfect place to confess your sins, it's also the perfect location to have sensational sex. These couples sin in church, moaning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 09:34:00" d="2020-05-18 09:54:00"><n>The Babysitter 5: Lily Carter &amp; Mr. Marcus</n>    <k>Stay at home mom Michelle Lay is worried about finances, and tells overworked husband Mr. Marcus that it's time to hire a babysitter so she</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 09:54:00" d="2020-05-18 10:24:00"><n>Restraint: Dahlia Sky &amp; Chad White</n>    <k>Hoping to invigorate their predictable sex life, married couple, Logan and Ashlyn, dabble in beginner BDSM sex with the help of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 10:24:00" d="2020-05-18 10:44:00"><n>A Girls' Getaway: Dan Lucia Love &amp; Luke Hotrod</n><t>O</t>    <k>Girls weekend out! The girls go away together each year for a relaxing weekend to the English countryside. But what happens when a game of tennis turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 10:44:00" d="2020-05-18 11:07:00"><n>After Forever: Alexa Grace &amp; Ryan Mclane</n>    <k>When Derrick plans a romantic weekend in his vacation house he soon finds out that his ex Penny had the same idea with her new partner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 11:07:00" d="2020-05-18 11:26:00"><n>HouseMates: Sicilia &amp; Sean</n>    <k>After a painful break up Jess flees to the city and is thrown into a world where hiding away is not an option. Her new housemates Ollie and Saskia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 11:26:00" d="2020-05-18 11:38:00"><n>Hunt Me Catch Me Eat Me</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: A fox hunts for the rabbit, devouring her in all her beauty in the end. In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 11:38:00" d="2020-05-18 12:09:00"><n>Sexy Massage Fantasies: Sinful Massage</n>    <k>A beautiful sensual film by Roma Amor for SinfulXXX. In this scene a couple explores just how sinful a relaxing massage can be. Sexual massages are hot!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 12:09:00" d="2020-05-18 12:32:00"><n>Positions: First</n>    <k>While finding inspiration at a dancer?s retreat, the ballet dancer Florence soon realises she?s not the only one who could do with practising</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 12:32:00" d="2020-05-18 13:04:00"><n>Sexy and Sensual: Mary Dee &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A romantic sex scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 13:04:00" d="2020-05-18 13:26:00"><n>Love Lust Longing: Jessica Drake &amp; Kurt Lockwood</n>    <k>Love Lust &amp; Longing takes place in a seemingly innocent Bed &amp; Breakfast. Rachel a prostitute who has set up shop in the master bedroom falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 13:26:00" d="2020-05-18 13:49:00"><n>Hugman</n>    <k>My girlfriend and I are not serious people, we like to have fun in our lives and we are always playing tricks and games to spice up our life. Playful porn by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 13:49:00" d="2020-05-18 14:12:00"><n>Tease: Ella Hughes &amp; Carly Rae</n>    <k>If according to Shakespeare, clothes make the man, then without doubt lingerie make the woman. A lesbian porn scene by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 14:12:00" d="2020-05-18 14:44:00"><n>Black Desire</n>    <k>Sinful interracial couples enjoy colorful erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 14:44:00" d="2020-05-18 15:01:00"><n>Soulmates</n>    <k>Nothing more fun than watching beautiful people together with your partner. Especially if that ends in super nice sex with your 'Soulmate(s)'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 15:01:00" d="2020-05-18 15:16:00"><n>An Appointment With My Master</n><t>S</t>    <k>The honest and truthful relationship between a dominant and a submissive. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, kinky female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 15:16:00" d="2020-05-18 15:35:00"><n>I'm Here For Love</n>    <k>I'm Here for Love is all about two lovers, sharing love, making love, and completely submitting to their love. The contact, the caring, this unexpectedly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 15:35:00" d="2020-05-18 15:57:00"><n>Sensuous Seduction: The Imaginary Boyfriend</n>    <k>Who is your imaginary boyfriend? A sex scene by Lara Tinelli for Dusk TV's' female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 15:57:00" d="2020-05-18 16:25:00"><n>Passion Noir: Nick &amp; Karol</n>    <k>A fantastic new romantic porn film from Roma Amor for Sinful XXX. The naked body as an art form and sex as a masterpiece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 16:25:00" d="2020-05-18 16:42:00"><n>The Guesthouse: Julia De Lucia &amp; Miguel Zayas</n>    <k>Porn for women by Joybear. Nestled in the Spanish countryside, there?s a Guesthouse where visitors enjoy more than just the sunshine on their bodies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 16:42:00" d="2020-05-18 17:08:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies 2: Rebeccca &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. This beautiful couple is exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A erotic sex scene from Favorite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 17:08:00" d="2020-05-18 17:43:00"><n>Guide To Kinky Sex For Couples: Asa Akira &amp; Derrick Pierce</n>    <k>Kink expert Tristan Taormino gives sexlessons to discuss, explore and finally act out your wildest fantasies, with your partner! 4 Hot couples demonstrate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 17:43:00" d="2020-05-18 17:56:00"><n>It's Complicated: Brooke &amp; Small Hands</n>    <k>Shauna (Gracie Glam) has been having casual sex with her handsome friend Will, biding her time until she can finally make a move on her long time crush Brandon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 17:56:00" d="2020-05-18 18:21:00"><n>Shades of Kink 6: Adrian Maya &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>A gorgeous girl starts to work for an eccentric kinky writer and learns everything there is to know about bondage and discipline. Starring vivacious Marley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 18:21:00" d="2020-05-18 18:36:00"><n>Birthday Surprise</n><t>S</t>    <k>It's Danny's birthday and Poppy has a big surprise prepared - he just needs to enjoy the show! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 18:36:00" d="2020-05-18 19:23:00"><n>Bound For Sex: Dahila Sky &amp; Ramon Nomar</n>    <k>For over 2 hrs. 40 mins., watch Jillian Janson, Sara Luvv, Samantha Hayes and Dahlia Sky get their share of blindfolds, silk ropes and hard cocks! These sex freaks can't wait to be tied up tight and fucked just right. We hope you?re ready, because tonight, we're all bound for sex!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 19:23:00" d="2020-05-18 19:48:00"><n>Secret Sex Society: Sicilia &amp; Sylvan</n>    <k>When colourful people meet and share their colourful fantasies. Starring the hot blooded Spanish beauty Julia Roca</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 19:48:00" d="2020-05-18 20:17:00"><n>My Love For you: Ana Rose &amp; Figi</n>    <k>A romantic film from Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 20:17:00" d="2020-05-18 20:57:00"><n>Hot Water: Vanessa Decker &amp; Ricky Rascal</n>    <k>Licking, sucking, kissing, thrusting, touching, stroking, becoming one with each other in hot water. A sexual and visual delight by Studio Sinfull</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 20:57:00" d="2020-05-18 21:14:00"><n>Among The Bushes</n>    <k>He's always sitting in this park, surrounded by the trees, reading a book, cute and charismatic. He's big, tall and handsome. I'll take him between</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 21:14:00" d="2020-05-18 21:23:00"><n>Can Vampires Smell My Period?</n><t>S</t>    <k>This is no teenage dream. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual confessions of her viewers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 21:23:00" d="2020-05-18 21:51:00"><n>I Love You: Sarah Kay &amp; Angelo Godshack</n>    <k>These beautiful desireable men and women are highly confident and have all the experience to bring you in a state of trance. A romatic sex scene by Desire media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 21:51:00" d="2020-05-18 22:07:00"><n>It's Complicated: Gracie Glam &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>Shauna (Gracie Glam) has been having casual sex with her handsome friend Will, biding her time until she can finally make a move on her long time crush Brandon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 22:07:00" d="2020-05-18 22:29:00"><n>Sex With Friends: Daydreams</n>    <k>When old college friends meet again they take the time to rekindle and explore each other?s bodies and sexual boundries. A reunion you don?t want to miss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 22:29:00" d="2020-05-18 22:48:00"><n>Coming of age</n><t>S</t>    <k>A coming of age tale of young lust, farewells and new encounters. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 22:48:00" d="2020-05-18 23:02:00"><n>The Fantasy Project: Madison Missina &amp; Ryan James</n>    <k>Kate Eden?s research into female sexual fantasies leads her deep into the erotic imagination of women, a lush world of pleasure without consequences. But will Kate?s passion for her work lead her to lose herself ? and her relationship? A female friendly porn film by Louise Lush</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 23:02:00" d="2020-05-18 23:37:00"><n>I Am All Yours: Daphne Klyde &amp; Nick Ross</n>    <k>A film by Dawn for Dusk's Porn for women label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting realistic excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 23:37:00" d="2020-05-18 23:55:00"><n>4 Passionate Women: First Time</n>    <k>Dusk-tv presents: explicit porn for women and couples by Lara Tinelli. A pleasure to all the senses representing real-life sex full of intimacy, laughter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-18 23:55:00" d="2020-05-19 00:12:00"><n>Everyday Turn-Ons: Close To The Edge</n>    <k>Like most modern couples, Shan and Mark struggle to fit sex into their busy lives along with family, friends and work. Snatching a few precious moments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 00:12:00" d="2020-05-19 00:44:00"><n>True Intensions: Stella Cox &amp; Max Deeds</n>    <k>From director Anjali Kara comes True Intentions, romantic passion and beautiful sex. Watch the palpable chemistry between partners as they climax together onscreen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 00:44:00" d="2020-05-19 01:09:00"><n>Friends And Lovers: Aaliyah Love &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>Caroline and Matt (Aaliyah Love and Tommy Pistol) have been best friends since college. Through break-ups they've been there for each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 01:09:00" d="2020-05-19 01:30:00"><n>Passion Noir: Lexi &amp; Jason</n>    <k>A fantastic new female friendly porn film from Roma Amor for Sinful XXX. The naked body as an art form and sex as a masterpiece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 01:30:00" d="2020-05-19 02:04:00"><n>My Hotwife's Lover: The Freedom of Being Tied Down</n>    <k>Kristin's (Karla Kush) forbidden attraction to her husband's best friend reaches a breaking point when he arranges a private get-together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 02:04:00" d="2020-05-19 02:23:00"><n>Connections: Leah &amp; Mal</n>    <k>Connections, celebrates all that?s great about porn for women: passion, laughter, teasing, giving, receiving, &amp; experiencing real pleasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 02:23:00" d="2020-05-19 02:40:00"><n>Win A Date With Sofia Blake: Olivia Austin &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>A-list Hollywood actress Sofia Blake (Olivia Austin) is having the worst day of her life and the paparazzi have made sure to plaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 02:40:00" d="2020-05-19 03:03:00"><n>Dude Looks Like A Lady</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: A girl gets a kick from dressing her boyfriend up as a lady. In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 03:03:00" d="2020-05-19 03:24:00"><n>Sex With Friends: Dessert</n>    <k>When old college friends meet again they take the time to rekindle and explore each other?s bodies and sexual boundries. A reunion you don?t want to miss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 03:24:00" d="2020-05-19 03:53:00"><n>Pure Thoughts: Roma Amor &amp; Lutro</n>    <k>Welcome to Pure Thoughts, Daring! Pure's newest installment, which reveals the depths, passion and boundaries of loving couples. The brain is an organ</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 03:53:00" d="2020-05-19 04:14:00"><n>Special Moments: The Shower</n><t>L</t>    <k>Watch how this couple shares a steamy shower. A romantic sex scene by Dusk TV's Porn for women label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women, sensuous films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 04:14:00" d="2020-05-19 04:34:00"><n>Friends And Lovers: Brett Rossi &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Caroline and Matt have been best friends since college. Through break-ups they've been there for each other. But they have yet to find true love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 04:34:00" d="2020-05-19 04:48:00"><n>Let me see your ponytail swing, I Want a Viking Warrior</n><t>S</t>    <k>She wishes he was a viking warrior, he wishes she'd dress up like a cheerleader. So what happens when they do? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 04:48:00" d="2020-05-19 05:08:00"><n>Oasis: Melody Jordan &amp; Derrick Pierce</n>    <k>A secluded oasis with design furniture appears to be the perfect place to have passionate sex. A scene from an Intimate Encounters film</k>  </p>
</a>
