<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="54" t="2021-07-09 07:42:54"><p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 05:23:00" d="2021-07-14 05:48:00"><n>Love Me Forever: Lily Cat &amp; Vega</n><t>L</t>    <k>Romantic, passionate love. These couples show each other how much they enjoy each others company. A romantic porn video by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 05:48:00" d="2021-07-14 06:11:00"><n>Pleasure Fix: Kali Sudhra, Bishop Black &amp; Nat Portnoy</n>    <k>Sex can be hard to talk about. Pleasure Fix is an app designed to help couples explore their sexuality by trying new things. Sexy porn for women by Joybear pictures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 06:11:00" d="2021-07-14 06:34:00"><n>Il Lungo Addio</n>    <k>Juan is bidding farewell to Cayenne as he drops her off at the station. But as Cayenne heads off with her luggage, and Lucho walks sadly away, the blonde</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 06:34:00" d="2021-07-14 06:57:00"><n>Positions: Fourth</n>    <k>While finding inspiration at a dancer's retreat, the ballet dancer Florence soon realises she's not the only one who could do with practising</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 06:57:00" d="2021-07-14 07:03:00"><n>Momentum 1: A day at the beach</n>    <k>Australian film maker Michelle Flynn has the most distinctive style within the alternative porn genre. Her debut film Momentum is a cinematic intimacy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 07:03:00" d="2021-07-14 07:31:00"><n>Facade: Keira Nicole &amp; James Deen</n>    <k>Amber and her friend Lindsay are average college students?who happen to moonlight as sexy webcam models. This complicates things when they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 07:31:00" d="2021-07-14 07:43:00"><n>A Feminist Man</n><t>S</t>    <k>Is there anything sexier than a man who can give perfect cunnilingus and have a conversation about Judith Butler? From the XConfessions series by Erika</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 07:43:00" d="2021-07-14 08:05:00"><n>Slutish: Kylie &amp; Jason</n><t>L</t>    <k>Kylie's first boyfriend taught her that monogamy doesn't have to be boring. Even when couples are apart there are plenty of ways to keep a relationship interesting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 08:05:00" d="2021-07-14 08:32:00"><n>Come Closer: My Sunny Side</n>    <k>What are you going to do when all of a suddon both of you are at home and have nothing to do? Exactly, enjoy each other and make your time together worthwhile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 08:32:00" d="2021-07-14 08:59:00"><n>Massage Room: Emma &amp; Alex</n>    <k>Please lay down, make yourself comfortable and make sure you are totally relaxed. Once the masseur starts their job, you only can think of one thing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 08:59:00" d="2021-07-14 09:30:00"><n>The Babysitter 8: Dillion Harper &amp; James Deen</n>    <k>Mona is a bitter woman who hates her ex-husband and has no qualms about bad mouthing him to her new babysitter, Alice. What happens when Alice catches</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 09:30:00" d="2021-07-14 10:02:00"><n>I Love My Hotwife: Romi Rain, Toni Ribas &amp; Otto Bauer</n>    <k>Four segments on the sexual fantasies of husbands and wives. A married couple hires a sexy male escort, Siri let?s her husband listen to her sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 10:02:00" d="2021-07-14 10:23:00"><n>The Engagement Party: Reena Sky &amp; Ramon Nomar</n>    <k>Carey?s engagement party takes an interesting turn when unexpected, mysterious guest arrives. A romantic porn for women scene from New Sensations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 10:23:00" d="2021-07-14 10:37:00"><n>Red Light: Lea Lexis &amp; Derrick Pierce</n>    <k>Red Light is like a waking dream set in the streets of Los Angeles. It's the story of a woman's transformation into her true self, and a wild chase</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 10:37:00" d="2021-07-14 11:03:00"><n>Secret Sex Society: Julia De Lucia &amp; Bishop Black</n>    <k>When colourful people meet and share their colourful fantasies. Starring the hot blooded Spanish beauty Julia Roca</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 11:03:00" d="2021-07-14 11:14:00"><n>Eat with me</n><t>S</t>    <k>Be fed all your deepest and most delicious desires by a gorgeous celeb chef. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 11:14:00" d="2021-07-14 11:40:00"><n>Once In A Blue Moon: Nikky Dream &amp; Lupro</n>    <k>In the blue light of the moon various couples love all parts of each other?s bodies on quiet spots in alleys, on rooftops and in fields. A Sinful production</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 11:40:00" d="2021-07-14 11:56:00"><n>Pleasure Fix: Kali Sudhra, Nat Portnoy &amp; Bishop Black</n>    <k>Sex can be hard to talk about. Pleasure Fix is an app designed to help couples explore their sexuality by trying new things. Sexy porn for women by Joybear pictures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 11:56:00" d="2021-07-14 12:19:00"><n>Sexy and Sensual: Sheri Vee &amp; Nikolas</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. A porn for women scene from Sexy and Sensual by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 12:19:00" d="2021-07-14 12:39:00"><n>Till Sex Do Us Part: Orgy</n>    <k>Helen is a young actress at the best of her life, she's got the job she likes, good friends and a well positioned boyfriend. However Helen's life changes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 12:39:00" d="2021-07-14 12:53:00"><n>Win A Date With Sofia Blake: Olivia Austin &amp; Ryan Mclean</n>    <k>A-list Hollywood actress Sofia Blake (Olivia Austin) is having the worst day of her life and the paparazzi have made sure to plaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 12:53:00" d="2021-07-14 13:11:00"><n>K</n>    <k>Inspiration can reach us when we are less expecting it. The simple vision of a white sheet of paper stresses me a bit as I am a writer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 13:11:00" d="2021-07-14 13:29:00"><n>Delilahs Top Tips: Emma Leigh &amp; Alexei Jackson</n><t>O</t>    <k>Delilah is the nation's naughtiest agony aunt dedicated to solving the nation's more. ntimate dilemmas. She whips two city workers into a frenzy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 13:29:00" d="2021-07-14 13:59:00"><n>So Wet Beside Her: Tina Kay &amp; Timea Bella</n>    <k>These girls love, lust, lick, becoming almost one in this sensual piece of erotica. Sinful Studio making art again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 13:59:00" d="2021-07-14 14:25:00"><n>Oral Reflections</n><t>L</t>    <k>Always wanted to know about anal sex, but never tried? This romantic porn film shows how nice anal massage can be</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 14:25:00" d="2021-07-14 14:35:00"><n>Cybersex</n><t>S</t>    <k>Can cybersex be more stimulating than the real thing? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual confessions of her viewers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 14:35:00" d="2021-07-14 14:56:00"><n>Bed Of Roses</n>    <k>A romance is a dynamic, ever-changing, constantly evolving relationship. &quot;Bed of Roses&quot; celebrates that blissful period in a couple's life when attraction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 14:56:00" d="2021-07-14 15:10:00"><n>Till Sex Do Us Part: Lady May &amp; Lesly Kiss</n>    <k>Helen is a young actress at the best of her life, she's got the job she likes, good friends and a well positioned boyfriend. However Helen's life changes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 15:10:00" d="2021-07-14 15:29:00"><n>Indecent Girls: Riley &amp; Avery</n>    <k>These hot couples are exploring their sexlives and they are definitely interested to try some new things</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 15:29:00" d="2021-07-14 15:47:00"><n>Delilahs Top Tips: Jess West &amp; Danielle Ashlea Maye</n><t>L</t>    <k>Delilah is the nation's naughtiest agony aunt dedicated to solving the nation's more. ntimate dilemmas. She shows a pretty young teacher how to get closer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 15:47:00" d="2021-07-14 16:07:00"><n>Sexy And Sensual 2: Sonia Sweet &amp; Vincent</n>    <k>Sensual but kind of naughty. These beautiful and sexy couples take you on a journey to their romantic escapades. Loving porn for couples by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 16:07:00" d="2021-07-14 16:47:00"><n>Darker Side of Desire: Cherie DeVille &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>When Natalie meets the perfect guy, she is afraid to scare him away with her deviant desires. Maybe the safest way to explore these intense desires</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 16:47:00" d="2021-07-14 17:03:00"><n>From Beyond: Monka Mora &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>Sofia is mourning her beloved husband, but still feels him everywhere in their house. Is he haunting her for a reason? Her best friend helps Sofia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 17:03:00" d="2021-07-14 17:41:00"><n>The Stepmother 8: Kendra Lust &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>Billy and Julia are getting close to marriage, but each have a single parent who?s loneliness is ruining their peace. But the real problem arises when Billy can?t stop thinking about Julia?s gorgeous mother, Theresa. Will Theresa settle for quiet companionship, or will she succumb to lust for the vibrant young man. A Sweet Sinner?s daring look into forbidden passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 17:41:00" d="2021-07-14 17:52:00"><n>Titty Titty Bang Bang</n><t>S</t>    <k>Miriam Prado is feeling like dancing. Breasts will jiggle and sparks will fly. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 17:52:00" d="2021-07-14 18:31:00"><n>Black And Blue: Erik Everhard &amp; Janice Griffith</n><t>L</t>    <k>In this tale of submission and dominance, wealthy businessman Patrick introduces young Alison to the world of BDSM. When they fall in lover it shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 18:31:00" d="2021-07-14 18:54:00"><n>Positions: First</n>    <k>While finding inspiration at a dancer?s retreat, the ballet dancer Florence soon realises she?s not the only one who could do with practising</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 18:54:00" d="2021-07-14 19:22:00"><n>Tenderness: Ria Sunn &amp; Jayden Cox</n>    <k>A erotic massage scene by Dusk TV's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Romantic porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 19:22:00" d="2021-07-14 19:59:00"><n>The Passionate Three: Vanessa Decker, Jayden &amp; Pavlos</n>    <k>Sinful trinity's enjoying a triad of erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 19:59:00" d="2021-07-14 20:18:00"><n>Heavy Contact</n>    <k>That feeling when you have a lot of contact with someone and the connection gets even heavier when you meet in real life? Yes, that's passion to the max</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 20:18:00" d="2021-07-14 20:42:00"><n>Dude Looks Like A Lady</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: A girl gets a kick from dressing her boyfriend up as a lady. In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 20:42:00" d="2021-07-14 21:12:00"><n>Beauty Of Nature: Eveline Dellai &amp; Nick Vargas</n><t>L</t>    <k>Wondering what it take to have fantastic sex that you will remmeber for the rest of your life? Watch and learn as Desire Media shows you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 21:12:00" d="2021-07-14 21:34:00"><n>Sensuous Seduction: The Imaginary Boyfriend</n>    <k>Who is your imaginary boyfriend? A sex scene by Lara Tinelli for Dusk TV's' female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 21:34:00" d="2021-07-14 22:09:00"><n>Jungleicious: Aaron Rock &amp; Antonia Saintz</n>    <k>Together alone, in a dense forest, Stacy treats her date to a dinner with a view</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 22:09:00" d="2021-07-14 22:19:00"><n>Magic Magnus</n><t>S</t>    <k>There's nothing like a man who dares to do a bit of dancing in order to spice things up, right? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 22:19:00" d="2021-07-14 22:42:00"><n>Confessions Of A Sound Girl: Living The Dream</n>    <k>Ever wondered what porn performers would actually get up to on set if they were in charge? Happy-go-lucky sound girl Ru gets a front row seat behind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 22:42:00" d="2021-07-14 23:13:00"><n>Sure Feels Right: Emma Starletto &amp; Ryan Mclane</n>    <k>Sometimes love is found in the most unlikely places and maybe the one that you're with isn't necessarily the one that you were destined for. Four sensual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 23:13:00" d="2021-07-15 01:03:00"><n>Camera Angle</n>    <k>Fiction and reality seem to blend when Hollywood actor Peter gets a concussion. His visions of heart-racing, sweat inducing sex seem very real though.</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 01:03:00" d="2021-07-15 03:02:00"><n>I Love My Hotwife</n>    <k>Four segments on the sexual fantasies of husbands and wives. A married couple hires a sexy male escort, Siri let?s her husband listen to her sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 03:02:00" d="2021-07-15 03:31:00"><n>My Love For you: Vinna Reed &amp; Lutro</n>    <k>A sex film by Roma Woodcock for Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 03:31:00" d="2021-07-15 03:52:00"><n>Secret Sex Society 2: All I want For Christmas</n>    <k>A mysterious invitation gives Emmy the chance to live out her fantasies. In The Game you can be anyone you want, with whoever you want but where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 03:52:00" d="2021-07-15 04:20:00"><n>I Love You: Blanche Bradburry &amp; Nick Ross</n>    <k>These beautiful desireable men and women are highly confident and have all the experience to bring you in a state of trance. A erotic porn film by Desire media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 04:20:00" d="2021-07-15 04:33:00"><n>Girlfriends: Casey Calvert &amp; Sasha Heart</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Small town girl Jamie (Casey Calvert) has made the difficult decision to tell her parents that she is in a same sex relationship. Unfortunately her family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-15 04:33:00" d="2021-07-15 05:02:00"><n>So Wet Beside Her: Victoria Pure &amp; Charlie Red</n>    <k>These girls love, lust, lick, becoming almost one in this sensual piece of erotica. Sinful Studio making art again</k>  </p>
</a>
