<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="63" t="2020-04-12 04:36:47"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 05:03:00" d="2020-04-19 05:31:00"><n>Sensuous Seduction: In the Evening</n>    <k>A scene from a romantic sex film by Lara Tinelli for Dusk TV's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 05:31:00" d="2020-04-19 06:02:00"><n>Colors Of Eden: Cecilia Scott &amp; Angelo</n><t>L</t>    <k>A gorgeous couple having breathtakingly hot sex, in colorful surroundings, showing both intimacy and sexual fulfilment in every little detail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 06:02:00" d="2020-04-19 06:21:00"><n>Delilahs Top Tips: Victoria Summers &amp; Ryan Ryder</n><t>O</t>    <k>Delilah is the nation's naughtiest agony aunt dedicated to solving the nation's more. ntimate dilemmas. She whips two city workers into a frenzy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 06:21:00" d="2020-04-19 06:39:00"><n>Camera Angle: Ivy Labelle &amp; Roman Nomar</n>    <k>Fiction and reality seem to blend when Hollywood actor Peter gets a concussion. His visions of heart-racing, sweat inducing sex seem very real though</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 06:39:00" d="2020-04-19 06:57:00"><n>Arousal</n>    <k>If you ever wondered why everybody wants to make threesomes with these two? Super sexy porn for women by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 06:57:00" d="2020-04-19 07:30:00"><n>Remy Loves Girls: Remy LaCroix &amp; Dani Daniels</n>    <k>Sweetheart proudly presents Performer of the year Remy La Croix. In the tradition of this title, Remy has chosen four of her favorite girls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 07:30:00" d="2020-04-19 07:53:00"><n>Sweet Memories: Together</n>    <k>A short erotic story by Lara Tinelli for female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting realistic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 07:53:00" d="2020-04-19 08:25:00"><n>Silver Shoes: Undressed</n>    <k>This award-winning explicit erotic trilogy from Jennifer Lyon Bell intertwines three short female friendly porn stories about the carnal power of what we wear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 08:25:00" d="2020-04-19 08:37:00"><n>Madmen Porn</n><t>S</t>    <k>Have you ever wondered what Don Draper's cock might be like? Find out in this fan fiction inspired short! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 08:37:00" d="2020-04-19 09:01:00"><n>Weekend: Katy Rose, Lexi Dona &amp; Dominica Phoenix</n>    <k>Shot in Portugal, episode 4 of The Weekend, &quot;Time for Love,&quot; begins with a new day. As Lutro and Dominika prepare breakfast, Lexie and Jason are enjoying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 09:01:00" d="2020-04-19 09:24:00"><n>Getting Cozy: Allie Haze &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>Recently single Marisa is unwillingly sent on a blind date by her best friend. After a few cocktails things get out of hand and Marisa wakes up in his bed? Due to an ice storm she cannot leave his appartment, and spends the weekend. A film from Wicked Pictures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 09:24:00" d="2020-04-19 09:50:00"><n>First Summer Love 2: Radek Chigsantor &amp; Samantha Joons</n><t>L</t>    <k>The temperature is not the only thing that rises. Love is in the air. The passion these couples show you is as warm as the sun - it's their &quot;first summer love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 09:50:00" d="2020-04-19 10:14:00"><n>Inside: Julia Roca &amp; Natalia Ferrari</n>    <k>Welcome to The Retreat: where curious minds come to play. Plug in and turn on to explore a virtual reality experience where you can be anyone, go anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 10:14:00" d="2020-04-19 10:27:00"><n>Let me see your ponytail swing, I Want a Viking Warrior</n><t>S</t>    <k>She wishes he was a viking warrior, he wishes she'd dress up like a cheerleader. So what happens when they do? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 10:27:00" d="2020-04-19 10:48:00"><n>Friends And Lovers: Brett Rossi &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Caroline and Matt have been best friends since college. Through break-ups they've been there for each other. But they have yet to find true love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 10:48:00" d="2020-04-19 11:14:00"><n>Her Desire: Sleeping</n>    <k>Dusk TV presents: porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion. A pleasure to all the senses representing realistic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 11:14:00" d="2020-04-19 11:20:00"><n>Before The Guests Arrive</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: Against the clock, this couple engage in a hot quickie before their dinner guests arrive! In XConfessions, people from all around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 11:20:00" d="2020-04-19 11:55:00"><n>Mother Daughter affair: Chanel Preston &amp; Steven St. Croix</n>    <k>Eric has an interesting dilemma. He?s going with a smoking hot woman who has an over-sexed erotic devilish daughter, he just can?t resist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 11:55:00" d="2020-04-19 12:16:00"><n>The Guesthouse: Clea Gaultier &amp; Anthony Gaultier</n>    <k>Nestled in the Spanish countryside, there?s a Guesthouse where visitors enjoy more than just the sunshine on their bodies. Come alone, come with a friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 12:16:00" d="2020-04-19 12:40:00"><n>Love Me Forever: Lily Cat &amp; Vega</n><t>L</t>    <k>Romantic, passionate love. These couples show each other how much they enjoy each others company. A romantic porn video by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 12:40:00" d="2020-04-19 13:08:00"><n>My Love For you: Vinna Reed &amp; Lutro</n>    <k>A sex film by Roma Woodcock for Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 13:08:00" d="2020-04-19 13:21:00"><n>Some never awaken</n><t>S</t>    <k>Experience a sexual awakening through dance, movement, and passionate sex. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 13:21:00" d="2020-04-19 13:43:00"><n>First Summer Love 2: Eliska &amp; Sweet Cat</n>    <k>The sequel of First Summer Love brings you more tantalizing scenes. The hot sun on their naked skin brings these girls in a state of permanent arousal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 13:43:00" d="2020-04-19 14:15:00"><n>The Passionate Three: Evelyn Dellai, Jean, Angel Piaff</n>    <k>Sinful trinity's enjoying a triad of erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 14:15:00" d="2020-04-19 14:52:00"><n>Couples Massage: Nicole Love &amp; Lutro</n>    <k>A crackling fire, relaxing music and a lot of warm oil for a total body massage. Delicious. These beautiful couples can’t get enough of it too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 14:52:00" d="2020-04-19 15:25:00"><n>I Love My Hotwife: Romi Rain, Toni Ribas &amp; Otto Bauer</n>    <k>Four segments on the sexual fantasies of husbands and wives. A married couple hires a sexy male escort, Siri let?s her husband listen to her sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 15:25:00" d="2020-04-19 15:48:00"><n>Potter In Love</n>    <k>Today we are are getting creative with clay, a dirty and exciting endeavor! Porn for women by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 15:48:00" d="2020-04-19 16:07:00"><n>Exposure: Touch Me</n>    <k>In a world where couples would rather play with their phones than each other, one woman uses her technology skills for good, nudging distracted lovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 16:07:00" d="2020-04-19 16:23:00"><n>I found your mother on tinder</n><t>S</t>    <k>The legendary Mrs. Robinson brought to life by the most modern of dating apps. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 16:23:00" d="2020-04-19 16:46:00"><n>Room 208: Julia Roca &amp; Sylvan Garcia</n>    <k>Would you like to be a pornstar? Watch how these beautiful performers reach full excitement and true pleasure. A beautiful porn for women film by Dusk TV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 16:46:00" d="2020-04-19 17:04:00"><n>Love Lust Longing: Allie Haze &amp; Jake Jace</n>    <k>Love Lust &amp; Longing takes place in a seemingly innocent Bed &amp; Breakfast. Rachel a prostitute who has set up shop in the master bedroom falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 17:04:00" d="2020-04-19 17:41:00"><n>Lesbian Surrender: Elle Alexandra &amp; Sovereign Syre</n>    <k>Watch as tattooed angel Ela Darling realizes her taboo fantasies, how French stunner Nikita Bellucci barely speaks English and how blond bombshell Aaliyah</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 17:41:00" d="2020-04-19 17:59:00"><n>Come With Me</n>    <k>Come with me, or cum with me? An super sexy female friendly porn film by Verso Cinema with breathtaking orgasms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 17:59:00" d="2020-04-19 18:19:00"><n>Pleasure Professionals 2: Samantha Bentley &amp; Alexei Jackson</n>    <k>A high quality couple's porn scene from Joybear. A secluded hotel provides the perfect getaway. With an air of mystery surrounding the elegant guest others</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 18:19:00" d="2020-04-19 18:47:00"><n>I'm Obsessed with Owen Gray</n><t>S</t>    <k>What would happen if your first time having sex on screen was with a pornstar you were totally obsessed with? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 18:47:00" d="2020-04-19 19:08:00"><n>4 Passionate Women: Feeling Hot</n>    <k>A porn for women scene by Award Winning director Lara Tinelli for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit female friendly porn , sensuous films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 19:08:00" d="2020-04-19 19:40:00"><n>Home Coming: Home for Diner</n>    <k>Oh, home sweet home. These couples experience that there's no place like home to come back to, especially since orgasms are awaiting them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 19:40:00" d="2020-04-19 19:58:00"><n>Dacrifilia</n><t>S</t>    <k>An artist brings a man to tears to fulfil her fetish - dacryphilia. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 19:58:00" d="2020-04-19 20:20:00"><n>At First Sight: Ryan Driller &amp; Allison Moore</n>    <k>Laura (Kaylani Lei) is a cute, hardworking waitress. Josh (Ryan Driller) is a handsome, famous actor. When Josh spots her from across a crowded nightclub, he's hooked</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 20:20:00" d="2020-04-19 20:34:00"><n>The Fantasy Project: Madison Missina &amp; Ryan James</n>    <k>Kate Eden?s research into female sexual fantasies leads her deep into the erotic imagination of women, a lush world of pleasure without consequences. But will Kate?s passion for her work lead her to lose herself ? and her relationship? A female friendly porn film by Louise Lush</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 20:34:00" d="2020-04-19 21:04:00"><n>Beauty Of Nature: Eveline Dellai &amp; Nick Vargas</n><t>L</t>    <k>Wondering what it take to have fantastic sex that you will remmeber for the rest of your life? Watch and learn as Desire Media shows you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 21:04:00" d="2020-04-19 21:27:00"><n>Question</n>    <k>Thomas stands on the street. When Ferrera joins him we soon learn what he was anticipating. He drops to one knee, holds up a shiny little box, and after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 21:27:00" d="2020-04-19 21:42:00"><n>Unbridled: Alana Cruise &amp; Dick Chibbles</n>    <k>To save her family’s ranch, city girl Avery has to return to Texas and face her demons and her old flame horse trainer Grant. Stormy Daniels stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 21:42:00" d="2020-04-19 21:58:00"><n>Red Light: Chanel Preston &amp; Damon Dice</n>    <k>Red Light is like a waking dream set in the streets of Los Angeles. It's the story of a woman's transformation into her true self, and a wild chase</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 21:58:00" d="2020-04-19 22:20:00"><n>Girls Sex Tricks: Carol Vega &amp; Didac Durán</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us on her first female friendly porn film as director for Thagson with a vibrant story which will take place in the streets of Barcelona</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 22:20:00" d="2020-04-19 22:42:00"><n>Sex With Friends: Dessert</n>    <k>When old college friends meet again they take the time to rekindle and explore each other?s bodies and sexual boundries. A reunion you don?t want to miss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 22:42:00" d="2020-04-19 23:11:00"><n>Surreal Encounters: Luna Corazon &amp; Steve Q</n>    <k>All Space &amp;Time Is Lost When Mysterious Lovers Meet. Steve finds luck in an oyster: a beautiful, black pearl. for him to cherish and to keep, to taste and to please</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 23:11:00" d="2020-04-19 23:27:00" c="1"><n>The Possession Of Mrs Hyde: Avi Love &amp; Ramon Nomar</n><t>F</t>    <k>The Possession of Mrs. Hyde is Axel Braun's first non-parody feature in 15 years and his most ambitious movie to date. Shot entirely in Black and White</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 23:27:00" d="2020-04-19 23:50:00"><n>A Sensual Touch: Amarna Miller &amp; Max Deeds</n>    <k>Intimate lovers escape the stresses of every day life and spend some relaxing time together. Couples pamper each other with erotic massage and intense sexual pleasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-19 23:50:00" d="2020-04-20 00:14:00"><n>Breakfast for Two</n>    <k>These girlfriends just wanna have fun. With each other. Especially while having a sleepover. A female friendly porn production by Dusk porn-TV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 00:14:00" d="2020-04-20 00:37:00"><n>Everyday Turn-Ons: Oral Fixation</n><t>L</t>    <k>Nelson loves the taste of Jackie?s body, but since her last boyfriend never went down on her, she?s become shy and self-conscious about oral sex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 00:37:00" d="2020-04-20 01:07:00"><n>Desire: Tasha Reign &amp; Johnny Castle</n>    <k>Intense feelings of desire causes two bodies melting into one, shivering of pleasure with every touch and longing for more. A female friendly porn scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 01:07:00" d="2020-04-20 01:17:00"><n>Chicazo</n><t>S</t>    <k>Luna Corazón will expose herself entirely for this show - only to dress herself again once it's all over. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 01:17:00" d="2020-04-20 01:36:00"><n>Sun stroke: Michelle And Jade</n>    <k>These girls are trying to beat the spanish summer heat at their beautiful summerhouse in the woods. But cooling down appears to be a major challenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 01:36:00" d="2020-04-20 01:59:00"><n>Firestarter</n>    <k>Firestarter opens with a frenzied, frenetic explosion of visual and aural energy. Once the couple is behind closed doors the scene shifts from a rolling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 01:59:00" d="2020-04-20 02:31:00"><n>Sexy and Sensual: Mary Dee &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A romantic sex scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 02:31:00" d="2020-04-20 02:56:00"><n>Tenderness: Keira &amp; Chriss Tom</n>    <k>A beautiful scene by Dusk TV's own female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real romantic sex and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 02:56:00" d="2020-04-20 03:17:00"><n>Make Me Sweat: Figi &amp; Anna</n>    <k>This super hot porn for women scene by Sinful XXX hold the human body as a piece of art, and super hot sex as a masterpiece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 03:17:00" d="2020-04-20 03:42:00"><n>Secret Sex Society: Sicilia &amp; Sylvan</n>    <k>When colourful people meet and share their colourful fantasies. Starring the hot blooded Spanish beauty Julia Roca</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 03:42:00" d="2020-04-20 04:04:00"><n>Love and Loss: Maddy O'Reilly &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>With more twists and turns than the German autobahn, Love and Loss follows the story of Lanie and Alex, an ex-cop involved in the shooting of Lanie's ex-lover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 04:04:00" d="2020-04-20 04:24:00"><n>Stair Love</n>    <k>Yet another cinematic Spanish female friendly porn scene from Verso Cinema featuring the super popular and multiply awarded Carolina Abril. Don't miss this encounter!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 04:24:00" d="2020-04-20 04:59:00"><n>The Teacher 4: Kastie St. Ives &amp; Joey Brass</n>    <k>Physicist Manuel Ferrara is on the verge of solving physics? biggest mysteries, and smitten young students treat him like a rock star. Obsessive young</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-20 04:59:00" d="2020-04-20 05:23:00"><n>Special Moments: The Second Date</n>    <k>What happens after the second date? Find out in this new romantic sex scene by AlexanFilm for Dusk TV's own female friendly porn label: Ooh la la</k>  </p>
</a>
