<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="61" t="2021-07-08 05:10:35"><p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 05:04:00" d="2021-07-13 05:30:00"><n>Brothers and Sisters 2: Ava Taylor &amp; Erik Everhard</n>    <k>Keisha Grey has the biggest crush on her step brother (Christian). She likes to play with herself in hoping that her step brother (Christian) walks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 05:30:00" d="2021-07-13 05:56:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies: Liona &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Sexy beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A porn for women scene from Favorite Fantasies by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 05:56:00" d="2021-07-13 06:18:00"><n>Close To The Bone: Cherry Kiss &amp; Matt Bird</n>    <k>Two immortal lovers are feeling the three-hundred-year-itch. As night falls the city becomes a playground for Jonus and Bryana, both seeking to quench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 06:18:00" d="2021-07-13 06:41:00"><n>Sex is for Lovers: Denise &amp; Renato</n>    <k>Indulge yourself in female friendly porn with an emphasis on passion, lovers, and true romance. Their inspiration is not found in anonymous encounters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 06:41:00" d="2021-07-13 07:03:00"><n>Housemates 3: Decoupled</n>    <k>Synopsis not available</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 07:03:00" d="2021-07-13 07:20:00"><n>The Fantasy Project: Vivienne L, Max &amp; Harley Jay</n><t>L</t>    <k>Have you ever been in a threesome? These three lovers show what it could be like if your fantasies came true. This erotic video by Louise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 07:20:00" d="2021-07-13 07:39:00"><n>Unbridled: Rachel Starr &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>To save her family’s ranch, city girl Avery has to return to Texas and face her demons and her old flame horse trainer Grant. Stormy Daniels stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 07:39:00" d="2021-07-13 07:51:00"><n>Romance Bullshit</n>    <k>From XConfessions 3: Every writer in the room types frantically, but she is just not inspired. Until she sees him. In XConfessions, people from all around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 07:51:00" d="2021-07-13 08:15:00"><n>Close To The Bone: Azazie Skymm &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Two immortal lovers are feeling the three-hundred-year-itch. As night falls the city becomes a playground for Jonus and Bryana, both seeking to quench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 08:15:00" d="2021-07-13 08:49:00"><n>Playful passion</n><t>L</t>    <k>A porn for women scene by former Playmate of the World, Zimra Geurts, for Dusk TV's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Jane von Detta has an exciting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 08:49:00" d="2021-07-13 09:19:00"><n>Hot Water: Francys Belle &amp; Steve Q</n>    <k>Licking, sucking, kissing, thrusting, touching, stroking, becoming one with each other in hot water. A sexual and visual delight by Studio Sinfull</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 09:19:00" d="2021-07-13 09:51:00"><n>Mother Daughter affair: Jodi Taylor &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>Eric has an interesting dilemma. He?s going with a smoking hot woman who has an over-sexed erotic devilish daughter, he just can?t resist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 09:51:00" d="2021-07-13 10:19:00"><n>Trying New Things: Sarah Luvv &amp; Donnie Rock</n>    <k>Passions explode when a sexually frustrated Alison asks her fiancé to take her virginity two weeks before their wedding day. Sara discovers that adult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 10:19:00" d="2021-07-13 10:47:00"><n>Office Love Affairs: Luna Rival &amp; Ben Kelly</n>    <k>Do you fantasize about your co-workers and what might happen between you and them? Watch how the heat in this office is turned up by 2 beautiful people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 10:47:00" d="2021-07-13 11:02:00"><n>From The First Moment: Alix Lynx &amp; Damon Dice</n>    <k>Kira (Alix Lynx) is about to marry her handsome movie star boyfriend James except he gets cold feet and leaves her at the wedding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 11:02:00" d="2021-07-13 11:19:00"><n>The Guesthouse: Bianca Resa &amp; Juan Lucho</n>    <k>Nestled in the Spanish countryside, there?s a Guesthouse where visitors enjoy more than just the sunshine on their bodies. Come alone, come with a friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 11:19:00" d="2021-07-13 11:41:00"><n>Sweet but Psycho</n><t>S</t>    <k>Four of the hottest and most popular performers on the scene create a hilarious and erotic film. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 11:41:00" d="2021-07-13 12:13:00"><n>Girls Crush: Constanze Berankova &amp; Nicole Dandova</n>    <k>These girls love, lust, lick, becoming almost one in this sensual piece of erotica. Sinful Studio making art again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 12:13:00" d="2021-07-13 12:31:00"><n>Exposure: New MSG!</n>    <k>In a world where couples would rather play with their phones than each other, one woman uses her technology skills for good, nudging distracted lovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 12:31:00" d="2021-07-13 12:55:00"><n>Anal Adventure: Dolce Vita &amp; Vincent Vega</n>    <k>Wondering what it takes to have that fantastic sex that you will remember for the rest of your life? These beautiful desirable couples are highly confident</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 12:55:00" d="2021-07-13 13:23:00"><n>Till Sex Do Us Part: Dunia Montenegro, Lesly Kiss &amp; David Galant</n>    <k>Helen is a young actress at the best of her life, she's got the job she likes, good friends and a well positioned boyfriend. However Helen's life changes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 13:23:00" d="2021-07-13 13:35:00"><n>Summer Loving: Nicole Aniston &amp; Bill Bailey</n>    <k>The attractive Keiko is bored in the tiny village where she grew up and longs for some excitement. Until a stranger arrives in the village</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 13:35:00" d="2021-07-13 13:59:00"><n>Potter In Love</n>    <k>Today we are are getting creative with clay, a dirty and exciting endeavor! Porn for women by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 13:59:00" d="2021-07-13 14:17:00"><n>The Guesthouse: Julia De Lucia &amp; Miguel Zayas</n>    <k>Porn for women by Joybear. Nestled in the Spanish countryside, there?s a Guesthouse where visitors enjoy more than just the sunshine on their bodies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 14:17:00" d="2021-07-13 14:57:00"><n>Hot Water: Vanessa Decker &amp; Ricky Rascal</n>    <k>Licking, sucking, kissing, thrusting, touching, stroking, becoming one with each other in hot water. A sexual and visual delight by Studio Sinfull</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 14:57:00" d="2021-07-13 15:16:00"><n u="Ages of Sex: Sex at">Ages of Sex: Sex at (40)</n>    <k>The Ages of Sex is a porn for women film by Thagson. 4 Well known directors will direct a short which represents a woman?s sexual reality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 15:16:00" d="2021-07-13 16:04:00"><n>Feminist &amp; Submissive</n><t>S</t>    <k>Can you be a feminist and submissive? A round table discussion accompanies a sensual BDSM scene. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 16:04:00" d="2021-07-13 16:28:00"><n>Lost In A Dream</n>    <k>Roca and Tomas are relaxing poolside when they kiss and caress with vigorous passion. As the autoerotic activities increase in intensity the devoid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 16:28:00" d="2021-07-13 16:49:00"><n>Apolonia's Musical Fantasies 1: Girlfriends</n>    <k>Apolonia Lapiedra is a beautiful Spanish spinner who is a classic example of good girl gone bad. In this scene, two gorgeous girls, Apolonia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 16:49:00" d="2021-07-13 17:20:00"><n>Colors Of Eden: Cecilia Scott &amp; Angelo</n><t>L</t>    <k>A gorgeous couple having breathtakingly hot sex, in colorful surroundings, showing both intimacy and sexual fulfilment in every little detail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 17:20:00" d="2021-07-13 17:43:00"><n>Ball Control: Rebecca More &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>They say that football is a man’s world, but there’s one Milf on this pitch with all the power. Physio Eva puts her massage skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 17:43:00" d="2021-07-13 18:06:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies 2: Miranda &amp; Joe T</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A female friendly porn scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 18:06:00" d="2021-07-13 18:34:00"><n>Student bodies 2: Casey Calvert &amp; Chad Alva</n>    <k>Kyra hates everything - school, the teachers, and especially Zadie who is messing around with the boy she?d like to date. It?s time to get busy and screw</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 18:34:00" d="2021-07-13 18:59:00"><n>Making Ends Meet: Mercedes Carrera &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>A suburbian family is in destress over money, but sex seems to really heal the wounds. Scorching hot sex and sharp comedy blend perfectly in a female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 18:59:00" d="2021-07-13 19:28:00"><n>My Girlfriends Mother 11: Marley Brinx &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>When Tylers sexy but demanding girlfriend Marley cheats on him, he takes solace in the arms and incredible hot body of Marley?s mom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 19:28:00" d="2021-07-13 19:44:00"><n>Coming of age</n><t>S</t>    <k>A coming of age tale of young lust, farewells and new encounters. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 19:44:00" d="2021-07-13 20:11:00"><n>Tales from the Heart: Carter Cruise &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>Love is in the air. specially on your Anniversary. A trip down memory lane is just the spark Michelle and Andy need to reignite the lustful feelings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 20:11:00" d="2021-07-13 20:37:00"><n>Secret Sex Society: Julia Roca &amp; Sylvan</n>    <k>When colourful people meet and share their colourful fantasies. Starring the hot blooded Spanish beauty Julia Roca</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 20:37:00" d="2021-07-13 21:02:00"><n>I Am All Yours: Eveline Neil &amp; Marcel Lee</n>    <k>A romantic film by Dawn for Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 21:02:00" d="2021-07-13 21:32:00"><n>Surreal Encounters: Luna Corazon &amp; Steve Q</n>    <k>All Space &amp;Time Is Lost When Mysterious Lovers Meet. Steve finds luck in an oyster: a beautiful, black pearl. for him to cherish and to keep, to taste and to please</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 21:32:00" d="2021-07-13 21:53:00"><n>On Bed</n>    <k>A young couple really enjoys each other while on bed. Kissing, licking, touching and moaning. A delicious female friendly porn video by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 21:53:00" d="2021-07-13 22:06:00"><n>Ibiza Splash Crush</n><t>S</t>    <k>One the most forbidden and oldest mythical taboos: a merman. Seduced by a gorgeous lifeguard in the blistering Ibiza sun. From the XConfessions series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 22:06:00" d="2021-07-13 22:35:00"><n>Soft And Sweet 2: Lady Dee &amp; Max D</n>    <k>Did you ever notice the softness of your lovers skin, the sweet taste when you move your tongue over her well formed sensual body? A porn for women film by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 22:35:00" d="2021-07-13 23:06:00"><n>Come Closer: Friday Night</n>    <k>A real life straight couple with real life sex. A romantic porn video by Dusk TV's own porn for women label</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 23:06:00" d="2021-07-13 23:37:00"><n>The Artist: Max Deeds &amp; Eveline Dellai</n>    <k>Another beautiful production by Studio Sinful, containing lots of close-ups, artistic lighting and delicious performers. In The Artist a man is sensually</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 23:37:00" d="2021-07-13 23:52:00"><n>Spectrophilia</n><t>S</t>    <k>See the ultimate taboo in this short all about supernatural fucking! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-13 23:52:00" d="2021-07-14 00:14:00"><n>4 Passionate Women: Feeling Hot</n>    <k>A porn for women scene by Award Winning director Lara Tinelli for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit female friendly porn , sensuous films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 00:14:00" d="2021-07-14 00:32:00"><n>Exposure: Tied Up</n>    <k>In a world where couples would rather play with their phones than each other, one woman uses her technology skills for good, nudging distracted lovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 00:32:00" d="2021-07-14 00:58:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies 2: Renata Fox &amp; Vincent Vega</n>    <k>These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. An erotic sex scene from Favorite Fantasies 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 00:58:00" d="2021-07-14 01:14:00"><n>Red Light: Kleio Valentien &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>Red Light is like a waking dream set in the streets of Los Angeles. It's the story of a woman's transformation into her true self, and a wild chase</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 01:14:00" d="2021-07-14 01:47:00"><n>Hot Water: Tiffany Tatum &amp; Lutro</n>    <k>Licking, sucking, kissing, thrusting, touching, stroking, becoming one with each other in hot water. A sexual and visual delight by Studio Sinfull</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 01:47:00" d="2021-07-14 02:10:00"><n>Remy's Angels: Remy Lacroix &amp; Lola Foxx</n>    <k>Watch the beautiful brunette Remy Lacroix explore her inner desires with some of her closest girlfriends in this all girl sexual adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 02:10:00" d="2021-07-14 02:28:00"><n>Bad Sometimes: Erica Fontes, Angelo Ferro &amp; Emilio Ardana</n><t>L</t>    <k>After the acclaimed success of his first film, Lara Tinelli surprises us with a completely different and transgressive film while staying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 02:28:00" d="2021-07-14 02:52:00"><n>Love Lust Longing: Jessica Drake &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Love Lust &amp; Longing takes place in a seemingly innocent Bed &amp; Breakfast. Rachel a milf who is staying in the master bedroom falls in love with James</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 02:52:00" d="2021-07-14 03:12:00"><n>We Know You Are Watching</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: A sexy young couple in Brazil notice how interested their neighbor is in observing their naturist habits at home. In XConfessions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 03:12:00" d="2021-07-14 03:33:00"><n>Tease: Ava Austen &amp; Luke Hardy</n>    <k>If according to Shakespeare, clothes make the man, then without doubt lingerie make the woman. Skyler is the gorgeous young owner and head designer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 03:33:00" d="2021-07-14 03:55:00"><n>Anal Adventure: Tori Fox &amp; Joe T</n>    <k>Wondering what it takes to have that fantastic sex that you will remember for the rest of your life? These beautiful desirable couples are highly confident</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 03:55:00" d="2021-07-14 04:14:00"><n>Naked Desire</n>    <k>An exciting porn for women video by Dusk TV's own female friendly porn label. Watch this beautiful young woman having sex with her tattooed, big dick boyfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 04:14:00" d="2021-07-14 04:37:00"><n>Camera Angle: Ryan Keely &amp; Ryan Mclane</n>    <k>Fiction and reality seem to blend when Hollywood actor Peter gets a concussion. His visions of heart-racing, sweat inducing sex seem very real though</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 04:37:00" d="2021-07-14 04:53:00"><n>Hello Pool Boy</n>    <k>From XConfessions 3: “I clean your pool. Easy going, good hearted, always horny.” In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2021-07-14 04:53:00" d="2021-07-14 05:23:00"><n>Desire: Tasha Reign &amp; Johnny Castle</n>    <k>Intense feelings of desire causes two bodies melting into one, shivering of pleasure with every touch and longing for more. A female friendly porn scene</k>  </p>
</a>
