<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="64" t="2020-04-14 04:36:12"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 05:26:00" d="2020-04-21 05:52:00"><n>Secret Sex Society: Julia Roca &amp; Sylvan</n>    <k>When colourful people meet and share their colourful fantasies. Starring the hot blooded Spanish beauty Julia Roca</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 05:52:00" d="2020-04-21 06:28:00"><n>Couples Massage: Antonia Sainz &amp; Adam Black</n>    <k>A crackling fire, relaxing music and a lot of warm oil for a total body massage. Delicious. These beautiful couples can’t get enough of it too. A beautiful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 06:28:00" d="2020-04-21 06:53:00"><n>Sweet Memories: Take Me Now</n>    <k>A hot romantic porn for women scene by Lara Tinelli for women who love rough sex with a guy who has a a big dick. A female friendly porn video by Dusk TV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 06:53:00" d="2020-04-21 07:09:00"><n>An Appointment With My Master</n><t>S</t>    <k>The honest and truthful relationship between a dominant and a submissive. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, kinky female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 07:09:00" d="2020-04-21 07:30:00"><n>In The Limelight 1: Lexi Belle &amp; Jeanie Marie</n><t>L</t>    <k>Daring! Pure?s film ?In the Limelight? shows a spectacular selection of nine of their best scenes. The most beautiful couples surpass your wildest dreams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 07:30:00" d="2020-04-21 08:01:00"><n>Voyeuristic Desires: Tina Kay, Wicky Angel &amp; Steve Q</n>    <k>Sinful trinity's enjoying a triad of erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 08:01:00" d="2020-04-21 08:29:00"><n>Soft And Sweet 2: Lady Dee &amp; Max D</n>    <k>Did you ever notice the softness of your lovers skin, the sweet taste when you move your tongue over her well formed sensual body? A porn for women film by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 08:29:00" d="2020-04-21 08:47:00"><n>Recipe for Romance: Missy Martinez &amp; Ramon Nomar</n>    <k>Love is cooking in Carolina's kitchen, and it's wonderfully delicious! Carolina is a passionate cook who is patiently waiting for Mr. Right. But what if Mr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 08:47:00" d="2020-04-21 08:59:00"><n>Hit Me With Your Best Shot</n>    <k>Every time he grabs it he feels so strong, as if his virility depended on it. It starts to annoy me when he's been shooting at cans for an</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 08:59:00" d="2020-04-21 09:19:00"><n>Ball Control: Marc Rose &amp; Anissa Kate</n>    <k>They say that football is a man’s world, but there’s one woman on this pitch with all the power. Super sexy porn for women by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 09:19:00" d="2020-04-21 09:35:00"><n>Hello Pool Boy</n>    <k>From XConfessions 3: “I clean your pool. Easy going, good hearted, always horny.” In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 09:35:00" d="2020-04-21 10:08:00"><n>Not to Innocent: Angel Piaf &amp; Max D</n>    <k>This scene is a true pleasure to all the senses representing natural sex full of intimacy, romance, chemistry and lots of naughtiness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 10:08:00" d="2020-04-21 10:23:00"><n>From Beyond: Monka Mora &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>Sofia is mourning her beloved husband, but still feels him everywhere in their house. Is he haunting her for a reason? Her best friend helps Sofia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 10:23:00" d="2020-04-21 10:50:00"><n>My Wife's First Girlfriend: Jenna Sativa &amp; Leah Gotti</n>    <k>Jenna?s secret desires become unleashed when her husband catches her masturbating to lesbian porn. When Jimmy notices a growing attraction between</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 10:50:00" d="2020-04-21 11:05:00"><n>Going Bananas</n>    <k>Stand up and pick up a banana, read the instructions carefully, follow the rules. Wait for me lying on our big white bed, I?ll come</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 11:05:00" d="2020-04-21 11:24:00"><n>The Invitation: Lola Gatsby &amp; Dean Van Damme</n>    <k>Jane and Tom's car unexpectedly breaks down late at night they find themselves knocking on a stranger?s door only to be presented with an invitation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 11:24:00" d="2020-04-21 11:35:00"><n>A Feminist Man</n><t>S</t>    <k>Is there anything sexier than a man who can give perfect cunnilingus and have a conversation about Judith Butler? From the XConfessions series by Erika</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 11:35:00" d="2020-04-21 11:58:00"><n>Seven Days</n>    <k>This couple can have dramatic fights, but when they make up, it?s nothing but passion, lust and a bit of rough sex. An erotic sex scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 11:58:00" d="2020-04-21 12:31:00"><n>Black Desire</n>    <k>Sinful interracial couples enjoy colorful erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 12:31:00" d="2020-04-21 12:52:00"><n>Sweet but Psycho</n><t>S</t>    <k>Four of the hottest and most popular performers on the scene create a hilarious and erotic film. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 12:52:00" d="2020-04-21 13:05:00"><n>It's Complicated: Brooke &amp; Eric Masterson</n>    <k>Shauna (Gracie Glam) has been having casual sex with her handsome friend Will, biding her time until she can finally make a move on her long time crush Brandon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 13:05:00" d="2020-04-21 13:21:00"><n>The Fantasy Project: Vivienne L, Max &amp; Harley Jay</n><t>L</t>    <k>Have you ever been in a threesome? These three lovers show what it could be like if your fantasies came true. This erotic video by Louise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 13:21:00" d="2020-04-21 13:44:00"><n>Sexy and Sensual: Sheri Vee &amp; Nikolas</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. A porn for women scene from Sexy and Sensual by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 13:44:00" d="2020-04-21 14:07:00"><n>Fantasies Come True 2: Capri Anderson &amp; Danny Mountain</n><t>O</t>    <k>The fantasies of a lifetime can be yours in five breathtaking scenes that set the standard for high definition erotica. A ballet studio, tennis court</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 14:07:00" d="2020-04-21 14:32:00"><n>He Loves To Watch: Penny Pax &amp; Van Wyle</n>    <k>This couple has found a unique way to keep the spark in their marriage. Passionate sex and powerful orgasms for everybody! Cuckolding porn with focus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 14:32:00" d="2020-04-21 14:48:00"><n>It's Complicated: Gracie Glam &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>Shauna (Gracie Glam) has been having casual sex with her handsome friend Will, biding her time until she can finally make a move on her long time crush Brandon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 14:48:00" d="2020-04-21 15:03:00"><n>Girls Sex Tricks: Julia De Lucia &amp; Emilio Saiz Olid</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us on her first film as director for Thagson with a vibrant female friendly porn story which will take place in the streets of Barcelona</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 15:03:00" d="2020-04-21 15:23:00"><n>Pleasure Professionals 2: Tiffany Doll &amp; Marc Rose</n>    <k>A kinky couple's porn film from Joybear. Every summer Mrs ERC bolts to the countryside to relax and unwind. A secluded hotel provides the perfect getaway</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 15:23:00" d="2020-04-21 15:56:00"><n>Home Coming: Burning Desire</n>    <k>Oh, home sweet home. These couples experience that there's no place like home to come back to, especially since orgasms are awaiting them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 15:56:00" d="2020-04-21 16:17:00"><n>Sex and Lies: Nikki Peach &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>In the world of the ultra-rich, sex and lies reign supreme. Alisa (Avi Love)is a personal assistant who craves nothing more than order; difficult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 16:17:00" d="2020-04-21 16:41:00"><n>Stay With Me: Lexi Lou &amp; Adrian Dimas</n>    <k>Five naturally passionate girls are waiting for attention of their lovers. Their minds are full of sensual memories as they start to pleasure themselves. A Daring! Film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 16:41:00" d="2020-04-21 17:04:00"><n>While You're Sleeping</n><t>L</t>    <k>A man secretly watches porn when he thinks his wife is asleep. But she know?s what he is doing and shows him that he doesn?t have to watch tv when he wants good porn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 17:04:00" d="2020-04-21 17:27:00"><n>Positions: Second</n>    <k>While finding inspiration at a dancer?s retreat, the ballet dancer Florence soon realises she?s not the only one who could do with practising</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 17:27:00" d="2020-04-21 17:52:00"><n>Tales from the Heart: Marie McCray &amp; Xander Corvus</n>    <k>Love is in the air. specially on your Anniversary. A trip down memory lane is just the spark Michelle and Andy need to reignite the lustful feelings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 17:52:00" d="2020-04-21 18:08:00"><n>I found your mother on tinder</n><t>S</t>    <k>The legendary Mrs. Robinson brought to life by the most modern of dating apps. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 18:08:00" d="2020-04-21 18:30:00"><n>Tease: Amber Nevada &amp; Billy King</n>    <k>If according to Shakespeare, clothes make the man, then without doubt lingerie make the woman. Skyler is the gorgeous young owner and head designer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 18:30:00" d="2020-04-21 18:51:00"><n>Racetrack</n>    <k>Helena and Thomas are in the middle of a fierce video game battle, but when his car begins to pull away from the pack and her chances of victory dwindle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 18:51:00" d="2020-04-21 19:13:00"><n>Sexy and Sensual: Dolce Vita &amp; Vega</n>    <k>These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A porn for women scene from Sexy and Sensual by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 19:13:00" d="2020-04-21 19:36:00"><n>The Party</n>    <k>A breasty Spanish beauty can’t get any sleep because of the loud party next door. But when she sees her attractive neighbor her angry feelings fade away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 19:36:00" d="2020-04-21 20:06:00"><n>Blind Date Swingers Club: Ricky Raskal &amp; Nikky Dream</n>    <k>Everyone is getting their fuck on! Swinging couples going wild!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 20:06:00" d="2020-04-21 20:23:00"><n>Everyday Turn-Ons: Close To The Edge</n>    <k>Like most modern couples, Shan and Mark struggle to fit sex into their busy lives along with family, friends and work. Snatching a few precious moments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 20:23:00" d="2020-04-21 20:48:00"><n>Sex and Lies: Sovereign Sire &amp; Daisy Stone</n>    <k>In the world of the ultra-rich, sex and lies reign supreme. Alisa (Avi Love)is a personal assistant who craves nothing more than order; difficult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 20:48:00" d="2020-04-21 21:10:00"><n>Milk</n>    <k>What kind of Milk are you drinking today? A romantic porn video featuring pornstar Julia Roca by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 21:10:00" d="2020-04-21 21:40:00"><n>The Babysitter 8: Dillion Harper &amp; James Deen</n>    <k>Mona is a bitter woman who hates her ex-husband and has no qualms about bad mouthing him to her new babysitter, Alice. What happens when Alice catches</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 21:40:00" d="2020-04-21 22:01:00"><n>Special Moments: The Shower</n><t>L</t>    <k>Watch how this couple shares a steamy shower. A romantic sex scene by Dusk TV's Porn for women label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women, sensuous films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 22:01:00" d="2020-04-21 22:33:00"><n>Momentum 4: Go for a walk</n>    <k>The fourth final and most epic adult film. The Volume 4 stage is set in the Australian desert - an aesthetic overthrow from the previous films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 22:33:00" d="2020-04-21 22:52:00"><n>I wish I was a lesbian</n><t>S</t>    <k>Maria's deepest fantasies come true when she finds herself being hosted by a hot and sweet lesbian couple. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 22:52:00" d="2020-04-21 23:10:00"><n>Erotic Massage Stories 3: Jessie Rogers &amp; Bruce Venture</n><t>L</t>    <k>So relaxing as you watch five sensuous massage fantasies that will overwhelm you. Every delicate curve and touch has been captured</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 23:10:00" d="2020-04-21 23:34:00"><n>Making Ends Meet: Gia Paige &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>A suburbian family is in destress over money, but sex seems to really heal the wounds. Scorching hot sex and sharp comedy blend perfectly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-21 23:34:00" d="2020-04-22 00:00:00"><n>Picture Perfect: Regina Crystal &amp; Marc Rose</n>    <k>In an age of social media, FaceTime and mobile communication, couples now have the ultimate sex toy at their disposal. They can tease each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 00:00:00" d="2020-04-22 00:16:00"><n>Exposure: Security Measures</n>    <k>In a world where couples would rather play with their phones than each other, one woman uses her technology skills for good, nudging distracted lovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 00:16:00" d="2020-04-22 00:35:00"><n>We Know You Are Watching</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: A sexy young couple in Brazil notice how interested their neighbor is in observing their naturist habits at home. In XConfessions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 00:35:00" d="2020-04-22 00:50:00"><n>Never Forgotten: Maddy Oreilly &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>Robert can’t stop thinking about Elizabeth, his first love during the 1940’s. An argument teared the perfect couple apart and decades later Robert is still</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 00:50:00" d="2020-04-22 01:22:00"><n>Not to Innocent: Bella Jordan &amp; Fernando</n>    <k>A scene by Dawn for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 01:22:00" d="2020-04-22 01:32:00"><n>Parallel Universe</n><t>S</t>    <k>There is another world out there, a world where you can exist purely as a piece of furniture. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 01:32:00" d="2020-04-22 02:12:00"><n>Darker Side of Desire: Cherie DeVille &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>When Natalie meets the perfect guy, she is afraid to scare him away with her deviant desires. Maybe the safest way to explore these intense desires</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 02:12:00" d="2020-04-22 02:31:00"><n>Housemates 3: Best Fucking Sex Ever</n>    <k>Synopsis not available</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 02:31:00" d="2020-04-22 02:56:00"><n>Gentle Loving 2: Tequila &amp; Vincent Vega</n>    <k>These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. An erotic sex scene from Favorite Fantasies 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 02:56:00" d="2020-04-22 03:22:00"><n>Sensuous Seduction: Sweet</n>    <k>How sweet is your partner? A romantic sex film by Lara Tinelli for Dusk TV's own porn for women label: &quot;Ooh la la&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 03:22:00" d="2020-04-22 03:35:00"><n>A Talk Too Dirty</n><t>S</t>    <k>The power of dirty talk is a wonderful thing. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual confessions of her viewers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 03:35:00" d="2020-04-22 04:03:00"><n>Coming Out: Minnie Manga &amp; Nia Black</n>    <k>In uncertainty about their sexual orientation these young women finally no longer conceal their sexual preference, and revealing their gender identity completely</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 04:03:00" d="2020-04-22 04:39:00"><n>Private Spa: Mugur &amp; Caroline de Jaie</n>    <k>This beautiful couple enjoys every bit of their private spa. We like it that hot! A delightful video by studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 04:39:00" d="2020-04-22 04:59:00"><n>Exploring Couples: Sheri Vi &amp; Nicolas</n>    <k>When the moment is right, it's time to take your romantic interests to the next level of passion by exploring the options. See what these couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 04:59:00" d="2020-04-22 05:27:00"><n>Don't Tell Daddy: Ana Foxxx &amp; Teanna Trump</n><t>L</t>    <k>Remember being young and doing naughty things that under certain circumstances could get you grounded for a month? Weekend house parties</k>  </p>
</a>
