<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="64" t="2019-07-13 23:58:19"><p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 05:02:00" d="2019-07-20 05:31:00"><n>Brave Hearts: Abigaile Johnson &amp; George Uhl</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sarah (Faye Regan), the most famous Romance Novelist in the world, is writing the final book in her series of best-selling love stories. Admired by women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 05:31:00" d="2019-07-20 05:41:00"><n>Cybersex</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 05:41:00" d="2019-07-20 06:04:00"><n>Corporate Bonding: Hannah Shaw &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>Good teamwork can lead to surprising situations. Rookie lawyer Leyla organises a team-building weekend by the beach for her and her firm of London lawyers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 06:04:00" d="2019-07-20 06:20:00"><n>At First Sight</n>    <k>The value and virtues of extended foreplay cannot be underestimated or undervalued. But there are times in life when the laws of attraction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 06:20:00" d="2019-07-20 06:47:00"><n>Wicked Dreams: Dora Amirah Andara &amp; Jaros Jan</n>    <k>To escape their hectic lives, young friends are eager to find their way of personal care and loving attention. What started out as an innocent visit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 06:47:00" d="2019-07-20 07:07:00"><n>Room 208: Sara May &amp; Juan Lucho</n>    <k>A new scene by Award Winning director Lara Tinelli for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 07:07:00" d="2019-07-20 07:44:00"><n>Nymphomaniac Diaries: Giggolo's</n>    <k>The blond Katerina loves sex so much that her dreams are filled with kinky stuff, but her sexual fantasies with men and women become even better</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 07:44:00" d="2019-07-20 08:03:00"><n>HouseMates: Sicilia &amp; Sean</n>    <k>After a painful break up Jess flees to the city and is thrown into a world where hiding away is not an option. Her new housemates Ollie and Saskia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 08:03:00" d="2019-07-20 08:27:00"><n>Love Blossoms: Heather Starlet &amp; Ryan Mclane</n>    <k>Jane?s life is perfect, until a car accident causes her to lose her memory. Gardener Brian is the only one who is able to understand her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 08:27:00" d="2019-07-20 08:49:00"><n>Blind</n>    <k>Open your eyes wide for this one! Gorgeous Spanish beauty Apolonia Lapiedra and Pablo Ferrari get steamy in this short film with another classic scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 08:49:00" d="2019-07-20 09:22:00"><n>Forbidden Affairs 4: Jade Nile &amp; Steven St. Croix</n>    <k>He is astounded by the drop-dead gorgeous girlfriend of his son. When she starts to flirt with him he can no longer resist the temptation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 09:22:00" d="2019-07-20 09:47:00"><n>Afternoon Love: Angel Piaf &amp; Max D</n>    <k>What are you going to do when all of a suddon both of you are at home and have nothing to do? Exactly, enjoy each other and make your time together worthwhile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 09:47:00" d="2019-07-20 10:13:00"><n>Sex in white: Erica Fontes &amp; Miquel Zayas</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us with her ?Sex In White? productions, where sexual encounters take place in a pure and white scenery, so the main focus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 10:13:00" d="2019-07-20 10:22:00"><n>Hold me so tight it hurts</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 10:22:00" d="2019-07-20 10:41:00"><n>Pure Sexual Attraction: Addison Avery &amp; Johnny Castle</n>    <k>Embark on an exciting journey of pure sexual attraction as five breathtaking girls are captured in five scenes that set the standard for high definition erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 10:41:00" d="2019-07-20 10:53:00"><n>Come Fly With Me</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 10:53:00" d="2019-07-20 11:20:00"><n>Coming Out: Candy Sweet &amp; Sandra</n>    <k>In uncertainty about their sexual orientation these young women finally no longer conceal their sexual preference, and revealing their gender identity completely</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 11:20:00" d="2019-07-20 11:44:00"><n>Inside: Julia Roca &amp; Natalia Ferrari</n>    <k>Welcome to The Retreat: where curious minds come to play. Plug in and turn on to explore a virtual reality experience where you can be anyone, go anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 11:44:00" d="2019-07-20 11:56:00"><n>My moaning neighbor</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 11:56:00" d="2019-07-20 12:10:00"><n>Never Forgotten: Maddy Oreilly &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>Robert can’t stop thinking about Elizabeth, his first love during the 1940’s. An argument teared the perfect couple apart and decades later Robert is still</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 12:10:00" d="2019-07-20 12:33:00"><n>Tenderness: Alexis Crystal &amp; George Lee</n>    <k>A new scene by Roma Woodcock for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 12:33:00" d="2019-07-20 12:43:00"><n>Magic Magnus</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 12:43:00" d="2019-07-20 13:21:00"><n>The Stepmother 8: Cameron Canada &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>Billy and Julia are getting close to marriage, but each have a single parent who?s loneliness is ruining their peace. But the real problem arises when Billy can?t stop thinking about Julia?s gorgeous mother, Theresa. Will Theresa settle for quiet companionship, or will she succumb to lust for the vibrant young man. A Sweet Sinner?s daring look into forbidden passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 13:21:00" d="2019-07-20 13:45:00"><n>Riot Girls: Ava Dalush &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>The Riot Girls are Jenna, Bett and Karma. An all-girl rock band touring the world and loving the Rock 'N Roll lifestyle. They are best friends and nothing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 13:45:00" d="2019-07-20 14:00:00"><n>Romeo &amp; Juliet: Chanel Preston &amp; Marie Rios</n>    <k>Directed by Lee Roy Myers, this film by DreamZone Entertainment features tragic lovers trapped within a web of love, lies and loyalties. A sexy and spicy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 14:00:00" d="2019-07-20 14:26:00"><n>Her Desire: Sleeping</n>    <k>A new scene by AlexanFilm for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 14:26:00" d="2019-07-20 14:42:00"><n>Cabaret Desire: Didac Duran and Samia Duarte</n>    <k>Welcome to nightclub Cabaret Desire ? indulge yourself with poets and their erotic tales filled with passion and temptation. A film by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 14:42:00" d="2019-07-20 15:08:00"><n>Fading Memories: Alessandra Jane &amp; Sam Bourne</n>    <k>A collection of four scenes of women having vivid memories about former lovers, especially about the fantastic sex they used to have with their handsome guys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 15:08:00" d="2019-07-20 15:29:00"><n>Passion Noir: Lexi &amp; Jason</n>    <k>Four passionate couples in a Sinful XXX film by Roma Amor. Beautiful, Arty and very sexy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 15:29:00" d="2019-07-20 15:54:00"><n>I Am All Yours: Eveline Neil &amp; Marcel Lee</n>    <k>A new scene by Dawn for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 15:54:00" d="2019-07-20 16:22:00"><n>Chance Encounters: April O'Neil , Dani Daniels &amp; Erik Erverhard</n>    <k>Several couples encounter love, affairs, sex and romance at a hotel. A Intimate Encounters film by J. Crawford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 16:22:00" d="2019-07-20 16:41:00"><n>Heavy Contact</n>    <k>That feeling when you have a lot of contact with someone and the connection gets even heavier when you meet in real life? Yes, that's passion to the max</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 16:41:00" d="2019-07-20 17:01:00"><n>Quartet: The Teacher</n>    <k>Penelope boards a plane from London to Budapest, eager to perform with her three best friends from music academy. Reunited, the foursome soon remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 17:01:00" d="2019-07-20 17:12:00"><n>Romance Bullshit</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 17:12:00" d="2019-07-20 17:43:00"><n>Not to Innocent: Ally &amp; Max D</n>    <k>A new scene by Dawn for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 17:43:00" d="2019-07-20 18:05:00"><n>Getting Cozy: Allie Haze &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>Recently single Marisa is unwillingly sent on a blind date by her best friend. After a few cocktails things get out of hand and Marisa wakes up in his bed? Due to an ice storm she cannot leave his appartment, and spends the weekend. A film from Wicked Pictures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 18:05:00" d="2019-07-20 18:33:00"><n>Oasis: Ryan Diller &amp; Tasha Reign</n>    <k>A secluded oasis with design furniture appears to be the perfect place to have passionate sex. A scene from an Intimate Encounters film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 18:33:00" d="2019-07-20 18:57:00"><n>Summer</n>    <k>What a better refreshment in the middle of a hot hazy and sticky summer day than playing with some ice in front of a breezy fan and having loads of good sex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 18:57:00" d="2019-07-20 19:22:00"><n>Secret Sex Society: Sicilia &amp; Sylvan</n>    <k>When colourful people meet and share their colourful fantasies. Starring the hot blooded Spanish beauty Julia Roca</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 19:22:00" d="2019-07-20 19:34:00"><n>Do You Find My Feet Suckable?</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 19:34:00" d="2019-07-20 19:57:00"><n>Her Desire: The Couch</n>    <k>A new scene by AlexanFilm for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 19:57:00" d="2019-07-20 20:37:00"><n>Nymphomaniac Diaries: Daydreaming</n>    <k>The blond Katerina loves sex so much that her dreams are filled with kinky stuff, but her sexual fantasies with men and women become even better</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 20:37:00" d="2019-07-20 20:55:00"><n>Dacrifilia</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 20:55:00" d="2019-07-20 21:17:00"><n>Love and Loss: Maddy O'Reilly &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>With more twists and turns than the German autobahn, Love and Loss follows the story of Lanie and Alex, an ex-cop involved in the shooting of Lanie's ex-lover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 21:17:00" d="2019-07-20 21:54:00"><n>Trying New Things: Casey Calvert &amp; Anthony Rosano</n>    <k>Passions explode when a sexually frustrated Alison asks her fiancé to take her virginity two weeks before their wedding day. Sara discovers that adult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 21:54:00" d="2019-07-20 22:23:00"><n>Couples Massage: Daphne &amp; Andrew Truck</n>    <k>A crackling fire, relaxing music and a lot of warm oil for a total body massage. Delicious. These beautiful couples can’t get enough of it too. Please do try this at home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 22:23:00" d="2019-07-20 22:41:00"><n>Don't Forget Me</n>    <k>Don't Forget Me has a simple and concise subtitle: &quot;a story about love.&quot; Lola Reve and Franck Franco give the romantic theme real life with little</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 22:41:00" d="2019-07-20 22:52:00"><n>Win A Date With Sofia Blake: Bianca Breeze &amp; Jake Jace</n>    <k>A-list Hollywood actress Sofia Blake (Olivia Austin) is having the worst day of her life and the paparazzi have made sure to plaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 22:52:00" d="2019-07-20 23:14:00"><n>Gentle Loving 2: Lana &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A scene from Gentle Loving 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 23:14:00" d="2019-07-20 23:44:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies: Dolce Vita &amp; Vega</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A scene from Favorite Fantasies by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-20 23:44:00" d="2019-07-21 00:07:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies 2: Rebeccca &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A scene from Favorite Fantasies 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-21 00:07:00" d="2019-07-21 00:30:00"><n>Sexy and Sensual: Sheri Vee &amp; Nikolas</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A scene from Sexy and Sensual by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-21 00:30:00" d="2019-07-21 00:54:00"><n>Anal Lovers: Liona &amp; Vega</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A scene from Anal Lovers by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-21 00:54:00" d="2019-07-21 01:23:00"><n>Our Sexual Secrets: Katarina &amp; Vega</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A scene from Our Sexual Secrets by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-21 01:23:00" d="2019-07-21 01:47:00"><n>He Loves To Watch: India Summer &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>This couple has found a unique way to keep the spark in their marriage. Passionate sex and powerful orgasms for everybody!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-21 01:47:00" d="2019-07-21 02:11:00"><n>Gentle Loving 2: Tequila &amp; Vincent Vega</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A scene from Gentle Loving 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-21 02:11:00" d="2019-07-21 02:26:00"><n>From Beyond: Aaliyah Love &amp; Jay Smooth</n>    <k>Sofia is mourning her beloved husband, but still feels him everywhere in their house. Is he haunting her for a reason? Her best friend helps Sofia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-21 02:26:00" d="2019-07-21 02:48:00"><n>Sweet but Psycho</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-21 02:48:00" d="2019-07-21 03:12:00"><n>Lena: Ava Dalush &amp; Lucia Love</n>    <k>Lena is in her 20s. A graduate. Cosmopolitan. The whole world at her fingertips. But the pressure of finding the perfect partner, the perfect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-21 03:12:00" d="2019-07-21 03:41:00"><n>So Wet Beside Her: Victoria Pure &amp; Charlie Red</n>    <k>These girls love, lust, lick, becoming almost one in this sensual piece of erotica. Sinful Studio making art again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-21 03:41:00" d="2019-07-21 04:06:00"><n>Facade: Edyn Blair &amp; James Deen</n>    <k>Amber and her friend Lindsay are average college students?who happen to moonlight as sexy webcam models. This complicates things when they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-21 04:06:00" d="2019-07-21 04:30:00"><n>In The Limelight 1: Conny Carter &amp; Denson</n><t>L</t>    <k>Daring! Pure?s film ?In the Limelight? shows a spectacular selection of nine of their best scenes. The most beautiful couples surpass your wildest dreams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-21 04:30:00" d="2019-07-21 04:57:00"><n>Sensuous Seduction: In the Evening</n>    <k>A new scene by Award Winning director Lara Tinelli for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-21 04:57:00" d="2019-07-21 05:17:00"><n>Sex With Friends: Three Wishes</n>    <k>When old college friends meet again they take the time to rekindle and explore each other?s bodies and sexual boundries. A reunion you don?t want to miss</k>  </p>
</a>
