<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="68" t="2020-04-16 04:40:07"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 05:02:00" d="2020-04-23 05:23:00"><n>Pleasure Professionals 2: Tiffany Doll &amp; Ava Austen</n>    <k>Every summer Mrs ERC bolts to the countryside to relax and unwind. A secluded hotel provides the perfect getaway. With an air of mystery surrounding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 05:23:00" d="2020-04-23 05:51:00"><n>Sexy And She Knows It: Lutro, Dorian Del Isla &amp; Anna Polina</n>    <k>Sinful trinity's enjoying a triad of erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 05:51:00" d="2020-04-23 06:17:00"><n>The Escort 2: Presley Hart &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>When a beautiful young woman enters the escorting profession, she's put off by her first client. But under the tutelage of a smart and capable madam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 06:17:00" d="2020-04-23 06:43:00"><n>All For You: Jess West &amp; Ryan Ryder</n>    <k>All For You? is an assembly of exotic, intense, romantic, couple-friendly scenes that highlight the intimacy of lovers. When every thought is focused</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 06:43:00" d="2020-04-23 07:14:00"><n>Sensuous Seduction: Messaging</n>    <k>A sensual massage is the gateway to your partners naughtiness and desires. Watch how this sexy couple is physically expressing their love to each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 07:14:00" d="2020-04-23 07:33:00"><n>Fit: Samantha Bentley &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>You are running on the beach, bathed in the beautiful sunshine. You feel alive and energized ? what could be better? Get outside. Get active</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 07:33:00" d="2020-04-23 08:02:00"><n u="The Submission Of Emma Marx: Penny Pax &amp; Richie Calhoun">The Submission Of Emma Marx: Penny Pax &amp; Richie Calhoun (5)</n>    <k>When a new contract is drafted up defining the parameters of their BDSM relationship, Emma realizes that Mr. Frederick is anything but predictable</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 08:02:00" d="2020-04-23 08:18:00"><n>Coming of age</n><t>S</t>    <k>A coming of age tale of young lust, farewells and new encounters. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 08:18:00" d="2020-04-23 08:35:00"><n>Exposure: Tied Up</n>    <k>In a world where couples would rather play with their phones than each other, one woman uses her technology skills for good, nudging distracted lovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 08:35:00" d="2020-04-23 08:46:00"><n>The Villa</n><t>L</t>    <k>&quot;The Villa&quot; shows luxuriously furnished rooms and lushly landscaped grounds of a secluded mansion. Two women are enjoying this posh and private location</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 08:46:00" d="2020-04-23 09:12:00"><n>Beautiful Young Couples: Jessica Malone &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A erotic scene from Beautiful Young</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 09:12:00" d="2020-04-23 09:40:00"><n>Afternoon Love: Bella Jordan &amp; Fernando</n>    <k>These real-life lovers are in a romantic and passionate relationship. Through the art of blowjob, pussy licking and loving intercourse, they reach their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 09:40:00" d="2020-04-23 10:11:00"><n>A Touch Of Lust: Dance D'amour</n>    <k>In this scene an intimate dance ends up in sultry sex on the kitchen table. A cinematic feast for the eyes by Roma Amor for SinfulXXX</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 10:11:00" d="2020-04-23 10:30:00"><n>HouseMates: Sicilia &amp; Sean</n>    <k>After a painful break up Jess flees to the city and is thrown into a world where hiding away is not an option. Her new housemates Ollie and Saskia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 10:30:00" d="2020-04-23 10:44:00"><n>Getting Cozy: AJ Applegate &amp; Daniel Hunter</n>    <k>Recently single Marisa is unwillingly sent on a blind date by her best friend. After a few cocktails things get out of hand and Marisa wakes up in his bed? Due to an ice storm she cannot leave his appartment, and spends the weekend. A film from Wicked Pictures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 10:44:00" d="2020-04-23 11:03:00"><n>Heavy Contact</n>    <k>That feeling when you have a lot of contact with someone and the connection gets even heavier when you meet in real life? Yes, that's passion to the max</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 11:03:00" d="2020-04-23 11:35:00"><n>Darker Side of Desire: Cassidy Klein &amp; Mickey Mod BDSM</n>    <k>When Natalie meets the perfect guy, she is afraid to scare him away with her deviant desires. Maybe the safest way to explore these intense desires</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 11:35:00" d="2020-04-23 12:03:00"><n>Her Desire: Shy Guy</n>    <k>Romantic porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion. A pleasure to all the senses representing realistic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 12:03:00" d="2020-04-23 12:13:00"><n>The Bathhouse</n><t>L</t>    <k>Always wanted to know about anal sex, but never tried? This film shows how nice anal massage can be. A romantic porn film full of bubbles and soap</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 12:13:00" d="2020-04-23 12:26:00"><n>Power Pussy</n><t>S</t>    <k>Two Power Pussies take on and dominate the burly Dean Van Damme, all in From Dawn Til Dawn style. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 12:26:00" d="2020-04-23 12:43:00"><n>Pure Sexual Attraction 2: Natasha White &amp; Johnny Castle</n>    <k>Embark on an exciting journey of pure sexual attraction as five breathtaking girls are captured in five scenes that set the standard for high definition erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 12:43:00" d="2020-04-23 13:00:00"><n>Win A Date With Sofia Blake: Olivia Austin &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>A-list Hollywood actress Sofia Blake (Olivia Austin) is having the worst day of her life and the paparazzi have made sure to plaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 13:00:00" d="2020-04-23 13:30:00"><n>The Bedroom Chronicles: Lutro &amp; Samantha Jolie</n>    <k>As women we all exactly know what kind of sex we want, need and prefer: 'romantic', 'sensual' and 'sophisticated' are the keywords as a prelude for great sex! All represented in this female friendly porn scene by Daring! Pure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 13:30:00" d="2020-04-23 13:50:00"><n>Housemates 2: Satine Spark &amp; Seth Strong</n>    <k>New house. New rules. Artist James moves to the UK in search of his ex-girlfriend (Dalush) and finds himself sharing a house with four incredibly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 13:50:00" d="2020-04-23 13:58:00"><n>My Roomie’s Toy</n><t>S</t>    <k>A young woman innocently looking for a phone charger stumbles across her roommate's sex toy. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 13:58:00" d="2020-04-23 14:11:00"><n>Girlfriends: Casey Calvert &amp; Sasha Heart</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Small town girl Jamie (Casey Calvert) has made the difficult decision to tell her parents that she is in a same sex relationship. Unfortunately her family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 14:11:00" d="2020-04-23 14:36:00"><n>Her Desire: Ladies Night</n>    <k>Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion. A pleasure to all the senses representing realistic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 14:36:00" d="2020-04-23 14:54:00"><n>If the Apocalypse Comes, Fuck Me</n><t>S</t>    <k>Maria Riot is lost and thirsty in an apocalyptical world. Luke seems to be the only man alive. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 14:54:00" d="2020-04-23 15:20:00"><n>My Girlfriends Mother 7: Chloe Foster &amp; Steven St. Croix</n>    <k>An ambitious young man, with a nave mother and a philandering father, returns home from college to discover that the girl next door has grown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 15:20:00" d="2020-04-23 15:42:00"><n>Positions: Fifth</n>    <k>While finding inspiration at a dancer?s retreat, the ballet dancer Florence soon realises she?s not the only one who could do with practising</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 15:42:00" d="2020-04-23 16:04:00"><n>Our Sexual Secrets 2: Dolce Vita &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A porn for women scene from Our Sexual Secrets 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 16:04:00" d="2020-04-23 16:23:00"><n>Room 208: Pamela Sanchez &amp; Sasha blonnde</n>    <k>An explicit porn for women video by Dusk TV's female friendly porn label &quot;Oh la la&quot;. Romantic sex films depicting real excitement and passion. A realistic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 16:23:00" d="2020-04-23 16:39:00"><n>An Appointment With My Master</n><t>S</t>    <k>The honest and truthful relationship between a dominant and a submissive. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, kinky female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 16:39:00" d="2020-04-23 16:59:00"><n>In The Limelight 1: Jay Dee &amp; Sindy Vega</n>    <k>Spectacular sex, the most beautiful couples surpass your wildest dreams to fulfill their sexual desires. A romantic porn for women scene by Daring! Pure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 16:59:00" d="2020-04-23 17:28:00"><n>Sexual Bliss: Keira &amp; Chriss</n>    <k>Four passionate couples in a Sinful XXX film by Roma Amor. Beautiful, Arty and very sexy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 17:28:00" d="2020-04-23 17:54:00"><n>Gentle Loving: Katarina &amp; Vega</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A female friendly porn scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 17:54:00" d="2020-04-23 18:26:00"><n>All In Your Head: Keira Nicole &amp; Ryan McClane</n><t>O</t>    <k>All In Your Head transcends expectations with its striking imagery and brilliant creative direction. There is something for everyone's perverted minds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 18:26:00" d="2020-04-23 18:40:00"><n>Belle Dame Sans Merci</n>    <k>I met a lady in the meads, full beautiful - a faery's child, her hair was long, her foot was light, and her eyes were wild. Porn for women by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 18:40:00" d="2020-04-23 19:02:00"><n>Housemates 3: Morning Sex</n>    <k>Synopsis not available</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 19:02:00" d="2020-04-23 19:14:00"><n>Late night out</n>    <k>From XConfessions 3: When that little bit too much makes you uncontrollably horny! In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 19:14:00" d="2020-04-23 19:33:00"><n>4 Passionate Women: My Friend Ana</n>    <k>Porn for women director Lara Tinelli for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 19:33:00" d="2020-04-23 19:52:00"><n>Perfect timing: Scarlet Red &amp; Jay Smooth</n>    <k>Christina has a dilemma. She was swept off her feet by a much older man, but now things have cooled. She then meets a charming guy and very soon sparks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 19:52:00" d="2020-04-23 20:29:00"><n>Trying New Things: Casey Calvert &amp; Anthony Rosano</n>    <k>Passions explode when a sexually frustrated Alison asks her fiancé to take her virginity two weeks before their wedding day. Sara discovers that adult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 20:29:00" d="2020-04-23 20:47:00"><n>Among The Bushes</n>    <k>He's always sitting in this park, surrounded by the trees, reading a book, cute and charismatic. He's big, tall and handsome. I'll take him between</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 20:47:00" d="2020-04-23 21:07:00"><n>Secret Sex Society: Julia Roca &amp; Julia De Lucia</n>    <k>When colourful people meet and share their colourful fantasies. Starring the hot blooded Spanish beauty Julia Roca</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 21:07:00" d="2020-04-23 21:21:00"><n>Public Submission</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sometimes you find the most thrilling encounters where you least expect. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 21:21:00" d="2020-04-23 21:41:00"><n>Afternoon Love: Lexi Dona &amp; Thomas Reed</n>    <k>A realistic couple with realistic sex. A romantic porn for women film by Dusk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 21:41:00" d="2020-04-23 22:06:00"><n>Our Summer of Love: Sienna Day &amp; Simony Diamond</n>    <k>A hot couple travels abroad and adores the new country, but they enjoy each other even more and especially the new sexy people they meet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 22:06:00" d="2020-04-23 22:18:00"><n>Eat with me</n><t>S</t>    <k>Be fed all your deepest and most delicious desires by a gorgeous celeb chef. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 22:18:00" d="2020-04-23 22:39:00"><n>Facade: Cassidy Klein</n>    <k>Amber and her friend Lindsay are average college students?who happen to moonlight as sexy webcam models. This complicates things when they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 22:39:00" d="2020-04-23 22:55:00"><n>Soulmates</n>    <k>Nothing more fun than watching beautiful people together with your partner. Especially if that ends in super nice sex with your 'Soulmate(s)'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 22:55:00" d="2020-04-23 23:22:00"><n>Soft And Sweet 2: Ornella Morgen &amp; Nic Vargas</n><t>L</t>    <k>These young couples show you their most intimate experiences, see the excitement they both have to endure when they tease each other by kissing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 23:22:00" d="2020-04-23 23:46:00"><n>Second Chances: Jessa Rhodes &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>During her Freshman year of college, Madison thought she'd met the love of her life when she starting dating handsome football player, Josh. This didn't work out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 23:46:00" d="2020-04-24 00:01:00"><n>Red Light: Kleio Valentien &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>Red Light is like a waking dream set in the streets of Los Angeles. It's the story of a woman's transformation into her true self, and a wild chase</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-24 00:01:00" d="2020-04-24 00:24:00"><n>He Loves To Watch: Nina Elle &amp; Bill Bailey</n>    <k>This couple has found a unique way to keep the spark in their marriage. Passionate sex and powerful orgasms for everybody!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-24 00:24:00" d="2020-04-24 00:37:00"><n>The Fantasy Project: Kara &amp; Devon</n>    <k>Massage is the ultimate sensation of touch and the complete focus on you, your body and your pleasure. Your pleasure only. A true female friendly porn video</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-24 00:37:00" d="2020-04-24 00:57:00"><n>Sex With Friends: Three Wishes</n>    <k>When old college friends meet again they take the time to rekindle and explore each other?s bodies and sexual boundries. A reunion you don?t want to miss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-24 00:57:00" d="2020-04-24 01:21:00"><n>Sexual Bliss: Alexis &amp; Jayden</n>    <k>Four passionate couples in a Sinful XXX film by Roma Amor. Beautiful, Arty and very sexy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-24 01:21:00" d="2020-04-24 01:38:00"><n>Red Light: Casey Calvert &amp; Damon Dice</n>    <k>Red Light is like a waking dream set in the streets of Los Angeles. It's the story of a woman's transformation into her true self, and a wild chase</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-24 01:38:00" d="2020-04-24 01:59:00"><n>A Girls' Getaway: Lucia Love &amp; Stella Cox</n>    <k>Girls weekend out! The girls go away together each year for a relaxing weekend to the English countryside. But what happens when the girls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-24 01:59:00" d="2020-04-24 02:26:00"><n>Come Closer: My Sunny Side</n>    <k>What are you going to do when all of a suddon both of you are at home and have nothing to do? Exactly, enjoy each other and make your time together worthwhile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-24 02:26:00" d="2020-04-24 02:50:00"><n>Close To The Bone: Azazie Skymm &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Two immortal lovers are feeling the three-hundred-year-itch. As night falls the city becomes a playground for Jonus and Bryana, both seeking to quench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-24 02:50:00" d="2020-04-24 03:18:00"><n>Hall Pass: Cherie De Ville &amp; Ryan McLane</n>    <k>With her husband's blessing, Anikka indulges in an afternoon seduction with a long time crush. Cherie's husband is eager to help her overcome her sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-24 03:18:00" d="2020-04-24 03:26:00"><n>Carnival Hustlers</n><t>S</t>    <k>Two rival thieves take advantage of a Carnival to sneak around a Fifth Avenue inspired party, in disguise. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-24 03:26:00" d="2020-04-24 03:42:00"><n>The Guesthouse: Bianca Resa &amp; Juan Lucho</n>    <k>Nestled in the Spanish countryside, there?s a Guesthouse where visitors enjoy more than just the sunshine on their bodies. Come alone, come with a friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-24 03:42:00" d="2020-04-24 04:08:00"><n>Sex is for Lovers: Denisa Doll &amp; James Brossman</n>    <k>Indulge yourself in female friendly porn with an emphasis on passion, lovers, and true romance. Their inspiration is not found in anonymous encounters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-24 04:08:00" d="2020-04-24 04:50:00"><n>True Intensions: Ava Dalush &amp; Ben Kelly</n>    <k>From director Anjali Kara comes True Intentions, romantic passion and beautiful sex. Watch the palpable chemistry between partners as they climax together onscreen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-24 04:50:00" d="2020-04-24 05:15:00"><n>Sweet Memories: Take Me Now</n>    <k>A hot romantic porn for women scene by Lara Tinelli for women who love rough sex with a guy who has a a big dick. A female friendly porn video by Dusk TV</k>  </p>
</a>
