<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="62" t="2020-05-14 05:03:54"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 05:22:00" d="2020-05-21 05:38:00"><n u="Ages of Sex: Sex at">Ages of Sex: Sex at (50)</n>    <k>The Ages of Sex is a porn for women film by Thagson. 4 Well known directors will direct a short which represents a woman?s sexual reality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 05:38:00" d="2020-05-21 05:53:00"><n>From The First Moment: Alexa Grace &amp; Lucas Frost</n><t>L</t>    <k>What happens at the ranch, stays at the ranch. Unless wicked pictures show up to shoot the hottest porn for women featuring cowboys we can imagine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 05:53:00" d="2020-05-21 06:04:00"><n>A Feminist Man</n><t>S</t>    <k>Is there anything sexier than a man who can give perfect cunnilingus and have a conversation about Judith Butler? From the XConfessions series by Erika</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 06:04:00" d="2020-05-21 06:21:00"><n>The Guesthouse: Bianca Resa &amp; Juan Lucho</n>    <k>Nestled in the Spanish countryside, there?s a Guesthouse where visitors enjoy more than just the sunshine on their bodies. Come alone, come with a friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 06:21:00" d="2020-05-21 06:50:00"><n>Sweet Petite Girls: Cheryl S &amp; Kristof Cale</n>    <k>These young beauties are starting to discover their sexuality, exploring their bodies and seek new limits. Director Roman Sluka captured these teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 06:50:00" d="2020-05-21 07:22:00"><n>Special Moments: The Apple</n>    <k>A truly romantic sex scene by Dusk TV's own porn for women label: &quot;Ooh la la&quot;. Passionate, realistic lovemaking for women whom enjoy romantic sex scenes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 07:22:00" d="2020-05-21 07:37:00"><n>It's Complicated: Yhivi &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>Shauna (Gracie Glam) has been having casual sex with her handsome friend Will, biding her time until she can finally make a move on her long time crush Brandon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 07:37:00" d="2020-05-21 07:51:00"><n>Cinema X Pigalle</n><t>S</t>    <k>The piano goes on as an old porn movie is projected just for their own private arousal. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 07:51:00" d="2020-05-21 08:22:00"><n>Swing with me: Ava dalush, Logan Pierce &amp; James Deen</n>    <k>Four segments on the sexual fantasies of husbands and wives. Siri let's her husband listen to her sexual exploits at work, Romi has sex with her co-worker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 08:22:00" d="2020-05-21 08:51:00"><n>Beauty Of Nature: Eveline Dellai &amp; Nick Vargas</n><t>L</t>    <k>Wondering what it take to have fantastic sex that you will remmeber for the rest of your life? Watch and learn as Desire Media shows you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 08:51:00" d="2020-05-21 09:12:00"><n>Tease: Ava Austen &amp; Luke Hardy</n>    <k>If according to Shakespeare, clothes make the man, then without doubt lingerie make the woman. Skyler is the gorgeous young owner and head designer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 09:12:00" d="2020-05-21 09:31:00"><n>Pure Milf 5: Johnny Castle &amp; Capri Cavanni</n><t>L</t>    <k>These pure MILFs always get what they want as you will see in these five tantalizing scenes. These sexy ladies show you the true meaning of seduction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 09:31:00" d="2020-05-21 09:51:00"><n>Hard Rain</n><t>L</t>    <k>Showering, always better in company! A super sensual sex scene with a leading roll for pornstar Juan Lucho. Porn for women by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 09:51:00" d="2020-05-21 10:10:00"><n>Girls Sex Tricks: Marta La Croft &amp; Xavi Tralla</n><t>L</t>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us on her first film as director for Thagson with a vibrant female friendly porn story which will take place in the streets of Barcelona</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 10:10:00" d="2020-05-21 10:32:00"><n>Love and Loss: Maddy O'Reilly &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>With more twists and turns than the German autobahn, Love and Loss follows the story of Lanie and Alex, an ex-cop involved in the shooting of Lanie's ex-lover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 10:32:00" d="2020-05-21 10:42:00"><n>Be A Hero</n><t>S</t>    <k>Anneke woke up horny and spotted her boyfriend's go pro lying around. What will she do with it? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 10:42:00" d="2020-05-21 10:59:00"><n>Exposure: Security Measures</n>    <k>In a world where couples would rather play with their phones than each other, one woman uses her technology skills for good, nudging distracted lovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 10:59:00" d="2020-05-21 11:17:00"><n>Room 208: Pamela Sanchez &amp; Sasha blonnde</n>    <k>An explicit porn for women video by Dusk TV's female friendly porn label &quot;Oh la la&quot;. Romantic sex films depicting real excitement and passion. A realistic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 11:17:00" d="2020-05-21 11:44:00"><n>The Passionate Three: Gina Gerson, Nick Gill &amp; Adam Black</n>    <k>Sinful trinity's enjoying a triad of erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 11:44:00" d="2020-05-21 12:17:00"><n>The Babysitter 8: Dana DeArmond &amp; Xander Corvus</n>    <k>Mona is a bitter woman who hates her ex-husband and has no qualms about bad mouthing him to her new babysitter, Alice. What happens when Alice catches</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 12:17:00" d="2020-05-21 12:47:00"><n>Desire: Tasha Reign &amp; Johnny Castle</n>    <k>Intense feelings of desire causes two bodies melting into one, shivering of pleasure with every touch and longing for more. A female friendly porn scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 12:47:00" d="2020-05-21 13:11:00"><n>Milf Affairs: Luke Hotrod &amp; Candi Coxx</n>    <k>Wouldn't be all like to be a MILF and have adventures with younger guys? Female director Anjali Kara delivers a cinematic porn movie in her trademark style</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 13:11:00" d="2020-05-21 13:30:00"><n>Camera Angle: Ivy Labelle &amp; Roman Nomar</n>    <k>Fiction and reality seem to blend when Hollywood actor Peter gets a concussion. His visions of heart-racing, sweat inducing sex seem very real though</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 13:30:00" d="2020-05-21 13:49:00"><n>Fit: Samantha Bentley &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>You are running on the beach, bathed in the beautiful sunshine. You feel alive and energized ? what could be better? Get outside. Get active</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 13:49:00" d="2020-05-21 14:02:00"><n>The Ultimate Kink</n><t>S</t>    <k>An adventure with a female couple who have tried it all when it comes to sex - except for a man. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, kinky female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 14:02:00" d="2020-05-21 14:32:00"><n>Wet!: A Wet Suprise</n>    <k>Sinful couples enjoy having seks when it pours? What's on your bucket list? A SinfulXXX film by Roma Amor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 14:32:00" d="2020-05-21 14:53:00"><n>Sex With Friends: Three Wishes</n>    <k>When old college friends meet again they take the time to rekindle and explore each other?s bodies and sexual boundries. A reunion you don?t want to miss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 14:53:00" d="2020-05-21 15:17:00"><n>Anal Lovers: Liona &amp; Vega</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A realistic porn scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 15:17:00" d="2020-05-21 15:31:00"><n>Never Forgotten: Maddy Oreilly &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>Robert can’t stop thinking about Elizabeth, his first love during the 1940’s. An argument teared the perfect couple apart and decades later Robert is still</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 15:31:00" d="2020-05-21 15:54:00"><n>Unwrap Me</n>    <k>Put the music on. And let yourself go wrapped in glossy vinyl bandages. Red and bright, that?s what excites me. Take them off quickly and fuck me</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 15:54:00" d="2020-05-21 16:20:00"><n>Everyday Turn-Ons: Oral Fixation</n><t>L</t>    <k>Nelson loves the taste of Jackie?s body, but since her last boyfriend never went down on her, she?s become shy and self-conscious about oral sex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 16:20:00" d="2020-05-21 16:47:00"><n>Sexual Bliss: Claudia &amp; Nic</n>    <k>Four passionate couples in a Sinful XXX film by Roma Amor. Beautiful, Arty and very sexy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 16:47:00" d="2020-05-21 17:19:00"><n>Silver Shoes: Undressed</n>    <k>This award-winning explicit erotic trilogy from Jennifer Lyon Bell intertwines three short female friendly porn stories about the carnal power of what we wear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 17:19:00" d="2020-05-21 17:35:00"><n>Memory Files of You</n><t>S</t>    <k>A deeply moving ode to loves lost, and irrevocable, unobtainable desires through Virtual Reality. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 17:35:00" d="2020-05-21 17:59:00"><n>Question</n>    <k>Thomas stands on the street. When Ferrera joins him we soon learn what he was anticipating. He drops to one knee, holds up a shiny little box, and after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 17:59:00" d="2020-05-21 18:29:00"><n>Sensuous Seduction: Messaging</n>    <k>A sensual massage is the gateway to your partners naughtiness and desires. Watch how this sexy couple is physically expressing their love to each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 18:29:00" d="2020-05-21 19:01:00"><n>Nymphomaniac Diaries: Nightmares</n>    <k>The blond Katerina loves sex so much that her dreams are filled with kinky stuff, but her sexual fantasies with men and women become even better</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 19:01:00" d="2020-05-21 19:19:00"><n>HouseMates: Sicilia &amp; Satine Spark</n>    <k>After a painful break up Jess flees to the city and is thrown into a world where hiding away is not an option. Her new housemates Ollie and Saskia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 19:19:00" d="2020-05-21 19:44:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies 2: Renata Fox &amp; Vincent Vega</n>    <k>These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. An erotic sex scene from Favorite Fantasies 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 19:44:00" d="2020-05-21 20:10:00"><n>Sex in white: Erica Fontes &amp; Miquel Zayas</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us with her ?Sex In White? productions, where sexual encounters take place in a pure and white scenery, so the main focus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 20:10:00" d="2020-05-21 20:24:00"><n>Never Forgotten: Katana &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>Robert can’t stop thinking about Elizabeth, his first love during the 1940’s. An argument teared the perfect couple apart and decades later Robert is still</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 20:24:00" d="2020-05-21 20:53:00"><n>The Stepmother 9: Kimberly Kane &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>Emma has a dark secret. Her fiancée--an older, distinguished gentleman--doesn't know anything about her salacious past. But when his son meets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 20:53:00" d="2020-05-21 21:06:00"><n>Fräulein O</n><t>S</t>    <k>The unbearable August Spanish heat. who wouldn't be seduced by the local boy with a bucket full of ice! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 21:06:00" d="2020-05-21 21:25:00"><n>Recipe for Romance: Gracie Glam &amp; Levi Cash</n>    <k>Love is cooking in Carolina's kitchen, and it's wonderfully delicious! Carolina is a passionate cook who is patiently waiting for Mr. Right. But what if Mr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 21:25:00" d="2020-05-21 21:50:00"><n>Inside: Frida Sante &amp; Alberta Blanco</n>    <k>Welcome to The Retreat: where curious minds come to play. Plug in and turn on to explore a virtual reality experience where you can be anyone, go anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 21:50:00" d="2020-05-21 22:16:00"><n>Afternoon Love: Angel Piaf &amp; Max D</n>    <k>Watch this straight couple enjoy each other and make their time together worthwhile. A real life couple having realistic sex. A porn for women film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 22:16:00" d="2020-05-21 22:45:00"><n>So Wet Beside Her: Victoria Pure &amp; Charlie Red</n>    <k>These girls love, lust, lick, becoming almost one in this sensual piece of erotica. Sinful Studio making art again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 22:45:00" d="2020-05-21 22:58:00"><n>Candles</n>    <k>Candles always set the tone for a romantic evening with your partner. Sometimes some candles more than others? Romantic porn for women by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 22:58:00" d="2020-05-21 23:30:00"><n>Remy's Angels: Lexi Belle, Remy LaCroix &amp; Dani Daniels</n>    <k>Watch the beautiful brunette Remy Lacroix explore her inner desires with some of her closest girlfriends in this all girl sexual adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 23:30:00" d="2020-05-21 23:54:00"><n>Weekend: Katy Rose, Lexi Dona &amp; Dominica Phoenix</n>    <k>Shot in Portugal, episode 4 of The Weekend, &quot;Time for Love,&quot; begins with a new day. As Lutro and Dominika prepare breakfast, Lexie and Jason are enjoying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-21 23:54:00" d="2020-05-22 00:10:00"><n>The Fantasy Project: Vivienne L, Max &amp; Harley Jay</n><t>L</t>    <k>Have you ever been in a threesome? These three lovers show what it could be like if your fantasies came true. This erotic video by Louise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 00:10:00" d="2020-05-22 00:34:00"><n>I Love My Hotwife: Sovereign Syre, Xander Crovus &amp; Rich Calhoum</n>    <k>Four segments on the sexual fantasies of husbands and wives. A married couple hires a sexy male escort, Siri let?s her husband listen to her sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 00:34:00" d="2020-05-22 00:58:00"><n>He Loves To Watch: India Summer &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>This couple has found a unique way to keep the spark in their marriage. Passionate sex and powerful orgasms for everybody!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 00:58:00" d="2020-05-22 01:24:00"><n>Friends And Lovers: AJ Applegate, Blair Williams &amp; Small Hands</n>    <k>Caroline and Matt have been best friends since college. Through break-ups they've been there for each other. But they have yet to find true love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 01:24:00" d="2020-05-22 01:43:00"><n>Housemates 2 : Alexei Jackson, Stella Cox &amp; Amber Nevada</n>    <k>New house. New rules. Artist James moves to the UK in search of his ex-girlfriend and finds himself sharing a house with four incredibly attractive women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 01:43:00" d="2020-05-22 02:10:00"><n>My Wife's First Girlfriend: Dana Vespoli &amp; Melissa Moore</n>    <k>Jenna?s secret desires become unleashed when her husband catches her masturbating to lesbian porn. When Jimmy notices a growing attraction between</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 02:10:00" d="2020-05-22 02:44:00"><n>Not to Innocent: Angel Piaf &amp; Max D</n>    <k>This scene is a true pleasure to all the senses representing natural sex full of intimacy, romance, chemistry and lots of naughtiness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 02:44:00" d="2020-05-22 03:04:00"><n>Sun stroke: Michelle And Jade</n>    <k>These girls are trying to beat the spanish summer heat at their beautiful summerhouse in the woods. But cooling down appears to be a major challenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 03:04:00" d="2020-05-22 03:33:00"><n>Intimate Moments: Leona &amp; Peter</n>    <k>Intimate moments for beautiful couples while exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A porn for women scene from Intimate Moments by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 03:33:00" d="2020-05-22 03:58:00"><n>After Forever: Peny Pax &amp; Derrick Pierce</n>    <k>When Derrick plans a romantic weekend in his vacation house he soon finds out that his ex Penny had the same idea with her new partner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 03:58:00" d="2020-05-22 04:28:00"><n>Voyeuristic Desires: Tina Kay, Wicky Angel &amp; Steve Q</n>    <k>Sinful trinity's enjoying a triad of erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 04:28:00" d="2020-05-22 05:10:00"><n>Restraint 2: Lucy Tyler &amp; Richie Calhoun</n>    <k>After placing an ad in search of a dominant man, Lucy finds herself blindfolded and restrained in the home of a mysterious stranger. An adventurous sexual</k>  </p>
</a>
