<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="52" t="2020-05-26 04:43:09"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 05:37:00" d="2020-06-02 05:54:00"><n>Win A Date With Sofia Blake: Olivia Austin &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>A-list Hollywood actress Sofia Blake (Olivia Austin) is having the worst day of her life and the paparazzi have made sure to plaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 05:54:00" d="2020-06-02 06:11:00"><n>The Couchsurfer</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: Making the most of your house guests has never been so sexy. In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 06:11:00" d="2020-06-02 06:31:00"><n>Tease: Ava Austen &amp; Luke Hardy</n>    <k>If according to Shakespeare, clothes make the man, then without doubt lingerie make the woman. Skyler is the gorgeous young owner and head designer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 06:31:00" d="2020-06-02 06:53:00"><n>Anticipation: Ella Hughes &amp; Marc Rose</n>    <k>Anticipation is a romantic porn for women movie directed by DiSanto for Daring! These pornstars are some of the very best players in the Adult Industry today</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 06:53:00" d="2020-06-02 07:15:00"><n>Elevator Dreams</n>    <k>When a guy meets an attractive girl in an elevator, she ignores him. But in his dreams all she want to do is having kinky, rough sex. A female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 07:15:00" d="2020-06-02 07:36:00"><n>Facade: Cassidy Klein</n>    <k>Amber and her friend Lindsay are average college students?who happen to moonlight as sexy webcam models. This complicates things when they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 07:36:00" d="2020-06-02 07:45:00"><n>Can Vampires Smell My Period?</n><t>S</t>    <k>This is no teenage dream. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual confessions of her viewers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 07:45:00" d="2020-06-02 08:14:00"><n>Remy's Angels: Remy Lacroix &amp; Abella Danger</n>    <k>Watch the beautiful brunette Remy Lacroix explore her inner desires with some of her closest girlfriends in this all girl sexual adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 08:14:00" d="2020-06-02 08:37:00"><n>Sexy and Sensual: Sheri Vee &amp; Nikolas</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. A porn for women scene from Sexy and Sensual by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 08:37:00" d="2020-06-02 08:57:00"><n>The Guesthouse: Julia Roca &amp; Sicilia</n>    <k>Nestled in the Spanish countryside, there?s a Guesthouse where visitors enjoy more than just the sunshine on their bodies. Come alone, come with a friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 08:57:00" d="2020-06-02 09:18:00"><n>Racetrack</n>    <k>Helena and Thomas are in the middle of a fierce video game battle, but when his car begins to pull away from the pack and her chances of victory dwindle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 09:18:00" d="2020-06-02 09:38:00"><n>Ouija</n>    <k>My girlfriend asked me to play with a Ouija board tonight. I?m dying to have some wild sex here on the floor. Let?s ask the ghosts what they think about it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 09:38:00" d="2020-06-02 09:52:00"><n>The Bathhouse</n><t>L</t>    <k>Always wanted to know about anal sex, but never tried? This film shows how nice anal massage can be. A romantic porn film full of bubbles and soap</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 09:52:00" d="2020-06-02 10:04:00"><n>When it Comes to you: Zoey Monroe &amp; Ryan Mclane</n>    <k>When It Comes To You is a captivating and scintillating story of a woman torn between two men who both profess great love. Directed by Stormy Daniels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 10:04:00" d="2020-06-02 10:16:00"><n>Car Sex Generation</n><t>S</t>    <k>Juan Lucho and Julia Roca show exactly why sex in a car is so exciting. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 10:16:00" d="2020-06-02 10:40:00"><n>Inside: Julia Roca &amp; Natalia Ferrari</n>    <k>Welcome to The Retreat: where curious minds come to play. Plug in and turn on to explore a virtual reality experience where you can be anyone, go anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 10:40:00" d="2020-06-02 11:05:00"><n>Special Moments: The Second Date</n>    <k>What happens after the second date? Find out in this new romantic sex scene by AlexanFilm for Dusk TV's own female friendly porn label: Ooh la la</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 11:05:00" d="2020-06-02 11:36:00"><n>Private Spa: Carlo Minaldi &amp; Rebecca Volpetti</n>    <k>This beautiful couple enjoys every bit of their private spa. We like it that hot! A delightful video by studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 11:36:00" d="2020-06-02 12:09:00"><n>My Girlfriends Mother 11: Gina Valentina &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>When Tylers sexy but demanding girlfriend Marley cheats on him, he takes solace in the arms and incredible hot body of Marley?s mom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 12:09:00" d="2020-06-02 12:59:00"><n>Lesbian Surrender: Nikita Bellucci &amp; Sovereign Syre</n>    <k>Watch as tattooed angel Ela Darling realizes her taboo fantasies, how French stunner Nikita Bellucci barely speaks English and how blond bombshell Aaliyah</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 12:59:00" d="2020-06-02 13:25:00"><n>All For You: Ella Hughes &amp; Max Deeds</n>    <k>When every thought is focused on one special person, thoughts quickly turn into fantasy. Memories of special moments become the seed of a sexual encounter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 13:25:00" d="2020-06-02 13:51:00"><n>The Escort 2: Presley Hart &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>When a beautiful young woman enters the escorting profession, she's put off by her first client. But under the tutelage of a smart and capable madam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 13:51:00" d="2020-06-02 14:08:00"><n>Delilahs Top Tips: Lynna Nilsson &amp; Clarke Kent</n><t>O</t>    <k>Delilah is the nation's naughtiest agony aunt dedicated to solving the nation's more. ntimate dilemmas. She whips two city workers into a frenzy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 14:08:00" d="2020-06-02 14:22:00"><n>La Reine Des Culottes</n><t>S</t>    <k>A woman's lingerie can say a lot about her - and about her neighbour. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 14:22:00" d="2020-06-02 14:54:00"><n>Colors Of Eden: Lady Dee &amp; Thomas</n><t>L</t>    <k>A gorgeous couple having breathtakingly hot sex, in colorful surroundings, showing both intimacy and sexual fulfilment in every little detail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 14:54:00" d="2020-06-02 15:15:00"><n>Pleasure Professionals 2: Tiffany Doll &amp; Marc Rose</n>    <k>A kinky couple's porn film from Joybear. Every summer Mrs ERC bolts to the countryside to relax and unwind. A secluded hotel provides the perfect getaway</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 15:15:00" d="2020-06-02 15:43:00"><n>I Love You: Antonia Sainz &amp; Ricky</n>    <k>These beautiful desireable men and women are highly confident and have all the experience to bring you in a state of trance. A female friendly porn film by Desire media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 15:43:00" d="2020-06-02 15:56:00"><n>Off limits: Keira Nicole &amp; Small Hands</n>    <k>Jesse is the quintessential bad boy. His band is the next big thing in Los Angeles and he is on a fast track to stardom. He then meets Caitlyn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 15:56:00" d="2020-06-02 16:15:00"><n>Heavy Contact</n>    <k>That feeling when you have a lot of contact with someone and the connection gets even heavier when you meet in real life? Yes, that's passion to the max</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 16:15:00" d="2020-06-02 16:33:00"><n>Delilahs Top Tips: Emma Leigh &amp; Alexei Jackson</n><t>O</t>    <k>Delilah is the nation's naughtiest agony aunt dedicated to solving the nation's more. ntimate dilemmas. She whips two city workers into a frenzy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 16:33:00" d="2020-06-02 17:12:00"><n>Nymphomaniac Diaries: Daydreaming</n>    <k>The blond Katerina loves sex so much that her dreams are filled with kinky stuff, but her sexual fantasies with men and women become even better</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 17:12:00" d="2020-06-02 17:32:00"><n u="Ages of Sex: Sex at">Ages of Sex: Sex at (50)</n>    <k>The Ages of Sex is a porn for women film by Thagson. 4 Well known directors will direct a short which represents a woman?s sexual reality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 17:32:00" d="2020-06-02 17:48:00"><n>I found your mother on tinder</n><t>S</t>    <k>The legendary Mrs. Robinson brought to life by the most modern of dating apps. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 17:48:00" d="2020-06-02 18:23:00"><n>A Mothers Love 2: Janet Mason &amp; Bruce Venture</n>    <k>There?s nothing better than a mother?s love. And mothers are always willing to give their love. This Janet Mason scene is breathtaking sexy. A Pure Passion film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 18:23:00" d="2020-06-02 18:43:00"><n>Afternoon Love: Lexi Dona &amp; Thomas Reed</n>    <k>A realistic couple with realistic sex. A romantic porn for women film by Dusk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 18:43:00" d="2020-06-02 19:08:00"><n>Passion Noir: Nick &amp; Karol</n>    <k>A fantastic new romantic porn film from Roma Amor for Sinful XXX. The naked body as an art form and sex as a masterpiece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 19:08:00" d="2020-06-02 19:27:00"><n>Tease: Victoria Summers &amp; Marc Rose</n>    <k>If according to Shakespeare, clothes make the man, then without doubt lingerie make the woman. Skyler is the gorgeous young owner and head designer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 19:27:00" d="2020-06-02 19:56:00"><n>Beauty Of Nature: Eveline Dellai &amp; Nick Vargas</n><t>L</t>    <k>Wondering what it take to have fantastic sex that you will remmeber for the rest of your life? Watch and learn as Desire Media shows you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 19:56:00" d="2020-06-02 20:09:00"><n>The Fantasy Project: Kara &amp; Devon</n>    <k>Massage is the ultimate sensation of touch and the complete focus on you, your body and your pleasure. Your pleasure only. A true female friendly porn video</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 20:09:00" d="2020-06-02 20:31:00"><n>Camera Angle: Ryan Keely &amp; Ryan Mclane</n>    <k>Fiction and reality seem to blend when Hollywood actor Peter gets a concussion. His visions of heart-racing, sweat inducing sex seem very real though</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 20:31:00" d="2020-06-02 20:59:00"><n>Student bodies 2: Casey Calvert &amp; Chad Alva</n>    <k>Kyra hates everything - school, the teachers, and especially Zadie who is messing around with the boy she?d like to date. It?s time to get busy and screw</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 20:59:00" d="2020-06-02 21:14:00"><n>Hello Pool Boy</n>    <k>From XConfessions 3: “I clean your pool. Easy going, good hearted, always horny.” In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 21:14:00" d="2020-06-02 21:34:00"><n>Love is in the Air: Maddy O'Reilly &amp; Xander Corvus</n>    <k>When her fiance gets sucked into never-ending conversation at a friend's party, a woman lures him to the bedroom for a passionate sexual encounter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 21:34:00" d="2020-06-02 21:57:00"><n>Positions: Second</n>    <k>While finding inspiration at a dancer?s retreat, the ballet dancer Florence soon realises she?s not the only one who could do with practising</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 21:57:00" d="2020-06-02 22:20:00"><n>The Party</n>    <k>A breasty Spanish beauty can’t get any sleep because of the loud party next door. But when she sees her attractive neighbor her angry feelings fade away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 22:20:00" d="2020-06-02 22:42:00"><n>Make Me Sweat: Kristof &amp; Kattie</n>    <k>A passionate couple in a Sinful XXX film by Roma Amor. Beautiful, Arty and very sexy. Porn for women with a focus on the humand body</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 22:42:00" d="2020-06-02 23:05:00"><n>Hugman</n>    <k>My girlfriend and I are not serious people, we like to have fun in our lives and we are always playing tricks and games to spice up our life. Playful porn by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 23:05:00" d="2020-06-02 23:14:00"><n>Dear Brother In Law</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lana is the perfect bourgeois wife who ends up feeling attracted by her messy brother-in-law. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 23:14:00" d="2020-06-02 23:39:00"><n>Love Me Forever: Lily Cat &amp; Vega</n><t>L</t>    <k>Romantic, passionate love. These couples show each other how much they enjoy each others company. A romantic porn video by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-02 23:39:00" d="2020-06-03 00:00:00"><n>Camera Angle: Ivy Labelle &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>Fiction and reality seem to blend when Hollywood actor Peter gets a concussion. His visions of heart-racing, sweat inducing sex seem very real though.</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-03 00:00:00" d="2020-06-03 00:19:00"><n>Corporate Bonding: Tamara Grace &amp; Max Deeds</n>    <k>Good teamwork can lead to surprising situations. Rookie lawyer Leyla organises a team-building weekend by the beach for her and her firm of London lawyers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-03 00:19:00" d="2020-06-03 22:42:00"><n>Coming of age</n><t>S</t>    <k>A coming of age tale of young lust, farewells and new encounters. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual</k>  </p>
</a>
