<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="65" t="2019-07-11 00:22:41"><p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 05:03:00" d="2019-07-16 05:25:00"><n>Positions: Fifth</n>    <k>While finding inspiration at a dancer?s retreat, the ballet dancer Florence soon realises she?s not the only one who could do with practising some new positions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 05:25:00" d="2019-07-16 05:44:00"><n>Pure Sexual Attraction: Bruce Venture &amp; Veronica Radke</n>    <k>Embark on an exciting journey of pure sexual attraction as five breathtaking girls are captured in five scenes that set the standard for high definition erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 05:44:00" d="2019-07-16 06:11:00"><n>First Summer Love 2: Jenny De Lugo &amp; Lexi Dona</n>    <k>The sequel of First Summer Love brings you more tantalizing scenes. The hot sun on their naked skin brings these girls in a state of permanent arousal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 06:11:00" d="2019-07-16 06:29:00"><n>4 Passionate Women: First Time</n>    <k>A new scene by Award Winning director Lara Tinelli for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 06:29:00" d="2019-07-16 06:54:00"><n>Our Summer of Love: Sienna Day &amp; Simony Diamond</n>    <k>A hot couple travels abroad and adores the new country, but they enjoy each other even more and especially the new sexy people they meet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 06:54:00" d="2019-07-16 07:17:00"><n>Positions: First</n>    <k>While finding inspiration at a dancer?s retreat, the ballet dancer Florence soon realises she?s not the only one who could do with practising some new positions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 07:17:00" d="2019-07-16 07:34:00"><n>Love Lust Longing: Allie Haze &amp; Jake Jace</n>    <k>Love Lust &amp; Longing takes place in a seemingly innocent Bed &amp; Breakfast. Rachel a prostitute who has set up shop in the master bedroom falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 07:34:00" d="2019-07-16 07:51:00"><n>Strip Chess</n>    <k>Are you up for a chess game? Join Silvia Rubi and Gabe Romero in this intimate scene full of chemistry, where the game (and the increasing lack of clothes)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 07:51:00" d="2019-07-16 08:26:00"><n>Mother Daughter affair: Chanel Preston &amp; Steven St. Croix</n>    <k>Eric has an interesting dilemma. He?s going with a smoking hot woman who has an over-sexed erotic devilish daughter, he just can?t resist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 08:26:00" d="2019-07-16 08:48:00"><n>4 Passionate Woman: Feeling Hot</n>    <k>A new scene by Award Winning director Lara Tinelli for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 08:48:00" d="2019-07-16 09:40:00"><n>An Arabian Night</n><t>L</t>    <k>Always wanted to know about anal sex, but never tried? This film shows how nice anal massage can be</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 09:40:00" d="2019-07-16 10:03:00"><n>Dude Looks Like A Lady</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 10:03:00" d="2019-07-16 10:26:00"><n>Right Now</n>    <k>A tranquil scene from daily life. Densen knows exactly what would enhance this quiet morning, and she knows exactly when she wants it: &quot;Right Now.&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 10:26:00" d="2019-07-16 10:38:00"><n>Dominate Me</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 10:38:00" d="2019-07-16 10:58:00"><n>Only women can: Tess Lyndon &amp; Susan Snow</n>    <k>Porna award-nominated director Kendo portrays the world of latex with a beautiful, filmic dark side and incredibly attractive women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 10:58:00" d="2019-07-16 11:20:00"><n>Quartet: Controlled</n>    <k>Penelope boards a plane from London to Budapest, eager to perform with her three best friends from music academy. Reunited, the foursome soon remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 11:20:00" d="2019-07-16 11:37:00"><n>Cabaret Desire: Lady Diamond and Mario Mentrup</n>    <k>Welcome to nightclub Cabaret Desire ? indulge yourself with poets and their erotic tales filled with passion and temptation. A film by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 11:37:00" d="2019-07-16 11:56:00"><n>Trouble X 2: Abigai lMac &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>On his first day back in the dating game, Nick meets not one but TWO beautiful women. Olivia (Abigail Mac) is hot, sexy, and confident. Jenny (Cherie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 11:56:00" d="2019-07-16 12:27:00"><n>Not to Innocent: Ally &amp; Max D</n>    <k>A new scene by Dawn for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 12:27:00" d="2019-07-16 12:39:00"><n>Ibiza Splash Crush</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 12:39:00" d="2019-07-16 13:07:00"><n>The Teacher 4: Bobbi Starr &amp; Manuel Ferrara</n>    <k>Physicist Manuel Ferrara is on the verge of solving physics? biggest mysteries, and smitten young students treat him like a rock star. Obsessive young</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 13:07:00" d="2019-07-16 13:32:00"><n>Sexology: Mira, Choky Ice &amp; Tifanny Naylor</n>    <k>For her graduation project, sexology student Tess researches how the female orgasm works. What do women really want in bed? Scene from a film by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 13:32:00" d="2019-07-16 14:05:00"><n>True Intensions: Bentley &amp; Max Deeds</n>    <k>Een zeer gewaardeerde film van Erotikara. Natuurlijk mooi en intiem spelen de koppels met elkaar vol overgave. Liefde, lust, passie en fantastische orgasmes!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 14:05:00" d="2019-07-16 14:30:00"><n>Special Moments: The Second Date</n>    <k>A new scene by AlexanFilm for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 14:30:00" d="2019-07-16 14:45:00"><n>Let's Make a Porno</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 14:45:00" d="2019-07-16 15:10:00"><n>Bedtime Stories 3: Marry Queen &amp; Eileen Sue</n>    <k>A scene from Bedtime Stories 3 by Daring! Sexy bedtime stories!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 15:10:00" d="2019-07-16 15:38:00"><n>Sex Sinners and Saints: Nathaly Cherie &amp; Steve</n>    <k>Not only is the church the perfect place to confess your sins, it's also the perfect location to have sensational sex. These couples sin in church, moaning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 15:38:00" d="2019-07-16 16:02:00"><n>Breakfast for Two</n>    <k>These girlfriends just wanna have fun. With each other. Especially while having a sleepover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 16:02:00" d="2019-07-16 16:37:00"><n>Summer Lovers: Carla Coz</n>    <k>When it's summer the temperature rises, you wear less clothes and get aroused much easier. Is there anything hotter than having outdoor sex surrounded by nature? A scene from an Intimate Encounters film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 16:37:00" d="2019-07-16 16:55:00"><n>K</n>    <k>Inspiration can reach us when we are less expecting it. The simple vision of a white sheet of paper stresses me a bit as I am a writer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 16:55:00" d="2019-07-16 17:14:00"><n>The Guesthouse: Julia Roca &amp; Sicilia</n>    <k>Nestled in the Spanish countryside, there?s a Guesthouse where visitors enjoy more than just the sunshine on their bodies. Come alone, come with a friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 17:14:00" d="2019-07-16 17:26:00"><n>Madmen Porn</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 17:26:00" d="2019-07-16 17:46:00"><n>4 Passionate Women: Next To You</n>    <k>A new scene by Award Winning director Lara Tinelli for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 17:46:00" d="2019-07-16 18:01:00"><n>Trouble X 2: Britney Amber &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>On his first day back in the dating game, Nick meets not one but TWO beautiful women. Olivia (Abigail Mac) is hot, sexy, and confident. Jenny (Cherie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 18:01:00" d="2019-07-16 18:30:00"><n>Remy's Angels: Remy Lacroix &amp; Abella Danger</n>    <k>Watch the beautiful brunette Remy Lacroix explore her inner desires with some of her closest girlfriends in this all girl sexual adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 18:30:00" d="2019-07-16 18:48:00"><n>Among The Bushes</n>    <k>He?s always sitting in this park, surrounded by the trees, reading a book, cute and charismatic. He?s big, tall and handsome. I?ll take him between the trees, I?ll make him take off his clothes and I?ll fuck him surrounded by leaves, sunlight and dog walkers. A Verso Cinema film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 18:48:00" d="2019-07-16 19:14:00"><n>Sexology: Nick Lange &amp; Kathia Knobili</n>    <k>For her graduation project, sexology student Tess researches how the female orgasm works. What do women really want in bed? Scene from a film by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 19:14:00" d="2019-07-16 19:27:00"><n>Take me drunk</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 19:27:00" d="2019-07-16 19:54:00"><n>Come Closer: My Sunny Side</n>    <k>What are you going to do when all of a suddon both of you are at home and have nothing to do? Exactly, enjoy each other and make your time together worthwhile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 19:54:00" d="2019-07-16 20:19:00"><n>Raw: Denisa &amp; Radek</n>    <k>Beautiful images of sexual tenderness in its pure but raw way. Close-ups of gorgeous toned bodies and horny sweat. One of Sinful?s most beautiful productions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 20:19:00" d="2019-07-16 20:32:00"><n>Latex Sessions</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 20:32:00" d="2019-07-16 20:49:00"><n>When it Comes to you: Hope Howell &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>When It Comes To You is a captivating and scintillating story of a woman torn between two men who both profess great love. Directed by Stormy Daniels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 20:49:00" d="2019-07-16 21:20:00"><n>Hair Down There: Nadine Sage &amp; Bruce Venture</n><t>L</t>    <k>She's got hair down there, and yes, we love that natural look! Let Mia Malkova, Nadine Sage, Tracey Sweet, and Anastasia Morna show you how their naturally</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 21:20:00" d="2019-07-16 21:58:00"><n>Couples Massage: Vanessa Decker &amp; Ricky</n>    <k>A crackling fire, relaxing music and a lot of warm oil for a total body massage. Delicious. These beautiful couples can’t get enough of it too. Please do try this at home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 21:58:00" d="2019-07-16 22:18:00"><n>Fill Me Up With Your Orgasm: Vanda Lust &amp; James Brossman</n>    <k>Such a waste to just get a little bit? Whether it be a refill on your drink, your gas tank, or your favorite piece of pussy, you gotta fill it to the brim! It's going to be a sticky situation when they get a fill of love butter that they crave! A Pure Passion film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 22:18:00" d="2019-07-16 22:40:00"><n>Hollywood Ending: Mercedes Carrera &amp; Jay Smooth</n>    <k>Childhood lovers Rebecca and Tommy are finally getting the acting success they always wanted. But their love is put to the test when fame, fortune</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 22:40:00" d="2019-07-16 22:52:00"><n>Girlfriends: Casey Calvert &amp; Sasha Heart</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Small town girl Jamie (Casey Calvert) has made the difficult decision to tell her parents that she is in a same sex relationship. Unfortunately her family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 22:52:00" d="2019-07-16 23:06:00"><n>El que no ama no conoce a Dios</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 23:06:00" d="2019-07-16 23:31:00"><n>Secret Sex Society: Cintia Shapiro &amp; Bel Gris</n>    <k>When colourful people meet and share their colourful fantasies. Starring the hot blooded Spanish beauty Julia Roca</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 23:31:00" d="2019-07-16 23:52:00"><n>Make Me Sweat: Nathaly &amp; Angelo</n>    <k>Four passionate couples in a Sinful XXX film by Roma Amor. Beautiful, Arty and very sexy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-16 23:52:00" d="2019-07-17 00:13:00"><n>If You Only Knew: Logan Pierce &amp; Allie Haze</n>    <k>For many years, the loyal and hardworking Kellie has been Mark?s assistant, and in love with him. Mark, however, is oblivious to this</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-17 00:13:00" d="2019-07-17 00:40:00"><n>All For You: Jess West &amp; Ryan Ryder</n>    <k>All For You? is an assembly of exotic, intense, romantic, couple-friendly scenes that highlight the intimacy of lovers. When every thought is focused</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-17 00:40:00" d="2019-07-17 01:07:00"><n>Tenderness: Ria Sunn &amp; Jayden Cox</n>    <k>A new scene by Roma Woodcock for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-17 01:07:00" d="2019-07-17 01:23:00"><n>The Guesthouse: Bianca Resa &amp; Juan Lucho</n>    <k>Nestled in the Spanish countryside, there?s a Guesthouse where visitors enjoy more than just the sunshine on their bodies. Come alone, come with a friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-17 01:23:00" d="2019-07-17 01:47:00"><n>A Lesbian Romance: Shyla Jennings &amp; Mia Malkova</n>    <k>When feelings develop after a one-night-stand, Kenna puts her heart on the line and fights for the woman she wants. Penny?s secret attraction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-17 01:47:00" d="2019-07-17 01:57:00"><n>Sit Down, Shut Up and Watch</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-17 01:57:00" d="2019-07-17 02:15:00"><n>Delilahs Top Tips: Jess West &amp; Danielle Ashlea Maye</n><t>O</t>    <k>Delilah is the nation's naughtiest agony aunt dedicated to solving the nation's more. ntimate dilemmas. She whips two city workers into a frenzy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-17 02:15:00" d="2019-07-17 02:34:00"><n>After Sunbathing</n>    <k>It's just another, relaxed and uneventful, summer day. Shapely blonde Mima A and her companion, Matt Ice, lounge poolside ? nowhere to go, no friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-17 02:34:00" d="2019-07-17 02:55:00"><n>In the limelight 2: Abigaile &amp; Denis Reed</n><t>L</t>    <k>Daring! Pure in the limelight shows you a spectacular selection of nine of our best scenes. The most beautiful girls surpass your wildest dreams to fulfill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-17 02:55:00" d="2019-07-17 03:29:00"><n>Not to Innocent: Angel Piaf &amp; Max D</n>    <k>A new scene by Dawn for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-17 03:29:00" d="2019-07-17 04:02:00"><n>Sexy Massage Fantasies: Smooth Seduction</n>    <k>A beautiful sensual film by Roma Amor for SinfulXXX. In this scene the combination of a blindfold and lots of oil prove to be the perfect ingredients</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-17 04:02:00" d="2019-07-17 04:22:00"><n>Pleasure Professionals 2: Tiffany Doll &amp; Ava Austen</n>    <k>A high quality couple's film from Joybear. Every summer Mrs ERC bolts to the countryside to relax and unwind. A secluded hotel provides the perfect getaway</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-17 04:22:00" d="2019-07-17 04:34:00"><n>It's Complicated: Olivia Austin &amp; Stephen StCroix</n>    <k>Shauna (Gracie Glam) has been having casual sex with her handsome friend Will, biding her time until she can finally make a move on her long time crush Brandon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-17 04:34:00" d="2019-07-17 04:48:00"><n>Thr3e</n>    <k>The threesome has always been a recurring fantasy in the imaginary of erotica. Sharing the pleasure with two other people, discovering their bodies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-17 04:48:00" d="2019-07-17 05:08:00"><n>My Girlfriends Mother 3: Nica Noelle &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>Stay-at-home mom Inari isn't so sure she approves of her daughter getting involved in a serious relationship, but Alyssa convinces her mom to invite</k>  </p>
</a>
