<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="59" t="2019-08-15 23:00:47"><p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 05:10:00" d="2019-08-21 05:28:00"><n>Matchmaker: Satine Spark &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>Casey Collins is the Matchmaker. She can find anyone the perfect partner. The ultimate professional, Casey always puts her clients first. Until now. A Joybear film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 05:28:00" d="2019-08-21 05:42:00"><n>Tender Love And Care: Anita Bellini &amp; Renato</n>    <k>Attractive young people having sultry, passionate sex, and beautifully filmed to boot! A scene from a film by Yourope Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 05:42:00" d="2019-08-21 06:01:00"><n>Naked Desire</n>    <k>This girl likes to play with her own beautiful body, but let?s her sexy tattooed boyfriend enjoy her luscious body too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 06:01:00" d="2019-08-21 06:12:00"><n>Pansexuals</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 06:12:00" d="2019-08-21 06:34:00"><n>Coming Out: Minnie Manga &amp; Candy Sweet</n>    <k>In uncertainty about their sexual orientation these young women finally no longer conceal their sexual preference, and revealing their gender identity completely</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 06:34:00" d="2019-08-21 06:58:00"><n>Passion Noir: Chrissy &amp; Thomas</n>    <k>Four passionate couples in a Sinful XXX film by Roma Amor. Beautiful, Arty and very sexy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 06:58:00" d="2019-08-21 07:17:00"><n>4 Passionate Women: Next To You</n>    <k>A new scene by Award Winning director Lara Tinelli for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 07:17:00" d="2019-08-21 07:43:00"><n>Recipe for Romance: Samantha Ryan &amp; Richie</n>    <k>Love is cooking in Carolina's kitchen, and it's wonderfully delicious! Carolina is a passionate cook who is patiently waiting for Mr. Right. But what if Mr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 07:43:00" d="2019-08-21 08:00:00"><n>Strip Chess</n>    <k>Are you up for a chess game? Join Silvia Rubi and Gabe Romero in this intimate scene full of chemistry, where the game (and the increasing lack of clothes)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 08:00:00" d="2019-08-21 08:20:00"><n>Fit: Luke Hardy &amp; Jasmine Jae</n>    <k>You are running on the beach, bathed in the beautiful sunshine. You feel alive and energized ? what could be better? Get outside. Get active</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 08:20:00" d="2019-08-21 08:28:00"><n>Before The Guests Arrive</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 08:28:00" d="2019-08-21 08:52:00"><n>I Am All Yours: Eveline Neil &amp; Marcel Lee</n>    <k>A new scene by Dawn for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 08:52:00" d="2019-08-21 09:04:00"><n>Girlfriends: Casey Calvert &amp; Sasha Heart</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Small town girl Jamie (Casey Calvert) has made the difficult decision to tell her parents that she is in a same sex relationship. Unfortunately her family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 09:04:00" d="2019-08-21 09:42:00"><n>Trying New Things: Casey Calvert &amp; Anthony Rosano</n>    <k>Passions explode when a sexually frustrated Alison asks her fiancé to take her virginity two weeks before their wedding day. Sara discovers that adult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 09:42:00" d="2019-08-21 10:04:00"><n>Hugman</n>    <k>My girlfriend and I are not serious people, we like to have fun in our lives and we are always playing tricks and games to spice up our life. A Verso Cinema film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 10:04:00" d="2019-08-21 10:26:00"><n>Sex With Friends: Daydreams</n>    <k>When old college friends meet again they take the time to rekindle and explore each other?s bodies and sexual boundries. A reunion you don?t want to miss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 10:26:00" d="2019-08-21 10:33:00"><n>Slo Blo Mo Job</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 10:33:00" d="2019-08-21 11:00:00"><n>Come Closer: My Sunny Side</n>    <k>What are you going to do when all of a suddon both of you are at home and have nothing to do? Exactly, enjoy each other and make your time together worthwhile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 11:00:00" d="2019-08-21 11:31:00"><n>The Artist: Max Deeds &amp; Eveline Dellai</n>    <k>Another beautiful production by Studio Sinful, containing lots of close-ups, artistic lighting and delicious performers. In The Artist a man is sensually</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 11:31:00" d="2019-08-21 11:43:00"><n>Try My Boyfriend</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 11:43:00" d="2019-08-21 11:55:00"><n>Immortal Love: Gracie Glam &amp; Kris Slater</n>    <k>Madelyn is disappointed in love, when Donovan enters her life. But there is something strange about this exceptionally handsome, mysterious man</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 11:55:00" d="2019-08-21 12:25:00"><n>My Hotwife's Lover: The Seduction Game</n>    <k>Kristin's (Karla Kush) forbidden attraction to her husband's best friend reaches a breaking point when he arranges a private get-together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 12:25:00" d="2019-08-21 12:54:00"><n>Soft And Sweet 2: Lady Dee &amp; Max D</n><t>L</t>    <k>Did you ever notice the softness of your lovers skin, the sweet taste when you move your tongue over her well formed sensual body? These young couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 12:54:00" d="2019-08-21 13:18:00"><n>Weekend: Katy Rose, Lexi Dona &amp; Dominica Phoenix</n>    <k>Shot in Portugal, episode 4 of The Weekend, &quot;Time for Love,&quot; begins with a new day. As Lutro and Dominika prepare breakfast, Lexie and Jason are enjoying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 13:18:00" d="2019-08-21 13:44:00"><n>The Escort 2: Presley Hart &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>When a beautiful young woman enters the escorting profession, she's put off by her first client. But under the tutelage of a smart and capable madam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 13:44:00" d="2019-08-21 14:06:00"><n>Afternoon Delight: Alie Haze &amp; Marco Rivera</n>    <k>Attractive people that have sex on gorgeous locations. A scene from an Intimate Encounters film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 14:06:00" d="2019-08-21 14:34:00"><n>Illicit Affairs: Susan Ayn &amp; Vanessa Decker</n><t>O</t>    <k>A relationship often starts with lots of passion and fun. But once the boredom sets in a prohibited affair can just rise up! It's hard to resist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 14:34:00" d="2019-08-21 15:09:00"><n>Exploring Couples 2: Sofi Goldfinger &amp; Vincent Vega</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A scene from Exploring Couples 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 15:09:00" d="2019-08-21 15:32:00"><n>Firestarter</n>    <k>Firestarter opens with a frenzied, frenetic explosion of visual and aural energy. Once the couple is behind closed doors the scene shifts from a rolling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 15:32:00" d="2019-08-21 15:51:00"><n>Recipe for Romance: Gracie Glam &amp; Levi Cash</n>    <k>Love is cooking in Carolina's kitchen, and it's wonderfully delicious! Carolina is a passionate cook who is patiently waiting for Mr. Right. But what if Mr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 15:51:00" d="2019-08-21 16:10:00"><n>A Young Mothers Request: Edita &amp; Denis Reed</n>    <k>Exciting, beautiful and erotic. Pure passion and intimate camera work. Enjoy sharing the way this young mother?s desires are fulfilled in a scene by daring Pure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 16:10:00" d="2019-08-21 16:30:00"><n>Tender Love And Care: Iwia &amp; Johny</n>    <k>Attractive young people having sultry, passionate sex, and beautifully filmed to boot! A scene from a film by Yourope Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 16:30:00" d="2019-08-21 17:02:00"><n>Girl Next Door Likes It Dirty: Kennedy Leigh &amp; Chad White</n>    <k>All of these next door girls are young, free, and secretly wild who love it dirty! They all get their pussies passionately pulverized over the course</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 17:02:00" d="2019-08-21 17:32:00"><n>Restraint: Dahlia Sky &amp; Chad White</n>    <k>Hoping to invigorate their predictable sex life, married couple, Logan and Ashlyn, dabble in beginner BDSM sex with the help of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 17:32:00" d="2019-08-21 17:55:00"><n>In the limelight 2: Raduschka &amp; Marco</n><t>L</t>    <k>Daring! Pure in the limelight shows you a spectacular selection of nine of our best scenes. The most beautiful girls surpass your wildest dreams to fulfill</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 17:55:00" d="2019-08-21 18:05:00"><n>Magic Magnus</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 18:05:00" d="2019-08-21 18:31:00"><n>Obedience</n>    <k>On a beautiful day a Spanish beauty gets a surprise phone call from a stranger. A man tells her exactly what to do to pleasure herself sexually</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 18:31:00" d="2019-08-21 19:00:00"><n>Sexy And She Knows It: Lutro, Dorian Del Isla &amp; Anna Polina</n>    <k>Sinful trinity's enjoying a triad of erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 19:00:00" d="2019-08-21 19:20:00"><n>Sun stroke: Michelle And Jade</n>    <k>When international DJ Cosmo needs a secluded escape, his boss? sun-kissed Spanish villa is the perfect location. Determined to tackle his writer?s block</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 19:20:00" d="2019-08-21 19:44:00"><n>Come Closer: Summer Love</n>    <k>What are you going to do when all of a suddon both of you are at home and have nothing to do? Exactly, enjoy each other and make your time together worthwhile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 19:44:00" d="2019-08-21 20:01:00"><n>Cabaret Desire: Lady Diamond and Mario Mentrup</n>    <k>Welcome to nightclub Cabaret Desire ? indulge yourself with poets and their erotic tales filled with passion and temptation. A film by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 20:01:00" d="2019-08-21 20:20:00"><n>4 Passionate Women: First Time</n>    <k>A new scene by Award Winning director Lara Tinelli for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 20:20:00" d="2019-08-21 20:51:00"><n>So Wet Beside Her: Vinna Reed &amp; Jennifer Jane</n>    <k>These girls love, lust, lick, becoming almost one in this sensual piece of erotica. Sinful Studio making art again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 20:51:00" d="2019-08-21 21:11:00"><n>Inside: Sicilia &amp; Juan Lucho</n>    <k>Welcome to The Retreat: where curious minds come to play. Plug in and turn on to explore a virtual reality experience where you can be anyone, go anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 21:11:00" d="2019-08-21 21:33:00"><n>The Party</n>    <k>A breasty Spanish beauty can’t get any sleep because of the loud party next door. But when she sees her attractive neighbor her angry feelings fade away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 21:33:00" d="2019-08-21 21:44:00"><n>Sit Down, Shut Up and Watch</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 21:44:00" d="2019-08-21 22:05:00"><n>Sensuous Seduction: The Imaginary Boyfriend</n>    <k>A new scene by Award Winning director Lara Tinelli for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 22:05:00" d="2019-08-21 22:19:00"><n>A love Story: Xander Corvus &amp; Alexa Nicole</n>    <k>Novel author Michael suffers from a writer?s block. His publisher sends him Danielle to get him back on track, but will they be a good match?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 22:19:00" d="2019-08-21 22:44:00"><n>Lena: Paige Turnah &amp; Kane Turner</n>    <k>Lena is in her 20s. A graduate. Cosmopolitan. The whole world at her fingertips. But the pressure of finding the perfect partner, the perfect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 22:44:00" d="2019-08-21 23:13:00"><n>Soft And Sweet 2: Vinna Reed &amp; Nick Ross</n><t>L</t>    <k>Did you ever notice the softness of your lovers skin, the sweet taste when you move your tongue over her well formed sensual body? These young couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-21 23:13:00" d="2019-08-22 02:07:00"><n>Guide To Kinky Sex For Couples</n>    <k>Kink expert Tristan Taormino gives how-to's to discuss, explore and finally act out your wildest fantasies, with your partner! 4 Hot couples demonstrate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-22 02:07:00" d="2019-08-22 02:26:00"><n>BFF's: Nicole Aniston &amp; Xander Corvus</n>    <k>John and Julia are best friends. John wants more but he once told Julia that he fancies men? will she be able to forgive him his lies?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-22 02:26:00" d="2019-08-22 02:38:00"><n>Take me drunk</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-22 02:38:00" d="2019-08-22 03:03:00"><n>Inside: Frida Sante &amp; Alberta Blanco</n>    <k>Welcome to The Retreat: where curious minds come to play. Plug in and turn on to explore a virtual reality experience where you can be anyone, go anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-22 03:03:00" d="2019-08-22 03:36:00"><n>Hot Water: Tiffany Tatum &amp; Lutro</n>    <k>Licking, sucking, kissing, thrusting, touching, stroking, becoming one with each other in hot water. A sexual and visual delight by Studio Sinfull</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-22 03:36:00" d="2019-08-22 04:02:00"><n>Facade: Edyn Blair &amp; James Deen</n>    <k>Amber and her friend Lindsay are average college students?who happen to moonlight as sexy webcam models. This complicates things when they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-22 04:02:00" d="2019-08-22 04:21:00"><n>Only women can: Kari &amp; Sunshine</n>    <k>Porna award-nominated director Kendo portrays the world of latex with a beautiful, filmic dark side and incredibly attractive women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-22 04:21:00" d="2019-08-22 04:43:00"><n>Seven Days</n>    <k>This couple can have dramatic fights, but when they make up, it?s more than just kissing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-08-22 04:43:00" d="2019-08-22 05:10:00"><n>Pleasure Professionals: Samantha Bentley &amp; Tiffany Doll</n>    <k>Do you harbour special sexual desires? Hire a professional and let them make your naughtiest dreams come true. Scene from a film by Joybear</k>  </p>
</a>
