<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="60" t="2020-04-09 04:38:23"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 05:01:00" d="2020-04-16 05:48:00"><n>Bound For Sex: Dahila Sky &amp; Ramon Nomar</n>    <k>For over 2 hrs. 40 mins., watch Jillian Janson, Sara Luvv, Samantha Hayes and Dahlia Sky get their share of blindfolds, silk ropes and hard cocks! These sex freaks can't wait to be tied up tight and fucked just right. We hope you?re ready, because tonight, we're all bound for sex!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 05:48:00" d="2020-04-16 06:11:00"><n>Girls Fight Club</n><t>S</t>    <k>What's the first rule of girls fight club? Only women allowed. An homage to David Fincher’s classic dystopian film, this time with lesbians</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 06:11:00" d="2020-04-16 06:30:00"><n>Housemates 2: Luke Hotrod &amp; Samantha Bentley</n>    <k>New house. New rules. Artist James moves to the UK in search of his ex-girlfriend (Dalush) and finds himself sharing a house with four incredibly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 06:30:00" d="2020-04-16 07:05:00"><n>A Mothers Love 2: Janet Mason &amp; Bruce Venture</n>    <k>There?s nothing better than a mother?s love. And mothers are always willing to give their love. This Janet Mason scene is breathtaking sexy. A Pure Passion film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 07:05:00" d="2020-04-16 07:28:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies 2: Miranda &amp; Joe T</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A female friendly porn scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 07:28:00" d="2020-04-16 07:57:00"><n>My Love For you: Vinna Reed &amp; Lutro</n>    <k>A sex film by Roma Woodcock for Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 07:57:00" d="2020-04-16 08:27:00"><n>Sex Sinners and Saints: Jan Seidl &amp; Michaela Mangova</n>    <k>Not only is the church the perfect place to confess your sins, it's also the perfect location to have sensational sex. These couples sin in church, moaning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 08:27:00" d="2020-04-16 08:49:00"><n>Inside: Kali Sudhra &amp; Miguel Zayas</n>    <k>Welcome to The Retreat: where curious minds come to play. Plug in and turn on to explore a virtual reality experience where you can be anyone, go anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 08:49:00" d="2020-04-16 09:13:00"><n>Love Lust Longing: Jessica Drake &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Love Lust &amp; Longing takes place in a seemingly innocent Bed &amp; Breakfast. Rachel a prostitute who has set up shop in the master bedroom falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 09:13:00" d="2020-04-16 09:31:00"><n>K</n>    <k>Inspiration can reach us when we are less expecting it. The simple vision of a white sheet of paper stresses me a bit as I am a writer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 09:31:00" d="2020-04-16 09:53:00"><n>My Daughters Boyfriend 10: Cody Sky &amp; Keisha Grey</n>    <k>A free spirited skateboarder wants to get more serious with her boyfriend, but he?s resisting. For one, he?s just met an uber-hot, elegant woman at the office</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 09:53:00" d="2020-04-16 10:18:00"><n>I Am All Yours: Eveline Neil &amp; Marcel Lee</n>    <k>A romantic film by Dawn for Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 10:18:00" d="2020-04-16 10:35:00"><n>Girls Sex Tricks: Carol Ferrer &amp; Pablo Ferrari</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us on her first film as director for Thagson with a vibrant female friendly porn story which will take place in the streets of Barcelona</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 10:35:00" d="2020-04-16 10:48:00"><n>Some never awaken</n><t>S</t>    <k>Experience a sexual awakening through dance, movement, and passionate sex. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 10:48:00" d="2020-04-16 11:11:00"><n>Pure Sexual Attraction: Skylar Green &amp; Johnny Castle</n>    <k>Embark on an exciting journey of pure sexual attraction as five breathtaking girls are captured in five scenes that set the standard for high definition erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 11:11:00" d="2020-04-16 11:37:00"><n>Making Ends Meet: Gia Paige &amp; Riley Nixon</n>    <k>A suburbian family is in destress over money, but sex seems to really heal the wounds. Scorching hot sex and sharp comedy blend perfectly in this lesbian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 11:37:00" d="2020-04-16 12:06:00"><n>A Touch of Nature: Holly &amp; Jesse Jazz</n>    <k>You can taste the love in the air. The heat of the sun guides hands and fingers to touch your deepest soul. Ecstasy, passion and sexual arousal, A Touch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 12:06:00" d="2020-04-16 12:23:00"><n>The Guesthouse: Julia De Lucia &amp; Miguel Zayas</n>    <k>Porn for women by Joybear. Nestled in the Spanish countryside, there?s a Guesthouse where visitors enjoy more than just the sunshine on their bodies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 12:23:00" d="2020-04-16 12:33:00"><n>Cybersex</n><t>S</t>    <k>Can cybersex be more stimulating than the real thing? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual confessions of her viewers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 12:33:00" d="2020-04-16 12:55:00"><n>Hollywood Ending: Karlee Grey &amp; Derrick Pierce</n>    <k>Childhood lovers Rebecca and Tommy are finally getting the acting success they always wanted. But their love is put to the test when fame, fortune</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 12:55:00" d="2020-04-16 13:25:00"><n>Come Closer: Friday Night</n>    <k>A real life straight couple with real life sex. A romantic porn video by Dusk TV's own porn for women label</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 13:25:00" d="2020-04-16 13:37:00"><n>Late night out</n>    <k>From XConfessions 3: When that little bit too much makes you uncontrollably horny! In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 13:37:00" d="2020-04-16 14:10:00"><n>Shades Of Kink 2: Logan Pierce &amp; Penny Pax</n>    <k>A young man is attracted to a seemingly innocent, sweet young woman, but when he discovers that she moonlights as an infamous dominatrix by night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 14:10:00" d="2020-04-16 14:35:00"><n>Secret Sex Society: Cintia Shapiro &amp; Bel Gris</n>    <k>When colourful people meet and share their colourful fantasies. Starring the hot blooded Spanish beauty Julia Roca</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 14:35:00" d="2020-04-16 15:02:00"><n>I Love You: Blanche Bradburry &amp; Nick Ross</n>    <k>These beautiful desireable men and women are highly confident and have all the experience to bring you in a state of trance. A erotic porn film by Desire media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 15:02:00" d="2020-04-16 15:25:00"><n>Her Desire: The Couch</n>    <k>A great scene by AlexanFilm for Dusk's Porn for women label: Ooh la la. Explicit erotic films for women and couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 15:25:00" d="2020-04-16 15:45:00"><n>The Ski Instructor</n><t>S</t>    <k>Baby, it's cold outside. Who doesn't want to sleep with their ski instructor? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 15:45:00" d="2020-04-16 16:06:00"><n>Anticipation: Sensi &amp; Lea Guerlin</n>    <k>Anticipation is the latest cinematic adult movie directed by DiSanto for Daring Sex. Romantic porn for women with a focus on female pleasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 16:06:00" d="2020-04-16 16:36:00"><n>Hot Water: Francys Belle &amp; Steve Q</n>    <k>Licking, sucking, kissing, thrusting, touching, stroking, becoming one with each other in hot water. A sexual and visual delight by Studio Sinfull</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 16:36:00" d="2020-04-16 17:11:00"><n>Exploring Couples 2: Sofi Goldfinger &amp; Vincent Vega</n>    <k>These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A beautiful porn for women scene from Exploring Couples 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 17:11:00" d="2020-04-16 17:34:00"><n>Tales from the Heart: Sara Luvv &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>Love is in the air. specially on your Anniversary. A trip down memory lane is just the spark Michelle and Andy need to reignite the lustful feelings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 17:34:00" d="2020-04-16 17:59:00"><n>Very Beautiful Lips</n><t>L</t>    <k>Starting with a shower, performers Apolonia Lapiedra and Alberto Blanco waste no time in exploring their lust for one another. As they move</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 17:59:00" d="2020-04-16 18:17:00"><n>Corporate Bonding: Amber Nevada &amp; Amarna Miller</n>    <k>Good teamwork can lead to surprising situations. Rookie lawyer Leyla organises a team-building weekend by the beach for her and her firm of London lawyers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 18:17:00" d="2020-04-16 18:31:00"><n>Fräulein O</n><t>S</t>    <k>The unbearable August Spanish heat. who wouldn't be seduced by the local boy with a bucket full of ice! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 18:31:00" d="2020-04-16 18:56:00"><n>Not to Innocent: Naomi Nevena &amp; Thomas Reed</n>    <k>A romantic sex film by Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous sex films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 18:56:00" d="2020-04-16 19:25:00"><n>Friends And Lovers: Chanel Preston &amp; Bill Bailey</n>    <k>Caroline and Matt (Aaliyah Love and Tommy Pistol) have been best friends since college. Through break-ups they've been there for each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 19:25:00" d="2020-04-16 19:52:00"><n>Trying New Things: Kasey Warner &amp; Richie Calhoun</n>    <k>Passions explode when a sexually frustrated Alison asks her fiancé to take her virginity two weeks before their wedding day. Sara discovers that adult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 19:52:00" d="2020-04-16 20:10:00"><n>Among The Bushes</n>    <k>He's always sitting in this park, surrounded by the trees, reading a book, cute and charismatic. He's big, tall and handsome. I'll take him between</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 20:10:00" d="2020-04-16 20:32:00"><n>Housemates 2: Tyler Nixon &amp; Samatha Bentley</n>    <k>Artist James moves to the UK in search of his ex-girlfriend (Dalush) and finds himself sharing a house with four incredibly attractive women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 20:32:00" d="2020-04-16 20:46:00"><n>Latex Sessions</n><t>S</t>    <k>Parker Marx and Amarna Miller feature in this steamy homage to latex and the psychology of fetishism. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 20:46:00" d="2020-04-16 21:09:00"><n>Sweet Memories: Lovers</n>    <k>A hot erotic video by Lara Tinelli for female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples who like big dick. Romantic sex films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 21:09:00" d="2020-04-16 21:40:00"><n>Nymphomaniac Diaries: Nightmares</n>    <k>The blond Katerina loves sex so much that her dreams are filled with kinky stuff, but her sexual fantasies with men and women become even better</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 21:40:00" d="2020-04-16 22:07:00"><n>Multiorgasmic Brunch</n><t>S</t>    <k>An explosive exploration of the possibilities for female pleasure; where the orgasms just never end. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 22:07:00" d="2020-04-16 22:31:00"><n>He Loves To Watch: Brandi Love &amp; Lucas Frost</n>    <k>This couple has found a unique way to keep the spark in their marriage. Passionate sex and powerful orgasms for everybody! Cuckold porn for women by Wicked Pictures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 22:31:00" d="2020-04-16 22:54:00"><n>Connections: Kara Dasha &amp; Devon</n>    <k>Connections, celebrates all that?s great about sex: passion, laughter, teasing, giving, receiving, &amp; experiencing real pleasure. For this real life couple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 22:54:00" d="2020-04-16 23:19:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies 2: Renata Fox &amp; Vincent Vega</n>    <k>These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. An erotic sex scene from Favorite Fantasies 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 23:19:00" d="2020-04-16 23:51:00"><n>The Escort 2: Lilly Love, Dana DeArmond &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>When a beautiful young woman enters the escorting profession, she's put off by her first client. But under the tutelage of a smart and capable madam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-16 23:51:00" d="2020-04-17 00:17:00"><n>Oral Reflections</n><t>L</t>    <k>Always wanted to know about anal sex, but never tried? This romantic porn film shows how nice anal massage can be</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 00:17:00" d="2020-04-17 00:40:00"><n>Taste: Ava Dalush &amp; Jess West</n>    <k>Audrey is a talented and beautiful chef with a gift. She has the power to make her unsuspecting diners feel overwhelmingly amorous. She is one mouthful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 00:40:00" d="2020-04-17 01:20:00"><n>Nymphomaniac Diaries: Daydreaming</n>    <k>The blond Katerina loves sex so much that her dreams are filled with kinky stuff, but her sexual fantasies with men and women become even better</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 01:20:00" d="2020-04-17 01:38:00"><n>When it Comes to you: Karlie Montana &amp; Steven St. Croix</n>    <k>When It Comes To You is a captivating and scintillating story of a woman torn between two men who both profess great love. Directed by Stormy Daniels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 01:38:00" d="2020-04-17 02:07:00"><n>Sweet Petite Girls: Cheryl S &amp; Kristof Cale</n>    <k>These young beauties are starting to discover their sexuality, exploring their bodies and seek new limits. Director Roman Sluka captured these teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 02:07:00" d="2020-04-17 02:31:00"><n>Sweet Memories: Touch me</n>    <k>A sex scene by Lara Tinelli for female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. An erotic video for women who are into guys with a big dick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 02:31:00" d="2020-04-17 02:54:00"><n>Housemates 3: Decoupled</n>    <k>Synopsis not available</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 02:54:00" d="2020-04-17 03:19:00"><n>My Wife's First Girlfriend: Karlie Montana &amp; Abigail Mac</n>    <k>Jenna?s secret desires become unleashed when her husband catches her masturbating to lesbian porn. When Jimmy notices a growing attraction between</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 03:19:00" d="2020-04-17 03:31:00"><n>Ibiza Splash Crush</n><t>S</t>    <k>One the most forbidden and oldest mythical taboos: a merman. Seduced by a gorgeous lifeguard in the blistering Ibiza sun. From the XConfessions series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 03:31:00" d="2020-04-17 03:53:00"><n>Sex With Friends: Daydreams</n>    <k>When old college friends meet again they take the time to rekindle and explore each other?s bodies and sexual boundries. A reunion you don?t want to miss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 03:53:00" d="2020-04-17 04:11:00"><n>Fill Me Up With Your Orgasm: Evilyn Fierce &amp; Johnny Castle</n>    <k>Such a waste to just get a little bit? Whether it be a refill on your drink, your gas tank, or your favorite piece of pussy, you gotta fill it to the brim! It's going to be a sticky situation when they get a fill of love butter that they crave! A Pure Passion film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 04:11:00" d="2020-04-17 04:40:00"><n>I Love You: Arian Joy &amp; Nick Vargas</n>    <k>These beautiful desireable men and women are highly confident and have all the experience to bring you in a state of trance. A porn for women film by Desire media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 04:40:00" d="2020-04-17 05:11:00"><n>Not to Innocent: Ally &amp; Max D</n>    <k>A sensuous sex video depicting real excitement and passion. A pleasure to all the senses representing realistic sex full of intimacy, laughter, chemistry</k>  </p>
</a>
