<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="49" t="2020-04-15 04:39:36"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 05:27:00" d="2020-04-22 05:45:00"><n>Come With Me</n>    <k>Come with me, or cum with me? An super sexy female friendly porn film by Verso Cinema with breathtaking orgasms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 05:45:00" d="2020-04-22 06:04:00"><n>Quartet: The Teacher</n>    <k>Penelope boards a plane from London to Budapest, eager to perform with her three best friends from music academy. Reunited, the foursome soon remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 06:04:00" d="2020-04-22 06:14:00"><n>Hysterical Piano Concert</n><t>S</t>    <k>A pianist's ultimate sexual fantasy is played out in an intimate concert that hits an exquisite note! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 06:14:00" d="2020-04-22 06:33:00"><n>4 Passionate Women: First Time</n>    <k>Dusk-tv presents: explicit porn for women and couples by Lara Tinelli. A pleasure to all the senses representing real-life sex full of intimacy, laughter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 06:33:00" d="2020-04-22 06:59:00"><n>Friends And Lovers: Angela White &amp; Donny Rock</n>    <k>Caroline and Matt have been best friends since college. Through break-ups they've been there for each other. But they have yet to find true love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 06:59:00" d="2020-04-22 07:32:00"><n>The Submission Of Emma Marx: Logan Pierce, Penny Pax &amp; Richie Calhoun</n>    <k>When a new contract is drafted up defining the parameters of their BDSM relationship, Emma realizes that Mr. Frederick is anything but predictable</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 07:32:00" d="2020-04-22 07:55:00"><n>Blind</n>    <k>Open your eyes wide for this one! Gorgeous Spanish beauty Apolonia Lapiedra and Pablo Ferrari get steamy in this short film with another classic scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 07:55:00" d="2020-04-22 08:13:00"><n>Sun stroke: Stephanie</n>    <k>When international DJ Cosmo needs a secluded escape, his boss? sun-kissed Spanish villa is the perfect location. The unannounced arrival of Chloe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 08:13:00" d="2020-04-22 08:23:00"><n>Garden of Eden</n>    <k>From XConfessions 3: Ever thought about a fresh fuck in the middle of nature, covered in the fruit of mother natures creation? In XConfessions, people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 08:23:00" d="2020-04-22 08:42:00"><n>4 Passionate Women: Next To You</n>    <k>A romantic porn scene by Lara Tinelli for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 08:42:00" d="2020-04-22 09:14:00"><n>Jungleicious: Luna Corazon &amp; Angelo Gotshack</n>    <k>The perfect spot, the perfect lady: Luna Corazon dances in the Jungle, waiting for Angelo to arrive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 09:14:00" d="2020-04-22 09:24:00"><n>Cybersex</n><t>S</t>    <k>Can cybersex be more stimulating than the real thing? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual confessions of her viewers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 09:24:00" d="2020-04-22 09:45:00"><n>Just Friends: Anna Morna &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>When a job assignment takes Courtney out of town for a few months she returns to find that James her childhood best friend is engaged. Naturally she's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 09:45:00" d="2020-04-22 10:18:00"><n>Rob And Marina</n>    <k>For Dusk Academy, Michelle Flynn produced a few scenes with tips, tricks and ideas from the Dusk panel. This scene features Rob and Marina, a real life couple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 10:18:00" d="2020-04-22 10:48:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies: Dolce Vita &amp; Vega</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. A romantic porn video from Favorite Fantasies by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 10:48:00" d="2020-04-22 11:12:00"><n>What Happens When</n>    <k>In this 6th Episode the party is finally beginning to wind down and Kiara departs the celebration in a huff. Not long after her departure she realizes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 11:12:00" d="2020-04-22 11:39:00"><n>Friends And Lovers: AJ Applegate, Blair Williams &amp; Small Hands</n>    <k>Caroline and Matt have been best friends since college. Through break-ups they've been there for each other. But they have yet to find true love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 11:39:00" d="2020-04-22 12:03:00"><n>Tenderness: Keira &amp; Chriss Tom</n>    <k>A beautiful scene by Dusk TV's own female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real romantic sex and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 12:03:00" d="2020-04-22 12:21:00"><n>Quartet: Inspiration</n>    <k>Penelope boards a plane from London to Budapest, eager to perform with her three best friends from music academy. Reunited, the foursome soon remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 12:21:00" d="2020-04-22 12:32:00"><n>Pansexuals</n><t>S</t>    <k>A documentary about pansexuality. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual confessions of her viewers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 12:32:00" d="2020-04-22 12:51:00"><n u="The Submission of Emma Marx: Riley Reid &amp; Van Wylde">The Submission of Emma Marx: Riley Reid &amp; Van Wylde (1)</n>    <k>By all accounts, Emma Marx is a beautiful, confident, well-adjusted woman. Unfortunately when it comes to love and romance, she has found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 12:51:00" d="2020-04-22 13:13:00"><n>Elevator Dreams</n>    <k>When a guy meets an attractive girl in an elevator, she ignores him. But in his dreams all she want to do is having kinky, rough sex. A female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 13:13:00" d="2020-04-22 13:34:00"><n>Exposure: Add Contact</n>    <k>In a world where couples would rather play with their phones than each other, one woman uses her technology skills for good, nudging distracted lovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 13:34:00" d="2020-04-22 13:48:00"><n>Fräulein O</n><t>S</t>    <k>The unbearable August Spanish heat. who wouldn't be seduced by the local boy with a bucket full of ice! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 13:48:00" d="2020-04-22 14:06:00"><n>Strip Chess</n>    <k>Are you up for a chess game? Join Silvia Rubi and Gabe Romero in this intimate scene full of chemistry, where the game (and the increasing lack of clothes)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 14:06:00" d="2020-04-22 14:47:00"><n>Light my Fire: Max Deeds &amp; Angel Wicky</n>    <k>This beautiful couple relishes each others body with sensual hand and mouth massages by candlelight. Another visual and erotic jewel by Studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 14:47:00" d="2020-04-22 15:11:00"><n>Tenderness: Alexis Crystal &amp; George Lee</n>    <k>A romantic sex scene by Dusk TV's own female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Romantic porn films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 15:11:00" d="2020-04-22 15:30:00"><n>The Invitation: Sienna Day, Alexei Jackson, Max Deeds &amp; Emma Leigh</n>    <k>Jane and Tom decide to pack the kids off and book a romantic weekend away. When their car unexpectedly breaks down late at night they find themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 15:30:00" d="2020-04-22 15:43:00"><n>The Ultimate Kink</n><t>S</t>    <k>An adventure with a female couple who have tried it all when it comes to sex - except for a man. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, kinky female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 15:43:00" d="2020-04-22 16:10:00"><n>In The Limelight 1: Giovanni Francesco &amp; Shazia Sahari</n><t>L</t>    <k>Daring! Pure?s film ?In the Limelight? shows a spectacular selection of nine of their best scenes. The most beautiful couples surpass your wildest dreams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 16:10:00" d="2020-04-22 16:51:00"><n>The Neighbours 2: India Summer &amp; Xander Corvus</n>    <k>Jessica and Dick live together in a sweet love filled house until the house next door becomes invaded by the wild young couple Rachel and frank</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 16:51:00" d="2020-04-22 17:13:00"><n>Facade: Layla Price &amp; Damon Dice</n>    <k>Amber and her friend Lindsay are average college students?who happen to moonlight as sexy webcam models. This complicates things when they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 17:13:00" d="2020-04-22 17:48:00"><n>I Am All Yours: Daphne Klyde &amp; Nick Ross</n>    <k>A film by Dawn for Dusk's Porn for women label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting realistic excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 17:48:00" d="2020-04-22 18:06:00"><n>Delilahs Top Tips: Jess West &amp; Danielle Ashlea Maye</n><t>L</t>    <k>Delilah is the nation's naughtiest agony aunt dedicated to solving the nation's more. ntimate dilemmas. She shows a pretty young teacher how to get closer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 18:06:00" d="2020-04-22 18:20:00"><n>La Reine Des Culottes</n><t>S</t>    <k>A woman's lingerie can say a lot about her - and about her neighbour. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 18:20:00" d="2020-04-22 18:42:00"><n>Just You &amp; Me: Silvie DeLuxe &amp; Miela</n>    <k>Sensual girl on girl sex is highly erotic to watch, and even more so for the stunning girls here who want to please their lover. A female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 18:42:00" d="2020-04-22 19:24:00"><n>Guide to Bondage For Couples: India Summer &amp; Danny Wylde</n>    <k>If Fifty Shades of Grey intrigued and inspired you, then get ready for Tristan Taormino's Guide to Bondage for Couples, an educational film for couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 19:24:00" d="2020-04-22 19:52:00"><n>Come Closer: Sunday Morning</n>    <k>Having a lazy sunday? This couple is enjoying each other and making their time together worthwhile. A real life couple with real life sex. A romantic sex film by Dusk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 19:52:00" d="2020-04-22 20:06:00"><n>El que no ama no conoce a Dios</n><t>S</t>    <k>Committing the ultimate sin has never been so sweet! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual confessions of her viewers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 20:06:00" d="2020-04-22 20:34:00"><n>Lovers Tryst: Rob Dean &amp; Lucia Love</n>    <k>Real mature couples have truly learned their way around each other's sensitive and aroused bodies. All that is needed to stimulate your senses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 20:34:00" d="2020-04-22 20:56:00"><n>Hugman</n>    <k>My girlfriend and I are not serious people, we like to have fun in our lives and we are always playing tricks and games to spice up our life. Playful porn by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 20:56:00" d="2020-04-22 21:14:00"><n>A Love Story</n>    <k>We meet Nataly and Franck as they get dressed to go out. In this case &quot;out&quot; means &quot;up&quot; and the love-struck couple enjoy the expansive views and a glass</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 21:14:00" d="2020-04-22 21:53:00"><n>Restraint: Persley Hart &amp; Ryan Mclane</n>    <k>Hoping to invigorate their predictable sex life, married couple, Logan and Ashlyn, dabble in beginner BDSM sex with the help of</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 21:53:00" d="2020-04-22 22:20:00"><n>Guide to Bondage For Couples: Samantha Ryan &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>If Fifty Shades of Grey intrigued and inspired you, then get ready for Tristan Taormino's Guide to Bondage for Couples, an educational film for couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 22:20:00" d="2020-04-22 22:52:00"><n>A Girls' Getaway: Lola Marie &amp; Kai Taylor</n>    <k>Girls weekend out! The girls go away together each year for a relaxing weekend to the English countryside. But they get some company and they didn't expect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-22 22:52:00" d="2020-04-23 00:52:00"><n>Summer Lovers</n>    <k>When it's summer the temperature rises, you wear less clothes and get aroused much easier. Is there anything hotter than having outdoor sex surrounded by nature? A scene from an Intimate Encounters film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 00:52:00" d="2020-04-23 04:12:00"><n u="Xconfessions">Xconfessions (9)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 04:12:00" d="2020-04-23 04:35:00"><n>Making Ends Meet: Mercedes Carrera &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>A suburbian family is in destress over money, but sex seems to really heal the wounds. Scorching hot sex and sharp comedy blend perfectly in a female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-23 04:35:00" d="2020-04-23 05:02:00"><n>Real And Molly</n>    <k>A new scene for Dusk Academy from Michelle Flynn. A different couple, a different style, a different setting. But 100% porna</k>  </p>
</a>
