<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="62" t="2020-05-12 04:41:47"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 05:08:00" d="2020-05-19 05:45:00"><n>Perfect And Pure: Mary Dee &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Romantic and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A romantic porn scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 05:45:00" d="2020-05-19 06:09:00"><n>Taste: Ava Dalush &amp; Jess West</n>    <k>Audrey is a talented and beautiful chef with a gift. She has the power to make her unsuspecting diners feel overwhelmingly amorous. She is one mouthful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 06:09:00" d="2020-05-19 06:36:00"><n>Spicing up the Marriage: Jillian Janson &amp; Chad White</n>    <k>When work and responsibility begin to pull a young couple apart, they find out working out becomes the ultimate foreplay. Romantic porn for couples by New Sensations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 06:36:00" d="2020-05-19 06:54:00"><n>K</n>    <k>Inspiration can reach us when we are less expecting it. The simple vision of a white sheet of paper stresses me a bit as I am a writer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 06:54:00" d="2020-05-19 07:26:00"><n>Momentum 4: Go for a walk</n>    <k>The fourth final and most epic adult film. The Volume 4 stage is set in the Australian desert - an aesthetic overthrow from the previous films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 07:26:00" d="2020-05-19 07:48:00"><n>Upon Further Reflection: Brittney Amber &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>Fiction writer, James Wharton (Ryan Mclane), is suffering from writers block and a drinking problem. His ex-wife is making his life a living</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 07:48:00" d="2020-05-19 08:01:00"><n>Power Pussy</n><t>S</t>    <k>Two Power Pussies take on and dominate the burly Dean Van Damme, all in From Dawn Til Dawn style. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 08:01:00" d="2020-05-19 08:23:00"><n>Pleasure Fix: Kali Sudhra, Bishop Black &amp; Nat Portnoy</n>    <k>Sex can be hard to talk about. Pleasure Fix is an app designed to help couples explore their sexuality by trying new things. Sexy porn for women by Joybear pictures</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 08:23:00" d="2020-05-19 08:45:00"><n>Room 208: Penelope Cum &amp; Salva Da Silva</n>    <k>A female friendly sex video by Lara Tinelli for Dusk TV. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 08:45:00" d="2020-05-19 09:17:00"><n>Once In A Blue Moon: Lovita Fate &amp; Ricky</n>    <k>In the blue light of the moon various couples love all parts of each other?s bodies on quiet spots in alleys, on rooftops and in fields. A Sinful production</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 09:17:00" d="2020-05-19 10:00:00"><n>Dani Loves Girls: Sovereign Syre &amp; Dani Daniels</n><t>L</t>    <k>Sweetheart Video presents the beautiful Dani Daniels in her own movie. Dani showcases her sensuality and voracious appetite in four scenes;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 10:00:00" d="2020-05-19 10:28:00"><n>Hair Down There: Tracey Sweet &amp; Anthony Rosano</n><t>L</t>    <k>She's got hair down there, and yes, we love that natural look! Let Mia Malkova, Nadine Sage, Tracey Sweet, and Anastasia Morna show you how their naturally</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 10:28:00" d="2020-05-19 10:58:00"><n>Anticipation: Kai Taylor &amp; Amirah Adara</n>    <k>Anticipation is the latest cinematic adult movie directed by DiSanto for Daring Sex. Five intense vignettes that feature some of the very best players</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 10:58:00" d="2020-05-19 11:20:00"><n>At First Sight: Ryan Driller &amp; Allison Moore</n>    <k>Laura (Kaylani Lei) is a cute, hardworking waitress. Josh (Ryan Driller) is a handsome, famous actor. When Josh spots her from across a crowded nightclub, he's hooked</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 11:20:00" d="2020-05-19 11:43:00"><n>Pleasure Professionals 2: Samantha Bentley &amp; Alexei Jackson</n>    <k>A high quality couple's porn scene from Joybear. A secluded hotel provides the perfect getaway. With an air of mystery surrounding the elegant guest others</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 11:43:00" d="2020-05-19 12:10:00"><n>Multiorgasmic Brunch</n><t>S</t>    <k>An explosive exploration of the possibilities for female pleasure; where the orgasms just never end. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 12:10:00" d="2020-05-19 12:32:00"><n>Make Me Sweat: Kristof &amp; Kattie</n>    <k>A passionate couple in a Sinful XXX film by Roma Amor. Beautiful, Arty and very sexy. Porn for women with a focus on the humand body</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 12:32:00" d="2020-05-19 12:49:00"><n>Exposure: New MSG!</n>    <k>In a world where couples would rather play with their phones than each other, one woman uses her technology skills for good, nudging distracted lovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 12:49:00" d="2020-05-19 13:26:00"><n>Couples Massage: Antonia Sainz &amp; Adam Black</n>    <k>A crackling fire, relaxing music and a lot of warm oil for a total body massage. Delicious. These beautiful couples can’t get enough of it too. A beautiful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 13:26:00" d="2020-05-19 13:45:00"><n>Unbridled: Rachel Starr &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>To save her family’s ranch, city girl Avery has to return to Texas and face her demons and her old flame horse trainer Grant. Stormy Daniels stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 13:45:00" d="2020-05-19 14:00:00"><n>Going Bananas</n>    <k>Stand up and pick up a banana, read the instructions carefully, follow the rules. Wait for me lying on our big white bed, I?ll come</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 14:00:00" d="2020-05-19 14:19:00"><n>Housemates 3: Best Fucking Sex Ever</n>    <k>Synopsis not available</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 14:19:00" d="2020-05-19 14:52:00"><n>Suspicious Minds: Steve Q &amp; Katy Rose</n>    <k>Max Deeds Is A Private Detective Caught In A World Of Suspicious Minds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 14:52:00" d="2020-05-19 15:01:00"><n>Momentum 4: Sun on our skin</n>    <k>The fourth final and most epic adult film. The Volume 4 stage is set in the Australian desert - an aesthetic overthrow from the previous films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 15:01:00" d="2020-05-19 15:23:00"><n>Horngry</n><t>S</t>    <k>Food and sex combine in a delicious foursome from Erika Lust's XConfessions series! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 15:23:00" d="2020-05-19 15:45:00"><n>Fill Me Up With Your Orgasm: Kennedy Nash &amp; Johnny Castle</n>    <k>Such a waste to just get a little bit? Whether it be a refill on your drink, your gas tank, or your favorite piece of pussy, you gotta fill it to the brim! It's going to be a sticky situation when they get a fill of love butter that they crave! A Pure Passion film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 15:45:00" d="2020-05-19 16:10:00"><n>Obedience</n>    <k>On a beautiful day a Spanish beauty gets a surprise phone call from a stranger. A man tells her exactly what to do to pleasure herself sexually</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 16:10:00" d="2020-05-19 16:44:00"><n>Home Coming: Burning Desire</n>    <k>Oh, home sweet home. These couples experience that there's no place like home to come back to, especially since orgasms are awaiting them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 16:44:00" d="2020-05-19 17:04:00"><n>Sex With Friends: Experience</n>    <k>When old college friends meet again they take the time to rekindle and explore each other?s bodies and sexual boundries. A reunion you don?t want to miss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 17:04:00" d="2020-05-19 17:32:00"><n>Gentle Loving: Dolce Vita &amp; Vega</n>    <k>Beautiful european couples. These sweethearts are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A porn for women scene from Gentle Loving by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 17:32:00" d="2020-05-19 17:52:00"><n>Girls Sex Tricks: Carol Ferrer &amp; Pablo Ferrari</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us on her first film as director for Thagson with a vibrant female friendly porn story which will take place in the streets of Barcelona</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 17:52:00" d="2020-05-19 18:12:00"><n>Red Light: Casey Calvert &amp; Damon Dice</n>    <k>Red Light is like a waking dream set in the streets of Los Angeles. It's the story of a woman's transformation into her true self, and a wild chase</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 18:12:00" d="2020-05-19 18:43:00"><n>The stepmother 7: Ash Hollywood &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>Lynn has it all, a caring successful husband in a sumptuous Hollywood mansion, but something is missing. When her husband's daughter comes to visit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 18:43:00" d="2020-05-19 18:54:00"><n>Parallel Universe</n><t>S</t>    <k>There is another world out there, a world where you can exist purely as a piece of furniture. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 18:54:00" d="2020-05-19 19:24:00"><n>Tales from the Heart: India Summers &amp; Steven St. Croix</n>    <k>Love is in the air. specially on your Anniversary. A trip down memory lane is just the spark Michelle and Andy need to reignite the lustful feelings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 19:24:00" d="2020-05-19 19:48:00"><n>Pleasure Professionals 2: Tiffany Doll &amp; Marc Rose</n>    <k>A kinky couple's porn film from Joybear. Every summer Mrs ERC bolts to the countryside to relax and unwind. A secluded hotel provides the perfect getaway</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 19:48:00" d="2020-05-19 20:07:00"><n>Room 208: Sara May &amp; Juan Lucho</n>    <k>A romantic sex film by Lara Tinelli for Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 20:07:00" d="2020-05-19 20:42:00"><n>Colors Of Eden: Vanessa Decker &amp; Steve</n><t>L</t>    <k>A gorgeous couple having breathtakingly hot sex, in colorful surroundings, showing both intimacy and sexual fulfilment in every little detail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 20:42:00" d="2020-05-19 21:04:00"><n>Milk</n>    <k>What kind of Milk are you drinking today? A romantic porn video featuring pornstar Julia Roca by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 21:04:00" d="2020-05-19 21:11:00"><n>Slo Blo Mo Job</n><t>S</t>    <k>The longest, most intense blow job imaginable. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual confessions of her viewers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 21:11:00" d="2020-05-19 21:41:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies: Dolce Vita &amp; Vega</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. A romantic porn video from Favorite Fantasies by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 21:41:00" d="2020-05-19 21:59:00"><n>When it Comes to you: Karlie Montana &amp; Steven St. Croix</n>    <k>When It Comes To You is a captivating and scintillating story of a woman torn between two men who both profess great love. Directed by Stormy Daniels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 21:59:00" d="2020-05-19 22:23:00"><n>Taste: Ava Dalush &amp; Antonio Black</n>    <k>Audrey is a talented and beautiful chef with a gift. She has the power to make her unsuspecting diners feel overwhelmingly amorous. She is one mouthful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 22:23:00" d="2020-05-19 22:43:00"><n>We Know You Are Watching</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: A sexy young couple in Brazil notice how interested their neighbor is in observing their naturist habits at home. In XConfessions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 22:43:00" d="2020-05-19 22:57:00"><n>Silver Shoes: Housesitter</n>    <k>This award-winning explicit erotic trilogy from Jennifer Lyon Bell intertwines three short porn for women stories about the carnal power of what we wear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 22:57:00" d="2020-05-19 23:24:00"><n>Sensuous Seduction: In the Evening</n>    <k>A scene from a romantic sex film by Lara Tinelli for Dusk TV's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 23:24:00" d="2020-05-19 23:47:00"><n>Sweet Memories: Together</n>    <k>A short erotic story by Lara Tinelli for female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting realistic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-19 23:47:00" d="2020-05-20 00:06:00"><n>Quartet: The Teacher</n>    <k>Penelope boards a plane from London to Budapest, eager to perform with her three best friends from music academy. Reunited, the foursome soon remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 00:06:00" d="2020-05-20 00:35:00"><n>Couples Massage: Daphne &amp; Andrew Truck</n>    <k>A crackling fire, relaxing music and a lot of warm oil for a total body massage. Delicious. These beautiful couples can’t get enough of it too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 00:35:00" d="2020-05-20 01:01:00"><n>Camera Angle: Ryan Keely &amp; Ryan Mclane</n>    <k>Fiction and reality seem to blend when Hollywood actor Peter gets a concussion. His visions of heart-racing, sweat inducing sex seem very real though</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 01:01:00" d="2020-05-20 01:33:00"><n>Blind Date Swingers Club: Natalie Shirley &amp; Conway Bush</n>    <k>Everyone is getting their fuck on! Swinging couples going wild! It's Georgies turn to have a blind rendez-vous with one of the guys. Who will it be?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 01:33:00" d="2020-05-20 01:59:00"><n>Tales from the Heart: Sara Luvv &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>Love is in the air. specially on your Anniversary. A trip down memory lane is just the spark Michelle and Andy need to reignite the lustful feelings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 01:59:00" d="2020-05-20 02:14:00"><n>Girls Sex Tricks: Julia De Lucia &amp; Emilio Saiz Olid</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us on her first film as director for Thagson with a vibrant female friendly porn story which will take place in the streets of Barcelona</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 02:14:00" d="2020-05-20 02:30:00"><n>Red Light: Bree Daniels &amp; Skin Diamond</n>    <k>Red Light is like a waking dream set in the streets of Los Angeles. It's the story of a woman's transformation into her true self, and a wild chase</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 02:30:00" d="2020-05-20 02:42:00"><n>Romance Bullshit</n>    <k>From XConfessions 3: Every writer in the room types frantically, but she is just not inspired. Until she sees him. In XConfessions, people from all around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 02:42:00" d="2020-05-20 03:02:00"><n>Positions: Third</n>    <k>While finding inspiration at a dancer?s retreat, the ballet dancer Florence soon realises she?s not the only one who could do with practising</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 03:02:00" d="2020-05-20 03:27:00"><n>Sweet Petite Girls: Katy Rose &amp; Lutro</n>    <k>These young beauties are starting to discover their sexuality, exploring their bodies and seek new limits. Director Roman Sluka captured these teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 03:27:00" d="2020-05-20 03:50:00"><n>Room 208: Julia Roca &amp; Sylvan Garcia</n>    <k>Would you like to be a pornstar? Watch how these beautiful performers reach full excitement and true pleasure. A beautiful porn for women film by Dusk TV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 03:50:00" d="2020-05-20 04:16:00"><n>Making Ends Meet: Cheri Deville &amp; Jay Smooth</n>    <k>A suburbian family is in destress over money, but sex seems to really heal the wounds. Scorching hot sex and sharp comedy blend perfectly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 04:16:00" d="2020-05-20 04:26:00"><n>Rush of the Forbidden</n><t>S</t>    <k>A sneaky rendezvous for a dose of sexy infidelity. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual confessions of her viewers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 04:26:00" d="2020-05-20 04:52:00"><n u="The Submission Of Emma Marx: Penny Pax &amp; Richie Calhoun">The Submission Of Emma Marx: Penny Pax &amp; Richie Calhoun (4)</n>    <k>When a new contract is drafted up defining the parameters of their BDSM relationship, Emma realizes that Mr. Frederick is anything but predictable</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-20 04:52:00" d="2020-05-20 05:17:00"><n>Love Me Forever: Lily Cat &amp; Vega</n><t>L</t>    <k>Romantic, passionate love. These couples show each other how much they enjoy each others company. A romantic porn video by Desire Media</k>  </p>
</a>
