<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="55" t="2019-07-17 12:28:23"><p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 05:20:00" d="2019-07-24 05:49:00"><n>Black Sweat</n>    <k>Sinful interracial couples enjoy colorful erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 05:49:00" d="2019-07-24 06:16:00"><n>Tenderness: Ria Sunn &amp; Jayden Cox</n>    <k>A new scene by Roma Woodcock for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 06:16:00" d="2019-07-24 06:56:00"><n>Black And Blue: Jade Nila &amp; James Deen</n><t>L</t>    <k>In this tale of submission and dominance, wealthy businessman Patrick introduces young Alison to the world of BDSM. When they fall in lover it shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 06:56:00" d="2019-07-24 07:14:00"><n>Among The Bushes</n>    <k>He?s always sitting in this park, surrounded by the trees, reading a book, cute and charismatic. He?s big, tall and handsome. I?ll take him between the trees, I?ll make him take off his clothes and I?ll fuck him surrounded by leaves, sunlight and dog walkers. A Verso Cinema film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 07:14:00" d="2019-07-24 07:31:00"><n>Sun stroke: Crowd control</n>    <k>When international DJ Cosmo needs a secluded escape, his boss? sun-kissed Spanish villa is the perfect location. Determined to tackle his writer?s block</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 07:31:00" d="2019-07-24 07:55:00"><n>Girls Fight Club</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 07:55:00" d="2019-07-24 08:27:00"><n>Playful passion</n><t>L</t>    <k>A fantastic directed scene by former Playmate of the World, Zimra Geurts, for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Newbie performer Jane von Detta</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 08:27:00" d="2019-07-24 08:48:00"><n>Camera Angle: Ivy Labelle &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>Fiction and reality seem to blend when Hollywood actor Peter gets a concussion. His visions of heart-racing, sweat inducing sex seem very real though.</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 08:48:00" d="2019-07-24 09:17:00"><n>Hair Down There: Tracey Sweet &amp; Anthony Rosano</n><t>L</t>    <k>She's got hair down there, and yes, we love that natural look! Let Mia Malkova, Nadine Sage, Tracey Sweet, and Anastasia Morna show you how their naturally</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 09:17:00" d="2019-07-24 09:40:00"><n>Hugman</n>    <k>My girlfriend and I are not serious people, we like to have fun in our lives and we are always playing tricks and games to spice up our life. A Verso Cinema film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 09:40:00" d="2019-07-24 10:02:00"><n>Ball Control: Rebecca More &amp; Luke Hotrod</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 10:02:00" d="2019-07-24 10:20:00"><n>Cabaret Desire: Sofia Prada, Saskia Condal &amp; Toni Fontana</n>    <k>Welcome to nightclub Cabaret Desire ? indulge yourself with poets and their erotic tales filled with passion and temptation. A film by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 10:20:00" d="2019-07-24 10:54:00"><n>Not to Innocent: Angel Piaf &amp; Max D</n>    <k>A new scene by Dawn for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 10:54:00" d="2019-07-24 11:24:00"><n>Raw: Ivana &amp; Lukas</n>    <k>Beautiful images of sexual tenderness in its pure but raw way. Close-ups of gorgeous toned bodies and horny sweat. One of Sinful?s most beautiful productions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 11:24:00" d="2019-07-24 11:40:00"><n>Memory Files of You</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 11:40:00" d="2019-07-24 12:04:00"><n>Making Ends Meet: Mercedes Carrera &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>A suburbian family is in destress over money, but sex seems to really heal the wounds. Scorching hot sex and sharp comedy blend perfectly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 12:04:00" d="2019-07-24 12:27:00"><n>Summer Lovers: Mia Minarote &amp; Matt Ice</n>    <k>When it's summer the temperature rises, you wear less clothes and get aroused much easier. Is there anything hotter than having outdoor sex surrounded by nature? A scene from an Intimate Encounters film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 12:27:00" d="2019-07-24 12:52:00"><n>Anal Lovers: Esparansa &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A scene from Anal Lovers by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 12:52:00" d="2019-07-24 13:10:00"><n>Fill Me Up With Your Orgasm: Kennedy Nash &amp; Billy Hart</n>    <k>Such a waste to just get a little bit? Whether it be a refill on your drink, your gas tank, or your favorite piece of pussy, you gotta fill it to the brim! It's going to be a sticky situation when they get a fill of love butter that they crave! A Pure Passion film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 13:10:00" d="2019-07-24 13:32:00"><n>At First Sight: Ryan Driller &amp; Allison Moore</n>    <k>Laura (Kaylani Lei) is a cute, hardworking waitress. Josh (Ryan Driller) is a handsome, famous actor. When Josh spots her from across a crowded nightclub, he's hooked</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 13:32:00" d="2019-07-24 13:54:00"><n>The Party</n>    <k>A breasty Spanish beauty can’t get any sleep because of the loud party next door. But when she sees her attractive neighbor her angry feelings fade away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 13:54:00" d="2019-07-24 14:16:00"><n>The Guesthouse: Clea Gaultier &amp; Anthony Gaultier</n>    <k>Nestled in the Spanish countryside, there?s a Guesthouse where visitors enjoy more than just the sunshine on their bodies. Come alone, come with a friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 14:16:00" d="2019-07-24 14:29:00"><n>My first time eating oysters and pussy</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 14:29:00" d="2019-07-24 15:01:00"><n>Hair Down There: Mia Malkova &amp; Jordan Ash</n><t>L</t>    <k>She's got hair down there, and yes, we love that natural look! Let Mia Malkova, Nadine Sage, Tracey Sweet, and Anastasia Morna show you how their naturally</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 15:01:00" d="2019-07-24 15:33:00"><n>Special Moments: The Apple</n>    <k>A new scene by AlexanFilm for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 15:33:00" d="2019-07-24 15:56:00"><n>Quartet: The Quartet</n>    <k>Penelope boards a plane from London to Budapest, eager to perform with her three best friends from music academy. Reunited, the foursome soon remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 15:56:00" d="2019-07-24 16:11:00"><n>Spectrophilia</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 16:11:00" d="2019-07-24 16:29:00"><n>Come With Me</n>    <k>Come with me, or cum with me? An exciting Verso Cinema film with breathtaking orgasms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 16:29:00" d="2019-07-24 17:05:00"><n>Girls Crush: Dominika Pankracova &amp; Drahomira Juzova</n>    <k>These girls love, lust, lick, becoming almost one in this sensual piece of erotica. Sinful Studio making art again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 17:05:00" d="2019-07-24 17:30:00"><n>Sweet Memories: Touch me</n>    <k>4 small erotic stories by Lara Tinelli for Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 17:30:00" d="2019-07-24 17:54:00"><n>Pearl Necklace: Seth Strong &amp; Tiffany Doll</n>    <k>When a maid working for Lord &amp; Lady Shadwell is unfairly sacked, she plots sweet revenge by robbing her detestable former employers of their priceless heirloom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 17:54:00" d="2019-07-24 18:14:00"><n>The Ski Instructor</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 18:14:00" d="2019-07-24 18:36:00"><n>First Summer Love 2: Eliska &amp; Sweet Cat</n>    <k>The sequel of First Summer Love brings you more tantalizing scenes. The hot sun on their naked skin brings these girls in a state of permanent arousal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 18:36:00" d="2019-07-24 19:06:00"><n>The Babysitter 8: Dillion Harper &amp; James Deen</n>    <k>Mona is a bitter woman who hates her ex-husband and has no qualms about bad mouthing him to her new babysitter, Alice. What happens when Alice catches</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 19:06:00" d="2019-07-24 19:26:00"><n>Just Friends: Anna Morna &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>When a job assignment takes Courtney out of town for a few months she returns to find that James her childhood best friend is engaged. Naturally she's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 19:26:00" d="2019-07-24 19:50:00"><n>Sweet Memories: Together</n>    <k>4 small erotic stories by Lara Tinelli for Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 19:50:00" d="2019-07-24 20:08:00"><n>Exposure: Touch Me</n>    <k>In a world where couples would rather play with their phones than each other, one woman uses her technology skills for good, nudging distracted lovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 20:08:00" d="2019-07-24 20:20:00"><n>Try My Boyfriend</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 20:20:00" d="2019-07-24 20:42:00"><n>Romeo &amp; Juliet: Anthony Rosano &amp; Andy San Dimas</n>    <k>Directed by Lee Roy Myers, this film by DreamZone Entertainment features tragic lovers trapped within a web of love, lies and loyalties. A sexy and spicy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 20:42:00" d="2019-07-24 20:58:00"><n u="Ages of Sex: Sex at">Ages of Sex: Sex at (50)</n>    <k>The Ages of Sex is a Thagson Digital Media project. 4 well known directors will direct a short which represents a woman?s sexual reality in her 30s, 40s and 50s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 20:58:00" d="2019-07-24 21:23:00"><n>I Am All Yours: Eveline Neil &amp; Marcel Lee</n>    <k>A new scene by Dawn for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 21:23:00" d="2019-07-24 21:30:00"><n>Before The Guests Arrive</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 21:30:00" d="2019-07-24 21:55:00"><n>After Midnight: Denisa Heaven &amp; Wein Lewis</n>    <k>The most beautiful and hottest meetings take place as the world slowly grows quiet after midnight. Scene from a film by Daring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 21:55:00" d="2019-07-24 22:15:00"><n>Ouija</n>    <k>My girlfriend asked me to play with a Ouija board tonight. I?m dying to have some wild sex here on the floor. Let?s ask the ghosts what they think about it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 22:15:00" d="2019-07-24 22:33:00"><n>Weekend: Katy Rose &amp; Lutro</n><t>L</t>    <k>Shot in Portugal, episode 3 of The Weekend, &quot;Lust,&quot; shows it's getting close to dinnertime and the three couples are drinking wine and chatting amiably</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 22:33:00" d="2019-07-24 23:00:00"><n>Jessie Loves Girls: Jessie Andrews &amp; Dana DeArmond</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sweetheart Video's celebrated showcase series presents Jessie Andrews, in four unique scenes with four of her favorite girls. Beautiful, sexy and intriguing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-24 23:00:00" d="2019-07-25 00:10:00"><n>Diet Of Sex</n>    <k>Diet of Sex is an experience, is a love story between Ágata and Marc told through sex. A culinary, sexual adventure through a variety of flavours. A Thagson film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-25 00:10:00" d="2019-07-25 02:24:00"><n u="My Girlfriends Mother">My Girlfriends Mother (6)</n>    <k>When she gets caught in a compromising position with her professor, Sandi escapes with her boyfriend to her artistic free-spirit mother, Moon-Rose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-25 02:24:00" d="2019-07-25 02:46:00"><n>Hollywood Ending: Karlee Grey &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>Rebecca and Tommy (India Summer and Tommy Pistol) met in acting school and thought they had the perfect life. They made their way up the ladder of success</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-25 02:46:00" d="2019-07-25 03:00:00"><n>Cinema X Pigalle</n><t>S</t>    <k>Ten &quot;true confessions&quot; shot in Erika Lust's signature style are densely lush and cinematically gorgeous. For lovers of high production, you will swoon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-25 03:00:00" d="2019-07-25 03:26:00"><n>Secret Sex Society: Julia Roca &amp; Sylvan</n>    <k>When colourful people meet and share their colourful fantasies. Starring the hot blooded Spanish beauty Julia Roca</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-25 03:26:00" d="2019-07-25 03:55:00"><n>Desire For Sex: Diner D'amour</n>    <k>A beautiful film by Roma Amor for SinfulXXX. In this scene a couple enjoys a delicious dinner. But when it's time for desert they themselves take place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-25 03:55:00" d="2019-07-25 04:19:00"><n>Haunted hearts: Aaliyah Love &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>When a distant aunt dies her nice guy nephew inherits her estate. While settling into his palatial mansion he discovers sexual temptation family rivalry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-25 04:19:00" d="2019-07-25 04:41:00"><n>In The Limelight 1: Lexi Belle &amp; Jeanie Marie</n><t>L</t>    <k>Daring! Pure?s film ?In the Limelight? shows a spectacular selection of nine of their best scenes. The most beautiful couples surpass your wildest dreams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2019-07-25 04:41:00" d="2019-07-25 05:01:00"><n>Afternoon Love: Lexi Dona &amp; Thomas Reed</n>    <k>What are you going to do when all of a suddon both of you are at home and have nothing to do? Exactly, enjoy each other and make your time together worthwhile</k>  </p>
</a>
