<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="65" t="2020-05-28 04:45:03"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 05:09:00" d="2020-06-04 05:35:00"><n>Oral Reflections</n><t>L</t>    <k>Always wanted to know about anal sex, but never tried? This romantic porn film shows how nice anal massage can be</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 05:35:00" d="2020-06-04 05:46:00"><n>Girlfriends: Casey Calvert &amp; AJ Applegate</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Small town girl Jamie (Casey Calvert) has made the difficult decision to tell her parents that she is in a same sex relationship. Unfortunately her family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 05:46:00" d="2020-06-04 06:05:00"><n>I wish I was a lesbian</n><t>S</t>    <k>Maria's deepest fantasies come true when she finds herself being hosted by a hot and sweet lesbian couple. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 06:05:00" d="2020-06-04 06:29:00"><n>Pleasure Professionals 2: Lexi Lowe &amp; Ryan Ryder</n>    <k>A high quality couple's film from Joybear. Every summer Mrs ERC bolts to the countryside to relax and unwind. A secluded hotel provides the perfect getaway</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 06:29:00" d="2020-06-04 06:51:00"><n>In The Limelight 1: Chris Johnson &amp; Lexi Belle</n><t>L</t>    <k>This female friendly porn film shows a spectacular selection of nine of their best scenes. In this scene the most beautiful couple surpasses your wildest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 06:51:00" d="2020-06-04 07:13:00"><n>Room 208: Penelope Cum &amp; Salva Da Silva</n>    <k>A female friendly sex video by Lara Tinelli for Dusk TV. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 07:13:00" d="2020-06-04 07:31:00"><n>Trouble X 2: Cherie Deville &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>On his first day back in the dating game, Nick meets not one but TWO beautiful women. Olivia (Abigail Mac) is hot, sexy, and confident. Jenny (Cherie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 07:31:00" d="2020-06-04 07:45:00"><n>Let me see your ponytail swing, I Want a Viking Warrior</n><t>S</t>    <k>She wishes he was a viking warrior, he wishes she'd dress up like a cheerleader. So what happens when they do? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 07:45:00" d="2020-06-04 08:13:00"><n>Chance Encounters: Capri Anderson &amp; Anthony Rosano</n>    <k>Several couples encounter love, affairs, sex and romance at a hotel. A Intimate Encounters film by J. Crawford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 08:13:00" d="2020-06-04 08:40:00"><n>Beauty Of Nature: Cayla Lions &amp; Nick Larsen</n><t>L</t>    <k>Wondering what it take to have fantastic sex that you will remmeber for the rest of your life? Watch and learn as Desire Media shows you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 08:40:00" d="2020-06-04 08:57:00"><n>Exposure: Security Measures</n>    <k>In a world where couples would rather play with their phones than each other, one woman uses her technology skills for good, nudging distracted lovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 08:57:00" d="2020-06-04 09:14:00"><n>Don't Forget Me</n>    <k>Don't Forget Me has a simple and concise subtitle: &quot;a story about love.&quot; Lola Reve and Franck Franco give the romantic theme real life with little</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 09:14:00" d="2020-06-04 09:37:00"><n>Blind</n>    <k>Open your eyes wide for this one! Gorgeous Spanish beauty Apolonia Lapiedra and Pablo Ferrari get steamy in this short film with another classic scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 09:37:00" d="2020-06-04 09:50:00"><n>Momentum 4: Car</n>    <k>The fourth final and most epic adult film. The Volume 4 stage is set in the Australian desert - an aesthetic overthrow from the previous films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 09:50:00" d="2020-06-04 10:10:00"><n>Just Friends: Anna Morna &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>When a job assignment takes Courtney out of town for a few months she returns to find that James her childhood best friend is engaged. Naturally she's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 10:10:00" d="2020-06-04 10:23:00"><n>Ibiza Splash Crush</n><t>S</t>    <k>One the most forbidden and oldest mythical taboos: a merman. Seduced by a gorgeous lifeguard in the blistering Ibiza sun. From the XConfessions series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 10:23:00" d="2020-06-04 10:45:00"><n>Positions: Fourth</n>    <k>While finding inspiration at a dancer's retreat, the ballet dancer Florence soon realises she's not the only one who could do with practising</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 10:45:00" d="2020-06-04 11:13:00"><n>Her Desire: Ladies Night</n>    <k>Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion. A pleasure to all the senses representing realistic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 11:13:00" d="2020-06-04 11:45:00"><n>Blind Date Swingers Club: Natalie Shirley &amp; Conway Bush</n>    <k>Everyone is getting their fuck on! Swinging couples going wild! It's Georgies turn to have a blind rendez-vous with one of the guys. Who will it be?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 11:45:00" d="2020-06-04 12:10:00"><n>Forbidden Affairs 4: Jodi Taylor &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>He is astounded by the drop-dead gorgeous girlfriend of his son. When she starts to flirt with him he can no longer resist the temptation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 12:10:00" d="2020-06-04 12:39:00"><n>Brave Hearts: Abigaile Johnson &amp; George Uhl</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sarah (Faye Regan), the most famous Romance Novelist in the world, is writing the final book in her series of best-selling love stories. Admired by women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 12:39:00" d="2020-06-04 13:00:00"><n>In The Limelight 1: Jay Dee &amp; Sindy Vega</n>    <k>Spectacular sex, the most beautiful couples surpass your wildest dreams to fulfill their sexual desires. A romantic porn for women scene by Daring! Pure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 13:00:00" d="2020-06-04 13:18:00"><n>It's Complicated: Yhivi &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>Shauna (Gracie Glam) has been having casual sex with her handsome friend Will, biding her time until she can finally make a move on her long time crush Brandon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 13:18:00" d="2020-06-04 13:40:00"><n>Quartet: The Quartet</n>    <k>Penelope boards a plane from London to Budapest, eager to perform with her three best friends from music academy. Reunited, the foursome soon remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 13:40:00" d="2020-06-04 13:52:00"><n>Hunt Me Catch Me Eat Me</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: A fox hunts for the rabbit, devouring her in all her beauty in the end. In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 13:52:00" d="2020-06-04 14:26:00"><n>Home Coming: Burning Desire</n>    <k>Oh, home sweet home. These couples experience that there's no place like home to come back to, especially since orgasms are awaiting them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 14:26:00" d="2020-06-04 14:47:00"><n>Tease: Tyler Nixon &amp; Stella Cox</n>    <k>If according to Shakespeare, clothes make the man, then without doubt lingerie make the woman. Naught porn for women by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 14:47:00" d="2020-06-04 15:16:00"><n>Couples Massage: Daphne &amp; Andrew Truck</n>    <k>A crackling fire, relaxing music and a lot of warm oil for a total body massage. Delicious. These beautiful couples can’t get enough of it too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 15:16:00" d="2020-06-04 15:39:00"><n>Girlfriends: August Ames &amp; Lily Cade</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Small town girl Jamie (Casey Calvert) has made the difficult decision to tell her parents that she is in a same sex relationship. Unfortunately her family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 15:39:00" d="2020-06-04 15:55:00"><n>Going Bananas</n>    <k>Stand up and pick up a banana, read the instructions carefully, follow the rules. Wait for me lying on our big white bed, I?ll come</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 15:55:00" d="2020-06-04 16:15:00"><n>Ball Control: Sienna Day &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>They say that football is a man’s world, but there’s one woman on this pitch with all the power. Physio Eva puts her massage skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 16:15:00" d="2020-06-04 16:42:00"><n>Confessions Of A Sinner: Dorian Del Isla &amp; Cassie Del Isla</n>    <k>This beautiful couple relishes each others body with sensual hand and mouth massages by candlelight. Another visual and erotic porn for women film by Studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 16:42:00" d="2020-06-04 17:12:00"><n>Silver Shoes: Mimosa</n>    <k>This award-winning explicit erotic trilogy from Jennifer Lyon Bell intertwines three short stories about the carnal power of what we wear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 17:12:00" d="2020-06-04 17:22:00"><n>Magic Magnus</n><t>S</t>    <k>There's nothing like a man who dares to do a bit of dancing in order to spice things up, right? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 17:22:00" d="2020-06-04 17:40:00"><n>Pure Sexual Attraction 2: August Ames &amp; Danny Mountain</n>    <k>Embark on an exciting journey of pure sexual attraction as five breathtaking girls are captured in five scenes that set the standard for high definition erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 17:40:00" d="2020-06-04 18:05:00"><n>Afternoon Love: Angel Piaf &amp; Max D</n>    <k>Watch this straight couple enjoy each other and make their time together worthwhile. A real life couple having realistic sex. A porn for women film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 18:05:00" d="2020-06-04 18:32:00"><n>The Passionate Three: Gina Gerson, Nick Gill &amp; Adam Black</n>    <k>Sinful trinity's enjoying a triad of erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 18:32:00" d="2020-06-04 19:01:00"><n>Sun stroke: The Final Song</n>    <k>When international DJ Cosmo needs a secluded escape, his boss? sun-kissed Spanish villa is the perfect location. Chloe soon becomes an intense distraction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 19:01:00" d="2020-06-04 19:25:00"><n>Favorite Fantasies 2: Miranda &amp; Joe T</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A female friendly porn scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 19:25:00" d="2020-06-04 19:41:00"><n>Soulmates</n>    <k>Nothing more fun than watching beautiful people together with your partner. Especially if that ends in super nice sex with your 'Soulmate(s)'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 19:41:00" d="2020-06-04 20:00:00"><n>When it Comes to you: Karlie Montana &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>When It Comes To You is a captivating and scintillating story of a woman torn between two men who both profess great love. Directed by Stormy Daniels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 20:00:00" d="2020-06-04 20:26:00"><n>My Girlfriends Mother 6: Julia Ann &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>Robbie dreaded meeting his girlfriend's mother, but when he finally does, he's taken back as how friendly, alluring and sensual she really is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 20:26:00" d="2020-06-04 20:41:00"><n>A Feminist Man</n><t>S</t>    <k>Is there anything sexier than a man who can give perfect cunnilingus and have a conversation about Judith Butler? From the XConfessions series by Erika</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 20:41:00" d="2020-06-04 21:08:00"><n>Love is in the Air: Jodi Taylor &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>When her fiance gets sucked into never-ending conversation at a friend's party, a woman lures him to the bedroom for a passionate sexual encounter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 21:08:00" d="2020-06-04 21:32:00"><n>Fit: Alexei Jackson &amp; Amarna Miller</n>    <k>You are running on the beach, bathed in the beautiful sunshine. You feel alive and energized ? what could be better? Get outside. Get active</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 21:32:00" d="2020-06-04 22:03:00"><n>Sensuous Seduction: Messaging</n>    <k>A sensual massage is the gateway to your partners naughtiness and desires. Watch how this sexy couple is physically expressing their love to each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 22:03:00" d="2020-06-04 22:32:00"><n>Sex Sinners and Saints: Nathaly Cherie &amp; Steve</n>    <k>Not only is the church the perfect place to confess your sins, it's also the perfect location to have sensational sex. These couples sin in church, moaning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 22:32:00" d="2020-06-04 22:57:00"><n>Very Beautiful Lips</n><t>L</t>    <k>Starting with a shower, performers Apolonia Lapiedra and Alberto Blanco waste no time in exploring their lust for one another. As they move</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 22:57:00" d="2020-06-04 23:15:00"><n>Dacrifilia</n><t>S</t>    <k>An artist brings a man to tears to fulfil her fetish - dacryphilia. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 23:15:00" d="2020-06-04 23:45:00"><n>Soft And Sweet 2: Vinna Reed &amp; Nick Ross</n>    <k>Did you ever notice the softness of your lovers skin, the sweet taste when you move your tongue over her well formed sensual body? A porn for women film by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 23:45:00" d="2020-06-04 23:56:00"><n>Unbridled: Lyra Law &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>To save her family’s ranch, city girl Avery has to return to Texas and face her demons and her old flame horse trainer Grant. Stormy Daniels stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-04 23:56:00" d="2020-06-05 00:19:00"><n>Housemates 2: Tyler Nixon &amp; Samatha Bentley</n>    <k>Artist James moves to the UK in search of his ex-girlfriend (Dalush) and finds himself sharing a house with four incredibly attractive women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 00:19:00" d="2020-06-05 00:30:00"><n>That Guy At The Nudist Beach</n><t>S</t>    <k>Julia Roca and Bel Gris play a gorgeous Spanish couple, seducing each other on a deserted beach. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 00:30:00" d="2020-06-05 00:47:00"><n>Girls Sex Tricks: Carol Ferrer &amp; Pablo Ferrari</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us on her first film as director for Thagson with a vibrant female friendly porn story which will take place in the streets of Barcelona</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 00:47:00" d="2020-06-05 01:14:00"><n>Tenderness: Ria Sunn &amp; Jayden Cox</n>    <k>A erotic massage scene by Dusk TV's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Romantic porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 01:14:00" d="2020-06-05 01:40:00"><n>Sex With Friends: Daydreams</n>    <k>When old college friends meet again they take the time to rekindle and explore each other?s bodies and sexual boundries. A reunion you don?t want to miss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 01:40:00" d="2020-06-05 02:17:00"><n>Couples Massage: Antonia Sainz &amp; Adam Black</n>    <k>A crackling fire, relaxing music and a lot of warm oil for a total body massage. Delicious. These beautiful couples can’t get enough of it too. A beautiful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 02:17:00" d="2020-06-05 02:44:00"><n>Haunted hearts: Aaliyah Love &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>When a distant aunt dies her nice guy nephew inherits her estate. While settling into his palatial mansion he discovers sexual temptation family rivalry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 02:44:00" d="2020-06-05 03:13:00"><n>So Wet Beside Her: Victoria Pure &amp; Charlie Red</n>    <k>These girls love, lust, lick, becoming almost one in this sensual piece of erotica. Sinful Studio making art again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 03:13:00" d="2020-06-05 03:39:00"><n>Hall Pass: Anikka Albrite &amp; Mick Blue</n>    <k>With her husband's blessing, Anikka indulges in an afternoon seduction with a long time crush. Cherie's husband is eager to help her overcome her sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 03:39:00" d="2020-06-05 03:54:00"><n>Girls Sex Tricks: Julia De Lucia &amp; Emilio Saiz Olid</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us on her first film as director for Thagson with a vibrant female friendly porn story which will take place in the streets of Barcelona</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 03:54:00" d="2020-06-05 04:16:00"><n>After Forever: Peny Pax &amp; Derrick Pierce</n>    <k>When Derrick plans a romantic weekend in his vacation house he soon finds out that his ex Penny had the same idea with her new partner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 04:16:00" d="2020-06-05 04:30:00"><n>Public Submission</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sometimes you find the most thrilling encounters where you least expect. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 04:30:00" d="2020-06-05 04:50:00"><n>Ball Control: Sienna Day &amp; Jess West</n>    <k>They say that football is a man’s world, but these two women on this pitch hold all the power. A romantic lesbian porn scene by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 04:50:00" d="2020-06-05 05:14:00"><n>Picture Perfect: Zoe Davies &amp; Juan Lucho</n>    <k>Sometimes all you need is a perfect picture from your lover to get the juices flowing. A romantic female friendly porn film by Daring! Pure</k>  </p>
</a>
