<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="62" t="2020-05-15 05:03:39"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 05:10:00" d="2020-05-22 05:26:00"><n>Momentum 2: Voyeur</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Momentum Volume. 2 lives up to it's predecessor, taking us back from the beach to the lazy Australian suburbs. Director Michelle Flynn retains the retro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 05:26:00" d="2020-05-22 05:51:00"><n>Hollywood Ending: India Summer &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>Childhood lovers Rebecca and Tommy are finally getting the acting success they always wanted. But their love is put to the test when fame, fortune</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 05:51:00" d="2020-05-22 06:02:00"><n>Hysterical Piano Concert</n><t>S</t>    <k>A pianist's ultimate sexual fantasy is played out in an intimate concert that hits an exquisite note! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 06:02:00" d="2020-05-22 06:19:00"><n>The Invitation: Sienna Day &amp; Max Deeds</n>    <k>Jane and Tom decide to pack the kids off and book a romantic weekend away. When their car unexpectedly breaks down late at night they find themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 06:19:00" d="2020-05-22 06:45:00"><n>Picture Perfect: Regina Crystal &amp; Marc Rose</n>    <k>In an age of social media, FaceTime and mobile communication, couples now have the ultimate sex toy at their disposal. They can tease each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 06:45:00" d="2020-05-22 07:13:00"><n>Tenderness: Violette Pink &amp; Angelo Godshack</n>    <k>A erotic video by Dusk TV. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion. A pleasure to all the senses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 07:13:00" d="2020-05-22 07:35:00"><n>Haunted Hearts: Michael Vegas &amp; Dana DeArmond</n>    <k>When a distant aunt dies her nice guy nephew inherits her estate. While settling into his palatial mansion he discovers sexual temptation family rivalry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 07:35:00" d="2020-05-22 07:46:00"><n>He Was First In My Ass</n><t>S</t>    <k>Tiffany gets inspired by an erotic book on anal sex, and decides that it's time for sexual liberty. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 07:46:00" d="2020-05-22 08:17:00"><n>I Love My Hotwife: Siri &amp; Chad White</n>    <k>Four segments on the sexual fantasies of husbands and wives. A married couple hires a sexy male escort, Siri let?s her husband listen to her sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 08:17:00" d="2020-05-22 08:55:00"><n>Couples Massage: Vanessa Decker &amp; Ricky</n>    <k>A crackling fire, relaxing music and a lot of warm oil for a total body massage. Delicious. These beautiful couples can’t get enough of it too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 08:55:00" d="2020-05-22 09:15:00"><n>The Guesthouse: Julia Roca &amp; Sicilia</n>    <k>Nestled in the Spanish countryside, there?s a Guesthouse where visitors enjoy more than just the sunshine on their bodies. Come alone, come with a friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 09:15:00" d="2020-05-22 09:24:00"><n u="Weekend: Lexie Dona &amp; Jason">Weekend: Lexie Dona &amp; Jason X</n><t>L</t>    <k>Shot in Portugal, episode 2 of The Weekend, &quot;Infidelity,&quot; picks up where the first episode left off, where Lexie joins her partner, Jason X, in the shower</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 09:24:00" d="2020-05-22 09:48:00"><n>Potter In Love</n>    <k>Today we are are getting creative with clay, a dirty and exciting endeavor! Porn for women by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 09:48:00" d="2020-05-22 10:07:00"><n u="Ages of Sex: Sex at">Ages of Sex: Sex at (40)</n>    <k>The Ages of Sex is a porn for women film by Thagson. 4 Well known directors will direct a short which represents a woman?s sexual reality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 10:07:00" d="2020-05-22 10:35:00"><n>Facade: Keira Nicole &amp; James Deen</n>    <k>Amber and her friend Lindsay are average college students?who happen to moonlight as sexy webcam models. This complicates things when they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 10:35:00" d="2020-05-22 10:46:00"><n>Before The Guests Arrive</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: Against the clock, this couple engage in a hot quickie before their dinner guests arrive! In XConfessions, people from all around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 10:46:00" d="2020-05-22 11:12:00"><n>Secret Sex Society: Julia Roca &amp; Sylvan</n>    <k>When colourful people meet and share their colourful fantasies. Starring the hot blooded Spanish beauty Julia Roca</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 11:12:00" d="2020-05-22 11:35:00"><n>Sweet Memories: Lovers</n>    <k>A hot erotic video by Lara Tinelli for female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples who like big dick. Romantic sex films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 11:35:00" d="2020-05-22 12:06:00"><n>Wet!: Color Me Wet</n>    <k>Sinful couples enjoy having seks when it pours? What's on your bucket list? A SinfulXXX film by Roma Amor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 12:06:00" d="2020-05-22 12:40:00"><n>Shades of Kink 6: Vixen Marley &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>A gorgeous girl starts to work for an eccentric kinky writer and learns everything there is to know about bondage and discipline. Starring vivacious Marley</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 12:40:00" d="2020-05-22 13:10:00"><n>Hair Down There: Anastasia Morna &amp; Jordan Ash</n><t>L</t>    <k>She's got hair down there, and yes, we love that natural look! Let Mia Malkova, Nadine Sage, Tracey Sweet, and Anastasia Morna show you how their naturally</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 13:10:00" d="2020-05-22 13:38:00"><n>Coming Out: Minnie Manga &amp; Nia Black</n>    <k>In uncertainty about their sexual orientation these young women finally no longer conceal their sexual preference, and revealing their gender identity completely</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 13:38:00" d="2020-05-22 14:03:00"><n>Sex and Lies: Sovereign Sire &amp; Daisy Stone</n>    <k>In the world of the ultra-rich, sex and lies reign supreme. Alisa (Avi Love)is a personal assistant who craves nothing more than order; difficult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 14:03:00" d="2020-05-22 14:22:00"><n>Fit: Jasmine Aruba &amp; Sienna Day</n>    <k>You are running on the beach, bathed in the beautiful sunshine. You feel alive and energized ? what could be better? Get outside. Get active</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 14:22:00" d="2020-05-22 14:34:00"><n>Try My Boyfriend</n><t>S</t>    <k>Her boyfriend was so good at cunnilingus that she felt the need of sharing him. With the world! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 14:34:00" d="2020-05-22 15:10:00"><n>Private Spa: Mugur &amp; Caroline de Jaie</n>    <k>This beautiful couple enjoys every bit of their private spa. We like it that hot! A delightful video by studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 15:10:00" d="2020-05-22 15:28:00"><n>Close To The Bone: Anya Olsen &amp; Loren Minardi</n>    <k>Two immortal lovers are feeling the three-hundred-year-itch. As night falls the city becomes a playground for Jonus and Bryana, both seeking to quench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 15:28:00" d="2020-05-22 16:09:00"><n>Couples Massage: Nicole Love &amp; Lutro</n>    <k>A crackling fire, relaxing music and a lot of warm oil for a total body massage. Delicious. These beautiful couples can’t get enough of it too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 16:09:00" d="2020-05-22 16:27:00"><n>From The First Moment: Alix Lynx &amp; Robby Echo</n>    <k>Kira (Alix Lynx) is about to marry her handsome movie star boyfriend James except he gets cold feet and leaves her at the wedding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 16:27:00" d="2020-05-22 16:44:00"><n>Strip Chess</n>    <k>Are you up for a chess game? Join Silvia Rubi and Gabe Romero in this intimate scene full of chemistry, where the game (and the increasing lack of clothes)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 16:44:00" d="2020-05-22 17:08:00"><n>Sex With Friends: Freedom</n>    <k>When old college friends meet again they take the time to rekindle and explore each other?s bodies and sexual boundries. A reunion you don?t want to miss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 17:08:00" d="2020-05-22 17:30:00"><n>Make Me Sweat: Figi &amp; Anna</n>    <k>This super hot porn for women scene by Sinful XXX hold the human body as a piece of art, and super hot sex as a masterpiece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 17:30:00" d="2020-05-22 17:57:00"><n>Real And Molly</n>    <k>A new scene for Dusk Academy from Michelle Flynn. A different couple, a different style, a different setting. But 100% porna</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 17:57:00" d="2020-05-22 18:11:00"><n>El que no ama no conoce a Dios</n><t>S</t>    <k>Committing the ultimate sin has never been so sweet! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual confessions of her viewers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 18:11:00" d="2020-05-22 18:36:00"><n>Girl Next Door Likes It Dirty: Dillion Harper &amp; Ryan McClane</n>    <k>All of these next door girls are young, free, and secretly wild who love it dirty! They all get their pussies passionately pulverized over the course</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 18:36:00" d="2020-05-22 19:05:00"><n>My Love For you: Vinna Reed &amp; Lutro</n>    <k>A sex film by Roma Woodcock for Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 19:05:00" d="2020-05-22 19:38:00"><n>The Artist: Max Deeds &amp; Misha Cross</n>    <k>Another beautiful production by Studio Sinful, containing lots of close-ups, artistic lighting and delicious performers. In The Artist a man is sensually</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 19:38:00" d="2020-05-22 19:58:00"><n>Ball Control: Marc Rose &amp; Anissa Kate</n>    <k>They say that football is a man’s world, but there’s one woman on this pitch with all the power. Super sexy porn for women by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 19:58:00" d="2020-05-22 20:23:00"><n>Romeo &amp; Juliet: Chanel Preston &amp; Rocco Reed</n>    <k>Directed by Lee Roy Myers, this romantic sex film by DreamZone Entertainment features tragic lovers trapped within a web of love, lies and loyalties</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 20:23:00" d="2020-05-22 20:52:00"><n>Silver Shoes: Mimosa</n>    <k>This award-winning explicit erotic trilogy from Jennifer Lyon Bell intertwines three short stories about the carnal power of what we wear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 20:52:00" d="2020-05-22 21:09:00"><n>Perfect timing: Sara Luvv &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>Christina has a dilemma. She was swept off her feet by a much older man, but now things have cooled. She then meets a charming guy and very soon sparks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 21:09:00" d="2020-05-22 21:42:00"><n>The Stepmother 10: Amanda Tate &amp; James Deen</n>    <k>Emma has a dark secret. Her fiancée doesn't know anything about her salacious past. But when his son meets his soon-to-be stepmother, he recognizes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 21:42:00" d="2020-05-22 21:55:00"><n>Ibiza Splash Crush</n><t>S</t>    <k>One the most forbidden and oldest mythical taboos: a merman. Seduced by a gorgeous lifeguard in the blistering Ibiza sun. From the XConfessions series</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 21:55:00" d="2020-05-22 22:26:00"><n>Love is in the Air: Chanel Preston &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>When her fiance gets sucked into never-ending conversation at a friend's party, a woman lures him to the bedroom for a passionate sexual encounter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 22:26:00" d="2020-05-22 22:44:00"><n>Quartet: Inspiration</n>    <k>Penelope boards a plane from London to Budapest, eager to perform with her three best friends from music academy. Reunited, the foursome soon remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 22:44:00" d="2020-05-22 23:06:00"><n>4 Passionate Women: My Friend Ana</n>    <k>Porn for women director Lara Tinelli for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 23:06:00" d="2020-05-22 23:32:00"><n>Our Summer of Love: Sienna Day &amp; Simony Diamond</n>    <k>A hot couple travels abroad and adores the new country, but they enjoy each other even more and especially the new sexy people they meet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 23:32:00" d="2020-05-22 23:55:00"><n>Summer</n>    <k>What a better refreshment in the middle of a hot hazy and sticky summer day than playing with some ice in front of a breezy fan and having loads of good sex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-22 23:55:00" d="2020-05-23 00:21:00"><n>Educating Reeves: Danny D &amp; Jess West</n>    <k>Motor racing champion Reeves wants to buy a piece of land in the countryside and build a race track. That is easier said than done? Porn for women by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 00:21:00" d="2020-05-23 00:56:00"><n>My Hotwife's Lover: My Wife, The Sex Lover</n>    <k>Kristin's (Karla Kush) forbidden attraction to her husband's best friend reaches a breaking point when he arranges a private get-together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 00:56:00" d="2020-05-23 01:16:00"><n>Afternoon Love: Lexi Dona &amp; Thomas Reed</n>    <k>A realistic couple with realistic sex. A romantic porn for women film by Dusk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 01:16:00" d="2020-05-23 01:35:00"><n>Housemates 2: Luke Hotrod &amp; Samantha Bentley</n>    <k>New house. New rules. Artist James moves to the UK in search of his ex-girlfriend (Dalush) and finds himself sharing a house with four incredibly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 01:35:00" d="2020-05-23 01:56:00"><n>Exploring Couples: Sheri Vi &amp; Nicolas</n>    <k>When the moment is right, it's time to take your romantic interests to the next level of passion by exploring the options. See what these couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 01:56:00" d="2020-05-23 02:12:00"><n>Perfect timing: Veronica Avluv &amp; Eric Masterson</n>    <k>Christina has a dilemma. She was swept off her feet by a much older man, but now things have cooled. She then meets a charming guy and very soon sparks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 02:12:00" d="2020-05-23 02:44:00"><n>Jungleicious: Luna Corazon &amp; Angelo Gotshack</n>    <k>The perfect spot, the perfect lady: Luna Corazon dances in the Jungle, waiting for Angelo to arrive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 02:44:00" d="2020-05-23 03:20:00"><n>Restraint 2: Aria Alexander &amp; Erik Everhard</n>    <k>After placing an ad in search of a dominant man, Valentina finds herself blindfolded and restrained in the home of a mysterious stranger. Although Aria?s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 03:20:00" d="2020-05-23 03:29:00"><n>Momentum 4: Alley</n>    <k>The fourth final and most epic adult film. The Volume 4 stage is set in the Australian desert - an aesthetic overthrow from the previous films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 03:29:00" d="2020-05-23 03:50:00"><n>Facade: Cassidy Klein</n>    <k>Amber and her friend Lindsay are average college students?who happen to moonlight as sexy webcam models. This complicates things when they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 03:50:00" d="2020-05-23 04:05:00"><n>Spectrophilia</n><t>S</t>    <k>See the ultimate taboo in this short all about supernatural fucking! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 04:05:00" d="2020-05-23 04:28:00"><n>Positions: Second</n>    <k>While finding inspiration at a dancer?s retreat, the ballet dancer Florence soon realises she?s not the only one who could do with practising</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 04:28:00" d="2020-05-23 04:51:00"><n>Breathless: Alessandra Noir &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>I get so breathless, when you call my name, I've often wondered, do you feel the same? There's a chemistry, energy, a synchronicity, between these lovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-23 04:51:00" d="2020-05-23 05:16:00"><n>Not to Innocent: Naomi Nevena &amp; Thomas Reed</n>    <k>A romantic sex film by Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous sex films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
</a>
