<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="64" t="2020-04-10 04:40:22"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 05:11:00" d="2020-04-17 05:37:00"><n>Passion Noir: Vinna &amp; Lutro</n>    <k>A fantastic new porn for women film from Roma Amor for Sinful XXX. The naked body as an art form and sex as a masterpiece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 05:37:00" d="2020-04-17 05:59:00"><n>Positions: Fourth</n>    <k>While finding inspiration at a dancer's retreat, the ballet dancer Florence soon realises she's not the only one who could do with practising</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 05:59:00" d="2020-04-17 06:25:00"><n>Making Ends Meet: Cheri Deville &amp; Jay Smooth</n>    <k>A suburbian family is in destress over money, but sex seems to really heal the wounds. Scorching hot sex and sharp comedy blend perfectly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 06:25:00" d="2020-04-17 06:49:00"><n>Summer</n>    <k>What a better refreshment in the middle of a hot hazy and sticky summer day than playing with some ice in front of a breezy fan and having loads of good sex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 06:49:00" d="2020-04-17 07:13:00"><n>Mother Daughter affair: Jodi Taylor &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>Eric has an interesting dilemma. He?s going with a smoking hot woman who has an over-sexed erotic devilish daughter, he just can?t resist</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 07:13:00" d="2020-04-17 07:37:00"><n>Come Closer: Summer Love</n>    <k>Feeling the summer? This couple is going outdoors to enjoy each other and make their time together worthwhile. A real couple having natural sex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 07:37:00" d="2020-04-17 08:03:00"><n>Sex in white: Erica Fontes &amp; Miquel Zayas</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us with her ?Sex In White? productions, where sexual encounters take place in a pure and white scenery, so the main focus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 08:03:00" d="2020-04-17 08:25:00"><n>Sweet but Psycho</n><t>S</t>    <k>Four of the hottest and most popular performers on the scene create a hilarious and erotic film. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 08:25:00" d="2020-04-17 08:48:00"><n>Right Now</n>    <k>A tranquil erotic scene from daily life. Densen knows exactly what would enhance this quiet morning, and she knows exactly when she wants it: &quot;Right Now.&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 08:48:00" d="2020-04-17 09:12:00"><n>He Loves To Watch: Aaliyah Love &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>This couple has found a unique way to keep the spark in their marriage. Passionate sex and powerful orgasms for everybody! Cuckold porn for women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 09:12:00" d="2020-04-17 09:37:00"><n>Sweet Petite Girls: Katy Rose &amp; Lutro</n>    <k>These young beauties are starting to discover their sexuality, exploring their bodies and seek new limits. Director Roman Sluka captured these teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 09:37:00" d="2020-04-17 09:55:00"><n>Close To The Bone: Loren Minard &amp; Sabby</n>    <k>Two immortal lovers are feeling the three-hundred-year-itch. As night falls the city becomes a playground for Jonus and Bryana, both seeking to quench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 09:55:00" d="2020-04-17 10:10:00"><n>Spectrophilia</n><t>S</t>    <k>See the ultimate taboo in this short all about supernatural fucking! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 10:10:00" d="2020-04-17 10:25:00"><n>Never Forgotten: Ella Nova &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>Robert can’t stop thinking about Elizabeth, his first love during the 1940’s. An argument teared the perfect couple apart and decades later Robert is still</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 10:25:00" d="2020-04-17 10:51:00"><n>Her Desire: Sleeping</n>    <k>Dusk TV presents: porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion. A pleasure to all the senses representing realistic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 10:51:00" d="2020-04-17 11:02:00"><n>My moaning neighbor</n><t>S</t>    <k>Your neighbor is always moaning out of pleasure, and quite loudly. What would you do? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 11:02:00" d="2020-04-17 11:23:00"><n>The Stepmother 6: April O’Niel &amp; Rocco Reed</n>    <k>When lonely widower Evan Stone announces he's become engaged son Rocco is eager to meet his stepmother-to-be. But Rocco's curiosity turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 11:23:00" d="2020-04-17 11:42:00"><n>Fit: Luke Hardy &amp; Jasmine Jae</n>    <k>You are running on the beach, bathed in the beautiful sunshine. You feel alive and energized ? what could be better? Get outside. Get active</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 11:42:00" d="2020-04-17 12:01:00"><n>Romeo &amp; Juliet: India Summer &amp; Tom Byron</n>    <k>Directed by Lee Roy Myers, this female friendly porn film by DreamZone Entertainment features tragic lovers trapped within a web of love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 12:01:00" d="2020-04-17 12:23:00"><n>Room 208: Penelope Cum &amp; Salva Da Silva</n>    <k>A female friendly sex video by Lara Tinelli for Dusk TV. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 12:23:00" d="2020-04-17 12:39:00"><n>Boat Buddies With Benefits</n>    <k>From XConfessions 3: Warning: mixing business with pleasure has orgasmic effects! In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 12:39:00" d="2020-04-17 13:00:00"><n>In The Limelight 1: Chris Johnson &amp; Lexi Belle</n><t>L</t>    <k>This female friendly porn film shows a spectacular selection of nine of their best scenes. In this scene the most beautiful couple surpasses your wildest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 13:00:00" d="2020-04-17 13:32:00"><n>Blind Date Swingers Club: Natalie Shirley &amp; Conway Bush</n>    <k>Everyone is getting their fuck on! Swinging couples going wild! It's Georgies turn to have a blind rendez-vous with one of the guys. Who will it be?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 13:32:00" d="2020-04-17 14:11:00"><n>Couples Massage: Vanessa Decker &amp; Ricky</n>    <k>A crackling fire, relaxing music and a lot of warm oil for a total body massage. Delicious. These beautiful couples can’t get enough of it too</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 14:11:00" d="2020-04-17 14:39:00"><n>Hair Down There: Tracey Sweet &amp; Anthony Rosano</n><t>L</t>    <k>She's got hair down there, and yes, we love that natural look! Let Mia Malkova, Nadine Sage, Tracey Sweet, and Anastasia Morna show you how their naturally</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 14:39:00" d="2020-04-17 14:53:00"><n>Thr3e</n>    <k>The threesome has always been a recurring fantasy in the imaginary of erotica. Sharing the pleasure with two other people, discovering their bodies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 14:53:00" d="2020-04-17 15:14:00"><n>Inside: Sicilia &amp; Juan Lucho</n>    <k>Welcome to The Retreat: where curious minds come to play. Plug in and turn on to explore a virtual reality experience where you can be anyone, go anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 15:14:00" d="2020-04-17 15:32:00"><n>Dacrifilia</n><t>S</t>    <k>An artist brings a man to tears to fulfil her fetish - dacryphilia. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 15:32:00" d="2020-04-17 15:53:00"><n>4 Passionate Women: Feeling Hot</n>    <k>A porn for women scene by Award Winning director Lara Tinelli for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit female friendly porn , sensuous films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 15:53:00" d="2020-04-17 16:19:00"><n>Facade: Edyn Blair &amp; James Deen</n>    <k>Amber and her friend Lindsay are average college students?who happen to moonlight as sexy webcam models. This complicates things when they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 16:19:00" d="2020-04-17 16:56:00"><n u="The Submission Of Emma Marx: Riley Reid &amp; Van Wylde">The Submission Of Emma Marx: Riley Reid &amp; Van Wylde (2)</n>    <k>When a new contract is drafted up defining the parameters of their BDSM relationship, Emma realizes that Mr. Frederick is anything but predictable</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 16:56:00" d="2020-04-17 17:14:00"><n>Strip Chess</n>    <k>Are you up for a chess game? Join Silvia Rubi and Gabe Romero in this intimate scene full of chemistry, where the game (and the increasing lack of clothes)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 17:14:00" d="2020-04-17 17:35:00"><n>Ball Control: Rebecca More &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>They say that football is a man’s world, but there’s one Milf on this pitch with all the power. Physio Eva puts her massage skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 17:35:00" d="2020-04-17 17:48:00"><n>A Talk Too Dirty</n><t>S</t>    <k>The power of dirty talk is a wonderful thing. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual confessions of her viewers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 17:48:00" d="2020-04-17 18:13:00"><n>Obedience</n>    <k>On a beautiful day a Spanish beauty gets a surprise phone call from a stranger. A man tells her exactly what to do to pleasure herself sexually</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 18:13:00" d="2020-04-17 18:49:00"><n>Private Spa: Renato &amp; Simony Diamond</n>    <k>This beautiful couple enjoys every bit of their private spa. We like it that hot! A delightful video by studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 18:49:00" d="2020-04-17 18:59:00"><n>Rush of the Forbidden</n><t>S</t>    <k>A sneaky rendezvous for a dose of sexy infidelity. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual confessions of her viewers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 18:59:00" d="2020-04-17 19:24:00"><n>Hollywood Ending: India Summer &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>Childhood lovers Rebecca and Tommy are finally getting the acting success they always wanted. But their love is put to the test when fame, fortune</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 19:24:00" d="2020-04-17 19:31:00"><n>Tactile</n>    <k>Their lips meet, their bodies meld, their fingers trace trails of sensation across flesh, they give in to pleasure. An erotic video full of desire and touch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 19:31:00" d="2020-04-17 19:58:00"><n>I Love You: Sarah Kay &amp; Angelo Godshack</n>    <k>These beautiful desireable men and women are highly confident and have all the experience to bring you in a state of trance. A romatic sex scene by Desire media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 19:58:00" d="2020-04-17 20:25:00"><n>Massage: Sunday morning</n>    <k>Some jobs have excellent benefits and for these guys. Sometimes you need that deep tissue technique that’s beyond skin deep. These hung studs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 20:25:00" d="2020-04-17 20:52:00"><n>My Wife's First Girlfriend: Dana Vespoli &amp; Melissa Moore</n>    <k>Jenna?s secret desires become unleashed when her husband catches her masturbating to lesbian porn. When Jimmy notices a growing attraction between</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 20:52:00" d="2020-04-17 21:00:00"><n>Momentum 4: Alley</n>    <k>The fourth final and most epic adult film. The Volume 4 stage is set in the Australian desert - an aesthetic overthrow from the previous films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 21:00:00" d="2020-04-17 21:31:00"><n>Lovers Tryst: Victoria Summers &amp; Max Deeds</n>    <k>5 Erotic scenes featuring the genuine sexual pleasure that real couples achieved when they have truly learned their way around each other's sensitive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 21:31:00" d="2020-04-17 21:58:00"><n>Beauty Of Nature: Cayla Lions &amp; Nick Larsen</n><t>L</t>    <k>Wondering what it take to have fantastic sex that you will remmeber for the rest of your life? Watch and learn as Desire Media shows you</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 21:58:00" d="2020-04-17 22:24:00"><n>Chef</n>    <k>After lessons in slicing, spicing, dicing, and sautéing, the class concludes with glasses of sparkling wine. They quickly make it clear that they're hungry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 22:24:00" d="2020-04-17 22:41:00"><n>Momentum 1: Backseat lovers</n>    <k>Australian film maker Michelle Flynn has the most distinctive style within the alternative porn genre. Her debut film Momentum is a cinematic intimacy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 22:41:00" d="2020-04-17 22:53:00"><n>That Guy At The Nudist Beach</n><t>S</t>    <k>Julia Roca and Bel Gris play a gorgeous Spanish couple, seducing each other on a deserted beach. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 22:53:00" d="2020-04-17 23:18:00"><n>My Love For you: Chrissy Fox &amp; Nic Vargas</n>    <k>Roma Woodcock for Dusk's Porn for women label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. A pleasure to all the senses representing real-life romantic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 23:18:00" d="2020-04-17 23:48:00"><n>Surreal Encounters: Aaron Rock &amp; Stacy Cruz</n>    <k>All Space &amp;Time Is Lost When Mysterious Lovers Meet. First there seems to be someone behind the mirror, then he's gone. Stacy looks closer and steps into an erotic dream</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 23:48:00" d="2020-04-17 23:58:00"><n>Tease</n>    <k>&quot;Tease&quot; is an erotic video shot from an straight female perspective, exploring the idea of playfulness in relationships. A porn for women film by Louise Lush</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-17 23:58:00" d="2020-04-18 00:31:00"><n>Matinée</n>    <k>Two theatre actors are not able to put on stage convincingly that they are each other?s lovers. Their careers are at stake so it?s time to stop acting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 00:31:00" d="2020-04-18 01:01:00"><n>Spicing up the Marriage: Kiera Nicole &amp; Ryan Mclane</n>    <k>When work and responsibility begin to pull a young couple apart, good old fashion love letters serve as the perfect remedy for their dry spell</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 01:01:00" d="2020-04-18 01:16:00"><n>From The First Moment: Alexa Grace &amp; Lucas Frost</n><t>L</t>    <k>What happens at the ranch, stays at the ranch. Unless wicked pictures show up to shoot the hottest porn for women featuring cowboys we can imagine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 01:16:00" d="2020-04-18 02:07:00"><n>An Arabian Night</n><t>L</t>    <k>Always wanted to know about anal sex, but never tried? This porn for women film shows how nice anal massage can be</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 02:07:00" d="2020-04-18 02:24:00"><n>Exposure: New MSG!</n>    <k>In a world where couples would rather play with their phones than each other, one woman uses her technology skills for good, nudging distracted lovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 02:24:00" d="2020-04-18 02:49:00"><n>Raw: Denisa &amp; Radek</n>    <k>Beautiful images of sexual tenderness in its pure but raw way. Close-ups of gorgeous toned bodies and horny sweat. One of Sinful?s most beautiful productions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 02:49:00" d="2020-04-18 03:12:00"><n>Love Lust Longing: Jessica Drake &amp; Kurt Lockwood</n>    <k>Love Lust &amp; Longing takes place in a seemingly innocent Bed &amp; Breakfast. Rachel a prostitute who has set up shop in the master bedroom falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 03:12:00" d="2020-04-18 03:34:00"><n>Kendo's Brunettes: Dominica Phoenix &amp; Renato</n>    <k>The Brunette. The classy, sexy alternative to the blonde. The lust filled mystery contained within the female character. A beautiful porn for women scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 03:34:00" d="2020-04-18 03:52:00"><n>4 Passionate Women: First Time</n>    <k>Dusk-tv presents: explicit porn for women and couples by Lara Tinelli. A pleasure to all the senses representing real-life sex full of intimacy, laughter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 03:52:00" d="2020-04-18 04:13:00"><n>Ball Control: Sienna Day &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>They say that football is a man’s world, but there’s one woman on this pitch with all the power. Physio Eva puts her massage skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 04:13:00" d="2020-04-18 04:39:00"><n>Tales from the Heart: Carter Cruise &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>Love is in the air. specially on your Anniversary. A trip down memory lane is just the spark Michelle and Andy need to reignite the lustful feelings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 04:39:00" d="2020-04-18 04:48:00"><n>Can Vampires Smell My Period?</n><t>S</t>    <k>This is no teenage dream. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual confessions of her viewers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-04-18 04:48:00" d="2020-04-18 05:07:00"><n>Corporate Bonding: Tamara Grace &amp; Max Deeds</n>    <k>Good teamwork can lead to surprising situations. Rookie lawyer Leyla organises a team-building weekend by the beach for her and her firm of London lawyers</k>  </p>
</a>
