<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="64" t="2020-05-30 04:43:43"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 05:27:00" d="2020-06-06 05:56:00"><n>My Love For you: Ana Rose &amp; Figi</n>    <k>A romantic film from Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 05:56:00" d="2020-06-06 06:21:00" c="1"><n>The Possession Of Mrs Hyde: Seth Gamble, Kenna James &amp; Victoria Voxxx</n><t>F</t>    <k>The Possession of Mrs. Hyde is Axel Braun's first non-parody feature in 15 years and his most ambitious movie to date. Shot entirely in Black and White</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 06:21:00" d="2020-06-06 06:32:00"><n>Be A Hero</n><t>S</t>    <k>Anneke woke up horny and spotted her boyfriend's go pro lying around. What will she do with it? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 06:32:00" d="2020-06-06 06:50:00"><n>Recipe for Romance: Gracie Glam &amp; Levi Cash</n>    <k>Love is cooking in Carolina's kitchen, and it's wonderfully delicious! Carolina is a passionate cook who is patiently waiting for Mr. Right. But what if Mr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 06:50:00" d="2020-06-06 07:12:00"><n>Sexy and Sensual: Dolce Vita &amp; Vega</n>    <k>These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A porn for women scene from Sexy and Sensual by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 07:12:00" d="2020-06-06 07:36:00"><n>Taste: Ava Dalush &amp; Antonio Black</n>    <k>Audrey is a talented and beautiful chef with a gift. She has the power to make her unsuspecting diners feel overwhelmingly amorous. She is one mouthful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 07:36:00" d="2020-06-06 07:58:00"><n>Pure Sexual Attraction: Bruce Venture &amp; Veronica Radke</n>    <k>Embark on an exciting journey of pure sexual attraction as five breathtaking girls are captured in five scenes that set the standard for high definition erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 07:58:00" d="2020-06-06 08:22:00"><n>Summer</n>    <k>What a better refreshment in the middle of a hot hazy and sticky summer day than playing with some ice in front of a breezy fan and having loads of good sex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 08:22:00" d="2020-06-06 08:52:00"><n>Connections: Aeryn Walker &amp; Theodore Dalton</n>    <k>Connections, celebrates all that?s great about sex: passion, laughter, teasing, giving, receiving, &amp; experiencing real pleasure. It?s about the connection</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 08:52:00" d="2020-06-06 09:13:00"><n>Sex and Lies: Nikki Peach &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>In the world of the ultra-rich, sex and lies reign supreme. Alisa (Avi Love)is a personal assistant who craves nothing more than order; difficult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 09:13:00" d="2020-06-06 09:24:00"><n>Titty Titty Bang Bang</n><t>S</t>    <k>Miriam Prado is feeling like dancing. Breasts will jiggle and sparks will fly. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 09:24:00" d="2020-06-06 09:45:00"><n>HouseMates: Satine Spark, Anna Darling &amp; Ryan Ryder</n>    <k>After a painful break up Jess flees to the city and is thrown into a world where hiding away is not an option. Her new housemates Ollie and Saskia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 09:45:00" d="2020-06-06 10:10:00"><n>Sweet Memories: Take Me Now</n>    <k>A hot romantic porn for women scene by Lara Tinelli for women who love rough sex with a guy who has a a big dick. A female friendly porn video by Dusk TV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 10:10:00" d="2020-06-06 10:39:00"><n>Black Sweat</n>    <k>Sinful interracial couples enjoy colorful erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 10:39:00" d="2020-06-06 11:10:00"><n>Exchange student 4: Tiffany Doll &amp; Alec Knight</n>    <k>Ben's been kicked out of his house because of his affair with an exchange student, so imagine his surprise when his buddy Alex and his wife Dana are taking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 11:10:00" d="2020-06-06 11:33:00"><n>Afternoon Delight: Alie Haze &amp; Marco Rivera</n>    <k>Attractive people that have sex on gorgeous locations. A scene from an Intimate Encounters film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 11:33:00" d="2020-06-06 11:57:00"><n>Sweet Petite Girls: Timea &amp; Jenny Appach</n>    <k>These young beauties are starting to discover their sexuality, exploring their bodies and seek new limits. Director Roman Sluka captured these teens</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 11:57:00" d="2020-06-06 12:11:00"><n>Never Forgotten: Katana &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>Robert can’t stop thinking about Elizabeth, his first love during the 1940’s. An argument teared the perfect couple apart and decades later Robert is still</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 12:11:00" d="2020-06-06 12:33:00"><n>Housemates 3: Morning Sex</n>    <k>Synopsis not available</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 12:33:00" d="2020-06-06 12:43:00"><n>Hysterical Piano Concert</n><t>S</t>    <k>A pianist's ultimate sexual fantasy is played out in an intimate concert that hits an exquisite note! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 12:43:00" d="2020-06-06 13:19:00"><n>Private Spa: Mugur &amp; Caroline de Jaie</n>    <k>This beautiful couple enjoys every bit of their private spa. We like it that hot! A delightful video by studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 13:19:00" d="2020-06-06 13:38:00"><n>Matchmaker: Satine Spark &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>Casey Collins is the Matchmaker. She can find anyone the perfect partner. The ultimate professional, Casey always puts her clients first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 13:38:00" d="2020-06-06 14:11:00"><n>True Intensions: Bentley &amp; Max Deeds</n>    <k>From director Anjali Kara comes True Intentions, romantic passion and beautiful sex. Watch the palpable chemistry between partners as they climax together onscreen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 14:11:00" d="2020-06-06 14:26:00"><n>Never Forgotten: Ella Nova &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>Robert can’t stop thinking about Elizabeth, his first love during the 1940’s. An argument teared the perfect couple apart and decades later Robert is still</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 14:26:00" d="2020-06-06 14:41:00"><n>Hit Me With Your Best Shot</n>    <k>Every time he grabs it he feels so strong, as if his virility depended on it. It starts to annoy me when he's been shooting at cans for an</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 14:41:00" d="2020-06-06 15:00:00"><n>HouseMates: Sicilia &amp; Sean</n>    <k>After a painful break up Jess flees to the city and is thrown into a world where hiding away is not an option. Her new housemates Ollie and Saskia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 15:00:00" d="2020-06-06 15:30:00"><n>Desire For Sex: Diner D'amour</n>    <k>A beautiful film by Roma Amor for SinfulXXX. In this scene a couple enjoys a delicious dinner. But when it's time for desert they themselves take place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 15:30:00" d="2020-06-06 15:46:00"><n>Connections: Leah &amp; Mal</n>    <k>Connections, celebrates all that?s great about porn for women: passion, laughter, teasing, giving, receiving, &amp; experiencing real pleasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 15:46:00" d="2020-06-06 15:58:00"><n>Romance Bullshit</n>    <k>From XConfessions 3: Every writer in the room types frantically, but she is just not inspired. Until she sees him. In XConfessions, people from all around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 15:58:00" d="2020-06-06 16:22:00"><n>Sex is for Lovers: Aleska Diamond &amp; Gery Taylor</n>    <k>Indulge yourself as four couples contribute with an emphasis on passion, lovers, and true romance. Their inspiration is not found in anonymous encounters</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 16:22:00" d="2020-06-06 16:42:00"><n>4 Passionate Women: Next To You</n>    <k>A romantic porn scene by Lara Tinelli for Dusk's Porna label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 16:42:00" d="2020-06-06 17:15:00"><n>Sex Sinners and Saints: Spiritual Desire</n>    <k>Not only is the church the perfect place to confess your sins, it's also the perfect location to have sensational sex. These couples sin in church, moaning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 17:15:00" d="2020-06-06 17:37:00"><n>Positions: First</n>    <k>While finding inspiration at a dancer?s retreat, the ballet dancer Florence soon realises she?s not the only one who could do with practising</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 17:37:00" d="2020-06-06 18:04:00"><n>Gentle Loving: Katarina &amp; Vega</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A female friendly porn scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 18:04:00" d="2020-06-06 18:20:00"><n>The Fantasy Project: Vivienne L, Max &amp; Harley Jay</n><t>L</t>    <k>Have you ever been in a threesome? These three lovers show what it could be like if your fantasies came true. This erotic video by Louise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 18:20:00" d="2020-06-06 18:47:00"><n>Friends And Lovers: Angela White &amp; Donny Rock</n>    <k>Caroline and Matt have been best friends since college. Through break-ups they've been there for each other. But they have yet to find true love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 18:47:00" d="2020-06-06 19:11:00"><n>My Girlfriends Mother 8: Julia Ann &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>When she gets caught in a compromising position with her professor, Sandi escapes with her boyfriend to her artistic free-spirit mother, Moon-Rose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 19:11:00" d="2020-06-06 19:19:00"><n>Carnival Hustlers</n><t>S</t>    <k>Two rival thieves take advantage of a Carnival to sneak around a Fifth Avenue inspired party, in disguise. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 19:19:00" d="2020-06-06 19:44:00"><n>Almost Relatives: Karla Kush &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>Things become heated between a bride and the best man when their explosive attraction to one another makes them question their loyalty to the groom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 19:44:00" d="2020-06-06 20:01:00"><n>Exposure: New MSG!</n>    <k>In a world where couples would rather play with their phones than each other, one woman uses her technology skills for good, nudging distracted lovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 20:01:00" d="2020-06-06 20:26:00"><n>Not to Innocent: Naomi Nevena &amp; Thomas Reed</n>    <k>A romantic sex film by Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous sex films depicting real excitement and passion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 20:26:00" d="2020-06-06 20:57:00"><n>Wet!: Color Me Wet</n>    <k>Sinful couples enjoy having seks when it pours? What's on your bucket list? A SinfulXXX film by Roma Amor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 20:57:00" d="2020-06-06 21:21:00"><n>Potter In Love</n>    <k>Today we are are getting creative with clay, a dirty and exciting endeavor! Porn for women by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 21:21:00" d="2020-06-06 21:42:00"><n>Sweet but Psycho</n><t>S</t>    <k>Four of the hottest and most popular performers on the scene create a hilarious and erotic film. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 21:42:00" d="2020-06-06 22:09:00"><n>Soft And Sweet 2: Ornella Morgen &amp; Nic Vargas</n><t>L</t>    <k>These young couples show you their most intimate experiences, see the excitement they both have to endure when they tease each other by kissing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 22:09:00" d="2020-06-06 22:27:00"><n>Camera Angle: Ivy Labelle &amp; Roman Nomar</n>    <k>Fiction and reality seem to blend when Hollywood actor Peter gets a concussion. His visions of heart-racing, sweat inducing sex seem very real though</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 22:27:00" d="2020-06-06 22:47:00"><n>Fit: Jasmine Aruba &amp; Sienna Day</n>    <k>You are running on the beach, bathed in the beautiful sunshine. You feel alive and energized ? what could be better? Get outside. Get active</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 22:47:00" d="2020-06-06 23:00:00"><n>The Ultimate Kink</n><t>S</t>    <k>An adventure with a female couple who have tried it all when it comes to sex - except for a man. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, kinky female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 23:00:00" d="2020-06-06 23:27:00"><n>Guide to Bondage For Couples: Samantha Ryan &amp; Michael Vegas</n>    <k>If Fifty Shades of Grey intrigued and inspired you, then get ready for Tristan Taormino's Guide to Bondage for Couples, an educational film for couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 23:27:00" d="2020-06-06 23:49:00"><n>Everyday Turn-Ons: Touchy-Feeley</n>    <k>Alone in her bedroom, Nora hears her neighbours fucking next door - and it's seriously hot. Pressing her ear to the wall, she begins to touch herself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 23:49:00" d="2020-06-07 00:20:00"><n>Momentum 4: Go for a walk</n>    <k>The fourth final and most epic adult film. The Volume 4 stage is set in the Australian desert - an aesthetic overthrow from the previous films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 00:20:00" d="2020-06-07 00:28:00"><n>Momentum 4: Alley</n>    <k>The fourth final and most epic adult film. The Volume 4 stage is set in the Australian desert - an aesthetic overthrow from the previous films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 00:28:00" d="2020-06-07 00:57:00"><n>Sweat On: Tina Kay &amp; Emilio Ardana</n>    <k>A Roma Amor sex film (suitable for watching together or alone) that proves that porn can really be BEAUTIFUL. Pure pleasure, beautiful, passionate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 00:57:00" d="2020-06-07 01:23:00"><n>Seven Days</n>    <k>This couple can have dramatic fights, but when they make up, it?s nothing but passion, lust and a bit of rough sex. An erotic sex scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 01:23:00" d="2020-06-07 01:40:00"><n>The Guesthouse: Bianca Resa &amp; Juan Lucho</n>    <k>Nestled in the Spanish countryside, there?s a Guesthouse where visitors enjoy more than just the sunshine on their bodies. Come alone, come with a friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 01:40:00" d="2020-06-07 02:08:00"><n>Anal Lovers: Liona &amp; Vega</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A realistic porn scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 02:08:00" d="2020-06-07 02:30:00"><n>Haunted Hearts: Michael Vegas &amp; Dana DeArmond</n>    <k>When a distant aunt dies her nice guy nephew inherits her estate. While settling into his palatial mansion he discovers sexual temptation family rivalry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 02:30:00" d="2020-06-07 03:02:00"><n>Home Coming: Home for Diner</n>    <k>Oh, home sweet home. These couples experience that there's no place like home to come back to, especially since orgasms are awaiting them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 03:02:00" d="2020-06-07 03:30:00"><n>Oasis: Ryan Diller &amp; Tasha Reign</n>    <k>A secluded oasis with design furniture appears to be the perfect place to have passionate sex. A scene from an Intimate Encounters film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 03:30:00" d="2020-06-07 03:53:00"><n>Momentum 2: Language of lust</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Momentum Volume. 2 lives up to it's predecessor, taking us back from the beach to the lazy Australian suburbs. Director Michelle Flynn retains the retro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 03:53:00" d="2020-06-07 04:13:00"><n>Friends And Lovers: Brett Rossi &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Caroline and Matt have been best friends since college. Through break-ups they've been there for each other. But they have yet to find true love</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 04:13:00" d="2020-06-07 04:29:00"><n>Birthday Surprise</n><t>S</t>    <k>It's Danny's birthday and Poppy has a big surprise prepared - he just needs to enjoy the show! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 04:29:00" d="2020-06-07 04:52:00"><n>Taste: Ava Dalush &amp; Jess West</n>    <k>Audrey is a talented and beautiful chef with a gift. She has the power to make her unsuspecting diners feel overwhelmingly amorous. She is one mouthful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-07 04:52:00" d="2020-06-07 05:22:00"><n>The Bedroom Chronicles: Natalie Blue &amp; Max Fonda</n>    <k>As women we all exactly know what kind of sex we want, need and prefer: 'sexy', 'sensual' and 'sophisticated' are the keywords as a prelude for great sex! These Chronicles from Daring! Pure are exactly as we want it. True porn for women</k>  </p>
</a>
