<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="61" t="2020-06-01 04:38:02"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 05:04:00" d="2020-06-08 05:15:00"><n>Before The Guests Arrive</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: Against the clock, this couple engage in a hot quickie before their dinner guests arrive! In XConfessions, people from all around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 05:15:00" d="2020-06-08 05:49:00"><n>My Hotwife's Lover: My Wife, The Sex Lover</n>    <k>Kristin's (Karla Kush) forbidden attraction to her husband's best friend reaches a breaking point when he arranges a private get-together</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 05:49:00" d="2020-06-08 06:14:00"><n>Our Sexual Secrets 2: Dolce Vita &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A porn for women scene from Our Sexual Secrets 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 06:14:00" d="2020-06-08 06:34:00"><n>Sex With Friends: Experience</n>    <k>When old college friends meet again they take the time to rekindle and explore each other?s bodies and sexual boundries. A reunion you don?t want to miss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 06:34:00" d="2020-06-08 06:52:00"><n>A Love Story</n>    <k>We meet Nataly and Franck as they get dressed to go out. In this case &quot;out&quot; means &quot;up&quot; and the love-struck couple enjoy the expansive views and a glass</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 06:52:00" d="2020-06-08 07:10:00"><n>Among The Bushes</n>    <k>He's always sitting in this park, surrounded by the trees, reading a book, cute and charismatic. He's big, tall and handsome. I'll take him between</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 07:10:00" d="2020-06-08 07:44:00"><n>Rob And Marina</n>    <k>For Dusk Academy, Michelle Flynn produced a few scenes with tips, tricks and ideas from the Dusk panel. This scene features Rob and Marina, a real life couple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 07:44:00" d="2020-06-08 08:01:00"><n>Love and Loss: Penny Pax &amp; Ramon Nomar</n>    <k>With more twists and turns than the German autobahn, Love and Loss follows the story of Lanie and Alex, an ex-cop involved in the shooting of Lanie's ex-lover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 08:01:00" d="2020-06-08 08:28:00"><n>Multiorgasmic Brunch</n><t>S</t>    <k>An explosive exploration of the possibilities for female pleasure; where the orgasms just never end. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 08:28:00" d="2020-06-08 08:53:00"><n>Inside: Frida Sante &amp; Alberta Blanco</n>    <k>Welcome to The Retreat: where curious minds come to play. Plug in and turn on to explore a virtual reality experience where you can be anyone, go anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 08:53:00" d="2020-06-08 09:24:00"><n>Come Closer: Friday Night</n>    <k>A real life straight couple with real life sex. A romantic porn video by Dusk TV's own porn for women label</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 09:24:00" d="2020-06-08 09:52:00"><n>Sexy And She Knows It: Lutro, Dorian Del Isla &amp; Anna Polina</n>    <k>Sinful trinity's enjoying a triad of erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 09:52:00" d="2020-06-08 10:20:00"><n>Forbidden Affairs 4: Logan Pierce &amp; Jade Nile</n>    <k>He is astounded by the drop-dead gorgeous girlfriend of his son. When she starts to flirt with him he can no longer resist the temptation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 10:20:00" d="2020-06-08 10:41:00"><n>Home alone: Carter Cruise &amp; August Ames</n>    <k>Remember being young and doing naughty things that under certain circumstances could get you grounded for a month? Weekend house parties</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 10:41:00" d="2020-06-08 11:08:00"><n>All For You: Lexi Lou &amp; Dan Daniels</n><t>L</t>    <k>Memories of special moments under the shower, become the seed of a new sexual encounter. All For You, the latest romantic porn release from Daring! Pure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 11:08:00" d="2020-06-08 11:22:00"><n>From Beyond: Aaliyah Love &amp; Jay Smooth</n><t>L</t>    <k>Romantic porn scene with a young couple fully in love. Let the beautiful Aaliyah Love &amp; Jay Smooth show you how they take care of eachothers needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 11:22:00" d="2020-06-08 11:40:00"><n>Sun stroke: Crowd control</n>    <k>When international DJ Cosmo needs a secluded escape, his boss? sun-kissed Spanish villa is the perfect location. Romantic outdoor pon for women by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 11:40:00" d="2020-06-08 11:50:00"><n>Parallel Universe</n><t>S</t>    <k>There is another world out there, a world where you can exist purely as a piece of furniture. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 11:50:00" d="2020-06-08 12:21:00"><n>Surreal Encounters: Aaron Rock &amp; Stacy Cruz</n>    <k>All Space &amp;Time Is Lost When Mysterious Lovers Meet. First there seems to be someone behind the mirror, then he's gone. Stacy looks closer and steps into an erotic dream</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 12:21:00" d="2020-06-08 12:40:00"><n>Housemates 2: Luke Hotrod &amp; Samantha Bentley</n>    <k>New house. New rules. Artist James moves to the UK in search of his ex-girlfriend (Dalush) and finds himself sharing a house with four incredibly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 12:40:00" d="2020-06-08 13:08:00"><n>I Love You: Sarah Kay &amp; Angelo Godshack</n>    <k>These beautiful desireable men and women are highly confident and have all the experience to bring you in a state of trance. A romatic sex scene by Desire media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 13:08:00" d="2020-06-08 13:33:00"><n>Sexual Situations: Kinky Sex</n>    <k>&quot;Wanna have sex?&quot; Gorgeous Gina Valentina takes the viewer through 5 sexy scenarios illustrating the various ways that people hook up -- Casual sex, kinky</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 13:33:00" d="2020-06-08 13:52:00"><n>Unwrap Me</n>    <k>Put the music on. And let yourself go wrapped in glossy vinyl bandages. Red and bright, that?s what excites me. Take them off quickly and fuck me</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 13:52:00" d="2020-06-08 14:13:00"><n>Delilahs Top Tips: Marc Rose &amp; Sicilia</n>    <k>Delilah is the nation's naughtiest agony aunt dedicated to solving the nation's more. ntimate dilemmas. A naughty female friendly porn scene by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 14:13:00" d="2020-06-08 14:34:00"><n>Passion Noir: Lexi &amp; Jason</n>    <k>A fantastic new female friendly porn film from Roma Amor for Sinful XXX. The naked body as an art form and sex as a masterpiece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 14:34:00" d="2020-06-08 14:47:00"><n>Momentum 2: Gardenwork</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Momentum Volume. 2 lives up to it's predecessor, taking us back from the beach to the lazy Australian suburbs. Director Michelle Flynn retains the retro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 14:47:00" d="2020-06-08 15:10:00"><n>Dude Looks Like A Lady</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: A girl gets a kick from dressing her boyfriend up as a lady. In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 15:10:00" d="2020-06-08 15:46:00"><n>Girl Next Door Likes It Dirty: Kennedy Leigh &amp; Chad White</n>    <k>All of these next door girls are young, free, and secretly wild who love it dirty! They all get their pussies passionately pulverized over the course</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 15:46:00" d="2020-06-08 16:14:00"><n>Her Desire: Shy Guy</n>    <k>Romantic porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting real excitement and passion. A pleasure to all the senses representing realistic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 16:14:00" d="2020-06-08 16:52:00"><n>The Artist: Max Deeds, Anna Rose &amp; Cherry Kiss</n>    <k>Another beautiful production by Studio Sinful, containing lots of close-ups, artistic lighting and delicious performers. In The Artist a man is sensually</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 16:52:00" d="2020-06-08 17:10:00"><n>HouseMates: Sicilia &amp; Satine Spark</n>    <k>After a painful break up Jess flees to the city and is thrown into a world where hiding away is not an option. Her new housemates Ollie and Saskia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 17:10:00" d="2020-06-08 17:36:00"><n>Intimate Moments: Leona &amp; Peter</n>    <k>Intimate moments for beautiful couples while exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A porn for women scene from Intimate Moments by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 17:36:00" d="2020-06-08 17:44:00"><n>Momentum 4: Sun on our skin</n>    <k>The fourth final and most epic adult film. The Volume 4 stage is set in the Australian desert - an aesthetic overthrow from the previous films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 17:44:00" d="2020-06-08 18:06:00"><n>Upon Further Reflection: Avi Love &amp; Derrick Pierce</n>    <k>Fiction writer, James Wharton (Ryan Mclane), is suffering from writers block and a drinking problem. His ex-wife is making his life a living</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 18:06:00" d="2020-06-08 18:31:00"><n>My Girlfriends Mother 8: Karla Kush &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>When she gets caught in a compromising position with her professor, Sandi escapes with her boyfriend to her artistic free-spirit mother, Moon-Rose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 18:31:00" d="2020-06-08 18:45:00"><n>Fräulein O</n><t>S</t>    <k>The unbearable August Spanish heat. who wouldn't be seduced by the local boy with a bucket full of ice! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 18:45:00" d="2020-06-08 19:23:00"><n>Remy's Angels: Remy Lacroix &amp; Dana Deomand</n>    <k>Watch the beautiful brunette Remy Lacroix explore her inner desires with some of her closest girlfriends in this all girl sexual adventure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 19:23:00" d="2020-06-08 19:44:00"><n>Close To The Bone: Cherry Kiss &amp; Matt Bird</n>    <k>Two immortal lovers are feeling the three-hundred-year-itch. As night falls the city becomes a playground for Jonus and Bryana, both seeking to quench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 19:44:00" d="2020-06-08 20:11:00"><n>Sensuous Seduction: Sweet</n>    <k>How sweet is your partner? A romantic sex film by Lara Tinelli for Dusk TV's own porn for women label: &quot;Ooh la la&quot;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 20:11:00" d="2020-06-08 20:47:00"><n>Blind Date Swingers Club: Tina Kay &amp; Lutro</n>    <k>Everyone is getting their fuck on! Swinging couples going wild!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 20:47:00" d="2020-06-08 21:11:00"><n>Two Girls Sofa</n>    <k>Two girls on a sofa, what else is there to do on a Sunday when you have nothing planned? These girls decide to explore each other's bodies? A lesbian porn for women scene byVerso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 21:11:00" d="2020-06-08 21:37:00"><n>My Love For you: Chrissy Fox &amp; Nic Vargas</n>    <k>Roma Woodcock for Dusk's Porn for women label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. A pleasure to all the senses representing real-life romantic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 21:37:00" d="2020-06-08 21:58:00"><n>Housemates 3: Good Company</n>    <k>Synopsis not available</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 21:58:00" d="2020-06-08 22:12:00"><n>Romeo &amp; Juliet: Chanel Preston &amp; Marie Rios</n>    <k>Romeo &amp; Juliet, maybe the most well known romantic couple. A sexy and spicy version of the traditional narrative. A porn for women flic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 22:12:00" d="2020-06-08 22:36:00"><n>After Forever: Alexa Grace &amp; Derrick Pierce</n>    <k>When Derrick plans a romantic weekend in his vacation house he soon finds out that his ex Penny had the same idea with her new partner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 22:36:00" d="2020-06-08 23:06:00"><n>So Wet Beside Her: Tina Kay &amp; Timea Bella</n>    <k>These girls love, lust, lick, becoming almost one in this sensual piece of erotica. Sinful Studio making art again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 23:06:00" d="2020-06-08 23:41:00"><n>Summer Lovers: Carla Coz</n>    <k>When it's summer the temperature rises, you wear less clothes and get aroused much easier. Is there anything hotter than having outdoor sex surrounded by nature? A scene from an Intimate Encounters film</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-08 23:41:00" d="2020-06-09 00:06:00"><n>Sex in white: Erica Fontes &amp; Miquel Zayas</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us with her ?Sex In White? productions, where sexual encounters take place in a pure and white scenery, so the main focus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-09 00:06:00" d="2020-06-09 00:21:00"><n>Win A Date With Sofia Blake: Charlotte Cross &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>A-list Hollywood actress Sofia Blake (Olivia Austin) is having the worst day of her life and the paparazzi have made sure to plaster</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-09 00:21:00" d="2020-06-09 00:37:00"><n>An Appointment With My Master</n><t>S</t>    <k>The honest and truthful relationship between a dominant and a submissive. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, kinky female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-09 00:37:00" d="2020-06-09 00:55:00"><n>Close To The Bone: Anya Olsen &amp; Loren Minardi</n>    <k>Two immortal lovers are feeling the three-hundred-year-itch. As night falls the city becomes a playground for Jonus and Bryana, both seeking to quench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-09 00:55:00" d="2020-06-09 01:17:00"><n>First Summer Love 2: Eliska &amp; Sweet Cat</n>    <k>The sequel of First Summer Love brings you more tantalizing scenes. The hot sun on their naked skin brings these girls in a state of permanent arousal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-09 01:17:00" d="2020-06-09 01:41:00"><n>Room 208: Julia Roca &amp; Sylvan Garcia</n>    <k>Would you like to be a pornstar? Watch how these beautiful performers reach full excitement and true pleasure. A beautiful porn for women film by Dusk TV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-09 01:41:00" d="2020-06-09 01:56:00"><n>From Beyond: Monka Mora &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>Sofia is mourning her beloved husband, but still feels him everywhere in their house. Is he haunting her for a reason? Her best friend helps Sofia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-09 01:56:00" d="2020-06-09 02:22:00"><n>Girls Fight Club</n><t>S</t>    <k>What's the first rule of girls fight club? Only women allowed. An homage to David Fincher’s classic dystopian film, this time with lesbians</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-09 02:22:00" d="2020-06-09 02:51:00"><n>Hair Down There: Tracey Sweet &amp; Anthony Rosano</n><t>L</t>    <k>She's got hair down there, and yes, we love that natural look! Let Mia Malkova, Nadine Sage, Tracey Sweet, and Anastasia Morna show you how their naturally</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-09 02:51:00" d="2020-06-09 03:19:00"><n>Soft And Sweet 2: Lady Dee &amp; Max D</n>    <k>Did you ever notice the softness of your lovers skin, the sweet taste when you move your tongue over her well formed sensual body? A porn for women film by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-09 03:19:00" d="2020-06-09 03:44:00"><n>Secret Sex Society: Sicilia &amp; Sylvan</n>    <k>When colourful people meet and share their colourful fantasies. Starring the hot blooded Spanish beauty Julia Roca</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-09 03:44:00" d="2020-06-09 04:13:00"><n>A Beautiful Solo 2: Abigail Grey</n>    <k>Tonight, these ladies are flying solo! Join them in their scenes of sweet female masturbation. Get ready to indulge in the art of self-pleasure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-09 04:13:00" d="2020-06-09 04:27:00"><n>Belle Dame Sans Merci</n>    <k>I met a lady in the meads, full beautiful - a faery's child, her hair was long, her foot was light, and her eyes were wild. Porn for women by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-09 04:27:00" d="2020-06-09 05:19:00"><n>An Arabian Night</n><t>L</t>    <k>Always wanted to know about anal sex, but never tried? This porn for women film shows how nice anal massage can be</k>  </p>
</a>
