<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="62" t="2020-05-29 04:35:31"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 05:14:00" d="2020-06-05 05:37:00"><n>Room 208: Sara May &amp; Juan Lucho</n>    <k>A romantic sex film by Lara Tinelli for Dusk's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films depicting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 05:37:00" d="2020-06-05 05:59:00"><n>Hollywood Ending: Karlee Grey &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>Childhood lovers Rebecca and Tommy are finally getting the acting success they always wanted. But their love is put to the test when fame, fortune</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 05:59:00" d="2020-06-05 06:27:00"><n>I'm Obsessed with Owen Gray</n><t>S</t>    <k>What would happen if your first time having sex on screen was with a pornstar you were totally obsessed with? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 06:27:00" d="2020-06-05 06:50:00"><n>Recipe for Romance: Allie Haze &amp; Johnny Castle</n>    <k>Love is cooking in Carolina's kitchen, and it's wonderfully delicious! Carolina is a passionate cook who is patiently waiting for Mr. Right. But what if Mr</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 06:50:00" d="2020-06-05 07:12:00"><n>Just You &amp; Me: Silvie DeLuxe &amp; Miela</n>    <k>Sensual girl on girl sex is highly erotic to watch, and even more so for the stunning girls here who want to please their lover. A female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 07:12:00" d="2020-06-05 07:37:00"><n>Sex With Friends: Dessert</n>    <k>When old college friends meet again they take the time to rekindle and explore each other?s bodies and sexual boundries. A reunion you don?t want to miss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 07:37:00" d="2020-06-05 07:56:00"><n>Second Chances: Allie Haze &amp; Chad White</n>    <k>During her Freshman year of college, Madison thought she'd met the love of her life when she starting dating handsome football player, Josh. This didn't work out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 07:56:00" d="2020-06-05 08:18:00"><n>Milk</n>    <k>What kind of Milk are you drinking today? A romantic porn video featuring pornstar Julia Roca by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 08:18:00" d="2020-06-05 08:40:00"><n>Girls Sex Tricks: Carol Vega &amp; Didac Durán</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us on her first female friendly porn film as director for Thagson with a vibrant story which will take place in the streets of Barcelona</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 08:40:00" d="2020-06-05 09:09:00"><n>Hollywood Ending: India Summer &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>Childhood lovers Rebecca and Tommy are finally getting the acting success they always wanted. But their love is put to the test when fame, fortune</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 09:09:00" d="2020-06-05 09:31:00"><n>Horngry</n><t>S</t>    <k>Food and sex combine in a delicious foursome from Erika Lust's XConfessions series! From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 09:31:00" d="2020-06-05 09:57:00"><n>Secret Sex Society: Julia De Lucia &amp; Bishop Black</n>    <k>When colourful people meet and share their colourful fantasies. Starring the hot blooded Spanish beauty Julia Roca</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 09:57:00" d="2020-06-05 10:22:00"><n>Obedience</n>    <k>On a beautiful day a Spanish beauty gets a surprise phone call from a stranger. A man tells her exactly what to do to pleasure herself sexually</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 10:22:00" d="2020-06-05 10:56:00"><n>Sexy Massage Fantasies: Sinful Massage</n>    <k>A beautiful sensual film by Roma Amor for SinfulXXX. In this scene a couple explores just how sinful a relaxing massage can be. Sexual massages are hot!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 10:56:00" d="2020-06-05 11:31:00"><n>The Teacher 4: Kastie St. Ives &amp; Joey Brass</n>    <k>Physicist Manuel Ferrara is on the verge of solving physics? biggest mysteries, and smitten young students treat him like a rock star. Obsessive young</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 11:31:00" d="2020-06-05 12:05:00"><n>All In Your Head: Keisha Grey &amp; Seth Gamble</n><t>O</t>    <k>All In Your Head transcends expectations with its striking imagery and brilliant creative direction. There is something for everyone's perverted minds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 12:05:00" d="2020-06-05 12:27:00"><n>Kendo's Brunettes: Dominica Phoenix &amp; Renato</n>    <k>The Brunette. The classy, sexy alternative to the blonde. The lust filled mystery contained within the female character. A beautiful porn for women scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 12:27:00" d="2020-06-05 12:50:00"><n>Love and Loss: Maddy O'Reilly &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>With more twists and turns than the German autobahn, Love and Loss follows the story of Lanie and Alex, an ex-cop involved in the shooting of Lanie's ex-lover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 12:50:00" d="2020-06-05 13:11:00"><n>Close To The Bone: Loren Minard &amp; Sabby</n>    <k>Two immortal lovers are feeling the three-hundred-year-itch. As night falls the city becomes a playground for Jonus and Bryana, both seeking to quench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 13:11:00" d="2020-06-05 13:21:00"><n>Wine Is The Best Lubricant</n><t>S</t>    <k>A french wine lover walks into a wine shop looking for something to taste. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 13:21:00" d="2020-06-05 13:55:00"><n>Wet!: A Wet Suprise</n>    <k>Sinful couples enjoy having seks when it pours? What's on your bucket list? A SinfulXXX film by Roma Amor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 13:55:00" d="2020-06-05 14:18:00"><n>Housemates 3: Decoupled</n>    <k>Synopsis not available</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 14:18:00" d="2020-06-05 14:43:00"><n>Gentle Loving 2: Tequila &amp; Vincent Vega</n>    <k>These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. An erotic sex scene from Favorite Fantasies 2 by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 14:43:00" d="2020-06-05 14:59:00"><n>Red Light: Bree Daniels &amp; Skin Diamond</n>    <k>Red Light is like a waking dream set in the streets of Los Angeles. It's the story of a woman's transformation into her true self, and a wild chase</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 14:59:00" d="2020-06-05 15:17:00"><n>K</n>    <k>Inspiration can reach us when we are less expecting it. The simple vision of a white sheet of paper stresses me a bit as I am a writer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 15:17:00" d="2020-06-05 15:37:00"><n>Close To The Bone: Anya Olsen &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>Two immortal lovers are feeling the three-hundred-year-itch. As night falls the city becomes a playground for Jonus and Bryana, both seeking to quench</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 15:37:00" d="2020-06-05 15:58:00"><n>Make Me Sweat: Nathaly &amp; Angelo</n>    <k>Nathaly &amp; Angelo's beautiful bodies are the centerpiece of this incredibly hot erotic scene by Sinful XXX. Super sexy female friendly porn with super sexy performers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 15:58:00" d="2020-06-05 16:17:00"><n>Sex in white: Amirah Adara &amp; Adrian Yuyu</n>    <k>Lara Tinelli seduces us with her female friendly porn production: ?Sex In White?, where sexual encounters take place in a pure and white scenery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 16:17:00" d="2020-06-05 16:31:00"><n>Latex Sessions</n><t>S</t>    <k>Parker Marx and Amarna Miller feature in this steamy homage to latex and the psychology of fetishism. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 16:31:00" d="2020-06-05 16:49:00"><n>Weekend: Katy Rose &amp; Lutro</n><t>L</t>    <k>Shot in Portugal, episode 3 of The Weekend, &quot;Lust,&quot; shows it's getting close to dinnertime and the three couples are drinking wine and chatting amiably</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 16:49:00" d="2020-06-05 17:12:00"><n>Her Desire: The Couch</n>    <k>A great scene by AlexanFilm for Dusk's Porn for women label: Ooh la la. Explicit erotic films for women and couples</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 17:12:00" d="2020-06-05 17:49:00"><n>Sexy Massage Fantasies: Smooth Seduction</n>    <k>A beautiful sensual film by Roma Amor for SinfulXXX. In this scene the combination of a blindfold and lots of oil prove to be the perfect ingredients</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 17:49:00" d="2020-06-05 18:11:00"><n>Everyday Turn-Ons: Restricted Behaviour</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sometimes we don?t choose our fetishes; they find us in the night. Gavin wakes up to find Mary has stolen the covers and is cocooned inside the sheets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 18:11:00" d="2020-06-05 18:42:00"><n>Soft And Sweet 2: Vanessa Decker &amp; Dean</n><t>L</t>    <k>These young couples show you their most intimate experiences, see the excitement they both have to endure when they tease each other by kissing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 18:42:00" d="2020-06-05 19:06:00"><n>Momentum 1: Before dinner</n>    <k>Australian film maker Michelle Flynn has the most distinctive style within the alternative porn genre. Her debut film Momentum is a cinematic intimacy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 19:06:00" d="2020-06-05 19:30:00"><n>He Loves To Watch: India Summer &amp; Tommy Pistol</n>    <k>This couple has found a unique way to keep the spark in their marriage. Passionate sex and powerful orgasms for everybody!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 19:30:00" d="2020-06-05 19:58:00"><n>The Stepmother 14: Keisha Grey &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>Andrew is mad at his dad when he misses out on important stuff to take care of his step-mother who broke her leg. Until he realizes how hot and sensual she is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 19:58:00" d="2020-06-05 20:10:00"><n>Power Pussy</n><t>S</t>    <k>Two Power Pussies take on and dominate the burly Dean Van Damme, all in From Dawn Til Dawn style. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 20:10:00" d="2020-06-05 20:35:00"><n>Love is in the Air: Jenna J Ross &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>When her fiance gets sucked into never-ending conversation at a friend's party, a woman lures him to the bedroom for a passionate sexual encounter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 20:35:00" d="2020-06-05 20:53:00"><n>HouseMates: Chessie Kay &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>After a painful break up Jess flees to the city and is thrown into a world where hiding away is not an option. Her new housemates Ollie and Saskia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 20:53:00" d="2020-06-05 21:20:00"><n>My Cam Model</n>    <k>The Portuguese Jesus sees his dreams come true when his favorite hot webcam girl invites him to comeÂ. t her house. A naughty porn for women film, watch if you like big dick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 21:20:00" d="2020-06-05 21:48:00"><n>Our Summer of Love: Sienna Day &amp; Mugur</n>    <k>A hot couple travels abroad and adores the new country, but they enjoy each other even more and especially the new sexy people they meet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 21:48:00" d="2020-06-05 22:03:00"><n>Belle Dame Sans Merci</n>    <k>I met a lady in the meads, full beautiful - a faery's child, her hair was long, her foot was light, and her eyes were wild. Porn for women by Verso Cinema</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 22:03:00" d="2020-06-05 22:19:00"><n>Memory Files of You</n><t>S</t>    <k>A deeply moving ode to loves lost, and irrevocable, unobtainable desires through Virtual Reality. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 22:19:00" d="2020-06-05 22:44:00"><n>Beautiful Young Couples: Jessica Malone &amp; Leo Dee</n>    <k>Soft and sweet but also intoxicatingly seductive. These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A erotic scene from Beautiful Young</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 22:44:00" d="2020-06-05 23:09:00"><n>He Loves To Watch: Penny Pax &amp; Van Wyle</n>    <k>This couple has found a unique way to keep the spark in their marriage. Passionate sex and powerful orgasms for everybody! Cuckolding porn with focus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 23:09:00" d="2020-06-05 23:21:00"><n>It's Complicated: Olivia Austin &amp; Stephen StCroix</n>    <k>Shauna (Gracie Glam) has been having casual sex with her handsome friend Will, biding her time until she can finally make a move on her long time crush Brandon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 23:21:00" d="2020-06-05 23:40:00"><n>4 Passionate Women: First Time</n>    <k>Dusk-tv presents: explicit porn for women and couples by Lara Tinelli. A pleasure to all the senses representing real-life sex full of intimacy, laughter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-05 23:40:00" d="2020-06-06 00:07:00"><n>True Intensions: Victoria Summers &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>From director Anjali Kara comes True Intentions, romantic passion and beautiful sex. Watch the palpable chemistry between partners as they climax together onscreen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 00:07:00" d="2020-06-06 00:40:00"><n>Matinée</n>    <k>Two theatre actors are not able to put on stage convincingly that they are each other?s lovers. Their careers are at stake so it?s time to stop acting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 00:40:00" d="2020-06-06 01:07:00"><n>In The Limelight 1: Giovanni Francesco &amp; Shazia Sahari</n><t>L</t>    <k>Daring! Pure?s film ?In the Limelight? shows a spectacular selection of nine of their best scenes. The most beautiful couples surpass your wildest dreams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 01:07:00" d="2020-06-06 01:35:00"><n>Sensuous Seduction: In the Evening</n>    <k>A scene from a romantic sex film by Lara Tinelli for Dusk TV's female friendly porn label: Ooh la la. Explicit porn for women and couples. Sensuous films</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 01:35:00" d="2020-06-06 01:55:00"><n>Inside: Sicilia &amp; Juan Lucho</n>    <k>Welcome to The Retreat: where curious minds come to play. Plug in and turn on to explore a virtual reality experience where you can be anyone, go anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 01:55:00" d="2020-06-06 02:37:00"><n>True Intensions: Ava Dalush &amp; Ben Kelly</n>    <k>From director Anjali Kara comes True Intentions, romantic passion and beautiful sex. Watch the palpable chemistry between partners as they climax together onscreen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 02:37:00" d="2020-06-06 02:55:00"><n>From The First Moment: Alix Lynx &amp; Robby Echo</n>    <k>Kira (Alix Lynx) is about to marry her handsome movie star boyfriend James except he gets cold feet and leaves her at the wedding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 02:55:00" d="2020-06-06 03:30:00"><n>Paparazzi: Tiffany Doll &amp; Angelo Godshack</n>    <k>Brandi Love, Paparazzi, a Scandalous Red Carpet Tale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 03:30:00" d="2020-06-06 03:49:00"><n>Brave Hearts: Rocco Reed &amp; Faye Reagan</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sarah (Faye Regan), the most famous Romance Novelist in the world, is writing the final book in her series of best-selling love stories. Admired by women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 03:49:00" d="2020-06-06 04:06:00"><n>Momentum 1: Backseat lovers</n>    <k>Australian film maker Michelle Flynn has the most distinctive style within the alternative porn genre. Her debut film Momentum is a cinematic intimacy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 04:06:00" d="2020-06-06 04:22:00"><n>It's Complicated: Gracie Glam &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>Shauna (Gracie Glam) has been having casual sex with her handsome friend Will, biding her time until she can finally make a move on her long time crush Brandon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 04:22:00" d="2020-06-06 04:34:00"><n>Dominate Me</n><t>S</t>    <k>This beautiful and intense film explores the intimacy of BDSM, carefully capturing every little detail. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 04:34:00" d="2020-06-06 04:58:00"><n>Inside: Julia Roca &amp; Anneke Necro</n>    <k>Welcome to The Retreat: where curious minds come to play. Plug in and turn on to explore a virtual reality experience where you can be anyone, go anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-06-06 04:58:00" d="2020-06-06 05:27:00"><n>Illicit Affairs: Vanessa Decker &amp; Elis Gilbert</n>    <k>A relationship often starts with lots of passion and fun. But once the boredom sets in a prohibited affair can just rise up! These girls mix</k>  </p>
</a>
