<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="63" t="2020-05-17 04:38:06"><p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 05:04:00" d="2020-05-24 05:25:00"><n>Love and Loss: Penny Pax &amp; Ramon Nomar</n>    <k>With more twists and turns than the German autobahn, Love and Loss follows the story of Lanie and Alex, an ex-cop involved in the shooting of Lanie's ex-lover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 05:25:00" d="2020-05-24 05:37:00"><n>A Feminist Man</n><t>S</t>    <k>Is there anything sexier than a man who can give perfect cunnilingus and have a conversation about Judith Butler? From the XConfessions series by Erika</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 05:37:00" d="2020-05-24 05:58:00"><n>Brave Hearts: Steve Q &amp; Kate</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sarah (Faye Regan), the most famous Romance Novelist in the world, is writing the final book in her series of best-selling love stories. Admired by women</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 05:58:00" d="2020-05-24 06:20:00"><n>Sexy and Sensual: Dolce Vita &amp; Vega</n>    <k>These beautiful couples are exploring eachothers bodies and desires. A porn for women scene from Sexy and Sensual by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 06:20:00" d="2020-05-24 06:38:00"><n>Delilahs Top Tips: Lynna Nilsson &amp; Clarke Kent</n><t>O</t>    <k>Delilah is the nation's naughtiest agony aunt dedicated to solving the nation's more. ntimate dilemmas. She whips two city workers into a frenzy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 06:38:00" d="2020-05-24 07:06:00"><n>Second Chances: Jessa Rhodes &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>During her Freshman year of college, Madison thought she'd met the love of her life when she starting dating handsome football player, Josh. This didn't work out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 07:06:00" d="2020-05-24 07:24:00"><n>Come With Me</n>    <k>Come with me, or cum with me? An super sexy female friendly porn film by Verso Cinema with breathtaking orgasms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 07:24:00" d="2020-05-24 07:34:00"><n>The Bathhouse</n><t>L</t>    <k>Always wanted to know about anal sex, but never tried? This film shows how nice anal massage can be. A romantic porn film full of bubbles and soap</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 07:34:00" d="2020-05-24 07:49:00"><n>From Beyond: Monka Mora &amp; Marcus London</n>    <k>Sofia is mourning her beloved husband, but still feels him everywhere in their house. Is he haunting her for a reason? Her best friend helps Sofia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 07:49:00" d="2020-05-24 07:57:00"><n>My Roomie’s Toy</n><t>S</t>    <k>A young woman innocently looking for a phone charger stumbles across her roommate's sex toy. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 07:57:00" d="2020-05-24 08:16:00"><n>The Invitation: Luke Hotrod, Ava Austen &amp; Carly Rae</n>    <k>Jane and Tom decide to pack the kids off and book a romantic weekend away. When their car unexpectedly breaks down late at night they find themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 08:16:00" d="2020-05-24 08:40:00"><n>Come Closer: Summer Love</n>    <k>Feeling the summer? This couple is going outdoors to enjoy each other and make their time together worthwhile. A real couple having natural sex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 08:40:00" d="2020-05-24 09:22:00"><n>Light my Fire: Max Deeds &amp; Angel Wicky</n>    <k>This beautiful couple relishes each others body with sensual hand and mouth massages by candlelight. Another visual and erotic jewel by Studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 09:22:00" d="2020-05-24 09:52:00"><n>Remy Loves Girls: Sovereign Syre &amp; Remy LaCroix</n>    <k>Sweetheart proudly presents Performer of the year Remy La Croix. In the tradition of this title, Remy has chosen four of her favorite girls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 09:52:00" d="2020-05-24 10:16:00"><n>The Temptation Of Eve: India Summer &amp; Xander Corvus</n>    <k>Thrust into an uncomfortable circumstance, Eve (Remy LaCroix) finds herself living under the same roof as Brandon (the man she shared the most intense</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 10:16:00" d="2020-05-24 10:27:00"><n>In The Limelight 1: Lexi Belle</n><t>L</t>    <k>Daring! Pure?s film ?In the Limelight? shows a spectacular selection of nine of their best scenes. The most beautiful couples surpass your wildest dreams</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 10:27:00" d="2020-05-24 10:48:00"><n>Sex and Lies: Nikki Peach &amp; Logan Pierce</n>    <k>In the world of the ultra-rich, sex and lies reign supreme. Alisa (Avi Love)is a personal assistant who craves nothing more than order; difficult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 10:48:00" d="2020-05-24 11:09:00"><n>Quartet: Controlled</n>    <k>Penelope boards a plane from London to Budapest, eager to perform with her three best friends from music academy. Reunited, the foursome soon remind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 11:09:00" d="2020-05-24 11:20:00"><n>Titty Titty Bang Bang</n><t>S</t>    <k>Miriam Prado is feeling like dancing. Breasts will jiggle and sparks will fly. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 11:20:00" d="2020-05-24 12:00:00"><n>Light my Fire: Daphne Klyde &amp; Steve Q</n>    <k>This beautiful couple relishes each others body with sensual hand and mouth massages by candlelight. Another visual and erotic jewel by Studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 12:00:00" d="2020-05-24 12:25:00"><n>Inside: Julia Roca &amp; Natalia Ferrari</n>    <k>Welcome to The Retreat: where curious minds come to play. Plug in and turn on to explore a virtual reality experience where you can be anyone, go anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 12:25:00" d="2020-05-24 12:54:00"><n>Soft And Sweet 2: Vinna Reed &amp; Nick Ross</n>    <k>Did you ever notice the softness of your lovers skin, the sweet taste when you move your tongue over her well formed sensual body? A porn for women film by Desire Media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 12:54:00" d="2020-05-24 13:08:00"><n>From Beyond: Chanel Preston &amp; Ryan Mclane</n>    <k>Sofia is mourning her beloved husband, but still feels him everywhere in their house. Is he haunting her for a reason? Her best friend helps Sofia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 13:08:00" d="2020-05-24 13:28:00"><n>Ouija</n>    <k>My girlfriend asked me to play with a Ouija board tonight. I?m dying to have some wild sex here on the floor. Let?s ask the ghosts what they think about it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 13:28:00" d="2020-05-24 13:49:00"><n>Ball Control: Sienna Day &amp; Jess West</n>    <k>They say that football is a man’s world, but these two women on this pitch hold all the power. A romantic lesbian porn scene by Joybear</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 13:49:00" d="2020-05-24 14:24:00"><n>The Artist: Max Deeds, Anna Rose &amp; Cherry Kiss</n>    <k>Another beautiful production by Studio Sinful, containing lots of close-ups, artistic lighting and delicious performers. In The Artist a man is sensually</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 14:24:00" d="2020-05-24 14:50:00"><n>Oral Reflections</n><t>L</t>    <k>Always wanted to know about anal sex, but never tried? This romantic porn film shows how nice anal massage can be</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 14:50:00" d="2020-05-24 15:06:00"><n>The Couchsurfer</n>    <k>From XConfessions 2: Making the most of your house guests has never been so sexy. In XConfessions, people from all around the world send their sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 15:06:00" d="2020-05-24 15:26:00"><n>Second Chances: Carter Cruise &amp; Brendon Miller</n>    <k>During her Freshman year of college, Madison thought she'd met the love of her life when she starting dating handsome football player, Josh. This didn't work out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 15:26:00" d="2020-05-24 15:48:00"><n>The Party</n>    <k>A breasty Spanish beauty can’t get any sleep because of the loud party next door. But when she sees her attractive neighbor her angry feelings fade away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 15:48:00" d="2020-05-24 16:17:00"><n>Sexy And She Knows It: Lutro, Dorian Del Isla &amp; Anna Polina</n>    <k>Sinful trinity's enjoying a triad of erotica</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 16:17:00" d="2020-05-24 16:35:00"><n>Matchmaker: Satine Spark &amp; Luke Hotrod</n>    <k>Casey Collins is the Matchmaker. She can find anyone the perfect partner. The ultimate professional, Casey always puts her clients first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 16:35:00" d="2020-05-24 17:03:00"><n>I Love You: Arian Joy &amp; Nick Vargas</n>    <k>These beautiful desireable men and women are highly confident and have all the experience to bring you in a state of trance. A porn for women film by Desire media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 17:03:00" d="2020-05-24 17:45:00"><n>Jade And Tommy</n>    <k>Jade and Tommy are a real-life couple and can't keep their hands off each other. This female friendly porn video captures their epic lovemaking session</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 17:45:00" d="2020-05-24 18:03:00"><n>Trouble X 2: Abigail Mac &amp; Damon Dice</n>    <k>On his first day back in the dating game, Nick meets not one but TWO beautiful women. Olivia (Abigail Mac) is hot, sexy, and confident. Jenny (Cherie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 18:03:00" d="2020-05-24 18:37:00"><n>Dani Loves Girls: Dani Daniels &amp; Natasha Nice</n><t>L</t>    <k>Sweetheart Video presents the beautiful Dani Daniels in her own movie. Dani showcases her sensuality and voracious appetite in four scenes;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 18:37:00" d="2020-05-24 18:47:00"><n>Dear Brother In Law</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lana is the perfect bourgeois wife who ends up feeling attracted by her messy brother-in-law. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 18:47:00" d="2020-05-24 19:14:00"><n>Hall Pass: Cherie De Ville &amp; Ryan McLane</n>    <k>With her husband's blessing, Anikka indulges in an afternoon seduction with a long time crush. Cherie's husband is eager to help her overcome her sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 19:14:00" d="2020-05-24 19:36:00"><n>Inside: Kali Sudhra &amp; Miguel Zayas</n>    <k>Welcome to The Retreat: where curious minds come to play. Plug in and turn on to explore a virtual reality experience where you can be anyone, go anywhere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 19:36:00" d="2020-05-24 20:03:00"><n>Breakfast for Two</n>    <k>These girlfriends just wanna have fun. With each other. Especially while having a sleepover. A female friendly porn production by Dusk porn-TV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 20:03:00" d="2020-05-24 20:35:00"><n>Colors Of Eden: Cecilia Scott &amp; Angelo</n><t>L</t>    <k>A gorgeous couple having breathtakingly hot sex, in colorful surroundings, showing both intimacy and sexual fulfilment in every little detail</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 20:35:00" d="2020-05-24 20:54:00"><n>Heavy Contact</n>    <k>That feeling when you have a lot of contact with someone and the connection gets even heavier when you meet in real life? Yes, that's passion to the max</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 20:54:00" d="2020-05-24 21:08:00"><n>La Reine Des Culottes</n><t>S</t>    <k>A woman's lingerie can say a lot about her - and about her neighbour. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 21:08:00" d="2020-05-24 21:40:00"><n>I Love You: Antonia Sainz &amp; Ricky</n>    <k>These beautiful desireable men and women are highly confident and have all the experience to bring you in a state of trance. A female friendly porn film by Desire media</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 21:40:00" d="2020-05-24 22:05:00"><n>The Escort 2: Presley Hart &amp; Seth Gamble</n>    <k>When a beautiful young woman enters the escorting profession, she's put off by her first client. But under the tutelage of a smart and capable madam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 22:05:00" d="2020-05-24 22:29:00"><n>Taste: Jasmine Jae &amp; Ryan Ryder</n>    <k>Audrey is a talented and beautiful chef with a gift. She has the power to make her unsuspecting diners feel overwhelmingly amorous. She is one mouthful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 22:29:00" d="2020-05-24 22:40:00"><n>Wine Is The Best Lubricant</n><t>S</t>    <k>A french wine lover walks into a wine shop looking for something to taste. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 22:40:00" d="2020-05-24 22:47:00"><n>Momentum 1: A day at the beach</n>    <k>Australian film maker Michelle Flynn has the most distinctive style within the alternative porn genre. Her debut film Momentum is a cinematic intimacy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 22:47:00" d="2020-05-24 23:15:00"><n>Come Closer: My Sunny Side</n>    <k>What are you going to do when all of a suddon both of you are at home and have nothing to do? Exactly, enjoy each other and make your time together worthwhile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 23:15:00" d="2020-05-24 23:43:00"><n>Jungleicious: Stacy Cruz &amp; Mugur</n>    <k>In a dream, Antonia goes out in the woods. She finds her love, sleeping and waiting for her to touch him. First softly, then firm</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-24 23:43:00" d="2020-05-25 00:03:00"><n>The Ski Instructor</n><t>S</t>    <k>Baby, it's cold outside. Who doesn't want to sleep with their ski instructor? From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly porn created</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-25 00:03:00" d="2020-05-25 00:33:00"><n>Soft And Sweet 2: Ornella Morgen &amp; Nic Vargas</n><t>L</t>    <k>These young couples show you their most intimate experiences, see the excitement they both have to endure when they tease each other by kissing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-25 00:33:00" d="2020-05-25 01:05:00"><n>The Escort 2: Lilly Love, Dana DeArmond &amp; Tyler Nixon</n>    <k>When a beautiful young woman enters the escorting profession, she's put off by her first client. But under the tutelage of a smart and capable madam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-25 01:05:00" d="2020-05-25 01:43:00"><n>Light my Fire: Dominica Phoenix &amp; Kristof Cale</n>    <k>This beautiful couple relishes each others body with sensual hand and mouth massages by candlelight. Another visual and erotic jewel by Studio Sinful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-25 01:43:00" d="2020-05-25 02:16:00"><n>Restraint 2: Ryan Driller &amp; Valentina Nappi</n>    <k>After placing an ad in search of a dominant man, Valentina finds herself blindfolded and restrained in the home of a mysterious stranger. Although Aria?s</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-25 02:16:00" d="2020-05-25 02:38:00"><n>Momentum 2: Language of lust</n><t>Z</t>    <k>Momentum Volume. 2 lives up to it's predecessor, taking us back from the beach to the lazy Australian suburbs. Director Michelle Flynn retains the retro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-25 02:38:00" d="2020-05-25 03:01:00"><n>Camera Angle: Ryan Keely &amp; Ryan Driller</n>    <k>Fiction and reality seem to blend when Hollywood actor Peter gets a concussion. His visions of heart-racing, sweat inducing sex seem very real though</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-25 03:01:00" d="2020-05-25 03:14:00"><n>Public Submission</n><t>S</t>    <k>Sometimes you find the most thrilling encounters where you least expect. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, porn for women created from the sexual</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-25 03:14:00" d="2020-05-25 03:36:00"><n>Positions: Fourth</n>    <k>While finding inspiration at a dancer's retreat, the ballet dancer Florence soon realises she's not the only one who could do with practising</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-25 03:36:00" d="2020-05-25 04:04:00"><n>Wicked Dreams: Dora Amirah Andara &amp; Jaros Jan</n>    <k>What started out as an innocent visit, soon leads to an exciting adventure. Introduced by sensual caresses, their loving dedication arouses to erotic Dreams! A sex film by Daring! Pure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-25 04:04:00" d="2020-05-25 04:26:00"><n>Elevator Dreams</n>    <k>When a guy meets an attractive girl in an elevator, she ignores him. But in his dreams all she want to do is having kinky, rough sex. A female friendly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-25 04:26:00" d="2020-05-25 04:41:00"><n>When it Comes to you: Zoey Monroe &amp; Ryan Mclane</n>    <k>When It Comes To You is a captivating and scintillating story of a woman torn between two men who both profess great love. Directed by Stormy Daniels</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="836" o="2020-05-25 04:41:00" d="2020-05-25 05:00:00"><n>If the Apocalypse Comes, Fuck Me</n><t>S</t>    <k>Maria Riot is lost and thirsty in an apocalyptical world. Luke seems to be the only man alive. From the XConfessions series by Erika Lust, female friendly</k>  </p>
</a>
