<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="42" t="2020-04-10 04:34:27"><p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 06:55:00" d="2020-04-17 07:00:00"><n u="Access MMXX">Access MMXX (16)</n>    <k>Entertainment round up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 07:00:00" d="2020-04-17 07:05:00"><n u="Mofy">Mofy III (5)</n>    <k>Mogu is trying to teach the Squirrel brothers how to fly a kite. When a gust of wind sweeps Mogu up into the trees, the little mole thinks that he would</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 07:05:00" d="2020-04-17 07:10:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig IV (30)</n>    <k>66% The school roof has a leak again, so the children organise a fete to raise money for a new roof</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 07:10:00" d="2020-04-17 07:15:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig IV (31)</n>    <k>66% Goldie the Goldfish is feeling a little lonely, so Peppa takes her to the aquarium. With all the different fish surely Peppa can find a new friend for Goldie?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 07:15:00" d="2020-04-17 07:20:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig IV (32)</n>    <k>66% Peppa, George and Grandpa Pig are sitting inside watching motor racing on the television, Granny Pig tells them all to go out and enjoy the sunshine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 07:20:00" d="2020-04-17 07:30:00"><n u="Fireman Sam">Fireman Sam X (4)</n>    <k>James starts to bake pizzas in the Whole Fish CafA©. Everyone is really impressed - the recipe is fantastic and James can really cook! Inspired to cook for the Railway Gala Open Day, James gets carried away and starts loading pizzas into every oven he can find</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 07:30:00" d="2020-04-17 07:45:00"><n u="Noddy Toyland Detective">Noddy Toyland Detective II (51)</n>    <k>Train hears cows near the railway tracks and insists on going very slow, but the builders on board need to get to Brickabuild fast. Noddy needs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 07:45:00" d="2020-04-17 07:55:00"><n u="Abby Hatcher">Abby Hatcher I (15)</n>    <k>When the littlest Squeaky Peeper goes missing, Abby has to find her and stop a Peeper Panic!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 07:55:00" d="2020-04-17 08:10:00"><n u="Thomas &amp; Friends: Big World! Big Adventures!">Thomas &amp; Friends: Big World! Big Adventures! XXIII (10)</n>    <k>Thomas thinks Raul the Brazilian tank engine is fun because he turns every boring task into a game. But Raul is also super-competitive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 08:10:00" d="2020-04-17 08:20:00"><n u="Daisy &amp; Ollie">Daisy &amp; Ollie III (2)</n>    <k>Daisy is rehearsing for a dance show, when she suddenly gets an attack of nerves. Luckily, Daddy knows lots of ways to calm her and gives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 08:20:00" d="2020-04-17 08:30:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig II (13)</n>    <k>66% Animated series. Granny and Grandpa Pig have invited Peppa and her family to lunch. On the way, Peppa's family get caught in a very long traffic jam</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 08:30:00" d="2020-04-17 08:40:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig VI (36)</n>    <k>66% Animated exploits of a lovable piglet. Doctor Hamster comes to school to talk about butterflies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 08:40:00" d="2020-04-17 08:55:00"><n u="Top Wing">Top Wing II (8)</n>    <k>65% Animated series about a team of bird rescue-cadets. Penny and the rest of the team use the HQ Command Flyer to rescue Survivor Bear from underwater</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 08:55:00" d="2020-04-17 09:10:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol V (15)</n>    <k>65% Farmer Al needs help to save his corn crop after the top of his silo is knocked off</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 09:10:00" d="2020-04-17 09:25:00"><n u="Floogals">Floogals III (14)</n>    <k>On a playdate in the garden, the Floogals can't understand why the Hoomans are running around, chasing each other. And when Boomer gets tagged 'It'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 09:25:00" d="2020-04-17 09:35:00"><n u="Secret Life Of Puppies">Secret Life Of Puppies II (10)</n>    <k>Hungarian vizsla pup Gilbert settles into his new house, and enjoys his new and highly rewarding exercise regime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 09:35:00" d="2020-04-17 09:45:00"><n u="Milkshake! Monkey's Amazing Adventures">Milkshake! Monkey's Amazing Adventures I (25)</n>    <k>Milkshake! Monkey visits Cheddar Gorge in Somerset to find out about caves. He meets Sarah, who tells him how the shapes inside caves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 09:45:00" d="2020-04-17 09:55:00"><n u="Little Princess">Little Princess V (11)</n>    <k>57% When the Prime Minister introduces a new cat to Princess, Puss is not happy and decides to run away. It's up to Princess to find her beloved Puss and convince him to stay</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 09:55:00" d="2020-04-17 10:10:00"><n u="Ben and Holly's Little Kingdom">Ben and Holly's Little Kingdom II (8)</n>    <k>72% When Redbeard, who is giving Nanny Plum, Ben and Holly a ride on his 'unsinkable' boat, hits a rock, he calls on the services of Elf Rescue!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 10:10:00" d="2020-04-17 10:15:00"><n u="Sunny Bunnies">Sunny Bunnies IV (10)</n>    <k>Turbo, Big Boo and Hopper are feeling lazy and pretend to be sick to get out of helping the girls pick raspberries. But Iris and Shiny know just how to get them to work!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 10:15:00" d="2020-04-17 13:45:00"><n u="Jeremy Vine MMXX">Jeremy Vine MMXX (77)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Jeremy Vine discusses and dissects the latest news, views and opinions, with co-host Storm Huntley helping on the live phone-ins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 13:45:00" d="2020-04-17 14:10:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VI (4)</n>    <k>An injured Joey must land an acting part in order to qualify for health insurance. Rachel finally learns the truth about her marriage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 14:10:00" d="2020-04-17 14:15:00"><n u="5 News MMXX">5 News MMXX (77)</n><t>D</t>    <k>National and international news</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 14:15:00" d="2020-04-17 14:45:00"><n u="Home and Away MMXX">Home and Away MMXX (7291)</n>    <k>The stress and anxiety over Leah is telling on Justin. A call from her, claiming to be fine and asking him not to contact her again, increases</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 14:45:00" d="2020-04-17 15:15:00"><n u="Neighbours MMXX">Neighbours MMXX (8335)</n>    <k>Claudia seeks legal advice about discrediting the Kennedys as carers for Aster, and gains a formidable ally who has less-than-friendly history with the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 15:15:00" d="2020-04-17 17:00:00"><n u="Cradles for Cash">Cradles for Cash (1)</n>    <k>When a woman's baby is snatched from the hospital she works at, she joins forces with another victim of child abduction to tackle an illegal adoption ring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 17:00:00" d="2020-04-17 17:30:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VI (8)</n>    <k>American sitcom. The guys explore their feminine sides. Ross overdoses on tooth whitener prior to a date and ends up with blindingly bright teeth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 17:30:00" d="2020-04-17 18:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VI (9)</n>    <k>On Thanksgiving, Chandler tries to gain favour with Monica's parents, but an old secret involving Ross causes problems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 18:00:00" d="2020-04-17 18:30:00"><n u="5 News MMXX">5 News MMXX (77)</n><t>D</t>    <k>National and international news</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 18:30:00" d="2020-04-17 19:00:00"><n u="Neighbours MMXX">Neighbours MMXX (8335)</n>    <k>Claudia seeks legal advice about discrediting the Kennedys as carers for Aster, and gains a formidable ally who has less-than-friendly history with the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 19:00:00" d="2020-04-17 19:10:00"><n u="Access MMXX">Access MMXX (16)</n>    <k>Entertainment round up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 19:10:00" d="2020-04-17 19:58:00"><n u="The Wonderful World Of Crafting">The Wonderful World Of Crafting I (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Brian loves turning old furniture into new pieces, James and Bridget spin alpaca yarn from their own farm, Tracey makes original paper craft pieces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 19:58:00" d="2020-04-17 20:00:00"><n u="Weather">Weather (4)</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 20:00:00" d="2020-04-17 20:55:00"><n u="Digging Up Britain's Past">Digging Up Britain's Past I (3)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Once thought to be a Roman temple, we now know Stonehenge has been around much longer. Alex Langlands investigations the unique properties of the stones</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 20:55:00" d="2020-04-17 21:00:00"><n u="5 News MMXX">5 News MMXX (77)</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 21:00:00" d="2020-04-17 21:58:00"><n u="Walking Britain's Lost Railways">Walking Britain's Lost Railways II (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Rob follows the line from King's Lynn to Great Yarmouth, discovering a lost railway through some of the quietest parts of England, but</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 21:58:00" d="2020-04-17 22:00:00"><n u="5 News MMXX">5 News MMXX (77)</n><t>D</t>    <k>National and international news</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 22:00:00" d="2020-04-17 23:00:00"><n u="Around The World By Train With Tony Robinson">Around The World By Train With Tony Robinson II (4)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Voyaging into Canada, Tony finds out what makes the locals tick, from the enormous Rockies to ice hockey. He also gets to chase elk from a town centre</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-17 23:00:00" d="2020-04-18 00:30:00"><n u="Comedy Playlists">Comedy Playlists I (2)</n>    <k>Sue Perkins presents a collection of clips of the most outrageous, entertaining and funny TV moments ever, featuring some of the biggest names</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 00:30:00" d="2020-04-18 02:15:00"><n u="Steptoe and son Ride Again">Steptoe and son Ride Again (1)</n>    <k>67% Spin-off from the TV sitcom starring Wilfrid Brambell and Harry H Corbett. Business is so bad that Harold is convinced Albert must die so he can collect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 02:15:00" d="2020-04-18 04:15:00"><n u="The 21.co.uk Live Casino Show">The 21.co.uk Live Casino Show (108)</n>    <k>Interactive casino show featuring live roulette. For more information and to register, visit www.21.co.uk</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 04:15:00" d="2020-04-18 05:00:00"><n u="The Yorkshire Steam Railway: All Aboard">The Yorkshire Steam Railway: All Aboard II (6)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Under pressure to bring in extra revenue now that the season is nearly over, the NYMR team decide to put on a massive bash for Halloween</k>  </p>
</a>
