<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="40" t="2021-07-11 04:58:58"><p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 05:05:00" d="2021-07-18 06:40:00"><n u="The Dog Rescuers With Alan Davies">The Dog Rescuers With Alan Davies X (6)</n><t>D</t>    <k>In the West Midlands, Inspector Herchy Boal receives an anonymous call about a labradoodle who is reportedly underweight, with infected ears and dirty matted fur</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 06:40:00" d="2021-07-18 07:00:00"><n u="Peppa Pig-Visually Signed">Peppa Pig-Visually Signed V (44)</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 07:00:00" d="2021-07-18 07:05:00"><n u="Mya Go">Mya Go I (45)</n>    <k>2D animated series about a little girl whose enthusiasm for life infects everyone around her. Mya Go and Mama Go are taking Doggy Go to the</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 07:05:00" d="2021-07-18 07:10:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig II (22)</n>    <k>66% Peppa and George have fun visiting Daddy Pig at work, and find out what all his colleagues do as a job. They soon realise that Daddy Pig works</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 07:10:00" d="2021-07-18 07:15:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig II (23)</n>    <k>66% Grandpa shows everyone how to use his metal detector to find treasure and they all build a big sandcastle. The children love Pirate Island, but eventually</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 07:15:00" d="2021-07-18 07:20:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig II (24)</n>    <k>66% Peppa and George love jumping in muddy puddles, even when its raining but when George takes off his rain hat, he catches a cold. After plenty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 07:20:00" d="2021-07-18 07:35:00"><n u="Bob The Builder">Bob The Builder I (35)</n>    <k>CGI animated adventures of the popular builder and his friends, reconstructed for the 21st century. After Leo and Muck stay up all night playing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 07:35:00" d="2021-07-18 07:45:00"><n u="Noddy In Toyland">Noddy In Toyland I (34)</n>    <k>The paper dolls have spent a long time making beautiful dresses for a fashion show, but the goblins steal them!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 07:45:00" d="2021-07-18 07:55:00"><n u="Shane The Chef">Shane The Chef I (8)</n>    <k>It's the county show, and Izzy is determined to win the large vegetable competition by growing the biggest marrow. But when a disaster in the kitchen means</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 07:55:00" d="2021-07-18 08:05:00"><n u="Thomas &amp; Friends">Thomas &amp; Friends XX (3)</n>    <k>CGI animated escapades of the little blue engine, based on the characters created by Rev W Awdry. When Gordon is late, the Fat Controller asks Henry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 08:05:00" d="2021-07-18 08:20:00"><n u="Ricky Zoom">Ricky Zoom I (4)</n>    <k>Ricky accidentally mistakes his dad's new rescue ramp for a toy ramp he won from a Steel Awesome breakfast cereal contest. Hank mistakes Ricky's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 08:20:00" d="2021-07-18 08:25:00"><n u="Daisy &amp; Ollie">Daisy &amp; Ollie III (19)</n>    <k>2D animated series about four-year-old best friends and neighbours Daisy and Ollie, who have lots of questions about the world around them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 08:25:00" d="2021-07-18 08:35:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig VII (6)</n>    <k>66% Peppa and George wake up in Granny and Grandpa's motorbike tent by the sea. Peppa finds a message in a bottle with a telephone number on it - but who is it from?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 08:35:00" d="2021-07-18 08:50:00"><n u="Pip and Posy">Pip and Posy I (8)</n>    <k>Pip and Posy are drawing ducklings, but an accident leaves Pip's yellow creation looking green. Will it be fun to try some different colours?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 08:50:00" d="2021-07-18 09:00:00"><n u="Milkshake! Bop Box Boogie">Milkshake! Bop Box Boogie I (27)</n>    <k>Join in at home with the Milkshake! presenters as they show you some joyful dance moves that will celebrate how much you love your family with Bop Box Boogie!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 09:00:00" d="2021-07-18 09:25:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol V (47)</n>    <k>64% Animation about a pack of resourceful pups. A comet is coming and the PAW Patrol get to work building a giant observatory!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 09:25:00" d="2021-07-18 09:55:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol VII (51)</n>    <k>64% Mayor Humdinger takes his Kitties to the Dino Wilds for some Dino acting lessons, but instead finds himself on top of a runaway Brachiosaurus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 09:55:00" d="2021-07-18 10:10:00"><n u="Butterbean's Café">Butterbean's Café I (47)</n>    <k>Animated series. Dazzle accidentally locks the smoothies inside the van and cannot find the key. Will she solve the problem in time for the Luau party?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 10:10:00" d="2021-07-18 10:20:00"><n u="Brave Bunnies">Brave Bunnies I (22)</n>    <k>Bop and Boo learn the value of a little teamwork while playing ball hockey with their new moose pal Dwayne in the snow-shrouded forest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 10:20:00" d="2021-07-18 10:30:00"><n u="Floogals">Floogals II (32)</n>    <k>The Floogals discover some strange smudges on the hallway mirror, then find them everywhere else too. What are they and where are they coming from? Detective Flo leads the case to solve this mystery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 10:30:00" d="2021-07-18 10:45:00"><n u="The World According to Grandpa">The World According to Grandpa I (14)</n>    <k>Poppy asks 'how were movies invented?' and Grandpa spins a tale about the time he starred in the world's first ever film called Bleep Bloop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 10:45:00" d="2021-07-18 10:55:00"><n u="Little Princess">Little Princess II (3)</n>    <k>56% Julian Clary narrates an animation based on the picture books. Little Princess decides to be a pirate, but is unhappy when she is told to do her chores</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 10:55:00" d="2021-07-18 11:05:00"><n u="Ben and Holly's Little Kingdom">Ben and Holly's Little Kingdom I (2)</n>    <k>73% Ben and Holly to cheer up their friend Gaston by tidying his cave, but do not realise that he likes it the way it is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 11:05:00" d="2021-07-18 11:20:00"><n u="SpongeBob SquarePants">SpongeBob SquarePants X (2)</n>    <k>78% Cartoon about an accident-prone sea sponge and his friends. The latest trend is flying your brain like a drone, and SpongeBob and Patrick are hooked!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 11:20:00" d="2021-07-18 11:35:00"><n u="SpongeBob SquarePants">SpongeBob SquarePants XI (6)</n>    <k>78% Comic animated misadventures of a sea sponge. Patrick's lemonade stand is unsuccessful - until Squidward inadvertently gives him a secret ingredient</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 11:35:00" d="2021-07-18 11:40:00"><n u="Entertainment News on">Entertainment News on 5 (2') MMXXI (140)</n>    <k>A daily round-up of showbiz news and gossip from around the world, focusing on celebrities, movies, music and entertainment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 11:40:00" d="2021-07-18 12:05:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VIII (16)</n>    <k>A guilt-ridden Joey confesses his love for Rachel to a flabbergasted Ross. Joey decides that he will tell Rachel, regardless of the consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 12:05:00" d="2021-07-18 12:35:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VIII (17)</n>    <k>Joey avoids Rachel after revealing his romantic feelings to her. Rachel attempts to rebuild their friendship by telling him a lie about her baby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 12:35:00" d="2021-07-18 13:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VIII (18)</n>    <k>Monica becomes lost for words when toasting her parents at their 35th wedding anniversary party. Phoebe shows off her latest boyfriend Parker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 13:00:00" d="2021-07-18 13:35:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VIII (19)</n>    <k>Though Joey is thrilled when his name is used in a Soap Opera Digest crossword puzzle, he is reluctant to let the magazine interview him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 13:35:00" d="2021-07-18 14:05:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VIII (20)</n>    <k>Rachel panics during her baby shower when she realises how unprepared she is to care for a child. Chandler and Ross exhaust themselves helping Joey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 14:05:00" d="2021-07-18 15:00:00"><n u="George Clarke's Build a New Life in the Country">George Clarke's Build a New Life in the Country I (6)</n><t>D</t>    <k>George Clarke follows a family throwing in secure jobs and a suburban home to convert a stone barn in Wales, doing the work themselves, with a tiny budget</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 15:00:00" d="2021-07-18 16:00:00"><n u="George Clarke's Build a New Life in the Country">George Clarke's Build a New Life in the Country I (7)</n><t>D</t>    <k>George Clarke meets a couple moving from the city to rural Devon. As well as the headaches of converting a derelict barn into a beautiful home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 16:00:00" d="2021-07-18 17:00:00"><n u="George Clarke's Build a New Life in the Country">George Clarke's Build a New Life in the Country I (8)</n><t>D</t>    <k>George Clarke follows a couple who are converting a chapel into their first home together. They are totally inexperienced and doing all the work themselves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 17:00:00" d="2021-07-18 19:25:00"><n u="The Best Exotic Marigold Hotel">The Best Exotic Marigold Hotel (1)</n>    <k>73% Comedy starring Judi Dench and Bill Nighy. A group of British pensioners retire in India, but their accommodation is not quite how they pictured it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 19:25:00" d="2021-07-18 19:30:00"><n u="5 News">5 News (55)</n><t>D</t>    <k>National and international news</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 19:30:00" d="2021-07-18 21:00:00"><n u="When Cruises Go Horribly Wrong &amp; Other Travel Nightmares">When Cruises Go Horribly Wrong &amp; Other Travel Nightmares I (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Documentary exploring travel disasters through eye-witness testimony and first-hand footage, from horrifying dramas at sea to one of the worst</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 21:00:00" d="2021-07-18 22:00:00"><n u="10 Years Younger in 10 Days">10 Years Younger in 10 Days II (7)</n><t>D</t>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-18 22:00:00" d="2021-07-19 00:15:00"><n u="Hellboy">Hellboy (1)</n>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2021-07-19 00:15:00" d="2021-07-19 03:15:00"><n u="Hercules">Hercules (1)</n>    <k>Fantasy action starring Dwayne Johnson. Hercules has his life as a sword-for-hire tested when the King of Thrace tasks him with defeating a tyrannical warlord</k>  </p>
</a>
