<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="36" t="2020-04-11 04:33:24"><p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 05:00:00" d="2020-04-18 07:00:00"><n u="A Country Life for Half the Price With Kate Humble">A Country Life for Half the Price With Kate Humble I (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>The massive Goldby family, all eleven of them, are bursting out of their four-bedroom house in Epsom, Surrey. Kate follows their move to a rural farmhouse</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 07:00:00" d="2020-04-18 07:05:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig II (28)</n>    <k>Peppa, George and Daddy are in the garden painting a picture when ducks run through the paint and all over their masterpiece</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 07:05:00" d="2020-04-18 07:10:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig II (29)</n>    <k>Grandpa Pig has built a little train called Gertrude. When he takes Peppa and George for a ride, there is room for lots of their friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 07:10:00" d="2020-04-18 07:15:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig II (30)</n>    <k>Peppa and George are visiting their cousin Chloe and will get to meet Chloe's new baby brother, Alexander, for the first time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 07:15:00" d="2020-04-18 07:20:00"><n u="The Day Henry Met">The Day Henry Met II (7)</n>    <k>Henry meets a telescope, who is very big and lives in an observatory. Telescope has just discovered a new constellation, but in his excitement he forgot</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 07:20:00" d="2020-04-18 07:35:00"><n u="Ben and Holly's Little Kingdom">Ben and Holly's Little Kingdom I (25)</n>    <k>72% Betty Caterpillar: Impish animation. Ben and Holly make a new caterpillar friend, but she is sad that she cannot fly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 07:35:00" d="2020-04-18 07:45:00"><n u="Bob The Builder">Bob The Builder I (8)</n>    <k>CGI animated adventures of the popular builder and his friends, reconstructed for the 21st century. When Bob takes Pilchard for her check-up at the vets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 07:45:00" d="2020-04-18 07:55:00"><n u="Fireman Sam">Fireman Sam VII (3)</n>    <k>Elvis breaks his leg dancing around the Fire Station and begins to wonder if he is really cut out to be a fireman. But when Mike Flood ends up dangling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 07:55:00" d="2020-04-18 08:05:00"><n u="Thomas &amp; Friends: Big World! Big Adventures!">Thomas &amp; Friends: Big World! Big Adventures! XXII (4)</n>    <k>Thomas is working on the Indian Railway. He's amazed by all the animals on top of trains, cows sleeping on the track and elephants wandering around the countryside! He disapproves when his friend Ashima tells him that elephants used to help shunt the carriages, but when Thomas ends up derailed in a paddy field, it's not an engine that comes to his rescue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 08:05:00" d="2020-04-18 08:20:00"><n u="Noddy Toyland Detective">Noddy Toyland Detective I (44)</n>    <k>CGI-animated series in which Enid Blyton's world-famous character becomes a detective. Noddy and his friends are building a toy tower, but who is trying to stop them?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 08:20:00" d="2020-04-18 08:35:00"><n u="Shane The Chef">Shane The Chef I (47)</n>    <k>A problem with Maggie's tuk-tuk sees the cabbages for Shane's dish of the day go careering out of town, with Shane and Sam Spratt in tow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 08:35:00" d="2020-04-18 08:45:00"><n u="Ben and Holly's Little Kingdom">Ben and Holly's Little Kingdom I (26)</n>    <k>72% Queen Holly: Impish animation. Holly is left in charge when King and Queen Thistle go away on important business. But ruling the Little Kingdom is not as easy as it looks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 08:45:00" d="2020-04-18 08:55:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig II (31)</n>    <k>Peppa and her family go for a day's cycle ride and Peppa instigates a downhill race</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 08:55:00" d="2020-04-18 09:05:00"><n u="Peppa Pig">Peppa Pig II (32)</n>    <k>Peppa decides that only girls can play in her treehouse, so Grandpa Pig builds the boys their own den</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 09:05:00" d="2020-04-18 09:20:00"><n u="Butterbean's Café">Butterbean's Café I (17)</n>    <k>Animated series about a fairy who runs a cafe. Butterbean has to borrow Ms Marmalady's freezer for her fruitsicles, but Ms Marmalady has her own plans for them!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 09:20:00" d="2020-04-18 09:40:00"><n u="PAW Patrol">PAW Patrol IV (16)</n>    <k>65% An encounter with a new shampoo and the hairdryer at Katie's Pet Parlour leaves the Kitten Catastrophe Crew fluffed up and blown out the door</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 09:40:00" d="2020-04-18 09:50:00"><n u="Nella the Princess Knight">Nella the Princess Knight II (9)</n>    <k>67% When Trinket loses her voice before a special duet, she and Nella journey into the Wilderwood where the Warblewolves live to find the Shimmering Steamspring for a cure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 09:50:00" d="2020-04-18 10:05:00"><n u="Wissper">Wissper II (45)</n>    <k>When a very sticky Honey Bear gets covered in twigs and leaves while running from bees in the wood, Ed and Ted Beaver think that she's a monster!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 10:05:00" d="2020-04-18 10:15:00"><n u="Pirata and Capitano">Pirata and Capitano I (3)</n>    <k>Pirata and Capitano race to be the first to name an island, but a mysterious third pirate also wants to be the first</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 10:15:00" d="2020-04-18 10:40:00"><n u="Floogals">Floogals II (2)</n>    <k>While exploring the attic, the Floogals find an instant camera. They have fun working out that it takes pictures, like cameraphones, and discover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 10:40:00" d="2020-04-18 10:50:00"><n u="Shimmer and Shine">Shimmer and Shine IV (20)</n>    <k>58% Animated series about young twin genies. When the girls bake a cake using bouncing flour, it bounces off. Can they catch it in time for Roya's Feather Day party?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 10:50:00" d="2020-04-18 11:05:00"><n u="SpongeBob SquarePants">SpongeBob SquarePants XI (14)</n>    <k>79% Animated comic misadventures of a sea sponge. When SpongeBob introduces Patrick to the world of books, it causes his brain to swell and take on a life of its own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 11:05:00" d="2020-04-18 11:15:00"><n u="The Loud House">The Loud House I (1)</n>    <k>When Lincoln wants to watch the finale of his favourite show, he has to beat each sister to get to the sofa first!</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 11:15:00" d="2020-04-18 11:30:00"><n u="Access MMXX">Access MMXX (16)</n>    <k>Entertainment round up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 11:30:00" d="2020-04-18 12:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VI (5)</n>    <k>Rachel forces Ross to annul their marriage. Phoebe's first triplet-babysitting experience proves stressful</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 12:00:00" d="2020-04-18 12:30:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VI (6)</n>    <k>American sitcom. The guys and girls prepare for big changes to their living arrangements</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 12:30:00" d="2020-04-18 13:00:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VI (7)</n>    <k>Chandler learns how obsessively neat Monica is when he attempts to do her a favour. Joey desperately tries not to flirt with his sexy new roommate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 13:00:00" d="2020-04-18 13:30:00"><n u="Friends">Friends VI (8)</n>    <k>American sitcom. The guys explore their feminine sides. Ross overdoses on tooth whitener prior to a date and ends up with blindingly bright teeth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 13:30:00" d="2020-04-18 16:20:00"><n u="Chitty Chitty Bang Bang">Chitty Chitty Bang Bang (1)</n>    <k>70% Classic musical fantasy starring Dick Van Dyke and Sally Ann Howes. An eccentric inventor rescues a derelict racing car and takes his children on an outing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 16:20:00" d="2020-04-18 19:25:00"><n u="Oliver!">Oliver! (1)</n>    <k>74% Musical adaptation of Charles Dickens's classic tale of an orphan who runs away from the orphanage and hooks up with a group of boys trained</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 19:25:00" d="2020-04-18 19:30:00"><n u="5 News">5 News (31)</n><t>D</t>    <k>National and international news</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 19:30:00" d="2020-04-18 21:20:00"><n u="Cruising South America With Jane McDonald">Cruising South America With Jane McDonald (1)</n>    <k>Another chance to take in the wonder of Wakefield's tour of South America</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 21:20:00" d="2020-04-18 22:20:00"><n u="Harry &amp; Meghan: Royals At War - Part">Harry &amp; Meghan: Royals At War - Part 2 I (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Documentary examining if there's any truth behind the media suggestions of unrest following Meghan Markle's entry into the Royal Family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 22:20:00" d="2020-04-18 23:15:00"><n u="Philip: The King Without A Crown">Philip: The King Without A Crown (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>The real story of Prince Philip - from war hero to the rock at the Queen's side. Exploring how Prince Philip gave up his naval career as</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-18 23:15:00" d="2020-04-19 00:10:00"><n u="The Royal Family: Affairs &amp; Infidelities">The Royal Family: Affairs &amp; Infidelities (1)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Documentary revealing how the blue-blooded royals are just as red-blooded as anyone. Royal-watchers recall what happened between Prince Charles and Camilla</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="851" o="2020-04-19 00:10:00" d="2020-04-19 03:10:00"><n u="Biopics">Biopics I (2)</n><t>D</t>    <k>Documentary with dramatic recreations of key scenes from the untold story of one of the world's greatest showbiz icons who, despite record-shattering</k>  </p>
</a>
