<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="32" t="2021-07-09 07:02:15"><p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 05:35:00" d="2021-07-16 06:30:00"><n u="Location, Location, Location">Location, Location, Location XXIX (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie house-hunts with a pair of nervous first-time buyers in Balham and Putney in south west London. Phil looks for a property with Aussie proportions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 06:30:00" d="2021-07-16 07:00:00"><n>Coach Trip: Road to Tenerife</n><t>S</t><e>TF</e>    <k>Coach Trip: Final Week: Road. 
. o Tenerife: The tourists are up bright and early for a morning of rock climbing and a personal growth workshop with horses. (Ep37/40)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 07:00:00" d="2021-07-16 07:40:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Anne Robinson and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Grace Dent joins Susie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 07:40:00" d="2021-07-16 08:05:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly I</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Molly Gets a Hat: When Mike's mother Peggy buys Molly a new hat as a gesture of goodwill, Molly feels obliged to invite her to spend Thanksgiving with her family. Ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 08:05:00" d="2021-07-16 08:25:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly I</n><e>RF</e>    <k>First Christmas: Mike attempts to find the perfect yuletide gift for Molly, but he has no idea what present he should buy her for their first Christmas together. Ep11)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 08:25:00" d="2021-07-16 08:50:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Tasteless Frank: Frank loses his sense of taste. Is it a side-effect of his potency medication? And will he have to tell Marie that he is receiving chemical assistance?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 08:50:00" d="2021-07-16 09:15:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Sister-in-Law: Trouble brews in the Barone family when Robert's wife Amy finds out that Ray thinks she is in the habit of talking too much</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 09:15:00" d="2021-07-16 09:40:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Power of No: Ray tries to make himself more desirable in Debra's eyes by playing hard to get, but there's trouble when she finds out what he's up to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 09:40:00" d="2021-07-16 10:10:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Whine Club: Frasier's hopes of being elected corkmaster of the wine club are dashed when Niles's girlfriend Mel convinces him to run against his brother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 10:10:00" d="2021-07-16 10:40:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Hot Pursuit: Martin helps Donny stake out a man who's cheating on his wife, while Frasier and Roz nearly have a romantic encounter at a conference</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 10:40:00" d="2021-07-16 11:10:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Matrimonial Momentum: Penny struggles with Leonard's confession that he kissed another woman. Sheldon doesn't know how to act when Amy breaks up with him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 11:10:00" d="2021-07-16 11:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Separation Oscillation: Sheldon films a special post-break-up episode of Fun with Flags. Bernadette feels guilty about withholding a secret from Penny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 11:35:00" d="2021-07-16 12:05:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Bachelor Party Corrosion: The guys' science skills are tested when they get a flat tyre during Leonard's surprise bachelor party weekend in Mexico</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 12:05:00" d="2021-07-16 12:35:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons VIII (10)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>87% The Springfield Files: FBI agents Fox Mulder and Dana Scully (David Duchovny and Gillian Anderson) investigate Homer's claims that he has seen an alien in the woods</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 12:35:00" d="2021-07-16 13:05:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons VIII (11)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>87% The Twisted World of Marge Simpson: Marge opens a pretzel franchise after meeting the Pretzel Man (guest star Jack Lemmon). But Fat Tony wants a slice of the action</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 13:05:00" d="2021-07-16 13:10:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 13:10:00" d="2021-07-16 14:10:00"><n u="Posh Pawnbrokers">Posh Pawnbrokers III (13)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>At Gold Arts in Brighton, father-and-son pawnbrokers Doug Senior and Doug Junior do deals on a pair of renovated vintage chairs and a French Victorian horse carriage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 14:10:00" d="2021-07-16 15:10:00"><n u="A New Life in the Sun">A New Life in the Sun VI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Spain, a guest house tempts visitors with local cuisine and a cycling retreat for some much-needed business. A Portuguese holiday village takes delivery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 15:10:00" d="2021-07-16 16:45:00"><n>Formula 1 ®</n><t>S</t>    <k>Live: F1 British GP Practice 1
Lee McKenzie presents live coverage of the first practice session from Silverstone, ahead of one of the most famous races on the F1 calendar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 16:45:00" d="2021-07-16 17:30:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><e>F</e>    <k>Bob and Lucretia from Southampton fell in love with Italy on their honeymoon and now want to buy a holiday home in the stunning Puglia region</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 17:30:00" d="2021-07-16 18:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><e>F</e>    <k>Maxine and Cormac recently got married in France's Dordogne region and now have ?100,000 to spend on a holiday home near Riberac</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 18:00:00" d="2021-07-16 20:30:00"><n>Formula 1 ®</n><t>S</t>    <k>Live: F1 British GP Qualifying
It's Qualifying - but not as you know it. This year, Qualifying will not determine the drivers' race grid position</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 20:30:00" d="2021-07-16 20:55:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 20:55:00" d="2021-07-16 22:00:00"><n>Britain's Most Expensive Houses</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>A sneak peek behind the doors of some of the UK's jaw-dropping homes, as brokers set out to sell a property in Highgate for ?40 million</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 22:00:00" d="2021-07-16 23:00:00"><n u="Celebrity Gogglebox">Celebrity Gogglebox III</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Celebrity Gogglebox
Some of Britain's most-loved personalities hit the sofa, as they turn their hands to being critics, watching the best TV shows of the week. Ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 23:00:00" d="2021-07-17 00:10:00"><n u="The Last Leg">The Last Leg XXII</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Live: The Last Leg
Asim Chaudhry and Rosie Jones join Adam Hills, Josh Widdicombe and Alex Brooker as they offer their entertaining insight into current world events. Ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-17 00:10:00" d="2021-07-17 01:10:00"><n>Joe Lycett: I'm About to Lose...</n><e>RF</e>    <k>. ontrol and I Think Joe Lycett: Joe shares jokes, paintings and some trolling he's been up to, such as breaking into banks, selling art for ?12.5million</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-17 01:10:00" d="2021-07-17 03:15:00"><n>Sisters</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Comedy starring Amy Poehler and Tina Fey. Two grown-up sisters, angry that their parents are selling their childhood home, throw one last party there</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-17 03:15:00" d="2021-07-17 03:40:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons VIII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>87% Treehouse of Horror VII: Bart finds his evil twin in the attic, Lisa becomes God to a race of tiny people, and Kang and Kodos assume the identities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-17 03:40:00" d="2021-07-17 04:05:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Rochdale. Fitness instructor Tanya serves up a Mediterranean feast. But is this glamorous host more style than substance? (Ep1/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-17 04:05:00" d="2021-07-17 04:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Rochdale. Business coach and passionate foodie Rod is determined to impress. But he has already offended Tanya - and HR manager Claire predicts fireworks. (Ep2/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-17 04:30:00" d="2021-07-17 05:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Rochdale. HR manager Claire hopes that her hosting skills will compensate for her 'imperfect' cooking. But tension rises when Tanya barely touches her food. (Ep3/5)</k>  </p>
</a>
