<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="35" t="2019-08-15 22:44:22"><p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 05:30:00" d="2019-08-22 05:55:00"><n u="Extreme Cake Makers">Extreme Cake Makers II</n><e>R</e>    <k>Molly must please her harshest critic with a keep fit birthday cake. Karisha has a design-conscious christening cake recipient, and Michelle makes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 05:55:00" d="2019-08-22 06:50:00"><n u="The ?100K Drop">The ?100K Drop III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Davina McCall is joined by Ky and Anvir, friends from Birmingham and Leicester, and Becki and her father from Carlisle. Will either pair</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 06:50:00" d="2019-08-22 07:30:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Dr Linda Papadopoulos is in Dictionary Corner with Susie Dent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 07:30:00" d="2019-08-22 07:55:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly II</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Victoria Can't Drive: When Victoria is arrested for various driving violations, Molly and Joyce ask Mike to help them spring her from jail. Ep12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 07:55:00" d="2019-08-22 08:20:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly II</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Joyce's Choices: Joyce drives Vince to distraction by making him jealous when she agrees to go out for dinner with her former boyfriend. Ep13)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 08:20:00" d="2019-08-22 08:45:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>Lush Life: Carrie starts Doug on a new diet but goes easy on him if she's been out drinking with her friends. But when she falls out with her friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 08:45:00" d="2019-08-22 09:10:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>Bun Dummy: Doug tries to stop Carrie wearing her hair in a bun because he wants her to look sexy at his high school reunion</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 09:10:00" d="2019-08-22 09:40:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Cousin Gerard: Ray is upset when Debra says that he is just like his cousin, so he turns to his family for reassurance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 09:40:00" d="2019-08-22 10:10:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>No Thanks: Debra spends a whole day cooking with Marie in an effort to get along with her mother-in-law, and Ray reluctantly agrees to take Robert and Frank to a car show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 10:10:00" d="2019-08-22 10:40:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>A Day in May: Frasier comforts a crestfallen husband whose house has been put up for sale after his wife abandoned him, taking the children with her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 10:40:00" d="2019-08-22 11:10:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Cranes Go Caribbean: Frasier is horrified when he learns Martin, Niles and Daphne are going to accompany him on his trip to Belize with Claire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 11:10:00" d="2019-08-22 11:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (12)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Jerusalem Duality: Sheldon's confidence is shaken to the core when he encounters Dennis, a 15-year-old physicist who is clearly much brighter than he is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 11:35:00" d="2019-08-22 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (13)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Bat Jar Conjecture: Sheldon is ousted from the gang's Physics Bowl quiz team, so he decides to prove his superiority by forming his own team for the event</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 12:00:00" d="2019-08-22 12:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Blame It on Lisa: The Simpsons go to Brazil to meet an orphan who Lisa's secretly been calling. But as soon as they arrive, Homer is kidnapped</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 12:30:00" d="2019-08-22 13:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Lisa vs. Malibu Stacey: Lisa decides Malibu Stacey dolls set a bad example to girls, so she pleads with their creator, Stacy Lovell (guest star Kathleen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 13:00:00" d="2019-08-22 13:05:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 13:05:00" d="2019-08-22 14:05:00"><n u="A New Life in the Sun">A New Life in the Sun IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Shropshire family are pushed to the limit in France, a couple from Cambridge juggle pets and guests and we meet a couple from London stirring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 14:05:00" d="2019-08-22 15:10:00"><n>Posh Pawnbrokers</n><e>RF</e>    <k>At London Road, Dan considers deals on famous cleaner Kim Woodburn's jewellery and a ?50,000 F1 car. In Kent, brothers Charlie and Patrick value</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 15:10:00" d="2019-08-22 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 16:00:00" d="2019-08-22 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2018 &amp; 2019</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun
Poppy and John want to enjoy their retirement in the Lot et Garonne region of France. Will Ben Hillman be able to find them the perfect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 17:00:00" d="2019-08-22 18:00:00"><n u="The ?100K Drop">The ?100K Drop III</n><e>F</e>    <k>Sam and Dan, work colleagues from Leicester, and Laura and her father Dawson, from Chester, join Davina McCall for more nail-biting drama against the drop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 18:00:00" d="2019-08-22 18:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n>    <k>The fourth host in Sheffield is wellness coach Andy who hopes to impress with a tasty and healthy meal. To liven up proceedings he shows off his singing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 18:30:00" d="2019-08-22 19:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Sweet Seymour Skinner's Baadasssss Song: Bart gets Principal Skinner sacked and Flanders takes over at the school. Out of work, Skinner befriends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 19:00:00" d="2019-08-22 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Little Girl in the Big Ten: Lisa pretends to be a student so that she can hang out with some college girls. Meanwhile, Bart is bitten by a mosquito</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 19:30:00" d="2019-08-22 20:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Maxine is over the moon for her big day, but will Sienna manage to convince her to tell the truth? Liam gives Mercedes a big ultimatum, and Jack helps a grieving villager</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 20:00:00" d="2019-08-22 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Includes sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 21:00:00" d="2019-08-22 22:00:00"><n>Kirstie and Phil's Love It or List It</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Kirstie and Phil's Love It. 
. r List It: The property gurus revisit Dawn and Paul, who back in 2015 were torn between renovating their Huddersfield</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 22:00:00" d="2019-08-22 23:00:00"><n>The Secret Teacher</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: The Secret Teacher
Social media marketing magnate Steven Bartlett goes undercover at a cash-strapped school in Liverpool, where he encounters a range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 23:00:00" d="2019-08-22 23:30:00"><n>This Way Up</n><t>S</t><e>TF</e>    <k>New: This Way Up
Comedy drama with Aisling Bea. Aine and Richard's relationship gets complicated when she is inadvertently invited for dinner but leaves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 23:30:00" d="2019-08-23 00:35:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XVIII</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Sean Lock and Rob Beckett take on special guest team captain Alan Carr and Sarah Millican. Nick Mohammed is in Dictionary Corner with Susie Dent. Ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-23 00:35:00" d="2019-08-23 01:30:00"><n>Call the Cops</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Juggling Chainsaws: This series goes inside the nerve centre of policing - the police communications and control centre - to shed light on law and order</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-23 01:30:00" d="2019-08-23 02:20:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay travels to Atlanta, Georgia, to help first-time restaurant owners Richard and Jorge, whose establishment, Park's Edge, is in big trouble</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-23 02:20:00" d="2019-08-23 04:15:00"><n>Queen and Country</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Callum Turner stars in John Boorman's sequel to his semi-autobiographical film Hope and Glory. It's the early 1950s and time for Bill to do his National Service. Strong language</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-23 04:15:00" d="2019-08-23 04:45:00"><n u="Stath Lets Flats">Stath Lets Flats II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Comedy with Greek-Cypriot letting agent Stath (Jamie Demetriou). Stath is struggling with his brash new boss, old rivals and new clients, while Sophie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-23 04:45:00" d="2019-08-23 05:40:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Expats club comic John, outspoken businesswoman Lisa, front of house manager Michelle, and estate agent and socialite Ross battle it out in this episode</k>  </p>
</a>
