<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="37" t="2019-08-10 01:40:16"><p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 05:00:00" d="2019-08-16 05:30:00"><n u="GameFace">GameFace (Signed Version) II (6)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>GameFace
Marcella is sober and turning things around. She receives word from Tom about their writing project. At Jon's art exhibition she discovers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 05:30:00" d="2019-08-16 05:55:00"><n>Extreme Cake Makers</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Phil and Christine grapple with flamingo anatomy, Eloise goes the eggs-tra mile to surprise a friend with a giant egg shaped cake, and Molly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 05:55:00" d="2019-08-16 06:50:00"><n u="The ?100K Drop">The ?100K Drop III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Davina McCall is joined by Stephen and Alex, a couple from Leeds and North Shields, and Motherwell couple Myra and Martin. Will anyone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 06:50:00" d="2019-08-16 07:30:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Charlie Higson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 07:30:00" d="2019-08-16 07:55:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly II</n><e>RF</e>    <k>'57 Chevy Bel Air: Mike is in hot water when Molly finds out that he bought Vince's used car without asking her first, because she thinks they should</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 07:55:00" d="2019-08-16 08:20:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly II</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Victoria Runs Away: Despite Mike's good intentions, he adds fuel to the fire when he's caught in the middle of an argument between Molly and her family. Ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 08:20:00" d="2019-08-16 08:45:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>Lyin' Hearted: Carrie discovers a secret about Arthur, and Doug regrets befriending a quirky stranger</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 08:45:00" d="2019-08-16 09:10:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>Life Sentence: Doug installs a camera in Arthur's room and his friends get addicted to Arthur TV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 09:10:00" d="2019-08-16 09:40:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Dancing with Debra: Ray regrets asking Robert to take Debra dancing when they become infatuated with their new hobby</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 09:40:00" d="2019-08-16 10:10:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Robert Moves Back: Robert and Amy move into Ray's basement in an attempt to get some privacy, but haven't accounted for Marie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 10:10:00" d="2019-08-16 10:40:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Show Must Go Off: Frasier and Niles try to revitalise the career of their boyhood actor idol, only to learn that he stinks. With Sir Derek Jacobi and Patrick Macnee</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 10:40:00" d="2019-08-16 11:10:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Sliding Frasier: In homage to the romantic film Sliding Doors, two radically different versions of Frasier's love life unfold</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 11:10:00" d="2019-08-16 11:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Pilot: The first ever episode of the hit sitcom. Leonard and Sheldon's ignorance of women seems set to change when the beautiful Penny moves in next door</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 11:35:00" d="2019-08-16 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Big Bran Hypothesis: Bothered by how messy Penny's flat is, Sheldon sneaks in to clean and organise it, but Penny isn't best pleased when she finds out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 12:00:00" d="2019-08-16 12:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Jaws Wired Shut: Homer becomes a good listener and a calming influence when his jaw is wired shut after he runs into a statue. But Marge is disturbed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 12:30:00" d="2019-08-16 13:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Rosebud: In spite of being obscenely rich, Mr Burns can never be truly happy without his childhood teddy bear Bobo, who Bart finds in a bag of ice and gives to Maggie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 13:00:00" d="2019-08-16 13:05:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 13:05:00" d="2019-08-16 14:05:00"><n u="A New Life in the Sun">A New Life in the Sun IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Two expats have teething troubles with their bar in Spain. A couple from Yorkshire tempt French locals with their new Thai takeaway business. Ep25)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 14:05:00" d="2019-08-16 15:10:00"><n>Posh Pawnbrokers</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Brothers Charlie and Patrick examine a huge collection of boxing memorabilia in Kent, while Dan at London Road in Sheffield has a diamond encrusted bracelet in his sights</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 15:10:00" d="2019-08-16 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Dr Linda Papadopoulos is in Dictionary Corner with Susie Dent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 16:00:00" d="2019-08-16 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2018 &amp; 2019</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun
Jo and Darrell from south west London are looking for a holiday home in Menorca. For their ?300,000, Danni Menzies shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 17:00:00" d="2019-08-16 18:00:00"><n u="The ?100K Drop">The ?100K Drop III</n><e>F</e>    <k>Coalville couple Jono and Danielle, and Cardiff couple Simon and Danielle, join Davina McCall to take on the mighty Drop. Will either pair win big? Ep25)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 18:00:00" d="2019-08-16 18:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>F</e>    <k>The final host in and around Leeds, lighting technician Dragos, treats his guests to an evening of traditional Romanian fare featuring hearty favourites. (Ep5/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 18:30:00" d="2019-08-16 19:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Deep Space Homer: Homer and Barney are recruited by Nasa to make it more appealing to the man in the street. And when Barney falls off the wagon, Homer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 19:00:00" d="2019-08-16 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Treehouse of Horror V: The Simpsons become winter caretakers at Mr Burns' mountain mansion, where Homer is driven mad by the lack of beer and TV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 19:30:00" d="2019-08-16 20:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>It's Jack and Breda's secret wedding day, but Breda has pressing matters to attend to. She tells Joel in the confession box that someone in her family has sinned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 20:00:00" d="2019-08-16 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Includes sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 21:00:00" d="2019-08-16 22:00:00"><n u="Animal Rescue Live: Supervet Special">Animal Rescue Live: Supervet Special II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Animal Rescue Live. 
. upervet Special: Anna Richardson drops by to lend her support and find a lady friend for Nigel the guinea fowl</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 22:00:00" d="2019-08-16 23:00:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XVIII</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: 8 Out of 10 Cats Does. 
. ountdown: Sean Lock and Rob Beckett take on special guest team captain Alan Carr and Sarah Millican. Nick Mohammed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 23:00:00" d="2019-08-17 00:05:00"><n>The Lateish Show with Mo Gilligan</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Lateish Show with Mo Gilligan
Mo Gilligan is joined by Tom Davis for chat, unexpected music performances, sketches and games where viewers can win a prize. (Ep5/6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 00:05:00" d="2019-08-17 00:40:00"><n u="Friday Night Dinner">Friday Night Dinner V (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>80% The Violin: Adam isn't happy when he is forced to play his violin for Mum and her best friend Val, but Jonny is relishing every moment. Dad is obsessed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 00:40:00" d="2019-08-17 01:05:00"><n u="Friday Night Dinner">Friday Night Dinner V (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>80% Wilson: The boys are threatened with no crumble if they don't help to assemble a wooden shelf, while Jim's dog Wilson keeps doing his 'dollops' in Mum and Dad's flowerbed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 01:05:00" d="2019-08-17 02:00:00"><n u="Rude Tube: Face Palms and Face...">Rude Tube: Face Palms and Face... XI</n><e>RF</e>    <k>. lants: Alex Zane presents some fresh, jaw-dropping internet clips featuring the worst wedding intro ever, and a head stuck in a pumpkin. Ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 02:00:00" d="2019-08-17 03:55:00"><n>Transcendence</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Johnny Depp stars in a violent sci-fi thriller about the potential pitfalls of creating an artificially intelligent computer. With Rebecca Hall</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 03:55:00" d="2019-08-17 04:20:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Cardiff. DJ Trishna hopes her cooking will be even better than her rapping at her hip-hop themed night. But when Yuno shakes his booty on the dance floor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 04:20:00" d="2019-08-17 04:50:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Cardiff. Host Nick plans to bring some refinement and fine dining to the week's proceedings. But is his massive tasting menu overambitious? (Ep2/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 04:50:00" d="2019-08-17 05:15:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Cardiff. Retail manager Yuno serves some traditional dancing alongside his Nepalese food. But are his spicy dishes too fiery for his guests' delicate British palates? (Ep3/5)</k>  </p>
</a>
