<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2019-07-11 00:18:50"><p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 05:10:00" d="2019-07-16 05:40:00"><n u="Extreme Cake Makers">Extreme Cake Makers II</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Molly creates a wedding cake with an agricultural touch, Phil and Christine tackle a towering choux bun cake, and it's a fright night for Ben as he creates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 05:40:00" d="2019-07-16 05:55:00"><n>Kirstie's Vintage Gems</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp brings a touch of romance and sophistication to Jannine and Shaun's neglected bedroom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 05:55:00" d="2019-07-16 06:50:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Grandma Sue hopes to impress her guests in north Somerset with her simple home cooking. But she's competing with Heidi's posh nosh, Myles' movie night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 06:50:00" d="2019-07-16 07:25:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Michaela Strachan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 07:25:00" d="2019-07-16 07:55:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers XI (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Ill-Gotten Gaines: Woody has Thanksgiving dinner with Kelly's family and realises his father-in-law is having an affair. The rest of the gang gathers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 07:55:00" d="2019-07-16 08:20:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers XI (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Feelings. Whoa, Whoa, Whoa: Carla's love-hate relationship with John Hill gets out of hand when a passionate encounter gives him a heart attack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 08:20:00" d="2019-07-16 08:45:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>Rayny Day: Doug takes a day off and decides to spend it with Richie, who is feeling bad about his divorce</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 08:45:00" d="2019-07-16 09:10:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>Train Wreck: Emotions are strained when Doug's new assistant turns out to be a beautiful young woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 09:10:00" d="2019-07-16 09:40:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Game: When the family's cable television stops working, they resort to a game of Scruples - accompanied by inevitable arguments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 09:40:00" d="2019-07-16 10:10:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Recovering Pessimist: Ray changes his ways after Debra accuses him of being too pessimistic, but his nearest and dearest reckon he has become a bighead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 10:10:00" d="2019-07-16 10:40:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Dial M for Martin: Frasier's unemployed status puts him on edge with everyone and when he blows up at Martin, Roz suggests that Martin moves in with Niles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 10:40:00" d="2019-07-16 11:10:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Hot Ticket: Frasier and Niles fail to get tickets to the hottest show in town, and Daphne's behind appears in the Seattle paper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 11:10:00" d="2019-07-16 12:05:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay tackles a struggling seafood restaurant in Manhattan. The Black Pearl is hampered by debts, kitchen problems and three different owners</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 12:05:00" d="2019-07-16 13:00:00"><n>Undercover Boss USA</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Mitchell Modell, CEO of Modell's Sporting Goods, America's oldest family-owned company selling athletics footwear, clothing and equipment, dons a disguise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 13:00:00" d="2019-07-16 13:05:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 13:05:00" d="2019-07-16 14:05:00"><n u="A New Life in the Sun">A New Life in the Sun IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Two B&amp;B hosts in Spain find out their property is a money-pit. There's trouble brewing for France's novice beer-makers. And the pressure</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 14:05:00" d="2019-07-16 15:10:00"><n>Posh Pawnbrokers</n><e>RF</e>    <k>At London Road in Sheffield, Dan looks at a collection of jewellery being sold to fund a holistic therapy centre. In Penzance, Larry and Neil get all fired</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 15:10:00" d="2019-07-16 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Michaela Strachan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 16:00:00" d="2019-07-16 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2018 &amp; 2019</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun
Scarlette Douglas is in Menorca to help Karl and Naomh, who love the relaxed lifestyle and want a place with outside space</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 17:00:00" d="2019-07-16 18:00:00"><n u="The ?100K Drop">The ?100K Drop III</n><e>F</e>    <k>Jo and June, mother and daughter from Cheshire, and Chris and Billy, a couple from the Midlands, join Davina McCall. Will either pair beat the drop and win the cash? Ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 18:00:00" d="2019-07-16 19:00:00"><n>Kirstie's Celebrity Craft Masters</n><e>F</e>    <k>Reality TV royalty Mark-Francis Vandelli and Queen of Clean Aggie MacKenzie go head to head, with a professional crafter who teaches them how to create</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 19:00:00" d="2019-07-16 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Burns and the Bees: Mr Burns wins a basketball team in a game of poker, but Lisa is left reeling by his proposal to erect a stadium in the same place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 19:30:00" d="2019-07-16 20:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Damon and Maxine go to view their wedding venue, but after some upsetting news, Maxine shocks everyone. Meanwhile, Liam goes on a date with Cindy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 20:00:00" d="2019-07-16 20:55:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Includes sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 20:55:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00"><n>Moon Landing Live</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Moon Landing Live
A daily mission update from the astronauts and Mission Control, as part of Channel 4's real-time live stream of Apollo 11's mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 22:00:00"><n u="Ackley Bridge">Ackley Bridge III (5)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>65% New: Ackley Bridge
Cory is kicked out after being caught with his dad's girlfriend. Hoping for sympathy, Cory is stunned when Naveed is appalled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 22:00:00" d="2019-07-16 23:00:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XVIII</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: 24 Hours in A&amp;E
Greg has been knocked off his motorbike and has critical injuries to his arm and leg. Cara, who's 11, has fallen from a human pyramid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 23:00:00" d="2019-07-17 00:00:00"><n>Drag SOS</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Drag SOS
The Family Gorgeous visits Dudley. Can the drag queens help Dominique rediscover her self-confidence by becoming an intergalactic space queen? (Ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 00:00:00" d="2019-07-17 01:05:00"><n>Let's Talk about Sex</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Let's Talk About Sex
The show looks at how sex education deals with actually having sex and all the baggage that comes with it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 01:05:00" d="2019-07-17 01:55:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon visits a Cuban cafe in Brooklyn. Owners Marcelo and Kata used to be a married couple but now fight over everything, and their bickering is driving customers away</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 01:55:00" d="2019-07-17 02:50:00"><n u="The Crystal Maze">The Crystal Maze VI</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Celebrity Crystal Maze
Sunetra Sarker leads Matthew Wright, Ann Widdecombe, Nikki Sanderson and Wes Nelson in one of the most breakaway entertaining</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 02:50:00" d="2019-07-17 03:45:00"><n>Extreme Tribe: The Last Pygmies</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>In the remote jungles of the Congo, Livia Simoka lives with the Mbendjele pygmies and sees a conflict with a rival tribe turns violent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 03:45:00" d="2019-07-17 04:40:00"><n>My Family Secrets Revealed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Octogenarian Caroline Owen wants a historic secret settled; John Bartlett discovers the shocking truth about his family. And is Dubliner Jeremy Kenny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 04:40:00" d="2019-07-17 05:05:00"><n u="The ?1 Houses: Britain's Cheapest Street">The ?1 Houses: Britain's Cheapest Street II</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The ?1 Houses: Britain's. 
. heapest Street: Victoria organises a Christmas party, but will anyone turn up? John risks all by wanting everything perfect</k>  </p>
</a>
