<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="33" t="2020-04-15 04:27:42"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 05:35:00" d="2020-04-22 06:30:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S I (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Austin Re-Powered: Tim Shaw and Fuzz Townshend head to Suffolk to secretly restore a charismatic but worn-out 1928 Austin 12 Tourer - a 'mobster's car', as Tim puts it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 06:30:00" d="2020-04-22 06:50:00"><n>Kirstie's Vintage Gems</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp brings the swinging 60s to Amber and Colin's seaside pad in Edinburgh's Portobello, with some cool concrete and a class in screen-printing furniture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 06:50:00" d="2020-04-22 07:25:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Nicki Chapman joins Susie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 07:25:00" d="2020-04-22 07:50:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers IV (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Cliffie's Big Score: Carla tells Cliff he's onto a sure thing with Diane, so he invites Diane to the postman's ball, hoping to make a move. Will she attend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 07:50:00" d="2020-04-22 08:15:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers IV (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Second Time Around: After one dinner date with an old flame of Sam's, Frasier announces he is to marry. The regulars agree this is a bad idea</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 08:15:00" d="2020-04-22 08:40:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Separation: Debra is upset by the unexpected news that her parents have separated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 08:40:00" d="2020-04-22 09:05:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Frank Paints the House: Frank offers to decorate Ray's house, but refuses to paint it the colour that Ray and Debra want</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 09:05:00" d="2020-04-22 09:35:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Radio Wars: An unwilling Frasier becomes the butt of pranks by the station's shock jock</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 09:35:00" d="2020-04-22 10:05:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Everyone's a Critic: Frasier and Niles are at loggerheads again when Niles gets a new job as the art critic for a prestigious magazine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 10:05:00" d="2020-04-22 10:30:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Dog That Rocks the Cradle: Martin returns from his friend's funeral upset by how it was conducted. Frasier assures his father that</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 10:30:00" d="2020-04-22 11:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Manchester. The first host, DJ and hairdresser Mozz, makes garlic Stilton mushrooms and poached pear, and pulls out all the stops with a party atmosphere</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 11:00:00" d="2020-04-22 11:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Manchester. Voiceover artist and film extra Matt serves a Jewish Friday night supper, featuring his mum's chicken soup. He has Sharon in hysterics</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 11:30:00" d="2020-04-22 12:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Manchester. Budding author and mum-of-five Cleona hosts with a menu based on her Jamaican roots and regales her guests with tales of her pastimes. (Ep3/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 12:00:00" d="2020-04-22 12:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Manchester. Australian radio content director James hopes some Chinese cuisine, his mum's cake recipe and a laid-back Aussie approach will lift the group's mood. (Ep4/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 12:30:00" d="2020-04-22 13:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Manchester. Events boss Sharon serves up a hearty, decadent menu. But her skills and decorum are put to the test by Cleona. (Ep5/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 13:00:00" d="2020-04-22 14:05:00"><n>The Steph Show</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Live: The Steph Show
Steph McGovern presents the daily programme live from her living room, featuring special guests and the latest information</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 14:05:00" d="2020-04-22 15:10:00"><n u="Sun, Sea and Selling Houses">Sun, Sea and Selling Houses II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Sharon and Steve help Les and Tammy from Fife find a retirement retreat in Almeria. In Alicante, Linda and Manuel help Bristol hotelier Ameena look for a holiday villa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 15:10:00" d="2020-04-22 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Nicki Chapman joins Susie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 16:00:00" d="2020-04-22 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2018 &amp; 2019</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Home or Away
John and Carole have different ideas on where to buy their first home together. Will it be the wild coastline</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 17:00:00" d="2020-04-22 18:00:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY III</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Donna and Paul are hard at work on their most ambitious project yet: creating a tea room. Alex and Ithaca need to raise cash to help repair their 300-year-old roof. Ep14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 18:00:00" d="2020-04-22 19:00:00"><n>Kirstie: Keep Crafting and Carry On</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>53% Kirstie: Keep Crafting and. 
. arry On: Kirstie Allsopp shows us crafts and skills to help us navigate these unique times. Kirstie makes the autumn section</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 19:00:00" d="2020-04-22 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Take My Life, Please: Homer is annoyed when his old high school nemesis Vance Connor gets inducted into the Springfield Walk of Fame</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 19:30:00" d="2020-04-22 20:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>RF</e>    <k>How the Test Was Won: After Bart gets a top score in a test, Lisa is so shocked that she freezes during an exam. Homer is late with an insurance payment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 20:00:00" d="2020-04-22 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 21:00:00" d="2020-04-22 22:00:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer house-hunt in Essex and east London. Kirstie seeks a future-proof home for a go-getting granny, while Phil has some fussy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 22:00:00" d="2020-04-22 23:00:00"><n>New: Can Science Beat the Virus?</n><e>F</e>    <k>As Britain looks beyond politics to science for reassurance, experts come together for a fact-based talk with answers to the big pandemic questions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 23:00:00" d="2020-04-22 23:30:00"><n>Feel Good</n><t>S</t><e>TF</e>    <k>New: Feel Good
Comedy about love and addiction. Mae hits rock bottom after her break-up with George and soon falls back into her old destructive habits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-22 23:30:00" d="2020-04-23 00:00:00"><n u="Friday Night Dinner">Friday Night Dinner VI</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Dad's Birthday: Dad has the birthday blues - he's worked out the date when he's going to die, and 'Horrible Grandma' turns up uninvited. Can Jim's magic do the trick? Ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 00:00:00" d="2020-04-23 01:00:00"><n u="Joe Lycett's Got Your Back">Joe Lycett's Got Your Back II</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Scarlett Moffatt shares her thrifty fast food tips. Joe takes on toll road fines with Atomic Kitten and Kim Woodburn. Plus, car insurance bad practice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 01:00:00" d="2020-04-23 01:50:00"><n u="Wife Swap USA">Wife Swap USA I</n><e>TF</e>    <k>A vegan mother with sugar-obsessed children swaps homes and lives with a meat-loving rancher wife with a bow-hunting husband in the US spouse-switch series. Ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 01:50:00" d="2020-04-23 02:35:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay returns to Woodland Park in Colorado to conclude his attempt to help Italian restaurant Mangia Mangia. Can he work his magic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 02:35:00" d="2020-04-23 03:25:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In north Devon, there's tension at Frankie and Jason's table. Kate and Ian entertain the guests with a bird of prey. And will a surprise discovery</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 03:25:00" d="2020-04-23 05:10:00"><n>The Way Way Back</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Comedy-drama. Liam James stars as a teen who gradually gains some self-confidence over the course of a summer. With Steve Carell, Toni Collette</k>  </p>
</a>
