<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2020-05-27 04:35:38"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 05:30:00" d="2020-06-03 06:20:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S V (10)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Austin Tilly Truck: It's a case of conservation over restoration as Tim and Fuzz tackle a 1941 Austin 10 Utility Truck, a British army relic owned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 06:20:00" d="2020-06-03 06:50:00"><n>Richard &amp; Judy: Keep Reading and Carry On</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Richard &amp; Judy: Keep Reading. 
. nd Carry On: Jo Brand and Tom Allen join Richard and Judy to review Normal People, Louis Theroux tells all about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 06:50:00" d="2020-06-03 07:30:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Kate Adie is in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 07:30:00" d="2020-06-03 07:55:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers VI (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Big Kiss-Off: The competition is intense when Sam and Woody bet on which of them can kiss Rebecca before midnight. Will either of them succeed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 07:55:00" d="2020-06-03 08:20:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers VI (25)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Backseat Becky, Upfront: Evan Drake is moving to Tokyo, so Rebecca drives him to the airport and takes the opportunity to confess her feelings. But he has a favour to ask</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 08:20:00" d="2020-06-03 08:45:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Sister-in-Law: Trouble brews in the Barone family when Robert's wife Amy finds out that Ray thinks she is in the habit of talking too much</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 08:45:00" d="2020-06-03 09:10:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Power of No: Ray tries to make himself more desirable in Debra's eyes by playing hard to get, but there's trouble when she finds out what he's up to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 09:10:00" d="2020-06-03 09:35:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly IV</n><e>RF</e>    <k>What Molly Hath Wrought: Molly decides to take a break from writing her novel and accepts a job as a forklift truck driver at Vince's warehouse, with mixed results. Ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 09:35:00" d="2020-06-03 10:00:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly IV</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Mike &amp; Molly's Excellent Adventure: Molly encourages Mike to embrace anything he wants in life. They try new things together, but reality</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 10:00:00" d="2020-06-03 10:30:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Analyzed Kiss: Frasier shares an unexpected kiss with Julia while trying to steal files from her ex's office. Niles enjoys a trip to the shooting range</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 10:30:00" d="2020-06-03 11:00:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>A New Position for Roz: Roz prepares to leave the radio station and join a rival company, but not before voicing her concerns about Frasier's new relationship with Julia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 11:00:00" d="2020-06-03 11:30:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>No Sex Please, We're Skittish: Roz isn't pleased when the station announces that it's found a replacement for her, but if she stays she'll</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 11:30:00" d="2020-06-03 12:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Swindon and Marlborough. The first host, super-confident software salesman Simon, hopes to impress with a night full of charm and hearty home-cooked food. (Ep1/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 12:00:00" d="2020-06-03 12:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Swindon and Marlborough. Business consultant Linda serves a game-based menu including pheasant and venison, and pastry swans. But Simon puts the cat among the pigeons. (Ep2/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 12:30:00" d="2020-06-03 13:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>Swindon and Marlborough. Parisienne Saleha serves up a vegetarian meal. with a side of steak tartare. (Ep3/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 13:00:00" d="2020-06-03 13:05:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 13:05:00" d="2020-06-03 13:35:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Swindon and Marlborough. Expectations are high as drama teacher Ben puts on a Middle Eastern and Asian menu. Simon raises eyebrows when he calls the group 'vanilla'. (Ep4/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 13:35:00" d="2020-06-03 14:05:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Swindon and Marlborough. Ex-military police officer Debs treats her guests to a medieval feast of local legends, including 'flying monk' and 'lamb</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 14:05:00" d="2020-06-03 15:10:00"><n u="A New Life in the Sun">A New Life in the Sun V</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>With a bar full of customers, two twenty-somethings battle with a dodgy pizza oven. A diving school's boat breaks down. And two gite owners receive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 15:10:00" d="2020-06-03 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Kate Adie is in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 16:00:00" d="2020-06-03 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Belinda and Alan from Essex want to buy a holiday home near the seaside resort of La Cala de Mijas on Spain's Costa del Sol. Laura Hamilton shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 17:00:00" d="2020-06-03 18:00:00"><n>Work on the Wild Side</n><e>F</e>    <k>Vets and volunteers rescue and rehabilitate animals in South Africa. Harriet's on a mission to save three naughty elephants and Debbie deals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 18:00:00" d="2020-06-03 19:00:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Sheffield, Ray and Chloe, Andrew and Claire, and Rob and Emma compete in a week featuring dinner party beginners, kitchen mishaps and Mr Bean impressions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 19:00:00" d="2020-06-03 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Great Wife Hope: The male citizens of Springfield become obsessed with the brutal sport of Ultimate Punching, and Marge ends up getting challenged</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 19:30:00" d="2020-06-03 20:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Treehouse of Horror XX: Bart and Lisa seek revenge on their teachers, Krusty's fast-food snack turns the citizens of Springfield into zombies, and Moe's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 20:00:00" d="2020-06-03 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 21:00:00" d="2020-06-03 22:00:00"><n u="Location, Location, Location">Location, Location, Location XXXII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer search Brighton and Hove on behalf of an anxious former hot air balloon pilot and a family who need their own space. Ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 22:00:00" d="2020-06-03 23:00:00"><n>New: Britain's Coronavirus...</n><e>F</e>    <k>. atastrophe: Did the Government Get It Wrong? Dispatches: Britain's confirmed Covid-19 death rate is one of the world's highest. Why? Antony Barnett</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 23:00:00" d="2020-06-04 00:05:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XVII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Sean Lock and David Mitchell take on Jon Richardson and Sara Pascoe. Ellie White and Natasia Demetriou join Susie Dent in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 00:05:00" d="2020-06-04 01:10:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox XV</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Britain's sharpest armchair critics share more of their insightful, passionate and sometimes emotional critiques of the week's biggest and best shows. Ep15)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 01:10:00" d="2020-06-04 02:30:00"><n>Hitched at Home: Our Lockdown...</n><e>R</e>    <k>. edding: As 60,000 British couples put their nuptials on ice due to Covid-19, First Dates's Fred Sirieix pulls out all the stops to give one couple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 02:30:00" d="2020-06-04 03:20:00"><n>Spring at Jimmy's Farm</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>As the end of spring approaches, work doesn't slow down at Jimmy's farm, as new calves need tending to and Steve McQueen, the escape-artist meerkat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 03:20:00" d="2020-06-04 04:10:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay travels to Carlstadt, New Jersey, to try to save the Grasshopper Also, a family-owned Irish restaurant that's on its last legs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 04:10:00" d="2020-06-04 05:05:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Gloucestershire, Debbie and Paul, Angela and John, and Kirsty and James compete in a week featuring a malfunctioning blender, a singing dog and plenty of catty comments</k>  </p>
</a>
