<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="33" t="2020-04-16 04:33:57"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 05:10:00" d="2020-04-23 06:00:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie and Phil are in west London. Professional rugby player Alex and his teacher wife Sarah are shocked by the speed of the market. Marion and Fraser</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 06:00:00" d="2020-04-23 06:50:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S I (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Zodiac Come Back: Tim and Fuzz head to Norfolk to revive an ageing Ford Zodiac, but tensions rise when Fuzz changes the paintwork back to its original colour scheme</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 06:50:00" d="2020-04-23 07:25:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Nicki Chapman joins Susie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 07:25:00" d="2020-04-23 07:50:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers IV (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Peterson Principle: Norm struggles with his conscience when he hears gossip that could win him a promotion by wrecking the chances of the other candidate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 07:50:00" d="2020-04-23 08:15:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers IV (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Dark Imaginings: Sam becomes increasingly aware of his age when he dates a younger woman he has nothing in common with and is admitted to hospital with a medical problem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 08:15:00" d="2020-04-23 08:40:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Angry Family: The whole family meet the school's counsellor and a local clergyman to uncover why there's constant bickering between them and Michael's parents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 08:40:00" d="2020-04-23 09:05:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Odd Man Out: Frank forces Marco to choose either Marie or him as a friend. Ray sides with Frank because he doesn't approve of his mother having a male friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 09:05:00" d="2020-04-23 09:35:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Rivals: Frasier and Niles compete for the attention of the same woman at a party. At least they think it's the same woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 09:35:00" d="2020-04-23 10:05:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>A Tsar Is Born: Frasier and Niles discover that they may be Russian royalty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 10:05:00" d="2020-04-23 10:30:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Late Doctor Crane: Frasier's name becomes confused with another in casualty. The next day, his death is announced on television and he reads his own obituary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 10:30:00" d="2020-04-23 11:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The first host in Newcastle, ballroom dance instructor Stuart, plans a rainbow-themed night with colourful food and a visit from one of the north east's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 11:00:00" d="2020-04-23 11:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>On the second night in and around Newcastle, geezer Adam plans a menu of fine dining and gastropub grub. But some of his guests prove hard to please</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 11:30:00" d="2020-04-23 12:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>On day three in and around Newcastle, horse-mad nursing student Harriet throws a party themed around her equestrian hobby, including space hopper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 12:00:00" d="2020-04-23 12:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Newcastle, videographer Jude hopes her experimental vegetarian menu can win over her meat-eating guests, on a night that features a lost voice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 12:30:00" d="2020-04-23 13:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the final night in and around Newcastle and Mo's turn to host. After two nights with no voice, Mo is back on form with a menu of traditional South African dishes. (Ep5/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 13:00:00" d="2020-04-23 14:05:00"><n>The Steph Show</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Live: The Steph Show
Steph McGovern presents the daily programme live from her living room, featuring special guests and the latest information</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 14:05:00" d="2020-04-23 15:10:00"><n u="Sun, Sea and Selling Houses">Sun, Sea and Selling Houses II (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Sharon and Shaun help Berkshire couple Graham and Trish find a retirement retreat in Almeria. In Alicante, Sophie Rodriguez's clients are Dublin cabbie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 15:10:00" d="2020-04-23 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Nicki Chapman joins Susie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 16:00:00" d="2020-04-23 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2018 &amp; 2019</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun
Tracey and Stephen from Staffordshire, who've been married for 38 years, want to make a permanent move to Malaga. Can Ben Hillman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 17:00:00" d="2020-04-23 18:00:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY III</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Strawbridge family head to the beaches of Saint-Malo to seek out chateau inspiration. Donna and Paul invite the mayor to the grand opening of their new tea room. Ep15)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 18:00:00" d="2020-04-23 19:00:00"><n>Kirstie: Keep Crafting and Carry On</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>53% Kirstie: Keep Crafting and. 
. arry On: Kirstie Allsopp shows us crafts and skills to help us navigate these unique times. Kirstie makes the winter panel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 19:00:00" d="2020-04-23 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>RF</e>    <k>No Loan Again, Naturally: When Homer and Marge's adjustable-rate mortgage skyrockets, they are forced to put their house up for sale - and it's bought</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 19:30:00" d="2020-04-23 20:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Gone Maggie Gone: When Springfield experiences a total solar eclipse, Marge damages her vision because Homer has stolen her gadget for viewing it safely</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 20:00:00" d="2020-04-23 21:05:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 21:05:00" d="2020-04-23 22:00:00"><n>Grayson's Art Club</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Grayson's Art Club
Grayson Perry gets people to send in their artworks of animals - a beloved pet, an abstract, or an exotic animal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 22:00:00" d="2020-04-23 23:00:00"><n>What's It Like to Catch Coronavirus?</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: What's It Like to Catch. 
. oronavirus?: Channel 4 has given cameras to people across the UK, to film themselves as they battle the virus, supported</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-23 23:00:00" d="2020-04-24 00:00:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XVII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>This episode meets patients who do extraordinary things for the people they love, under difficult circumstances. David has severe leg pain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-24 00:00:00" d="2020-04-24 01:00:00"><n u="Celebrity SAS: Who Dares Wins">Celebrity SAS: Who Dares Wins II</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Twelve celebrities, from Katie Price to Joey Essex, leave their glamorous homes to take on the SAS selection course, the toughest challenge of their lives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-24 01:00:00" d="2020-04-24 01:55:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon makes the first of two visits to Zayna Flaming Grill, a Mediterranean restaurant owned by Faye and her niece Brenda in Redondo Beach. The food isn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-24 01:55:00" d="2020-04-24 02:20:00"><n>Feel Good</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Comedy about love and addiction. Mae hits rock bottom after her break-up with George and soon falls back into her old destructive habits. Is she a lost cause? (Ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-24 02:20:00" d="2020-04-24 03:15:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Devon, Matt and Sarah admit to not knowing what scallops or celeriac are, Jake and Ian question the canapés (crisps), while foodies James and Laura</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-24 03:15:00" d="2020-04-24 04:10:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick IX (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>The Supervet
Professor Noel Fitzpatrick's patients include a shih-tzu cross with deformed legs, a golden retriever who needs a tumour removed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-24 04:10:00" d="2020-04-24 05:05:00"><n u="Grand Designs Australia">Grand Designs Australia VII</n><e>F</e>    <k>IT engineer Damien from Canberra combines green building materials with commercial elements to create a zero-carbon family home with sophisticated</k>  </p>
</a>
