<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="31" t="2020-05-30 04:37:05"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 05:15:00" d="2020-06-06 06:10:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp helps Stuart and Lara find a home near Amersham in Buckinghamshire after living 100 miles apart. Phil Spencer meets Randhir and Sheetal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 06:10:00" d="2020-06-06 07:00:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S VII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Lotus Elise: Tim and Fuzz take on the task of restoring a British pocket rocket - a 1997 Lotus Elise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 07:00:00" d="2020-06-06 07:25:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>I Wish I Were Gus: Ray is chosen to give the eulogy at his great uncle's funeral, but he gets more than he bargained for when his aunt turns up to rekindle a family feud</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 07:25:00" d="2020-06-06 07:50:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Standard Deviation: Robert asks Ray and Debra to complete IQ tests as part of his criminal psychology class, but then tells each of them that they scored the highest mark</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 07:50:00" d="2020-06-06 08:10:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Look, Don't Touch: Debra is suspicious when Angelina, a waitress at Nemo's, calls Ray at home. Although it's all perfectly innocent, Ray feels guilty</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 08:10:00" d="2020-06-06 08:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Celebration Experimentation: The gang persuade Sheldon to celebrate his birthday and invite a few special guests along to his party in the 200th episode</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 08:30:00" d="2020-06-06 08:50:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Application Deterioration: Leonard, Sheldon and Howard run into problems when they file for a patent. Emily reaches out to Raj after their break-up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 08:50:00" d="2020-06-06 09:15:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Solder Excursion Diversion: Sheldon makes a surprise revelation when Amy buys him a new laptop. Leonard and Howard lie to their wives to avoid an errand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 09:15:00" d="2020-06-06 09:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Big Bear Precipitation: Sheldon shares a secret about Leonard when the two of them go on a weekend trip to a cabin in the country with Amy and Penny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 09:35:00" d="2020-06-06 10:05:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Simpson Tide: Homer, Barney and Moe become trapped in a nuclear submarine in a combat situation. Then Homer accidentally ejects the captain (guest star Rod Steiger)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 10:05:00" d="2020-06-06 10:35:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Trouble with Trillions: Homer and Mr Burns go on the run to Cuba with a trillion-dollar note that Mr Burns was meant to deliver to post-war Europe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 10:35:00" d="2020-06-06 11:05:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Homer the Whopper: When Homer is chosen to appear in a superhero movie, the film studio hires a celebrity trainer (guest star Seth Rogen)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 11:05:00" d="2020-06-06 11:35:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Bart Gets a 'Z': When Edna Krabappel confiscates all her students' phones, Bart gets revenge by spiking her coffee with alcohol, prompting Principal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 11:35:00" d="2020-06-06 12:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>RF</e>    <k>The Great Wife Hope: The male citizens of Springfield become obsessed with the brutal sport of Ultimate Punching, and Marge ends up getting challenged</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 12:00:00" d="2020-06-06 13:55:00"><n>The Boxtrolls</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Oscar-nominated animation. Sometimes scary and badly behaved - but ultimately harmless - trolls living below a hilltop town face extermination</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 13:55:00" d="2020-06-06 14:55:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Liverpool. Dramatic duo Ryan and Kitty serve family classics with a twist. Hairdresser Karen and builder Alun host a sophisticated night. And talkative</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 14:55:00" d="2020-06-06 15:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Carolyn and her daughter Galatea hope that their peaceful woodland cabins at the North Star Club in Yorkshire will impress their guests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 15:25:00" d="2020-06-06 15:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Luke and John claim to be the unique selling point at their establishment, Friends B&amp;B in Blackpool. But some of the feedback leaves a bitter taste</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 15:55:00" d="2020-06-06 16:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>For the third visit, the group head to the Lincoln Holiday Retreat, which Debbie has built from the ground up over the past 20 years. But Carolyn finds the decor dated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 16:25:00" d="2020-06-06 16:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Mark and Heidi pride themselves on offering something different in their converted chapel - called The Chapel - in Harrogate. But one guest is concerned</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 16:55:00" d="2020-06-06 17:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the final day, and the owners meet for the last time to settle some scores. After dramatic discoveries and cutting comments, the payments are revealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 17:25:00" d="2020-06-06 18:30:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Musician Donagh is taking the giant step of relocating to the vibrant Spanish city of Valencia. Can Scarlette Douglas find him the perfect city pad for ?125,000?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 18:30:00" d="2020-06-06 19:25:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>R</e>    <k>Richard and Felicia set out to turn a vast underground water reservoir near the Humber Estuary into a family home: an almighty feat of engineering</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 19:25:00" d="2020-06-06 19:55:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4 news with sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 19:55:00" d="2020-06-06 22:15:00"><n>Life of Pi</n><e>R</e>    <k>Ang Lee's Oscar-winning adventure. A young Indian boy is cast adrift in a lifeboat with a Bengal tiger when his family's voyage to Canada goes badly wrong. Scenes of threat</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 22:15:00" d="2020-06-07 00:45:00"><n>Miss Peregrine's Home for...</n><e>RF</e>    <k>. eculiar Children: (2016) Eva Green and Asa Butterfield star in Tim Burton's fantasy adventure. A teenager enters the magical, but scary and violent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 00:45:00" d="2020-06-07 02:20:00"><n>Big Game</n><e>R</e>    <k>Action-adventure starring Samuel L. Jackson and Onni Tommila. In a forest in Finland, a timid local boy attempts to save the US president from terrorists</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 02:20:00" d="2020-06-07 03:15:00"><n>The Last Leg</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Last Leg: Locked Down Under
Adam Hills, Josh Widdicombe and Alex Brooker host from their homes in Australia and the UK with their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 03:15:00" d="2020-06-07 03:40:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Pranks and Greens: Bart is determined to seek out the best prankster in Springfield Elementary's history to ask him all about his legendary practical jokes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 03:40:00" d="2020-06-07 04:30:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>In Boston, Gordon Ramsay visits an Italian restaurant that's been run into the ground by brothers Frank and Anthony. Can they learn to trust each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 04:30:00" d="2020-06-07 05:20:00"><n>Hollyoaks: Omnibus</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>49% Hollyoaks Omnibus
Nancy debates whether she can ever trust Kyle again. Jordan and Leela have a heart-to-heart. An uninvited guest makes a shock</k>  </p>
</a>
