<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="24" t="2020-05-31 04:35:38"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 05:20:00" d="2020-06-07 06:10:00"><n u="Grand Designs New Zealand">Grand Designs New Zealand III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>A couple use energy-efficient insulated panels to build a retirement home near the tidal estuary at Nelson on the South Island, inspired by fruit-packing sheds. Ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 06:10:00" d="2020-06-07 07:00:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S VII (2)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Peugeot 504: Tim Shaw and Fuzz Townshend take on Barry's 1972 Peugeot 504 cabriolet - a rare French classic that has seen better days</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 07:00:00" d="2020-06-07 07:25:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Frank, the Writer: Frank submits ideas for a column to Ray's editor after getting anecdotes published in Reader's Digest. But Ray's editor thinks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 07:25:00" d="2020-06-07 07:50:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Your Place or Mine?: When Ray's parents fall out, his mum moves in with him and Debra. But Debra isn't happy and tries to convince Ray's dad to apologise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 07:50:00" d="2020-06-07 08:10:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Viewing Party Combustion: During a get-together to watch TV at the flat, a minor argument between Sheldon and Leonard escalates into a heated debate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 08:10:00" d="2020-06-07 08:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Fermentation Bifurcation: The gang run into Penny's ex-boyfriend, Zack, at a wine bar. Bernadette, who can't drink, hangs out with Sheldon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 08:30:00" d="2020-06-07 09:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Treehouse of Horror XX: Bart and Lisa seek revenge on their teachers, Krusty's fast-food snack turns the citizens of Springfield into zombies, and Moe's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 09:00:00" d="2020-06-07 09:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>RF</e>    <k>The Devil Wears Nada: Marge and her friends raise money for charity by posing for a racy calendar, but Marge is too shy to show off her body, until</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 09:30:00" d="2020-06-07 10:30:00"><n u="Bake Off: The Professionals">Bake Off: The Professionals III</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The five remaining teams make the classic layered dessert millefeuille, master the art of illusion, and create a bird-themed piece montée adorned with Paris-Brest. Ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 10:30:00" d="2020-06-07 13:30:00"><n>Sunday Brunch</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Live: Sunday Brunch
Tim Lovejoy and Simon Rimmer host the food and chat show with celebrity guests including Fearne Cotton and music from Mahalia</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 13:30:00" d="2020-06-07 14:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>RF</e>    <k>O Brother, Where Bart Thou?: Bart grows jealous of Lisa's relationship with Maggie and asks Homer if he can have a baby brother. Featuring Kim Cattrall</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 14:00:00" d="2020-06-07 14:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Rednecks and Broomsticks: Homer spends time with Cletus and his pals when he discovers that they are making moonshine. Lisa gets to know three teenage Wiccans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 14:30:00" d="2020-06-07 17:40:00"><n>World Cup Final '66: England v...</n>    <k>. est Germany: A chance to watch the 1966 World Cup Final alongside Geoff Hurst, Gabby Logan and other stars, in a charity re-run for the National</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 17:40:00" d="2020-06-07 18:45:00"><n>Celebrity Deal or No Deal:...</n><e>RF</e>    <k>. onathan Ross: Noel Edmonds hosts a celebrity edition of the classic game show as TV presenter Jonathan Ross battles with the Banker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 18:45:00" d="2020-06-07 19:15:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4 news with sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 19:15:00" d="2020-06-07 20:15:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau">Escape to the Chateau V (6)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>It's harvest time at Dick and Angel's chateau. But the family also find time to make over the basement, convert the old piggery into a chicken</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 20:15:00" d="2020-06-07 21:15:00"><n>The Fantastical Factory of Curious Craft</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Keith Lemon's Fantastical. 
. actory of Curious Craft: Keith Lemon hosts as the amateur crafters make superhero costumes and then a Scottish-themed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 21:15:00" d="2020-06-07 22:15:00"><n>Britain's Most Expensive Home</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Britain's Most Expensive Home:. 
. uilding for a Billionaire: Documentary following billionaire John Caudwell as his ?65 million property refurbishment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 22:15:00" d="2020-06-07 23:15:00"><n>New: Murder in the Outback: The...</n><e>F</e>    <k>. alconio and Lees Mystery: Over four nights, leading experts launch a detailed re-investigation of the infamous case of abduction and death</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-07 23:15:00" d="2020-06-08 00:15:00"><n u="Celebrity Gogglebox">Celebrity Gogglebox II</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Some of Britain's best-loved personalities hit the sofa to watch the week's biggest TV shows, including Zoe Ball, Harry Redknapp, Denise van Outen and Nick Grimshaw. Ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 00:15:00" d="2020-06-08 02:30:00"><n>Joy</n>    <k>Fact-based drama about a single mother (Jennifer Lawrence) who invents a miracle household tool that changes her life. Also starring Robert De Niro and Bradley Cooper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 02:30:00" d="2020-06-08 03:20:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>In Bridgeport, Connecticut, Gordon Ramsay visits Cafe Tavolini, a restaurant that is being neglected as the couple who run it teeter on the edge of divorce</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 03:20:00" d="2020-06-08 04:15:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In north Wales, country types Des and Jo, fake tan lover Kev and his fiancée Victoria and property professionals Les and Vicky compete</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 04:15:00" d="2020-06-08 05:10:00"><n>Grayson's Art Club</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>This episode celebrates all things Britain, from the clap for carers to our 'national spirit' - featuring Liza Tarbuck, British artists the Singh Twins</k>  </p>
</a>
