<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="28" t="2019-08-13 02:13:23"><p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 06:05:00" d="2019-08-18 06:20:00"><n>Kirstie's Handmade Treasures</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp's battle in the afternoon tea tent at the Devon County Show is not for the faint-hearted. What will the judges think of her scones</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 06:20:00" d="2019-08-18 07:15:00"><n u="The ?100K Drop">The ?100K Drop III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Davina McCall is joined by David and Jon, a couple from Torquay, and Grimsby couple Millie and Scott. Will either pair take home the cash? Ep24)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 07:15:00" d="2019-08-18 07:40:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>Ovary Action: Doug's parents' visit coincides with Carrie's 'fertile time'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 07:40:00" d="2019-08-18 08:05:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>Food Fight: Carrie is jealous when Doug falls for Spence's new girlfriend's excellent cooking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 08:05:00" d="2019-08-18 08:30:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Tortelli Tort: When waitress Carla attacks an obnoxious sports fan who is making trouble at the bar, the man threatens to sue the establishment unless</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 08:30:00" d="2019-08-18 09:00:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers I (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Sam at Eleven: Sam is delighted when an old baseball teammate arrives to film a sports report about him, but his ego is shattered when he finds himself</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 09:00:00" d="2019-08-18 09:30:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Hungry Heart: In a comedy of mistaken identity, Frasier intercedes to save station manager Kenny's marriage by diverting him from a rendezvous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 09:30:00" d="2019-08-18 10:00:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Hooping Cranes: Frasier agrees to take his dad and Niles to the basketball, but can't believe his eyes when Niles is plucked out of the crowd and given</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 10:00:00" d="2019-08-18 10:30:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Docu Drama: Frasier can't narrate Roz's ambitious space documentary, so she turns to legendary space hero and US senator John Glenn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 10:30:00" d="2019-08-18 13:30:00"><n>Sunday Brunch</n><e>F</e>    <k>Tim Lovejoy and Simon Rimmer host the Sunday food and chat show. Guests include Amanda Abbington, Laurie Kynaston and Jamie Demetriou. Plus Slaves perform live in the studio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 13:30:00" d="2019-08-18 14:00:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIV (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>87% Dark Knight Court: When Bart is accused of playing a prank on the school marching band - a prank he says he didn't commit - Lisa must step in to defend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 14:00:00" d="2019-08-18 14:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIV (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>87% Pulpit Friction: Homer is recruited as a deacon by a trendy new reverend at the church. Dry cleaners mistakenly swap Marge's wedding dress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 14:30:00" d="2019-08-18 14:55:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIV (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>87% The Fabulous Faker Boy: Marge encourages Bart to explore his creative side by having piano lessons. Homer loses the last two hairs on his head but keeps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 14:55:00" d="2019-08-18 15:25:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXIV (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>87% The Saga of Carl: When Homer, Moe, Lenny and Carl win the Springfield Lottery, Carl goes to cash in the ticket but fails to return and runs off to Iceland with the winnings</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 15:25:00" d="2019-08-18 17:50:00"><n>We Bought a Zoo</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Fact-based family comedy-drama. Matt Damon stars as a father who moves his family to the Californian countryside, where they renovate a dilapidated zoo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 17:50:00" d="2019-08-18 18:35:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2017 &amp; 2018</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Winter Sun
In an updated version of a previous episode, Jasmine Harman meets Bernie and George Wilks, who have sold up</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 18:35:00" d="2019-08-18 19:30:00"><n>The Yorkshire Dales and The Lakes</n><t>S</t><e>TF</e>    <k>The Yorkshire Dales and the Lakes
Michelin-star chef Kevin Tickle goes foraging. Gamekeeper David prepares for a shoot in Wensleydale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 19:30:00" d="2019-08-18 20:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Includes sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 20:00:00" d="2019-08-18 21:00:00"><n>George Clarke's Amazing Spaces</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: George Clarke's Amazing. 
. paces: George rediscovers the most ingenious vehicle projects he's seen, including a helicopter, a camper</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 21:00:00" d="2019-08-18 22:00:00"><n>The Queen's Lost Family</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: The Queen's Lost Family
After George V's death, Edward proves himself the King some feared he would be: resolved to marry American divorcee Wallis Simpson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 22:00:00" d="2019-08-18 23:05:00"><n u="The Handmaid's Tale">The Handmaid's Tale III</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: The Handmaid's Tale
Liars: June must rely on an unpredictable Commander Lawrence to execute her plan, but a terrifying return to a place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 23:05:00" d="2019-08-19 00:10:00"><n>Cruises, Trains, Holidays &amp; Flights from Hell</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Flights from Hell Caught on. 
. amera: From airport tantrums to on-board brawls, this programme reveals some of the most dramatic, extraordinary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 00:10:00" d="2019-08-19 01:25:00"><n>No Second Chance</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: No Second Chance: Walter. 
. resents: Thriller. An attack leaves Alice injured, her husband murdered, and her daughter kidnapped. The detectives</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 01:25:00" d="2019-08-19 02:15:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>In the first half of a two-part Nightmare, Gordon tries to save The Burger Kitchen in Los Angeles, which is run by a dysfunctional family in a state of constant conflict</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 02:15:00" d="2019-08-19 03:00:00"><n>Undercover Boss USA</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Scott Gerber, CEO of hospitality business the Gerber Group, goes undercover in his own organisation to make sure it is maintaining the reputation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 03:00:00" d="2019-08-19 03:55:00"><n u="Jamie and Jimmy's Friday Night Feast">Jamie and Jimmy's Friday Night Feast VI</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jamie and Jimmy's Friday Night. 
. east: Jamie and Jimmy bring back memories for Sir Patrick Stewart. Jimmy creates a rotating garden, and they discover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 03:55:00" d="2019-08-19 04:50:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Milton Keynes, Becky hopes to impress her guests with a menu that has cheese in every course. But the atmosphere turns heated; can Chris</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 04:50:00" d="2019-08-19 05:45:00"><n u="Grand Designs New Zealand">Grand Designs New Zealand III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>A mother of six from Helensville, north-west of Auckland, aims to recreate a historic villa she fell in love with as a child but her husband wants a modern house. Ep1)</k>  </p>
</a>
