<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2019-07-11 00:18:51"><p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 05:05:00" d="2019-07-17 05:55:00"><n u="Grand Designs New Zealand">Grand Designs New Zealand I (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>A builder and his wife create a hand-crafted American Gothic-style house, complete with ornate detailing such as spandrels and lacework valances, near Auckland</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 05:55:00" d="2019-07-17 06:50:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Glasgow, John hopes his Scottish themed night will wow his guests. And how will non-Scottish contestant Peter fare when he attempts some traditional local food?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 06:50:00" d="2019-07-17 07:25:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Michaela Strachan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 07:25:00" d="2019-07-17 07:55:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers XI (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Daddy's Little Middle-Aged Girl: Rebecca's father tries to persuade her to move back into the family home in San Diego. Woody and Kelly can't agree about where to live</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 07:55:00" d="2019-07-17 08:20:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers XI (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Love Me, Love My Car: When Sam hears the friend who bought his beloved car has died, he plots and schemes to get it back. Rebecca takes to Woody and Kelly's pet pig</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 08:20:00" d="2019-07-17 08:45:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>Hungry Man: Doug turns up hungry - and half-naked - at Carrie's sophisticated work function</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 08:45:00" d="2019-07-17 09:10:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>Time Share: Doug and Carrie befriend their annoying neighbours in order to get a free holiday. And Arthur develops a nasty rash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 09:10:00" d="2019-07-17 09:40:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Dog: Ray and Robert both want to keep a stray bulldog that Ray brings home, but it turns out that the canine isn't so stray after all</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 09:40:00" d="2019-07-17 10:10:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Neighbors: Ray's neighbours demand a meeting at his house to discuss what to do about his noisy dad Frank and interfering mum Marie. But then Frank and Marie arrive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 10:10:00" d="2019-07-17 10:40:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>First Do No Harm: Frasier undertakes huge projects to make up for being unemployed, while Martin persuades him to date Duke's daughter Marie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 10:40:00" d="2019-07-17 11:10:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Secret Admirer: Frasier mistakenly thinks he has a secret admirer while he's dating an attractive new woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 11:10:00" d="2019-07-17 12:05:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>J Willy's Bar &amp; Grille in South Bend, Indiana, is more than a million dollars in debt. Can Gordon Ramsay bring some discipline into the kitchen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 12:05:00" d="2019-07-17 13:00:00"><n>Undercover Boss USA</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Ron Lynch, the founder and President of Tilted Kilt Pub &amp; Eatery, one of the USA's fastest growing chains of sports pubs, goes incognito to work among his own staff</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 13:00:00" d="2019-07-17 13:05:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 13:05:00" d="2019-07-17 14:05:00"><n u="A New Life in the Sun">A New Life in the Sun IV</n><e>R</e>    <k>There's little glamour for the B&amp;B hosts in Spain. Could a new ale be an epic fail in France? And two British sailing instructors start</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 14:05:00" d="2019-07-17 15:10:00"><n>Posh Pawnbrokers</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Larry and Neil at Cashbrokers in Penzance look at a vintage fairground slide in the shape of a giant head, and test-driving a unique hand-built</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 15:10:00" d="2019-07-17 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Rory Bremner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 16:00:00" d="2019-07-17 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2018 &amp; 2019</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun
Paul and Bev want to fulfil their lifelong dream of relocating to Torrevieja, Spain. With ?100,000 to spend on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 17:00:00" d="2019-07-17 18:00:00"><n u="The ?100K Drop">The ?100K Drop III</n>    <k>Davina McCall is joined by Jordan and Mo, grandson and grandfather from Portsmouth, and Kate and Lucy, who are best friends from Yorkshire. But will either pair win big? Ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 18:00:00" d="2019-07-17 19:00:00"><n>Kirstie's Celebrity Craft Masters</n><e>F</e>    <k>Comedians Rufus Hound and Jenny Eclair go head to head, each paired with a professional crafter, who teaches them to create foot stools and quilled creations. (Ep13)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 19:00:00" d="2019-07-17 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Lisa the Drama Queen: Lisa befriends Juliet (guest Emily Blunt), an equally talented and clever girl. Together, they create a fantasy world that takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 19:30:00" d="2019-07-17 20:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Sienna is on a mission to get what is hers. Cindy realises Liam's true intentions. And Sadie returns with a demand for Liam. Also, Dr Levi wants Maxine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 20:00:00" d="2019-07-17 20:55:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Includes sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 20:55:00" d="2019-07-17 21:00:00"><n>Moon Landing Live</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Moon Landing Live
A daily mission update from the astronauts and Mission Control, as part of Channel 4's real-time live stream of Apollo 11's mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 21:00:00" d="2019-07-17 22:00:00"><n u="The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick">The Supervet: Noel Fitzpatrick XIV</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: The Supervet Noel Fitzpatrick
A bull terrier puppy needs a 3D printed implant for a new lease of life. A Siamese cat has multiple injuries after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 22:00:00" d="2019-07-17 23:00:00"><n>The Invention of Boris Johnson</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: The Invention of Boris. 
. ohnson: This documentary sifts through Boris Johnson's archive interviews and newspaper columns to build a compelling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 23:00:00" d="2019-07-17 23:35:00"><n u="GameFace">GameFace II (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: GameFace
The award-winning comedy with Roisin Conaty returns. Marcella takes her driving test and has a date with Jon. All seems well</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-17 23:35:00" d="2019-07-18 00:35:00"><n>Generation Porn</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Generation Porn
Generation Porn explores the free porn revolution by meeting people who make porn and people who watch it. This episode visits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-18 00:35:00" d="2019-07-18 01:35:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates XII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Serial dater Jack, who's looking for a 'naughty sort', thinks his luck's in when he meets glamorous fire-breather Safina. But will his laddish charm impress her? Ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-18 01:35:00" d="2019-07-18 02:25:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon travels to New York to visit PJ's Steakhouse. Owners Joe and Madalyn are in serious debt after opening the high-end restaurant and are struggling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-18 02:25:00" d="2019-07-18 03:15:00"><n>Catch-22</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Drama based on Joseph Heller's seminal novel of the same name. On a surreal trip, Yossarian begins to realise the magnitude and influence of Milo's business empire. (Ep4/6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-18 03:15:00" d="2019-07-18 04:05:00"><n>Undercover Boss Australia and Canada</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Undercover Boss Australia
In this episode, an Australian high-flier goes undercover at one of Australia's largest supermarket chains, Ritchies Stores</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-18 04:05:00" d="2019-07-18 04:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Treehouse of Horror XIX: In the Halloween special, Homer tries to vote for Barack Obama but the machine is rigged to place votes for John McCain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-18 04:30:00" d="2019-07-18 05:25:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>In Glasgow, will David woo his guests with a modern-day Irish menu featuring a very special cabbage pesto. And Liz blows everyone away with her bling</k>  </p>
</a>
