<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2020-05-16 04:52:56"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 05:25:00" d="2020-05-23 05:50:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>East Hampshire. The final host, glamorous Sue, throws a Caribbean-themed party that ends with some down-and-dirty dancing. (Ep5/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 05:50:00" d="2020-05-23 06:45:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer are in the budget-busting capital, looking for properties for friends Sam and Michael, and London-born Nishita, who plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 06:45:00" d="2020-05-23 07:05:00"><n>Kirstie's Handmade Treasures</n><e>RF</e>    <k>What will the judges in the afternoon tea tent at the Devon County Show think of Kirstie Allsopp's unconventional kumquat éclairs?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 07:05:00" d="2020-05-23 07:30:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Security: After Robert takes a second job selling security systems, he reveals he's been asked to join the firm and is mulling over retiring from the police force</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 07:30:00" d="2020-05-23 07:55:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Ingrate: Debra is hurt when Ray receives an honorary doctorate and thanks everyone except her in his acceptance speech</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 07:55:00" d="2020-05-23 08:20:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Crazy Chin: Amy's parents put Robert on the defensive when they point out his strange habit of touching food to his chin before he eats it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 08:20:00" d="2020-05-23 08:40:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Bachelor Party Corrosion: The guys' science skills are tested when they get a flat tyre during Leonard's surprise bachelor party weekend in Mexico</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 08:40:00" d="2020-05-23 09:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The 2003 Approximation: Sheldon sulks when Penny and Leonard announce that they're moving in together. Howard and Raj form a band to play at the comic book shop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 09:00:00" d="2020-05-23 09:20:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Perspiration Implementation: The guys take fencing lessons from Barry Kripke. Stuart struggles to attract female customers to the comic book shop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 09:20:00" d="2020-05-23 09:50:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Helium Insufficiency: Sheldon and Leonard struggle to find the supplies they need for an experiment. Penny and Bernadette download a dating app for Amy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 09:50:00" d="2020-05-23 10:20:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>This Little Wiggy: Marge invites Ralph over for a playdate with Bart, but when Bart is invited to the Wiggum household, he finds it filled with police</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 10:20:00" d="2020-05-23 10:50:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>22 Short Films about Springfield: A Pulp Fiction-style trip through the everyday life of Springfield reveals what really goes on in this apparently normal town</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 10:50:00" d="2020-05-23 11:20:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Raging Abe Simpson and His Grumbling Grandson in 'The Curse of the Flying Hellfish': Mr Burns wants Grampa out of the way so that he can get his hands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 11:20:00" d="2020-05-23 11:50:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Much Apu About Nothing: Homer helps Apu study for a naturalisation exam to prove that he's American enough to stay in the country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 11:50:00" d="2020-05-23 12:20:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Homerpalooza: Homer goes on the road with alternative rock festival Hullabalooza in a sideshow where he has cannonballs fired at his belly. Guest stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 12:20:00" d="2020-05-23 12:50:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Summer of 4'2&quot;: During the holidays, Lisa changes her image and gets in with a cool crowd (including guest star Christina Ricci). But Bart is not pleased</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 12:50:00" d="2020-05-23 13:20:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Lisa on Ice: Bart and Lisa's rivalry intensifies when she takes up ice hockey and their teams are scheduled to play each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 13:20:00" d="2020-05-23 14:15:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay travels to Philadelphia to visit floundering Mexican restaurant Zocalo, which has become an albatross around the necks of its owners, married</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 14:15:00" d="2020-05-23 14:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The first hosts, Ronnie and Steph, welcome their rivals to the Inn at the Park in Aberdeen. One guest's culinary background raises the stakes at breakfast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 14:50:00" d="2020-05-23 15:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The second visit is to Shauna and Fiona at Ingliston Country Club in Renfrewshire. Steve and Allard find the décor dated, and at breakfast the guests play a waiting game</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 15:20:00" d="2020-05-23 15:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Steve and Allard host at the B&amp;B they built themselves, 1692 Wasdale, in the Lake District. Shauna and Fiona think it's picture-perfect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 15:50:00" d="2020-05-23 16:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The final visit is to the Lynbar Hotel, where John boasts that he serves the best breakfast in Blackpool. But will his guests agree?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 16:20:00" d="2020-05-23 16:50:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The B&amp;B owners meet for the last time, to settle some scores and find out how much they've been paid</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 16:50:00" d="2020-05-23 17:50:00"><n u="A Place in the Sun 2018 -">A Place in the Sun 2018 - 2020</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun
Susan and her partner Ilse want to make a permanent move to Spain's Costa Tropical. Can Laura Hamilton find their perfect three-bedroom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 17:50:00" d="2020-05-23 18:50:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kevin McCloud revisits Strathaven in Scotland, where flying instructor Colin and trapeze enthusiast Marta built an incredible metal home inspired</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 18:50:00" d="2020-05-23 19:20:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 19:20:00" d="2020-05-23 20:20:00"><n u="Old People's Home for 4 Year Olds">Old People's Home for 4 Year Olds I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Pre-schoolers and pensioners are halfway through an experiment mixing a nursery and a retirement village. What has the impact been on the older group's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 20:20:00" d="2020-05-23 21:20:00"><n>Dunkirk: The New Evidence</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Dunkirk has long been viewed as the RAF's poorest hour, but this documentary draws on evidence that reveals the hidden story of the key role it played in the evacuation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 21:20:00" d="2020-05-23 22:20:00"><n>Dunkirk: The Forgotten Heroes</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The untold story of the 51st Highland Division, who were left in France when Dunkirk was evacuated and ordered to fight on against Hitler's war machine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 22:20:00" d="2020-05-24 00:15:00"><n u="Pitch Perfect">Pitch Perfect 3</n><e>F</e>    <k>Anna Kendrick and Rebel Wilson return for more perfect harmonies, imperfect issues and another bout of competitive singing in the third musical comedy of the franchise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 00:15:00" d="2020-05-24 02:25:00"><n>Slumdog Millionaire</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Oscar-winning drama. A lowly tea-seller is set to win a fortune on a TV game show when he's accused of cheating and arrested. Can he prove his innocence? Violence/strong language</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 02:25:00" d="2020-05-24 03:20:00"><n>The Last Leg</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Last Leg: Locked Down Under
Sarah Millican joins Adam Hills, Josh Widdicombe and Alex Brooker as they bring topical comedy from their homes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 03:20:00" d="2020-05-24 04:15:00"><n>Hollyoaks: Omnibus</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>49% Hollyoaks Omnibus
Will Verity jeopardise Edward's plan? Drug-dealer Jordan sets his sights on young Charlie. Tony makes a surprising decision</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 04:15:00" d="2020-05-24 05:05:00"><n u="60 Days in Jail">60 Days in Jail II (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Trouble in Store: Once the sewerage system at the jail is repaired, the participants return to their pods, only to encounter some new challenges and dangerous threats</k>  </p>
</a>
