<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="35" t="2020-06-01 04:34:42"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 05:10:00" d="2020-06-08 06:00:00"><n u="Grand Designs New Zealand">Grand Designs New Zealand III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Brendan and Nikki plan to build a penthouse apartment with a Balinese-inspired rooftop garden as part of a ground-breaking mixed-use development</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 06:00:00" d="2020-06-08 06:50:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S VII (3)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Triumph TR4: Tim Shaw and Fuzz Townshend rescue a 1962 Triumph TR4 - a British classic that turns out to be one of their biggest-ever rebuilds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 06:50:00" d="2020-06-08 07:30:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Kate Adie is in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 07:30:00" d="2020-06-08 07:55:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers VII (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Those Lips, Those Ice: Carla awaits Eddie's return from his latest road trip with the ice show, but she's angry when she discovers he may be fooling around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 07:55:00" d="2020-06-08 08:25:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers VII (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Norm, Is That You?: Norm's hidden talents as an interior designer are discovered after Frasier and Lilith fire their decorator and get him to spruce up their apartment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 08:25:00" d="2020-06-08 08:45:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly IV</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Rich Man, Poor Girl: When Victoria brings home a new boyfriend called James, the entire family wonders whether she might have found 'The One' at last. Ep13)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 08:45:00" d="2020-06-08 09:05:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly IV</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Three Girls and an Urn: Molly meets the best buddy of her dreams when Peggy's childhood friend Kay comes to town for a visit, but Peggy isn't keen on sharing. Ep14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 09:05:00" d="2020-06-08 09:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Line Substitution Solution: Sheldon pays Stuart to spend the afternoon shopping with Amy so that he can queue up to see a special film screening instead</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 09:30:00" d="2020-06-08 10:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Convergence Convergence: Conflict arises when Leonard's recently divorced parents and Sheldon's devoutly religious mother are all in town at the same time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 10:00:00" d="2020-06-08 10:30:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Murder Most Maris (Part 2/2): Niles is suspected as an accomplice to murder, and Frasier accidentally recommends that his brother should be executed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 10:30:00" d="2020-06-08 11:00:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Guns 'N' Neuroses: Lilith and Frasier are set up on blind dates on the same day by a mutual friend. Niles and Daphne are upset when Martin's gun accidentally goes off</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 11:00:00" d="2020-06-08 11:25:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Seabee Jeebies: After Maris is accused of murdering her husband, Niles becomes famous and starts mixing in the highest echelons of Seattle society</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 11:25:00" d="2020-06-08 12:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Swansea area. DJ Kevin hosts a Spanish-themed night of laughter, singing and flirting, inspired by his favourite holiday destination: Benidorm. (Ep1/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 12:00:00" d="2020-06-08 12:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Swansea area. Café bar owner Tino serves up an African banquet inspired by her homeland, and teaches her guests to twerk. But former bodybuilder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 12:30:00" d="2020-06-08 13:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>Swansea area. Natalie has made some daft comments on the first two nights, and now her guests have low expectations. But will her George Michael-themed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 13:00:00" d="2020-06-08 13:05:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 13:05:00" d="2020-06-08 13:35:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Swansea area. Sales manager Rob serves a 'simple but tasty' Thai menu. But his main is very similar to his starter and his dessert takes 'simple'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 13:35:00" d="2020-06-08 14:05:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>Swansea area. The final host, GP Janine, hopes to serve up an ace tennis-themed evening. The guests turn up dressed for Centre Court</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 14:05:00" d="2020-06-08 15:10:00"><n u="A New Life in the Sun">A New Life in the Sun V</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>A couple from Southend open a glamping site in rural France, an Anglo-French couple renovate a townhouse, and two ex-army pals build a crazy golf course in Spain. Ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 15:10:00" d="2020-06-08 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Ken Bruce is in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 16:00:00" d="2020-06-08 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><e>R</e>    <k>Sonia and Andrew are ready to make a permanent move to inland Almeria to enjoy their semi-retirement in Spain. Can Laura Hamilton find the perfect property within their ?145,000 budget?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 17:00:00" d="2020-06-08 18:00:00"><n>Work on the Wild Side</n><e>F</e>    <k>Vets and volunteers rescue and rehabilitate animals in South Africa. Harriet searches for a partially blind and injured bull elephant, and Emily and Annie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 18:00:00" d="2020-06-08 19:00:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>In Bournemouth, animal-lover Sarah-Jane is disturbed by talk of animal butchery and pescatarian Zoe is accidentally served meat as three couples compete</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 19:00:00" d="2020-06-08 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Thursdays with Abie: Grampa tells a journalist about his wartime service on a battleship. He gets plenty of attention when the story is published</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 19:30:00" d="2020-06-08 20:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>There are more surprises in store for Sylver and Mercedes following the shock announcement at their vow renewal. Mandy tries everything to help Darren</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 20:00:00" d="2020-06-08 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4 news with sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 21:00:00" d="2020-06-08 22:00:00"><n u="Devon and Cornwall">Devon and Cornwall II</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Devon and Cornwall
The series that celebrates the beautiful south west returns. Fisherman Phil prepares for the annual fish festival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 22:00:00" d="2020-06-08 23:00:00"><n>New: Murder in the Outback: The...</n><e>F</e>    <k>. alconio and Lees Mystery: The detailed re-examination of the Falconio murder case continues with a close look at girlfriend Joanne Lees</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-08 23:00:00" d="2020-06-09 00:00:00"><n>Women Who Kill</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Unlike many male murderers, female killers tend to know their victims. This documentary meets three women who murdered people they</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-09 00:00:00" d="2020-06-09 01:05:00"><n u="First Dates Hotel">First Dates Hotel V</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>It's the end of another summer of love, and Fred and his team are determined to go out on a high as cat-lover Zoe dates Joseph and James meets six-foot-six Max from Oxford. Ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-09 01:05:00" d="2020-06-09 01:55:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>In New Orleans, Gordon Ramsay visits Zeke's, a restaurant famed for its Cajun food and loyal locals. But under new ownership, standards have slipped</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-09 01:55:00" d="2020-06-09 02:50:00"><n>Murder in the Outback: The...</n><e>RF</e>    <k>. alconio and Lees Mystery: Leading experts launch a detailed re-investigation of the infamous case, a horror story of abduction and death that's always</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-09 02:50:00" d="2020-06-09 03:40:00"><n>Emergency Helicopter Medics</n><e>F</e>    <k>A visitor to the Appleby horse fair in Cumbria needs help after a cardiac arrest. A 12-year-old girl is treated for multiple injuries after a collision with a vehicle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-09 03:40:00" d="2020-06-09 04:35:00"><n u="Bake Off: The Professionals">Bake Off: The Professionals III</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The five remaining teams make the classic layered dessert millefeuille, master the art of illusion, and create a bird-themed piece montée adorned with Paris-Brest. Ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-09 04:35:00" d="2020-06-09 05:30:00"><n>Britain's Coronavirus...</n><e>RF</e>    <k>. atastrophe: Did the Government Get It Wrong? Dispatches: Britain's confirmed Covid-19 death rate is one of the world's highest. Why? Antony Barnett</k>  </p>
</a>
