<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2020-04-11 04:33:32"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 05:00:00" d="2020-04-18 05:55:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer search the Midlands for dream properties. An expectant couple are keen on Stratford-upon-Avon, while a married couple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 05:55:00" d="2020-04-18 06:50:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S I (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Anglia Angels: Tim Shaw and Fuzz Townshend meet the Hutchings-Clarke family, who all drive Ford Anglias - except James, whose car hasn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 06:50:00" d="2020-04-18 07:05:00"><n>Kirstie's Fill Your House for Free</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Can Kirstie Allsopp and her team help Louise turn her dilapidated Essex flat into a peaceful paradise without breaking the bank?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 07:05:00" d="2020-04-18 07:25:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly II</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Happy Halloween: Mike is thoroughly spooked when Molly's boss invites them to a costume party at his house on Halloween night - a holiday he always dreads. Ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 07:25:00" d="2020-04-18 07:50:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly II</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Carl Meets a Lady: Carl tries to get a date with an attractive woman he spots at the diner, but he worries that this new love connection might be out of his league. Ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 07:50:00" d="2020-04-18 08:15:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Super Bowl: Ray is sent by his paper to cover the Super Bowl, but his excitement is tempered by having to choose someone to accompany him. Will he make the right choice?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 08:15:00" d="2020-04-18 08:40:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Ray's Journal: Ray is horrified to learn that his mother used to read his diary, which contained his most personal - and perverted - thoughts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 08:40:00" d="2020-04-18 09:05:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Silent Partners: After spending a Valentine's dinner without talking to each other, Ray and Debra agree to take an interest in each other's hobbies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 09:05:00" d="2020-04-18 09:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (16)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Table Polarization: Leonard buys a dining table for the flat but Sheldon objects to such a big change inside his home. Meanwhile, Howard</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 09:30:00" d="2020-04-18 09:55:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Friendship Turbulence: In an attempt to improve their strained friendship, Howard invites Sheldon to visit Nasa with him. Penny is upset when her car breaks down</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 09:55:00" d="2020-04-18 10:25:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Mommy Observation: Sheldon pays a surprise visit to his mother in Houston and is forced to confront a new reality. Raj throws a murder mystery-themed dinner party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 10:25:00" d="2020-04-18 10:50:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VII (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Indecision Amalgamation: Raj faces a dating dilemma, Penny can't decide whether to accept a role in a terrible film, and Sheldon chooses between two gaming systems</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 10:50:00" d="2020-04-18 11:20:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Mypods and Broomsticks: The family go to the mall to buy Lisa a Mypod, but Bart causes chaos when he interrupts tycoon Steve Mobbs' announcement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 11:20:00" d="2020-04-18 11:45:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Burns and the Bees: Mr Burns wins a basketball team in a game of poker, but Lisa is left reeling by his proposal to erect a stadium in the same place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 11:45:00" d="2020-04-18 12:15:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Dangerous Curves: Homer and Marge drive away to a log cabin for the weekend and start reminiscing about their early courtship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 12:15:00" d="2020-04-18 12:45:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Homer and Lisa Exchange Cross Words: Lisa enters a tournament after discovering that she has a knack for doing crosswords. But Homer thinks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 12:45:00" d="2020-04-18 13:40:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay visits Italian restaurant Pantaleone's, whose stubborn owner Pete claims that he makes 'the best pizza in Denver'. Sadly, Gordon's taste</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 13:40:00" d="2020-04-18 14:10:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Mark and Jo Warden host first, at The Cimon in Torquay. Nigel is blown away by the sea view, but their guests think the breakfast lacks the four-star feel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 14:10:00" d="2020-04-18 14:40:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The second visit is to The Cardinal's Hat, in Worcester, whose owner Nigel Smith likes the finer things in life. There's a divide at breakfast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 14:40:00" d="2020-04-18 15:15:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>For the third visit, the group head to Russ and Karen Colman's glamping site in the Cledan Valley in Wales. Nigel embraces his shepherd's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 15:15:00" d="2020-04-18 15:45:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The final visit is to Lucinda Renshaw, and her friend Diane, at Springfield House in Instow, Devon. Things take a turn when Mark and Jo discover there's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 15:45:00" d="2020-04-18 16:20:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the final day of the competition and the B&amp;B owners are meeting for the last time. There are tantrums and bitter rebukes before the winner is announced</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 16:20:00" d="2020-04-18 17:20:00"><n>Mend It for Money</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Britain's best restorers compete for the opportunity to give a new lease of life to a vintage Allwin penny arcade machine, a Porsche 928 and a vintage British postbox</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 17:20:00" d="2020-04-18 18:20:00"><n>Animal Rescue School</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Animal Rescue School
The trainees are investigating cases by themselves for the first time. Debs deals with a potentially deadly snake, Rowena rushes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 18:20:00" d="2020-04-18 19:15:00"><n>Food Unwrapped</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>76% Food Unwrapped Does Chocolate
Some favourite chocolate-based investigations, from after-dinner mints to bubbly chocolate and white chocolate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 19:15:00" d="2020-04-18 20:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 20:00:00" d="2020-04-18 21:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><e>R</e>    <k>Stuart and Rosie turn their 1960s bungalow on the Wirral into a slick piece of 21st-century architecture. But what will the neighbours make of their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 21:00:00" d="2020-04-18 22:00:00"><n u="Great Canal Journeys">Great Canal Journeys VIII (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Timothy West and Prunella Scales voyage down the Rio Douro, through the dramatic landscape of north west Portugal, with its deep locks, hilltop vineyards</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 22:00:00" d="2020-04-19 00:35:00"><n>Star Trek Into Darkness</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Sci-fi action adventure starring Chris Pine, Zachary Quinto and Benedict Cumberbatch. Kirk loses command of the Enterprise and a renegade operative</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-19 00:35:00" d="2020-04-19 02:15:00"><n>47 Metres Down</n>    <k>Action thriller with Mandy Moore and Claire Holt. Two sisters find themselves in a terrifying situation when they go shark cage diving in Mexico</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-19 02:15:00" d="2020-04-19 03:05:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay heads to Arvada, Colorado, where out-of-control hoarder Randy and his wife Alexa have allowed their restaurant Old Neighborhood</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-19 03:05:00" d="2020-04-19 03:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Joy of Sect: The family join a cult that brainwashes its disciples into believing they will be taken to the planet Blisstonia, but Marge escapes and plans a rescue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-19 03:30:00" d="2020-04-19 04:50:00"><n>Hollyoaks: Omnibus</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>49% Hollyoaks Omnibus
Jordan sends Sid and Juliet to the seaside to make a delivery. Nancy decides to tell Kyle's parents about their engagement. Scott urges</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-19 04:50:00" d="2020-04-19 05:45:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>R</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer house-hunt in Manchester with two couples. Katherine and Andrew want a renovation project, while Sarah and Claude</k>  </p>
</a>
