<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="35" t="2020-05-25 04:50:47"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 05:40:00" d="2020-06-01 06:30:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S V (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Sunbeam Alpine: Tim Shaw and Fuzz Townshend use all their know-how to restore a Sunbeam Alpine, one of the most stylish British sports cars of the 1960s, for motor fan Ray</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 06:30:00" d="2020-06-01 06:50:00"><n>Kirstie's Fill Your House for Free</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and the team help Jasbinder, a single mum from west London, with a new bedroom for two of her children and a refurbishment of her bathroom and front garden</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 06:50:00" d="2020-06-01 07:30:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Mark Foster is in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 07:30:00" d="2020-06-01 07:55:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers VI (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Sam in the Gray Flannel Suit: Rebecca is jealous when Evan Drake gives Sam an executive sales job at corporate headquarters and comes to suspect there</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 07:55:00" d="2020-06-01 08:20:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers VI (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Our Hourly Bread: When the staff ask for pay rises, Rebecca insists money is tight and gives them new job titles instead. To get the bar out of its slump</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 08:20:00" d="2020-06-01 08:45:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>A Date for Peter: Amy's parents ask Ray to give their son Peter some tips on dating. Debra throws a cocktail party, but Ray isn't impressed by the guest list</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 08:45:00" d="2020-06-01 09:10:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Favors: Marie helps Debra to deal with Ray's bad habit of leaving his possessions lying around the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 09:10:00" d="2020-06-01 09:35:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly IV</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Careful What You Dig For: Molly meets her literary idol, who tells her to write about things in her life she wouldn't want people to know. Mike invites</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 09:35:00" d="2020-06-01 10:00:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly IV</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Poker in the Front, Looker in the Back: Molly believes her neighbour is up to no good and recruits Joyce to help her spy on him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 10:00:00" d="2020-06-01 10:30:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Kenny on the Couch: Frasier is jealous when his depressed station manager finds more comfort in Martin's advice than Frasier's psychiatry. Niles and Daphne study yoga</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 10:30:00" d="2020-06-01 11:00:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Roe to Perdition: The Crane brothers find their social influence growing, thanks to a Russian backstreet caviar dealer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 11:00:00" d="2020-06-01 11:30:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Some Assembly Required: Frasier turns his hand to DIY and interior design when he helps out with a local homebuilding scheme. Unfortunately, his plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 11:30:00" d="2020-06-01 12:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Middlesbrough. Glamorous sales assistant Gail hosts a night of gourmet grub and gets the glitter, sparklers and hair extensions out to give her guests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 12:00:00" d="2020-06-01 12:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Middlesbrough. Goalkeeping coach Dan hosts a James Bond evening, with 007-inspired food, a villain and. a penalty shoot-out. But some of his guests don't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 12:30:00" d="2020-06-01 13:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Middlesbrough. Pub landlord Gary hosts a 1980s night, flambéing his steaks at the table. There's tension between the guests, but Gary has a trick</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 13:00:00" d="2020-06-01 13:05:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 13:05:00" d="2020-06-01 13:35:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Middlesbrough. Vintage shop owner Jane serves up a retro menu and a clothes competition, on a lively night with yet more drama between the diners. (Ep4/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 13:35:00" d="2020-06-01 14:05:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Middlesbrough. For the final night, art enthusiast Julie serves an Indian menu. But her food gets mixed reviews, and there are shocks, revelations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 14:05:00" d="2020-06-01 15:10:00"><n u="A New Life in the Sun">A New Life in the Sun V</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>A family from the Midlands gamble an inheritance on a diving school in the Balearics. In France, a Warwickshire couple take on a massive gite renovation project. Ep11)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 15:10:00" d="2020-06-01 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Kate Adie is in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 16:00:00" d="2020-06-01 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><e>R</e>    <k>Denise and her best pal Karen enlist the help of Jonnie Irwin to find the perfect holiday home for Denise and her beloved Jack Russell near Guardamar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 17:00:00" d="2020-06-01 18:00:00"><n>Work on the Wild Side</n><e>F</e>    <k>Vets and volunteers rescue and rehabilitate animals in South Africa. Emily oversees a tricky giraffe capture and Emma releases six rehabilitated animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 18:00:00" d="2020-06-01 19:00:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Lincolnshire. Lara and Greg serve a travel-inspired menu. Andrew and Liz attempt a dress rehearsal for their wedding breakfast. And Jenna and Mitch prove</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 19:00:00" d="2020-06-01 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Homer the Whopper: When Homer is chosen to appear in a superhero movie, the film studio hires a celebrity trainer (guest star Seth Rogen)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 19:30:00" d="2020-06-01 20:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Can Nancy ever trust Kyle again? Jordan and Leela have a heart-to-heart about their upbringings. Mercedes and Sylver are loved-up but unaware that someone is watching them</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 20:00:00" d="2020-06-01 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 21:00:00" d="2020-06-01 22:00:00"><n>Grayson's Art Club</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Grayson's Art Club
This episode celebrates all things Britain, from the clap for carers to our 'national spirit' - featuring Liza Tarbuck, British</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 22:00:00" d="2020-06-01 23:35:00"><n>New: Hitched at Home: Our...</n>    <k>. ockdown Wedding: As 60,000 British couples put their nuptials on ice due to Covid-19, First Dates's Fred Sirieix pulls out all the stops</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-01 23:35:00" d="2020-06-02 00:35:00"><n u="First Dates Hotel">First Dates Hotel V</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Chef James dates an actor seeking his leading man. Hayley fancies a bloke who's a bit of a 'viking'. And Duncan James from boyband Blue gets his mum Fiona</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 00:35:00" d="2020-06-02 01:35:00"><n>Emergency Helicopter Medics</n>    <k>Heli-medics rush to a skydiver who has sustained serious injuries after smashing into a house. And there's a race to reach a man who has fallen 40 feet from a ladder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 01:35:00" d="2020-06-02 02:25:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay visits Classic American in New York. Best pals Colleen and Naomi bought the restaurant together, but their lack of experience is pushing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 02:25:00" d="2020-06-02 03:20:00"><n u="Bake Off: The Professionals">Bake Off: The Professionals III</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The toughest Bake Off on TV returns. The six teams tackle two miniature classics, strawberry tarts and fruit salad, before reinventing the retro pineapple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 03:20:00" d="2020-06-02 04:15:00"><n>Britain's Unsung Heroes</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>A celebration of the key workers keeping Britain going in the coronavirus crisis: refuse collectors, bus drivers, carers, cleaners, shelf-stackers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 04:15:00" d="2020-06-02 04:40:00"><n>Reasons to Be Cheerful with Matt Lucas</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Matt Lucas's Reasons to Be. 
. heerful: Comic genius Matt Lucas and his celebrity chums entertain the nation with a dose of comedy that celebrates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 04:40:00" d="2020-06-02 07:40:00"><n u="Location, Location, Location">Location, Location, Location XXXI</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Kirstie and Phil are in Greater Manchester with two couples. Kate and Vicky want to find their first home. Angelina and Thomas have sold their</k>  </p>
</a>
