<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="35" t="2019-08-13 02:13:24"><p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 05:45:00" d="2019-08-19 05:55:00"><n>Kirstie's Vintage Gems</n><e>RF</e>    <k>In this bite-size episode of Kirstie's Vintage Home, Kirstie Allsopp uses vintage fabric and felt to create a fun bedroom for a couple of young girls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 05:55:00" d="2019-08-19 06:50:00"><n u="The ?100K Drop">The ?100K Drop III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Coalville couple Jono and Danielle, and Cardiff couple Simon and Danielle, join Davina McCall to take on the mighty Drop. Will either pair win big? Ep25)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 06:50:00" d="2019-08-19 07:30:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Dr Linda Papadopoulos is in Dictionary Corner with Susie Dent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 07:30:00" d="2019-08-19 07:55:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly II</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Happy Halloween: Mike is thoroughly spooked when Molly's boss invites them to a costume party at his house on Halloween night, which is a holiday he always dreads. Ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 07:55:00" d="2019-08-19 08:20:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly II</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Carl Meets a Lady: Carl tries to get a date with an attractive woman he spots at the diner, but he worries that this new love connection might be out of his league. Ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 08:20:00" d="2019-08-19 08:45:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>Double Downer: Carrie and Doug go on an anniversary trip to Atlantic City with Doug's boss</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 08:45:00" d="2019-08-19 09:10:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>Dougie Nights: Doug and Deacon go clubbing and Doug discovers that he enjoys it. Meanwhile, Carrie feels threatened by her new colleague, who looks just like her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 09:10:00" d="2019-08-19 09:40:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>How They Met: Ray and Debra reminisce about how they first met 15 years earlier, including the first time Ray sampled Debra's cooking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 09:40:00" d="2019-08-19 10:10:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>b Jo:Deradcistnuxpmf</e>    <k>B</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 10:10:00" d="2019-08-19 10:40:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>It Takes Two to Tangle: Frasier and Niles desperately search for a wealthy patron to lend support to the failing prep school they both attended</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 10:40:00" d="2019-08-19 11:10:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Forgotten But Not Gone: Frasier resigns from his beloved wine club to avoid a conflict of interest when he begins a new radio show about wine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 11:10:00" d="2019-08-19 11:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Middle Earth Paradigm: Penny decides to host a big Halloween party, putting Leonard, Sheldon, Howard and Raj through a demanding new test of their social skills</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 11:35:00" d="2019-08-19 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Dumpling Paradox: When Howard seduces Penny's friend and spends the night with her in Penny's flat, Penny asks if she can sleep on Leonard and Sheldon's sofa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 12:00:00" d="2019-08-19 12:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Lastest Gun in the West: Bart befriends an old cowboy who used to be a film star and tries to help him regain his fame, but Bart isn't prepared</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 12:30:00" d="2019-08-19 13:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>$pringfield (or How I Learned to Stop Worrying and Love Legalized Gambling): Homer gets a job at Mr Burns' new casino and Marge becomes addicted to the slot machines</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 13:00:00" d="2019-08-19 13:05:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 13:05:00" d="2019-08-19 14:05:00"><n u="A New Life in the Sun">A New Life in the Sun IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Brits try to rent out their treehouse in France. In Spain, an Anglo Dutch couple race to open their new bistro, and two pensioners from Cambridgeshire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 14:05:00" d="2019-08-19 15:10:00"><n>Posh Pawnbrokers</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Bosses Larry and Neil at Cashbrokers in Cornwall consider deals on some very rare vintage champagne and wine. In Kent, brothers Patrick and Charlie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 15:10:00" d="2019-08-19 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Dr Linda Papadopoulos is in Dictionary Corner with Susie Dent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 16:00:00" d="2019-08-19 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2018 &amp; 2019</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun
Julie and Jerry have been married for 33 years; with Jerry due to retire soon, the time is right to buy a holiday home in Brittany, France</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 17:00:00" d="2019-08-19 18:00:00"><n u="The ?100K Drop">The ?100K Drop III</n><e>F</e>    <k>Davina McCall is joined by Jayne and her father Patrick from West Drayton, and Sarah and Becca, sisters from Liverpool. But can either pair beat The 100k Drop? Ep26)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 18:00:00" d="2019-08-19 18:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>F</e>    <k>The competition takes place in and around Sheffield where first host chocolate shop manager - and party girl - Ginnette hopes to win over her guests</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 18:30:00" d="2019-08-19 19:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Homer Loves Flanders: Homer realises that he likes Flanders and starts to hang around with him all the time. Unfortunately, Flanders realises</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 19:00:00" d="2019-08-19 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Gump Roast: Aliens Kang and Kodos, decide that as Homer is the 'fat, selfish epitome of modern man' the earth must be destroyed. Guest starring Stephen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 19:30:00" d="2019-08-19 20:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Goldie is forced to lie to her mum about Joel. Maxine has some distressing news for Damon, and Liam tries to fix things with Bobby. There's a shocking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 20:00:00" d="2019-08-19 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Includes sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 21:00:00" d="2019-08-19 22:00:00"><n>Food Unwrapped</n><t>S</t>    <k>76% New: Food Unwrapped
Jimmy Doherty investigates whether protein supplements really build a buff body; Matt finds out which foods generate the most wind;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 22:00:00" d="2019-08-19 23:00:00"><n>New: Call the Cops</n>    <k>Juggling Chainsaws: This series goes inside the nerve centre of policing - the police communications and control centre - to shed light on law and order</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 23:00:00" d="2019-08-19 23:30:00"><n u="Stath Lets Flats">Stath Lets Flats II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Stath Lets Flats
Comedy with Greek-Cypriot letting agent Stath (Jamie Demetriou). Stath is struggling with his brash new boss, old rivals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-19 23:30:00" d="2019-08-20 00:30:00"><n>Born Famous</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Born Famous: Michelle Mone
Entrepreneur Michelle Mone's daughter Bethany discovers what life could have been like if her mother wasn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 00:30:00" d="2019-08-20 01:30:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates XII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Fred and his Cupids bid adieu to the winter blues as they welcome more hopeful singletons to the First Dates restaurant. Georgia is looking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 01:30:00" d="2019-08-20 02:25:00"><n>The Secret Teacher</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Millionaire Kate Stewart becomes a support worker in a Sheffield school, where rule-breaker Zain, and Molly, who has a poor attendance record, catch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 02:25:00" d="2019-08-20 03:15:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>The second half of a two-part special. Can Gordon bring together the fragmented Saffron family and save The Burger Kitchen in Los Angeles?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 03:15:00" d="2019-08-20 04:10:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Northampton, Russell serves camel meatballs; Justyna is confident about her Polish food; Mr T impersonator John reveals his celeb lifestyle; and Brenda</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 04:10:00" d="2019-08-20 05:05:00"><n>The Lateish Show with Mo Gilligan</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Mo Gilligan is joined by Ashley Banjo and Tom Davis for chat, unexpected music performances, sketches and games where viewers can win a prize. (Ep5/6)</k>  </p>
</a>
