<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="35" t="2019-08-13 02:13:25"><p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 05:05:00" d="2019-08-20 05:55:00"><n u="Grand Designs New Zealand">Grand Designs New Zealand III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>A keen skier who is a fan of Alpine homes constructs a new log house using traditional techniques in Horopito, at the base of Mount Ruapehu on the North Island. Ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 05:55:00" d="2019-08-20 06:50:00"><n u="The ?100K Drop">The ?100K Drop III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Davina McCall is joined by Jayne and her father Patrick from West Drayton, and Sarah and Becca, sisters from Liverpool. But can either pair beat The 100k Drop? Ep26)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 06:50:00" d="2019-08-20 07:30:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Dr Linda Papadopoulos is in Dictionary Corner with Susie Dent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 07:30:00" d="2019-08-20 07:55:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly II</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Peggy Gets a Job: When Mike encourages his mother Peggy to get a job, he never imagines how badly it will interfere with Molly's life. Ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 07:55:00" d="2019-08-20 08:20:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly II</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Mike Cheats: As Thanksgiving Day approaches, Mike starts cheating by breaking the rules of his diet and hiding the truth from Molly. Ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 08:20:00" d="2019-08-20 08:45:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>No Orleans: Doug and Carrie find an expired cheque in an old unopened wedding present from Doug's annoying cousin. Can they convince him to write another one?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 08:45:00" d="2019-08-20 09:10:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>Missing Links: Carrie tries to set Deacon up with a woman at a golf outing, even though he has brought a date. And is the attractive Holly secretly pining for him?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 09:10:00" d="2019-08-20 09:40:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Can Opener: When Ray and Debra have an argument about their new can opener, Marie, Frank and Robert can't help getting involved</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 09:40:00" d="2019-08-20 10:10:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>You Bet: Is Ray right to be sceptical when Frank uncharacteristically displays keen interest in his work?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 10:10:00" d="2019-08-20 10:40:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Daphne Returns: Niles's romantic chances could be scuppered when Daphne's return sparks a squabble that could end it all</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 10:40:00" d="2019-08-20 11:10:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Wizard and Roz: Frasier seeks advice from his mentor, who seems more interested in Roz, and Daphne tries to convince Niles that she is psychic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 11:10:00" d="2019-08-20 11:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Grasshopper Experiment: Raj panics when his parents arrange a blind date for him, only to discover he actually can talk to a member of the opposite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 11:35:00" d="2019-08-20 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Cooper-Hofstadter Polarization: Sheldon and Leonard are asked to give a paper at a physics conference, but Sheldon is reluctant to share the credit</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 12:00:00" d="2019-08-20 12:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Tales from the Public Domain: Homer reads out classic tales from an overdue library book, with himself as Odysseus at the Battle of Troy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 12:30:00" d="2019-08-20 13:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Bart Gets Famous: Thanks to his new catchphrase, 'I didn't do it', Bart becomes famous, getting his own TV series and releasing a lucrative line of merchandise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 13:00:00" d="2019-08-20 13:05:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 13:05:00" d="2019-08-20 14:05:00"><n u="A New Life in the Sun">A New Life in the Sun IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>A couple in France welcome paying guests to their treehouse B&amp;B, there's a grand opening for a bistro in Spain, and ill health threatens to ruin a couple's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 14:05:00" d="2019-08-20 15:10:00"><n>Posh Pawnbrokers</n><e>RF</e>    <k>In Kent, can a deal be done on a unique painting of Muhammad Ali? Up in Sheffield at London Road, pawnbroker Dan taken for a ride in an unusual fairground dodgem car</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 15:10:00" d="2019-08-20 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Dr Linda Papadopoulos is in Dictionary Corner with Susie Dent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 16:00:00" d="2019-08-20 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2018 &amp; 2019</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun
Shami and Clive share a love of Sicily and can't wait to find a place where they can eventually relocate to with their three cats</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 17:00:00" d="2019-08-20 18:00:00"><n u="The ?100K Drop">The ?100K Drop III</n><e>F</e>    <k>Davina McCall is joined by Joe and Jamie, friends from London, and Lyndsay and Keith, a couple from Edinburgh. Will they get to the final question</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 18:00:00" d="2019-08-20 18:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>F</e>    <k>The competition comes from in and around Sheffield, where the second host, emergency services worker Josh, plans to woo his guests with an evening</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 18:30:00" d="2019-08-20 19:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Bart Gets an Elephant: Bart wins an elephant as a radio quiz prize. He christens his new best friend Stampy, but Homer can't afford his upkeep and decides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 19:00:00" d="2019-08-20 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>I Am Furious Yellow: Bart is inspired to become an animator and finds inspiration close to home, creating Angry Dad</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 19:30:00" d="2019-08-20 20:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>The village is shaken by the disturbing discovery. The walls are closing in on Breda, but she will manage to talk her way out of it? Damon has a big idea to show Maxine how special she is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 20:00:00" d="2019-08-20 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Includes sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 21:00:00" d="2019-08-20 22:00:00"><n>Train Your Baby Like a Dog</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Train Your Baby Like a Dog
Dog trainer and behaviourist Jo-Rosie Haffenden believes we should apply dog training reward techniques to our kids</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 22:00:00" d="2019-08-20 23:00:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XVIII</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: 24 Hours in A&amp;E
Leslie (75) is rushed to A&amp;E after suffering a stroke; Hannah (37) has pain in her spine after falling from her horse; and Isabella</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-20 23:00:00" d="2019-08-21 00:00:00"><n>Kathy Burke's All Woman</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Kathy Burke's All Woman
Kathy explores motherhood, talking to actor Samantha Morton and comedian Katherine Ryan about their experiences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 00:00:00" d="2019-08-21 01:00:00"><n>Jade: The Reality Star Who Changed Britain</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Jade: The Reality Star Who. 
. hanged Britain: By 2007 Jade Goody was Britain's first reality TV millionaire. But joining the celebrity version</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 01:00:00" d="2019-08-21 01:55:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay travels to Orange County in southern California to try to save Italian restaurant Luigi's from a disaster caused by family arguments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 01:55:00" d="2019-08-21 02:50:00"><n u="Jamie and Jimmy's Friday Night Feast">Jamie and Jimmy's Friday Night Feast VI</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jamie and Jimmy's Friday Night. 
. east. Davina McCall joins the boys for some slow-cooked rabbit casserole. There's also spicy lamb, a beach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 02:50:00" d="2019-08-21 03:35:00"><n>Undercover Boss USA</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Bryon Stephens, President and COO of Marco's Pizza, dons a disguise to go incognito among the employees in his own company to assess how the organisation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 03:35:00" d="2019-08-21 04:30:00"><n u="Grand Designs New Zealand">Grand Designs New Zealand III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>A remote home is built on Slipper Island off the Coromandel Peninsula, but all materials must travel from the mainland by barge past the dangerous Tairua sandbar. Ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 04:30:00" d="2019-08-21 05:40:00"><n>Sherlock Holmes: Terror by Night</n><e>R</e>    <k>Sherlock Holmes murder-mystery starring Basil Rathbone and Nigel Bruce. Holmes and Dr Watson are employed to protect a priceless diamond</k>  </p>
</a>
