<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2020-05-26 04:36:47"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 05:35:00" d="2020-06-02 06:25:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S V (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Caterham 7: Tim and Fuzz get their hands on a legendary British two-seater sports car, owned by family man Jason, that's an amateur racer's dream</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 06:25:00" d="2020-06-02 06:50:00"><n>Richard &amp; Judy: Keep Reading and Carry On</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Richard &amp; Judy: Keep Reading. 
. nd Carry On: Richard and Judy chat to Graham Norton; Stacey Dooley and Rev Richard Coles review Elton John's memoir;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 06:50:00" d="2020-06-02 07:30:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Mark Foster is in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 07:30:00" d="2020-06-02 07:55:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers VI (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Slumber Party Massacre: Rebecca throws a slumber party for Carla, who is depressed at the prospect of becoming a grandmother after Anthony and Annie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 07:55:00" d="2020-06-02 08:20:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers VI (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Bar Wars: Traditional rivalry between Cheers and Gary's Old Town Tavern grows as they play increasingly bizarre practical jokes on each other after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 08:20:00" d="2020-06-02 08:45:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Faux Pas: Ray accidentally insults the twins' new friend to the boy's father and then makes it worse by repeating his mistake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 08:45:00" d="2020-06-02 09:10:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Tasteless Frank: Frank loses his sense of taste. Is it a side-effect of his potency medication? And will he have to tell Marie that he is receiving chemical assistance?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 09:10:00" d="2020-06-02 09:35:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly IV</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Shoeless Molly Flynn: Molly is forced to conclude that she needs to adjust her spending habits - especially in relation to shoes - if she wants to maintain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 09:35:00" d="2020-06-02 10:00:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly IV</n><e>RF</e>    <k>They Shoot Asses, Don't They?: After being shot during a robbery, Mike aims to make the most of every day and tells Carl that the time is right</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 10:00:00" d="2020-06-02 10:30:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Farewell, Nervosa: Frasier and Niles search for a new coffee house when they are annoyed by a street singer (Elvis Costello) who starts playing at Café Nervosa</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 10:30:00" d="2020-06-02 11:00:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Devil and Dr Phil: Frasier is jealous when he finds out about his former agent Bebe's relationship with his old friend Dr Phil (guest starring as himself)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 11:00:00" d="2020-06-02 11:30:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Fathers and Sons: Martin worries that he might not be Frasier and Niles' father when he notices the similarities they share with his wife's former colleague</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 11:30:00" d="2020-06-02 12:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Manchester. Full-time mum Johanna dedicates the first night to her favourite food - takeaways - from kebabs to chicken curry. But the main proves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 12:00:00" d="2020-06-02 12:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Manchester. Lorry-driving film buff Ryan plans a movie-inspired menu, including a 'Prawn Identity' starter, 'Sausage Meat the Fockers' main and 'Chocolate</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 12:30:00" d="2020-06-02 13:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Manchester. Glamorous 'domestic delegator' Fiona serves a classy but effortless menu. But Linzi takes issue with Fiona's mum chopping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 13:00:00" d="2020-06-02 13:05:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 13:05:00" d="2020-06-02 13:35:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Manchester. After dishing out criticism all week, can launderette owner Linzi impress her guests with her food and ironing competition entertainment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 13:35:00" d="2020-06-02 14:05:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Manchester. On the final night, Italian Nico plans to show the Brits how it's done. But there are shocks and confrontations, and a game of table football</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 14:05:00" d="2020-06-02 15:10:00"><n u="A New Life in the Sun">A New Life in the Sun V</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Warwickshire couple who run gites in France get hitched. Two bar owners race to open on the Costa del Sol. And a broken-down van threatens to cripple</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 15:10:00" d="2020-06-02 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Kate Adie is in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 16:00:00" d="2020-06-02 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Tracy from Southport is searching for a country home with B&amp;B potential around the lakes of Languedoc in France. Can Jonnie Irwin find her perfect property on a budget of ?100,000?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 17:00:00" d="2020-06-02 18:00:00"><n>Work on the Wild Side</n><e>F</e>    <k>Vets and volunteers rescue and rehabilitate animals in South Africa. Annie and Will move an infamous pride of lions and Josie introduces some blind monkeys</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 18:00:00" d="2020-06-02 19:00:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>In Lincolnshire, former soldier Scott is under his partner Clare's command. Su and Dylan serve up a pagan ritual and a Gary Barlow tribute</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 19:00:00" d="2020-06-02 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Bart Gets a 'Z': When Edna Krabappel confiscates all her students' phones, Bart gets revenge by spiking her coffee with alcohol, prompting Principal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 19:30:00" d="2020-06-02 20:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Mercedes and Sylver renew their vows, but there's a shock when an uninvited guest makes a big announcement. Kyle urges Darren to help him fix things with Nancy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 20:00:00" d="2020-06-02 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 21:00:00" d="2020-06-02 22:00:00"><n u="Bake Off: The Professionals">Bake Off: The Professionals III</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Bake Off: The Professionals
The five remaining teams make the classic layered dessert millefeuille, master the art of illusion, and create</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 22:00:00" d="2020-06-02 23:00:00"><n>A Very British Hotel Chain</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: A Very British Hotel. 
. hain: Inside Best Western: Mark has ambitious plans to repurpose an old job centre. Alasdair visits a swanky new hotel in Edinburgh</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-02 23:00:00" d="2020-06-03 00:05:00"><n>My</n>    <k>-ing Tourette's Family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 00:05:00" d="2020-06-03 01:05:00"><n u="Ramsay's 24 Hours to Hell and Back">Ramsay's 24 Hours to Hell and Back II</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay visits Stone's Throw, a family-owned fine-dining restaurant on the Housatonic River in Connecticut, to overhaul the drab interior and update the menu. Ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 01:05:00" d="2020-06-03 02:50:00"><n>Formula E: And We Go Green</n>    <k>Leonardo DiCaprio produced this cinematic documentary following the 2017/18 Formula E championship. Experience the live wires, underdogs and visionaries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 02:50:00" d="2020-06-03 03:40:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay tries to save struggling restaurant Down City, in Providence, Rhode Island. But tough-talking owner Abby refuses to take advice from anyone</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 03:40:00" d="2020-06-03 04:35:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>High-flyers Bob and Louise, ditzy Will and Kim, and Iranian expats Pasha and Haleh compete in Cheltenham, in a week featuring massive portions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-03 04:35:00" d="2020-06-03 05:30:00"><n>Kirstie: Keep Crafting and Carry On</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>51% Kirstie: Keep Crafting and. 
. arry On: Kirstie Allsopp shows us crafts and skills to help us navigate these unique times. She makes a 3D flower panel</k>  </p>
</a>
