<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="27" t="2020-05-10 04:33:55"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 05:35:00" d="2020-05-17 06:25:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S III (6)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Alfa Romeo Renaissance: Tim and Fuzz rescue a beloved 1963 Alfa Romeo Giulia Spider, a two-seater convertible that has been kept in a dusty barn in Essex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 06:25:00" d="2020-05-17 06:50:00"><n>Beat the Chef</n><e>R</e>    <k>Chef James Tanner and a talented amateur cook each make a classic cod loin with crushed potatoes and peas. Who will produce the flakiest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 06:50:00" d="2020-05-17 07:00:00"><n>Kirstie's Fill Your House for Free</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp visits a house with a recycled cinema in Somerset and a country cottage in Cheltenham</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 07:00:00" d="2020-05-17 07:25:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Home from School: When Michael stays home from school for two days in a row, Ray mistakenly suspects that he simply has homework he hasn't finished</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 07:25:00" d="2020-05-17 07:50:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Misery Loves Company: Debra and Ray are annoyed by the over-the-top affection that Robert and Amy express towards each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 07:50:00" d="2020-05-17 08:15:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Contractor: Debra persuades Ray to hire Gianni to do some DIY work in their kitchen, but they both come to regret it due to their friend's laziness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 08:15:00" d="2020-05-17 08:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Commitment Determination: Sheldon pressures Leonard and Penny to choose a date for their wedding while dealing with changes in his own relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 08:35:00" d="2020-05-17 09:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Matrimonial Momentum: Penny struggles with Leonard's confession that he kissed another woman. Sheldon doesn't know how to act when Amy breaks up with him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 09:00:00" d="2020-05-17 09:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Separation Oscillation: Sheldon films a special post-break-up episode of Fun with Flags. Bernadette feels guilty about withholding a secret from Penny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 09:30:00" d="2020-05-17 10:30:00"><n u="Jamie and Jimmy's Friday Night Feast">Jamie and Jimmy's Friday Night Feast VI</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Jamie and Jimmy's Friday Night. 
. east: Jamie Oliver and Jimmy Doherty go vegan, recreating one of actress Jessica Chastain's favourite meals. Jimmy pimps up his popcorn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 10:30:00" d="2020-05-17 13:30:00"><n>Sunday Brunch</n><e>F</e>    <k>Tim Lovejoy and Simon Rimmer meet up online to present a special edition of the food and chat show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 13:30:00" d="2020-05-17 13:55:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Bart on the Road: With Bart's fake driving licence and $600 that Martin made on the stock market, Bart, Milhouse, Martin and Nelson set off</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 13:55:00" d="2020-05-17 14:25:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>A Fish Called Selma: Actor Troy McClure is in desperate need of some good publicity, following his implication in a sordid sea-life scandal. So he arranges</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 14:25:00" d="2020-05-17 14:55:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>This Little Wiggy: Marge invites Ralph over for a playdate with Bart, but when Bart is invited to the Wiggum household, he finds it filled with police</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 14:55:00" d="2020-05-17 16:55:00"><n>Dragonheart</n><e>F</e>    <k>Sean Connery, Dennis Quaid and David Thewlis star in a fantasy adventure of dragons, tyrannical rulers and one man's campaign of regret-induced vengeance</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 16:55:00" d="2020-05-17 17:55:00"><n u="Coast vs Country">Coast vs Country V</n><e>R</e>    <k>After 10 years in Dubai, Chris and Marie are ready to make the move to Dorset. Marie is on the hunt for a slice of coastal life, but Chris hopes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 17:55:00" d="2020-05-17 19:00:00"><n u="Penelope Keith's Hidden Villages">Penelope Keith's Hidden Villages I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Penelope visits the rugged hills and valleys of north Wales, goes to her first music festival, meets the Cheshire set, and attends an ancient fertility</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 19:00:00" d="2020-05-17 19:30:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 19:30:00" d="2020-05-17 20:30:00"><n>The Truth About Amazon</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>With the High Street shut down for now, Amazon is booming. This Supershoppers special shares tips and tricks for buying smart from the online retail giant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 20:30:00" d="2020-05-17 21:00:00"><n>Reasons to Be Cheerful with Matt Lucas</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Matt Lucas's Reasons to Be. 
. heerful: Comic genius Matt Lucas and his celebrity chums entertain the nation with a dose of comedy that celebrates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 21:00:00" d="2020-05-17 22:00:00"><n>The Fantastical Factory of Curious Craft</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Keith Lemon's Fantastical. 
. actory of Curious Craft: Keith Lemon hosts as skilled amateur crafters make animal headdresses and a 'catropolis'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 22:00:00" d="2020-05-17 23:00:00"><n>Walking with Elephants</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Walking with Elephants
Levison Wood continues his epic journey following the migration of Botswana's elephants. After trekking to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-17 23:00:00" d="2020-05-18 00:00:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox XV</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Britain's sharpest armchair critics share more of their insightful, passionate and sometimes emotional critiques of the week's biggest and best shows. Ep13)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-18 00:00:00" d="2020-05-18 02:00:00"><n>Mercury Rising</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Violent thriller starring Bruce Willis. A demoted FBI agent tries to protect an autistic boy from being assassinated by a branch of the US government</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-18 02:00:00" d="2020-05-18 02:55:00"><n>Grayson's Art Club</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Sculptor Antony Gormley joins Grayson. The theme this time is fantasy, and anything goes: from an abstract to depicting the thing you're dreaming of doing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-18 02:55:00" d="2020-05-18 04:45:00"><n>L'Amant Double</n><e>F</e>    <k>François Ozon's erotic thriller starring Marine Vacth as a fragile young woman who falls for her therapist. But is he as he seems to her? Strong language/sex/violence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-18 04:45:00" d="2020-05-18 07:45:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Portsmouth, Claire and Alex, Jack and Robyn, and Elle and Graham compete in an edition that features organic fare, glitter and sparkle, and some school dinner comparisons</k>  </p>
</a>
