<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2019-07-11 00:18:49"><p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 05:45:00" d="2019-07-15 05:55:00"><n>Extreme Cake Makers</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Phil and Christine hope to scale new heights with a five foot long lemon and elderflower cake designed to look like a leaping fish</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 05:55:00" d="2019-07-15 06:50:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In an episode of extreme highs and ravaging lows in Bristol, straight-talking Frenchwoman Anne refuses to drink Richard's wine, calls his job boring, barks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 06:50:00" d="2019-07-15 07:25:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Michaela Strachan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 07:25:00" d="2019-07-15 07:55:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers XI (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Teaching with the Enemy: Lilith tells Frasier she's been having an affair with a colleague. Sam has to hire a bouncer when patrons of a biker bar start drinking at Cheers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 07:55:00" d="2019-07-15 08:20:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers XI (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Girl in the Plastic Bubble: Frasier climbs out onto a high window ledge in protest when Lilith reveals she intends to spend a year sealed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 08:20:00" d="2019-07-15 08:45:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>Court Date: Carrie is given a ticket for reckless driving and tries to get out of it by chatting up the policeman who issued it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 08:45:00" d="2019-07-15 09:10:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>White Collar: When Doug gets a new promotion at work, he rapidly becomes miserable with life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 09:10:00" d="2019-07-15 09:40:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Car: Debra refuses to drive the car Ray buys from his parents after finding out that Ray 'got lucky' in it as a teenager</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 09:40:00" d="2019-07-15 10:10:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Diamonds: When Ray finds out that the diamond in the engagement ring he bought Debra is a fake, he decides to get it changed without her knowing;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 10:10:00" d="2019-07-15 10:40:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Good Grief: Frasier's unemployment situation brings about various emotional responses including denial, anger and depression</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 10:40:00" d="2019-07-15 11:10:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Frasier's Curse: Frasier worries about going to his high school reunion because every time a reunion comes up he has bad luck</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 11:10:00" d="2019-07-15 12:05:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay's rescue mission is Hannah &amp; Mason's, a French bistro in the quaint little town of Cranbury, New Jersey</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 12:05:00" d="2019-07-15 13:00:00"><n u="Undercover Boss USA">Undercover Boss USA VIII (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Celebrity Undercover Boss USA
Restaurateur Marcus Samuelsson dons a disguise to work incognito in a teaching kitchen, a food truck and a culinary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 13:00:00" d="2019-07-15 13:05:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 13:05:00" d="2019-07-15 14:05:00"><n u="A New Life in the Sun">A New Life in the Sun IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>A couple attempt to make British beer for the French. Two restaurateurs from Wales try to create a boutique B&amp;B in Spain. Plus, drama in the Spanish countryside. Ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 14:05:00" d="2019-07-15 15:10:00"><n>Posh Pawnbrokers</n><e>RF</e>    <k>In Sheffield, Dan looks at a luxury watch he suspects might not be the genuine article. At Nikolas Patrick in London, a Roman ring found in a loft could</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 15:10:00" d="2019-07-15 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Michaela Strachan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 16:00:00" d="2019-07-15 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2018 &amp; 2019</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun
Wendy and Chris from Surrey have been dreaming of owning a holiday home in Mojacar for more than 10 years. Will Danni Menzies impress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 17:00:00" d="2019-07-15 18:00:00"><n u="The ?100K Drop">The ?100K Drop III</n><e>F</e>    <k>Davina McCall is back with the big money game show and joined by Cambridge friends Cat and Oli, and Jo and David, a couple from Glasgow</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 18:00:00" d="2019-07-15 19:00:00"><n>Kirstie's Celebrity Craft Masters</n><e>F</e>    <k>Property presenter pals Lucy Alexander and Martin Roberts go head to head, each paired with a professional crafter who teaches them how to create</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 19:00:00" d="2019-07-15 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Mypods and Broomsticks: The family go to the mall to buy Lisa a Mypod but Bart causes chaos when he interrupts tycoon Steve Mobbs' announcement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 19:30:00" d="2019-07-15 20:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Liam and Mercedes know the identity of their blackmailer, so Liam comes to a drastic decision. Sparks continue to fly between Goldie and Joel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 20:00:00" d="2019-07-15 20:55:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Includes sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 20:55:00" d="2019-07-15 21:00:00"><n>Moon Landing Live</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Moon Landing Live
A daily mission update from the astronauts and Mission Control, as part of Channel 4's real-time live stream of Apollo 11's mission</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 21:00:00" d="2019-07-15 21:30:00"><n>Dispatches</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Britain's New Build Scandal
Dispatches: Liam Halligan investigates allegations of shoddy standards, poor customer care and excessive profits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 21:30:00" d="2019-07-15 22:00:00"><n u="The ?1 Houses: Britain's Cheapest Street">The ?1 Houses: Britain's Cheapest Street II</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: The ?1 Houses: Britain's. 
. heapest Street: Victoria organises a Christmas party, but will anyone turn up? John risks all by wanting everything perfect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 22:00:00" d="2019-07-15 23:00:00"><n>Extreme Tribe: The Last Pygmies</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Extreme Tribe: The Last. 
. ygmies: In the remote jungle of the Congo, Livia Simoka lives with the Mbendjele pygmies where a conflict with a rival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 23:00:00" d="2019-07-15 23:35:00"><n>Year of the Rabbit</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Year of the Rabbit
Things are not looking good for Rabbit - he's either been framed for murder, or committed a murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-15 23:35:00" d="2019-07-16 00:40:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XIV (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>In this show, captain Jon Richardson and Jason Manford take on guest captain Alan Carr and Katherine Ryan. Ivan Brackenbury is in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 00:40:00" d="2019-07-16 01:35:00"><n>Generation Porn</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>This series meets the people who make porn and people who watch it, to explore the impact of the free porn revolution. Gia is 19. Gianna is 21</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 01:35:00" d="2019-07-16 02:30:00"><n>Drag SOS</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Can drag collective The Family Gorgeous help Mark let go of his action man identity? And can Fleur's new drag persona help her find the confidence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 02:30:00" d="2019-07-16 03:25:00"><n u="The Restoration Man">The Restoration Man IV (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Best Builds: George Clarke looks back at four of the most dramatic tower conversions from the show, including a Georgian windmill and a railway water tower</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 03:25:00" d="2019-07-16 04:20:00"><n u="Grand Designs New Zealand">Grand Designs New Zealand I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>A writer builds a sculptural steel house on a hill behind Pakiri beach on the North Island. The bold design features sloping walls and an angular, vaulted ceiling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-07-16 04:20:00" d="2019-07-16 05:10:00"><n>My Family Secrets Revealed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's case closed for retired police officer David Bunce. Keith Attwood reunites some WWI medals with their rightful relatives. Stephen Gerard Scullion</k>  </p>
</a>
