<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2019-08-09 01:38:33"><p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 05:35:00" d="2019-08-15 05:55:00"><n>Kirstie's Handmade Treasures</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Under the instruction of master florist Sioned Rowlands, Kirstie Allsopp learns how to create a flower arrangement for the 'petite' category at the Royal Cornwall Show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 05:55:00" d="2019-08-15 06:50:00"><n u="The ?100K Drop">The ?100K Drop III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Friends Kev and Leigh from Aberdare and Belfast couple Rachael and Niall join Davina McCall to battle the Drop. But can either pair win</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 06:50:00" d="2019-08-15 07:30:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Charlie Higson</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 07:30:00" d="2019-08-15 07:55:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly II</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Dennis's Birthday: Molly urges Mike to give up his apartment and move in with her. Mike's mother Peggy gets a big surprise when she celebrates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 07:55:00" d="2019-08-15 08:20:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly II</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Mike in the House: When Mike moves in with Molly and her family, he has to adjust from life in his bachelor pad to staying in a house full of women. Ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 08:20:00" d="2019-08-15 08:45:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>No Retreat: Doug and Carrie go for a weekend away together but Doug tells Carrie's colleagues a huge lie. Meanwhile, back in Queens, Arthur manages</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 08:45:00" d="2019-08-15 09:10:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>Tricker Treat: Doug festoons the house with Halloween decorations even though Arthur has a phobia about it</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 09:10:00" d="2019-08-15 09:40:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Working Girl: When Debra gets a job, Ray is unhappy about helping with the housework and Marie worries about the effect it will have on the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 09:40:00" d="2019-08-15 10:10:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Be Nice: Ray and Debra vow to change their ways when they realise they're nicer to strangers than to each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 10:10:00" d="2019-08-15 10:40:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Cranes Unplugged: Frasier can't adjust to his 13-year-old son's new attitude, so he forces Freddy to go camping with him and Martin in an attempt at some male bonding</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 10:40:00" d="2019-08-15 11:10:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Motor Skills: After relying on the breakdown service one too many times, Frasier and Niles take a car maintenance class. And when Roz gets Alice a puppy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 11:10:00" d="2019-08-15 11:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (23)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>The Change Constant: Sheldon and Amy stay up late awaiting a phone call that could bring big news from the Nobel Committee: are their lives about to change?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 11:35:00" d="2019-08-15 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory XII (24)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>The Stockholm Syndrome: Howard and Bernadette go away on a trip without their children, Leonard and Penny try to keep a secret, and Raj makes a new friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 12:00:00" d="2019-08-15 12:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Half Decent Proposal: Marge's incredibly rich high school prom date Artie makes Homer and Marge an indecent proposal, which they can't afford to turn down</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 12:30:00" d="2019-08-15 13:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Simpsons Tall Tales: The family meet a hobo who regales them with his own versions of classic American tales, starring the Simpsons as, among others</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 13:00:00" d="2019-08-15 13:05:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 13:05:00" d="2019-08-15 14:05:00"><n u="A New Life in the Sun">A New Life in the Sun IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Smallholders in France have to diversify in an unusual direction when disaster strikes. A couple take on a bar renovation in Spain. Two expats expand their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 14:05:00" d="2019-08-15 15:10:00"><n>Posh Pawnbrokers</n><e>RF</e>    <k>At Pickwick Pawnbrokers, boss Nathan and manager Debbs are taken aback by a chatty vintage ventriloquist's dummy. In Sheffield, Dan considers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 15:10:00" d="2019-08-15 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Dr Linda Papadopoulos is in Dictionary Corner with Susie Dent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 16:00:00" d="2019-08-15 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2018 &amp; 2019</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun
Colin and Elspeth from Edinburgh have been visiting Menorca for nearly 20 years and are ready to buy a holiday home there</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 17:00:00" d="2019-08-15 18:00:00"><n u="The ?100K Drop">The ?100K Drop III</n><e>F</e>    <k>Davina McCall is joined by David and Jon, a couple from Torquay, and Grimsby couple Millie and Scott. Will either pair take home the cash? Ep24)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 18:00:00" d="2019-08-15 18:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>F</e>    <k>The fourth host in and around Leeds, ex-dancer Diana, prepares an Italian menu. There's a touch of the 80s about her starter and her dessert is extra boozy. (Ep4/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 18:30:00" d="2019-08-15 19:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Lisa vs. Malibu Stacey: Lisa decides Malibu Stacey dolls set a bad example to girls, so she pleads with their creator, Stacy Lovell (guest star Kathleen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 19:00:00" d="2019-08-15 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Blame It on Lisa: The Simpsons go to Brazil to meet an orphan who Lisa's secretly been calling. But as soon as they arrive, Homer is kidnapped</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 19:30:00" d="2019-08-15 20:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Stuart and Jonny have an alarming secret plan, which is discovered by an intruder. Goldie is burning all of her clothes from her exes, and Mercedes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 20:00:00" d="2019-08-15 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Includes sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 21:00:00" d="2019-08-15 22:00:00"><n u="Animal Rescue Live: Supervet Special">Animal Rescue Live: Supervet Special II (4)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Animal Rescue Live. 
. upervet Special: The mission to get Britain to adopt rescue animals and support local shelters continues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 22:00:00" d="2019-08-15 23:00:00"><n>The Secret Teacher</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: The Secret Teacher
Millionaire Kate Stewart becomes a support worker in a Sheffield school, where rule-breaker Zain, and Molly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 23:00:00" d="2019-08-15 23:30:00"><n>This Way Up</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: This Way Up
Aine interviews for a new tutoring job teaching a young French boy, who has recently lost his mother, but she's at risk of missing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-15 23:30:00" d="2019-08-16 00:35:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XVIII</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Sean Lock and Joe Wilkinson take on Jon Richardson and Sara Pascoe. Sam Simmons is in Dictionary Corner, while maths whizz Rachel Riley looks after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 00:35:00" d="2019-08-16 01:35:00"><n u="First Dates">First Dates IX</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Stu lost his sight 13 years ago; he hopes to meet a feisty redhead. Wrestler Lewis returns to the restaurant. His first visit was dramatic;</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 01:35:00" d="2019-08-16 02:25:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay visits Plainfield, New Jersey, to save floundering soul food eatery Blackberry's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 02:25:00" d="2019-08-16 04:35:00"><n>Her</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Sci-fi romance starring Joaquin Phoenix. A man falls in love with his computer's AI operating system. With the voice of Scarlett Johansson. Strong language/sex</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-16 04:35:00" d="2019-08-16 05:00:00"><n u="GameFace">GameFace (Signed Version) II (5)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>GameFace
Marcella (Roisin Conaty) goes to stay in a country cottage to write and stay off the booze. While she is there, she encounters a horse, a spider</k>  </p>
</a>
