<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2020-05-17 04:28:22"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 05:05:00" d="2020-05-24 06:00:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>R</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer house-hunt in Kent. Savannah and John want to find their first home in Maidstone. Matt and Tricia have ?1.5 million</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 06:00:00" d="2020-05-24 06:50:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S V (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Jaguar Mark 2: Tim Shaw and Fuzz Townshend restore Tony's 1962 Jaguar Mark 2 - which has been stored in a garage for nearly two decades - to its former glory</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 06:50:00" d="2020-05-24 07:00:00"><n>Kirstie's Fill Your House for Free</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp visits a stunning Georgian home in Brighton, and a house in Devon whose furniture was made for free</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 07:00:00" d="2020-05-24 07:25:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Nice Talk: When the MacDougalls are invited to spend Easter with the Barones, the families attempt to bond over a 500-piece jigsaw puzzle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 07:25:00" d="2020-05-24 07:50:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Blabbermouths: When Robert tells Ray that Amy filled him in on some juicy gossip about him, Ray decides to get even by sharing some nasty secrets of his own</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 07:50:00" d="2020-05-24 08:15:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Model: A modelling agent tells Robert he has a unique look and convinces him to pose for headshots with their in-house photographer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 08:15:00" d="2020-05-24 08:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Spock Resonance: While he's being interviewed for a documentary about Star Trek character Mr Spock, Sheldon can't suppress his emotions about his split from Amy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 08:35:00" d="2020-05-24 09:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Mystery Date Observation: While Amy's out on a date with a mystery man, Sheldon enlists Howard and Raj to help him find a new girlfriend online</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 09:00:00" d="2020-05-24 09:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Platonic Permutation: At Thanksgiving, Sheldon and Amy hang out as friends at the aquarium, and Howard reluctantly agrees to volunteer at a soup kitchen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 09:30:00" d="2020-05-24 10:30:00"><n u="Jamie and Jimmy's Friday Night Feast">Jamie and Jimmy's Friday Night Feast VI</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jamie and Jimmy's Friday Night. 
. east: Dame Jessica Ennis-Hill joins Jamie Oliver and Jimmy Doherty for a katsu curry and cod wrapped in Iberico ham</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 10:30:00" d="2020-05-24 13:30:00"><n>Sunday Brunch</n><e>F</e>    <k>Tim Lovejoy and Simon Rimmer meet up online to present a special edition of the food and chat show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 13:30:00" d="2020-05-24 13:55:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Homer Badman: The babysitter accuses Homer of sexual harassment when he tries to pick a rare sweet off the back of her trousers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 13:55:00" d="2020-05-24 14:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Lisa the Simpson: Lisa begins to suspect that she's not as clever as she used to be and starts to worry that she's going to end up a permanent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 14:30:00" d="2020-05-24 16:25:00"><n>Megamind</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Animated adventure. There are unexpected consequences when a blue-skinned, large-headed alien supervillain outwits and defeats his superhero enemy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 16:25:00" d="2020-05-24 17:10:00"><n u="A Place in the Sun 2018 -">A Place in the Sun 2018 - 2020</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun
Retirees Dawn and Les from Basingstoke want to relocate to sunny south-east Cyprus, where they have ?100,000 to spend on a property</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 17:10:00" d="2020-05-24 18:15:00"><n u="Coast vs Country">Coast vs Country V</n><e>R</e>    <k>Rob has lived on the Isle of Sheppey for most of his life and wants a new home on the Kent coast. But his partner Caroline longs to return</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 18:15:00" d="2020-05-24 19:15:00"><n u="Penelope Keith's Hidden Villages">Penelope Keith's Hidden Villages II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Penelope Keith explores the nation's smallest communities. In Devon and Cornwall, she visits inland mining villages and the rugged coast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 19:15:00" d="2020-05-24 19:45:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 19:45:00" d="2020-05-24 20:15:00"><n>Reasons to Be Cheerful with Matt Lucas</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Matt Lucas's Reasons to Be. 
. heerful: Comic genius Matt Lucas and his celebrity chums entertain the nation with a dose of comedy that celebrates</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 20:15:00" d="2020-05-24 21:15:00"><n>New: How to Go on Holiday This...</n>    <k>. ummer: Steph McGovern answers some of the nation's burning holiday questions and explores whether now is a safe time to book a holiday for summer 2020</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 21:15:00" d="2020-05-24 22:15:00"><n>The Fantastical Factory of Curious Craft</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Keith Lemon's Fantastical. 
. actory of Curious Craft: Keith Lemon hosts as the amateur crafters make illuminated landmarks and a well-being</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 22:15:00" d="2020-05-24 23:15:00"><n>Walking with Elephants</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Walking with Elephants
Levison Wood concludes his journey following Botswana's elephants. After wading through wetland teeming with wildlife</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-24 23:15:00" d="2020-05-25 00:20:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox XV</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Britain's sharpest armchair critics share more of their insightful, passionate and sometimes emotional critiques of the week's biggest and best shows. Ep14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-25 00:20:00" d="2020-05-25 00:25:00"><n>Ramadan in Lockdown</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Ramadan in Lockdown
This year, Britain's 2.6 million Muslims will observe Ramadan - up to 30 days fasting from sunrise to sunset - in lockdown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-25 00:25:00" d="2020-05-25 02:10:00"><n>East Is East</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Comedy. Jimi Mistry stars as the son of a Pakistani chippie owner (Om Puri) who's trying to raise his kids amid cultural tensions in 1970s Salford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-25 02:10:00" d="2020-05-25 03:05:00"><n>Grayson's Art Club</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Jim Moir, aka Vic Reeves, joins Grayson. The theme is the 'view from my window'. Jim shares his view. As do members of the public, from a tower block</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-25 03:05:00" d="2020-05-25 03:55:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay travels to Fremont, California, to try to save the struggling Spin a Yarn restaurant. Despite an expensive refurbishment, the business</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-25 03:55:00" d="2020-05-25 04:50:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>In Worthing and Portsmouth, pensioners Bill and Hilary, dance fans Micaela and Sanchez, and children's entertainer Doug and Patsy compete</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-25 04:50:00" d="2020-05-25 05:45:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer are in the East Midlands with property veterans Nigel and Jane, and novices Sam and Becky, who want a house with a garden</k>  </p>
</a>
