<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="36" t="2020-04-10 04:34:37"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 05:30:00" d="2020-04-17 06:25:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S I (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Fiat Fiasco: Tim Shaw and Fuzz Townshend meet Jeremy, who lost his wife and was unable to work after a car accident. Can they give his Fiat Spider</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 06:25:00" d="2020-04-17 06:50:00"><n>Beat the Chef</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Amateur cook Jasmine from Durham and top chef Clodagh McKenna each make their version of macaroni cheese, but whose dish will win votes from the Food Jury? (Ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 06:50:00" d="2020-04-17 07:25:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Tom Kerridge joins Susie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 07:25:00" d="2020-04-17 07:50:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers IV (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Barstoolie: Cliff is thrilled to meet his long-lost father when he pays a visit to the bar with a message. Sam suspects that Diane intentionally</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 07:50:00" d="2020-04-17 08:15:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers IV (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Don Juan Is Hell: Diane uses Sam as a case study for an essay in her psychology class but paints an unflattering picture of him. Woody challenges Carla</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 08:15:00" d="2020-04-17 08:40:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Christmas Present: Ray buys Debra an elaborate Christmas present, in the hope that she'll let him go on a golfing weekend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 08:40:00" d="2020-04-17 09:05:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>What Good Are You?: Ray tries to prove his manliness after failing to act swiftly enough in an emergency involving Debra</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 09:05:00" d="2020-04-17 09:35:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Taps at the Montana: Niles wants his apartment back, but must face up to both the snooty neighbours who think he is a menace and the person who is renting from him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 09:35:00" d="2020-04-17 10:05:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>IQ: Who has the most impressive IQ - Frasier or Niles? The results of their childhood tests are finally revealed, and one is much higher than the other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 10:05:00" d="2020-04-17 10:35:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Dr Nora: Christine Baranski guest stars as venomous radio therapist Dr Nora, who joins Frasier at KACL. Piper Laurie cameos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 10:35:00" d="2020-04-17 11:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The first host in Blackpool and Preston, student and barmaid Rachel, serves an American diner-themed menu, which confuses her guests. But they agree</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 11:00:00" d="2020-04-17 11:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The second host in Blackpool and Preston, lady of leisure Jill - who has dined at The Ivy three times - plans to wow her guests with an Italian</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 11:30:00" d="2020-04-17 12:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The third host in Blackpool and Preston, flight attendant Mark, plans to give his guests a taste of the high life with his duck, venison and gin jelly cake. (Ep3/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 12:00:00" d="2020-04-17 12:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The fourth host in Blackpool and Preston is parole officer Bernard, who serves a classic combination of Northern Soul and tasty grub. But there's a walkout</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 12:30:00" d="2020-04-17 13:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>On the final day in Blackpool and Preston, health assistant Lisa banks on her no-faff menu to bag her the cash. But tempers flare as some home truths are delivered. (Ep5/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 13:00:00" d="2020-04-17 14:05:00"><n>The Steph Show</n><t>S</t>    <k>Live: The Steph Show
Steph McGovern presents the brand-new daily programme live from her living room, featuring special guests and the latest information</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 14:05:00" d="2020-04-17 15:10:00"><n>Posh Pawnbrokers</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Kent, brothers Charlie and Patrick receive an Olympic torch, designer bags and an impressive collection of antique firearms, while in Sheffield</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 15:10:00" d="2020-04-17 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Tom Kerridge joins Susie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 16:00:00" d="2020-04-17 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2018 &amp; 2019</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Home or Away
Sonal and Tina can't wait to give up busy Birmingham for a new home on Wales's Gower Peninsula and a bolthole</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 17:00:00" d="2020-04-17 18:00:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY IV</n><e>F</e>    <k>Ben and Billie get to work on their dilapidated boathouse, Amy and Marc get their barn and café ready for their first yoga class, and Wendy and Marcus</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 18:00:00" d="2020-04-17 18:30:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>F</e>    <k>It's the final day of the competition and time for the B&amp;Bers to settle some scores. After dramatic discoveries and cutting comments, the payments</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 18:30:00" d="2020-04-17 19:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Manchester. On the last night, DJing cabin crew Oscar hopes to impress with his mouth-watering Mediterranean treats. But has he bitten off more than he can chew? (Ep5/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 19:00:00" d="2020-04-17 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Burns and the Bees: Mr Burns wins a basketball team in a game of poker, but Lisa is left reeling by his proposal to erect a stadium in the same place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 19:30:00" d="2020-04-17 20:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Lisa the Drama Queen: Lisa befriends Juliet (guest star Emily Blunt), an equally talented and clever girl. Together, they create a fantasy world that takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 20:00:00" d="2020-04-17 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 21:00:00" d="2020-04-17 22:00:00"><n u="Joe Lycett's Got Your Back">Joe Lycett's Got Your Back II</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Joe Lycett's Got Your Back
Scarlett Moffatt shares her thrifty fast food tips. Joe takes on toll road fines with Atomic Kitten and Kim Woodburn</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 22:00:00" d="2020-04-17 23:00:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox XV</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Gogglebox
Britain's sharpest armchair critics share more of their insightful, passionate and sometimes emotional critiques of the week's biggest and best shows. Ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 23:00:00" d="2020-04-17 23:35:00"><n u="Friday Night Dinner">Friday Night Dinner VI</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Friday Night Dinner
Dad's Birthday: Dad has the birthday blues - he's worked out the date when he's going to die, and 'Horrible Grandma' turns up uninvited</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 23:35:00" d="2020-04-18 00:05:00"><n>Duncanville</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Duncanville
Fridgy: Animated comedy that revolves around a 15-year-old boy with a rich fantasy life. The family get a new smart fridge that turns</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 00:05:00" d="2020-04-18 01:10:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XVI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Sean Lock and Rob Beckett take on Jon Richardson and Claudia Winkleman. Plus special guests Nick Mohammed and Joe Wilkinson join Susie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 01:10:00" d="2020-04-18 02:45:00"><n>American Ultra</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Action-comedy with Jesse Eisenberg and Kristen Stewart. A perpetually stoned slacker learns he's actually a deadly CIA sleeper agent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 02:45:00" d="2020-04-18 03:10:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Oxford. First to host is ladies' man Marlon, whose Love Island-themed evening gets off to a shambolic start - and ends with smashing plates. (Ep1/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 03:10:00" d="2020-04-18 03:40:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Oxford. Inventor Richard serves up a home-made extravaganza, including some rather 'unique' entertainment. But the wine flows a little too freely. (Ep2/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 03:40:00" d="2020-04-18 04:05:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Oxford. Mum-of-three Victoria starts her day with a hangover and a few culinary disasters. And things only get worse when her guests arrive. (Ep3/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 04:05:00" d="2020-04-18 04:35:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Oxford. On day four, doggy daycare owner James tries to fib his way through an interrogation of his food, and his four-legged friends threaten</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-18 04:35:00" d="2020-04-18 05:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Oxford. It's the final day of the competition and party girl Heidi wants to lighten the mood with the best dinner party of the week. But will her guests let her? (Ep5/5)</k>  </p>
</a>
