<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="29" t="2019-08-11 01:29:08"><p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 05:15:00" d="2019-08-17 05:40:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Cardiff. Host Michelle is out to impress with a culinary trip around the world, but will a third serving of lamb this week leave her guests bleating with despair? (Ep4/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 05:40:00" d="2019-08-17 06:05:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Cardiff. Host Suzanne is pinning her hopes on an evening of sophistication and fine French cuisine. Can Cardiff's queen of the saucy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 06:05:00" d="2019-08-17 06:55:00"><n u="The ?100K Drop">The ?100K Drop III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Davina McCall is joined by Jayne and her daughter Claire from Jersey, and brothers John and Jim from London. Can either couple beat the drop and take home the cash? Ep23)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 06:55:00" d="2019-08-17 07:20:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>Veiled Threat: Carrie and Doug reminisce about their wedding after finding a memento of the event</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 07:20:00" d="2019-08-17 07:50:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>Oxy Moron: Carrie is upset when, on a bumpy plane landing, Doug takes the only available oxygen mask. Things don't go as well as hoped for Spence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 07:50:00" d="2019-08-17 08:15:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>Depo Man: Carrie is embarrassed when Doug is called as an expert witness for a case she is working on. Meanwhile, Danny and Spence fight over Holly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 08:15:00" d="2019-08-17 08:40:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>The Fuzzyboots Corollary: Leonard is depressed when he discovers that Penny is seeing someone, so he summons up the courage to ask a woman out on a date</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 08:40:00" d="2019-08-17 09:05:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Luminous Fish Effect: Getting fired forces Sheldon to ponder life outside physics, leaving Leonard to take drastic action to snap his friend out of his reverie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 09:05:00" d="2019-08-17 09:30:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Hamburger Postulate: Leonard fears he's wasting his time on Penny and ends up making a connection with Leslie. Sheldon frets over a change to his hamburger routine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 09:30:00" d="2019-08-17 10:00:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon I (20)</n><t>S</t>    <k>74% A Dog, a Squirrel, and a Fish Named Fish: A neighbourhood feud erupts between the Coopers and the Sparks family when the Sparks' new dog terrorises Sheldon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 10:00:00" d="2019-08-17 10:25:00"><n u="Young Sheldon">Young Sheldon I (21)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>74% Summer Sausage, a Pocket Poncho, and Tony Danza: Sheldon is busy obsessing over the status of Meemaw's budding relationship with his mentor Dr John Sturgis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 10:25:00" d="2019-08-17 10:55:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>A Streetcar Named Marge: Marge gives the performance of a lifetime in a musical version of A Streetcar Named Desire</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 10:55:00" d="2019-08-17 11:25:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Lisa the Beauty Queen: Lisa enters the Little Miss Springfield beauty pageant to prove a point, and with coaching from Bart, she comes second</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 11:25:00" d="2019-08-17 11:55:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Tree House of Horror III: The Simpsons' Halloween Special III: The Simpsons throw a Halloween party during which Lisa, Grampa and Bart each tell a scary story</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 11:55:00" d="2019-08-17 12:25:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>This week's competition starts at the Brighton Surf Hotel, where Jeremy Mann and his Russian wife Elena hope their hands-off hosting style</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 12:25:00" d="2019-08-17 12:55:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The second visit is to Number 16, in Greenwich, London, owned by actor and antiques dealer Robert Gray, who charms with his hosting but</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 12:55:00" d="2019-08-17 13:30:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>At the Fleur de Lis in Sandwich, Kent, hosts Jan and Les Fisher are convinced that their traditional place will impress their guests. But Robert is bent on revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 13:30:00" d="2019-08-17 14:00:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The week's last visit is to The Barn at Dale End House near Matlock in the Peak District, owned by Sarah Summers. Sarah is dreading Robert's arrival</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 14:00:00" d="2019-08-17 14:30:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>It's the final day in the competition and the owners meet for the last time to find out what they've been paid. There's harsh criticism, accusations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 14:30:00" d="2019-08-17 17:30:00"><n>Live Rugby Union: Wales vs England</n><e>F</e>    <k>Wales host England at the Principality, as both sides' preparations for the World Cup intensify. Lee McKenzie is joined by Sam Warburton and Ugo Monye</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 17:30:00" d="2019-08-17 18:35:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer are in Bournemouth, helping two single parents looking to bring their families together, as well as a family who are stuck in a rental rut. (Ep4)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 18:35:00" d="2019-08-17 19:30:00"><n>Portrait Artist of the Year 2019</n><e>F</e>    <k>Nine semi-finalists battle for three spots in the final as they get four hours to paint jazz star Courtney Pine at Hackney's Round Chapel. Stephen Mangan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 19:30:00" d="2019-08-17 20:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Includes sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 20:00:00" d="2019-08-17 21:00:00"><n>Secrets of Egypt's Valley of the Kings</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Secrets of Egypt's Valley of. 
. he Kings: When Egyptologists find a sphinx in an ancient quarry, it reveals clues about great female pharaoh Hatshepsut</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 21:00:00" d="2019-08-17 22:00:00"><n>Hidden Britain by Drone</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Hidden Britain by Drone. 
. eatwave Special: A roasting summer has uncovered huge finds from the parched landscape. Sir Tony Robinson meets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-17 22:00:00" d="2019-08-18 00:25:00"><n>Miss Peregrine's Home for...</n><e>F</e>    <k>. eculiar Children: (2016) Eva Green and Asa Butterfield star in Tim Burton's fantasy adventure. A teenager enters the magical but scary and violent world</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 00:25:00" d="2019-08-18 03:10:00"><n>Exodus: Gods and Kings</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Drama. Christian Bale and Joel Edgerton star in Ridley Scott's account of Moses' attempt to free the Hebrews from Egyptian slavery and lead his people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 03:10:00" d="2019-08-18 04:00:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay visits New Jersey to rescue Italian restaurant Leone's, which has been run into the ground by the owner's son during her long illness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-18 04:00:00" d="2019-08-18 06:05:00"><n>Hollyoaks: Omnibus</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>52% Hollyoaks Omnibus
The Maalik family's Eid celebration turns nasty and Ste is very shocked by the level of intimidation that Stuart and Jonny inflict upon the family</k>  </p>
</a>
