<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="36" t="2020-05-12 04:26:26"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 05:50:00" d="2020-05-19 06:40:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S V (8)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Fiat Dino: The boys restore a rusty 1971 coupé with a Ferrari engine for its owner, ex-mechanic Chris, who had to put the restoration on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 06:40:00" d="2020-05-19 06:50:00"><n>Kirstie's Handmade Treasures</n><e>R</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp wants to surprise some guests with two delicious mains: roast beef with mulled wine gravy and a vegetarian option of masala cauliflower</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 06:50:00" d="2020-05-19 07:30:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Martin Lewis is in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 07:30:00" d="2020-05-19 07:50:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Mike's Boss: Mike is put in an uncomfortable position when his mother Peggy starts dating his boss, Police Captain Patrick Murphy, despite his many reservations. Ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 07:50:00" d="2020-05-19 08:15:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Yard Sale: Molly plans to declutter the house by holding a jumble sale, but whose old junk will get the boot? Mike takes Carl on a fishing trip to distract</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 08:15:00" d="2020-05-19 08:40:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers VI (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>'I' on Sports: Sam is asked to fill in for a TV sports reporter for a week, and persuades Rebecca to give him time off from the bar, but broadcasting isn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 08:40:00" d="2020-05-19 09:10:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers VI (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Little Carla, Happy at Last (Part 1): Carla and Eddie plan to marry but have many superstitious obstacles to overcome, including his mother, her children</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 09:10:00" d="2020-05-19 09:35:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Surprise Party: After Debra's mother suggests throwing Debra an old-fashioned English tea party, Ray reluctantly agrees, as long as she promises to do all the work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 09:35:00" d="2020-05-19 10:05:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Bird: Robert and Amy convince their families that it would be fun to spend Thanksgiving together, but the day gets off to a bad start</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 10:05:00" d="2020-05-19 10:35:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Juvenilia: Frasier is ambushed when he agrees to appear on a seemingly innocent teen-oriented radio show but is then interrogated by the brainy high-school panel</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 10:35:00" d="2020-05-19 11:00:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Proposal: A fussy Niles leaves nothing to chance when he plans the perfect evening as the backdrop for asking Daphne to be his wife</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 11:00:00" d="2020-05-19 11:30:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Wheels of Fortune: Lilith's half-brother Blaine Sternin (Michael Keaton) comes to town seeking Frasier's forgiveness for his past misdeeds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 11:30:00" d="2020-05-19 12:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Edinburgh. The first host, Canadian comedian Larah, plans a night of fine dining. It's an entertaining evening, featuring wonderful wigs and celebrity selfies. (Ep1/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 12:00:00" d="2020-05-19 12:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Edinburgh. Cafe owner Nutan hopes to impress her guests with her happy-go-lucky attitude and authentic north Indian menu. But eagle-eyed Sindiso</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 12:30:00" d="2020-05-19 13:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Edinburgh. South African-born family man Sindiso hosts the third night. After he dished out criticism, he's got his work cut out with his spicy chakalaka. (Ep3/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 13:00:00" d="2020-05-19 13:05:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 13:05:00" d="2020-05-19 13:35:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Edinburgh. Security company manager Anne plans to calm the simmering tension with a homely, relaxed atmosphere, on a night featuring strange collections</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 13:35:00" d="2020-05-19 14:05:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Edinburgh. Pilot James hopes that a touch of sophistication in his high-flying menu will see him land safely in first place. But can he keep the peace</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 14:05:00" d="2020-05-19 15:10:00"><n u="Sun, Sea and Selling Houses">Sun, Sea and Selling Houses II (17)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Mike and Sharon from Somerset are looking for a villa in Almería, but the first property that Sharon and Steve show them doesn't go down well</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 15:10:00" d="2020-05-19 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Margaret Mountford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 16:00:00" d="2020-05-19 17:00:00"><n u="A Place in the Sun 2018 -">A Place in the Sun 2018 - 2020</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun
Richard and Eileen have been holidaying in Cyprus for years and now want their own holiday home in their favourite town of Oroklini</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 17:00:00" d="2020-05-19 18:00:00"><n>Work on the Wild Side</n><e>F</e>    <k>Vets and volunteers rescue and rehabilitate animals in South Africa. Emily has a close call with a lion. Harriet hunts for an elephant. A baby rhino isn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 18:00:00" d="2020-05-19 19:00:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Laura and James, Sarah and Dan, and Edward and Carol compete to throw the best dinner party in Surrey, in an edition featuring rapping, monobrows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 19:00:00" d="2020-05-19 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Raging Abe Simpson and His Grumbling Grandson in 'The Curse of the Flying Hellfish': Mr Burns wants Grampa out of the way so that he can get his hands</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 19:30:00" d="2020-05-19 20:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Edward urges Verity to take his side. Tony makes a surprising decision. Charlie passes Jordan's test. Sami makes a move. And are Tom and Yazz about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 20:00:00" d="2020-05-19 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 21:00:00" d="2020-05-19 22:00:00"><n>The Great Celebrity Bake Off for SU2C</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>The Great Celebrity Bake Off. 
. or Stand Up To Cancer: Another chance to see Jeremy Paxman, Joe Wilkinson, Sally Lindsay and Georgia Toffolo</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 22:00:00" d="2020-05-19 23:00:00"><n>A Very British Hotel Chain</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: A Very British Hotel. 
. hain: Inside Best Western: Behind the scenes at Britain's largest independent hotel chain. New CEO Rob rejuvenates the brand</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-19 23:00:00" d="2020-05-20 00:05:00"><n u="First Dates Hotel">First Dates Hotel V</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Stacey wants a break from bad boys. Is Paul, who sells penile implants, the one for her? And can five-foot-four Reece get over the dating stumbling block</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 00:05:00" d="2020-05-20 00:10:00"><n>Ramadan in Lockdown</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Ramadan in Lockdown
This year, Britain's 2.6 million Muslims will observe Ramadan - up to 30 days fasting from sunrise to sunset - in lockdown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 00:10:00" d="2020-05-20 01:05:00"><n u="Ramsay's 24 Hours to Hell and Back">Ramsay's 24 Hours to Hell and Back II</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Gordon visits Vasi's Restaurant and Bar, a family-owned eatery in Waterbury, Connecticut, to remodel the dated interior as an inviting Mediterranean seaside taverna. Ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 01:05:00" d="2020-05-20 02:00:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Lincolnshire and Yorkshire, there's a one-man comedy show, a posh take on some Yorkshire classics, and a big surprise in store for one guest</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 02:00:00" d="2020-05-20 02:50:00"><n u="60 Days in Jail">60 Days in Jail II (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Sewer Gate: Raw sewage flows up through the floor into the inmate pods, causing chaos in the jail and making it necessary to turn off the water supply</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 02:50:00" d="2020-05-20 03:40:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay travels to Oakhurst, New Jersey, to help the overwhelmed owner of Mike and Nellie's restaurant, who lost his way when his father and business partner died</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 03:40:00" d="2020-05-20 04:30:00"><n u="Grand Designs New Zealand">Grand Designs New Zealand III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>A keen skier, who is a fan of Alpine homes, constructs a new log house using traditional techniques in Horopito, at the base of Mount Ruapehu on the North Island. Ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 04:30:00" d="2020-05-20 05:25:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie and Phil conduct a vast search across Hampshire, Wiltshire and Surrey. Retirees Sheila and Jason have been living out of boxes for a year</k>  </p>
</a>
