<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2021-07-09 07:02:12"><p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 05:15:00" d="2021-07-15 06:05:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>In Austin, Texas, Gordon Ramsay visits struggling Greek restaurant El Greco, where the owners have secretly recruited 'Chef Mike' the microwave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 06:05:00" d="2021-07-15 07:00:00"><n u="Location, Location, Location">Location, Location, Location XXIX (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>In south Devon, Kirstie Allsopp scours a sought-after seaside town where there's nothing for sale. And Phil Spencer meets a couple who are looking</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 07:00:00" d="2021-07-15 07:40:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Anne Robinson and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Grace Dent joins Susie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 07:40:00" d="2021-07-15 08:05:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly I</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Mike Snores: Annoyed about spending all of her time at Mike's home, Molly insists he stays at her place for a night, giving him a taste of how it would</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 08:05:00" d="2021-07-15 08:25:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly I</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Mike's New Boots: Molly becomes jealous when Mike introduces her as his 'friend' to Jill, a woman who is clearly enjoying flirting with him. Ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 08:25:00" d="2021-07-15 08:50:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>A Date for Peter: Amy's parents ask Ray to give their son Peter some tips on dating. Debra throws a cocktail party, but Ray isn't impressed by the guest list</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 08:50:00" d="2021-07-15 09:15:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Favors: Marie helps Debra to deal with Ray's bad habit of leaving his possessions lying around the house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 09:15:00" d="2021-07-15 09:40:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Faux Pas: Ray accidentally insults the twins' new friend to the boy's father and then makes it worse by repeating his mistake</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 09:40:00" d="2021-07-15 10:10:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Out with Dad: An unlikely chain of events forces Martin to pretend that he is gay on Valentine's Day</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 10:10:00" d="2021-07-15 10:40:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Something About Dr Mary: Frasier's temporary call-screener, 'Dr' Mary (Kim Coles), hijacks his show with her sassy attitude and no-nonsense advice</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 10:40:00" d="2021-07-15 11:10:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (22)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Graduation Transmission: Leonard is invited to make a speech at his old high school. Howard and Sheldon can't make a toy drone fly</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 11:10:00" d="2021-07-15 11:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (23)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Maternal Combustion: Personalities collide when Sheldon and Leonard's mothers finally meet. Howard decides to 'man up' and do his share of the housework</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 11:35:00" d="2021-07-15 12:05:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (24)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Commitment Determination: Sheldon pressures Leonard and Penny to choose a date for their wedding while dealing with changes in his own relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 12:05:00" d="2021-07-15 12:35:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons VIII (8)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>87% Hurricane Neddy: The Flanders' home is blown down by a hurricane and the Leftorium is looted. Homer leads the rebuilding project, but will Ned be happy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 12:35:00" d="2021-07-15 13:05:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons VIII</n><e>R</e>    <k>El Viaje Misterioso de Nuestro Jomer (The Mysterious Voyage of Our Homer): Homer eats a dangerous chilli grown by Guatemalan psychiatric patients and takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 13:05:00" d="2021-07-15 13:10:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 13:10:00" d="2021-07-15 14:10:00"><n u="Posh Pawnbrokers">Posh Pawnbrokers III (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>At London Road in Sheffield, Dan deals on a mysterious sculpture and a platinum ring. At Pickwick Pawnbrokers in London, Nathan and Debbs are gobsmacked</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 14:10:00" d="2021-07-15 15:10:00"><n u="A New Life in the Sun">A New Life in the Sun VI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Guest house owners in Spain hope the police won't visit their music event. In France, a motorhome business deals with damaged vehicles. A holiday village</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 15:10:00" d="2021-07-15 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Anne Robinson and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Philippa Perry joins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 16:00:00" d="2021-07-15 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Former police officer Steve McGibbon is looking for the perfect holiday home on Fuerteventura, on a budget of ?120,000</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 17:00:00" d="2021-07-15 18:00:00"><n>Mend It for Money</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>A church pew, an architect's table with an unusual story, and a copper bucket that's lost its shine need some TLC. Which restorers will be chosen to revive them? (Ep9/20)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 18:00:00" d="2021-07-15 19:00:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Brighton, David and Liz serve up crowd-pleasers with a twist, James and Paul make their evening personal, and Martin and Lorena host a Spanish fiesta</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 19:00:00" d="2021-07-15 19:30:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>The Maalik family are rattled by a shock confession, but there's another twist. Martine and Felix are drawn together. A minor slip-up allows captive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 19:30:00" d="2021-07-15 20:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>A stag do leads to a confession from the husband-to-be. Elsewhere, a startling secret is uncovered, there's a heartfelt conversation in the Maalik</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 20:00:00" d="2021-07-15 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 21:00:00" d="2021-07-15 22:00:00"><n>Can I Improve My Memory?</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Can I Improve My Memory?
Sandi Toksvig hosts, as celebs supercharge their memories, mastering a subject - and being quizzed on it. Can Chris Eubank</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 22:00:00" d="2021-07-15 23:00:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: Make Do and Mend">Escape to the Chateau: Make Do and Mend II (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Escape to the Chateau:. 
. ake Do and Mend: Dick and Angel help Amy to turn her summer house into a tropical room. Dick helps Sophia and Jenny build a bird hide</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 23:00:00" d="2021-07-16 00:05:00"><n u="Gordon Ramsay: Uncharted">Gordon Ramsay: Uncharted I (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Gordon Ramsay: Uncharted
The Mountains of Morocco: With help from Moroccan locals, Gordon dives into the food culture and ancient traditions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 00:05:00" d="2021-07-16 01:05:00"><n u="999: What's Your Emergency?">999: What's Your Emergency? XIII</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Northamptonshire police deal with the fallout from the hidden housing crisis of shared accommodation, from a row about unpaid rent to the suspected theft</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 01:05:00" d="2021-07-16 02:05:00"><n>Murder in the Outback</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Murder in the Outback: The. 
. alconio and Lees Mystery: A closer look at crucial DNA evidence raises serious questions about this controversial crime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 02:05:00" d="2021-07-16 02:55:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay visits Michon's, a family-run smokehouse eatery in Atlanta, Georgia, whose future is in doubt because of the owner's ill health</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 02:55:00" d="2021-07-16 03:55:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Brighton, romance, bedroom revelations and dancing in a tiny club are on the menu, as Sam and Nick, Maria and Terry, and Dave and Sarah compete</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 03:55:00" d="2021-07-16 04:40:00"><n u="Wife Swap USA">Wife Swap USA II</n><e>TF</e>    <k>A sideshow circus wife, whose dangerous occupation demands precision, swaps lives with a frazzled mother of four, whose home life is like a three-ring circus. Ep8)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-16 04:40:00" d="2021-07-16 05:35:00"><n>Food Unwrapped</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>77% Food Unwrapped: Fast Food Special
A celebration of the world of takeaways and fast food, from the pizzas at Papa John's, to the health risks</k>  </p>
</a>
