<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="35" t="2019-08-15 22:44:13"><p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 05:40:00" d="2019-08-21 05:55:00"><n>Kirstie's Vintage Gems</n><e>RF</e>    <k>In this bite-size edition, Kirstie Allsopp helps single dad Rich to create an original bedroom for his two young daughters, featuring a fabulous tree mural</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 05:55:00" d="2019-08-21 06:50:00"><n u="The ?100K Drop">The ?100K Drop III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Davina McCall is joined by Joe and Jamie, friends from London, and Lyndsay and Keith, a couple from Edinburgh. Will they get to the final question</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 06:50:00" d="2019-08-21 07:30:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Dr Linda Papadopoulos is in Dictionary Corner with Susie Dent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 07:30:00" d="2019-08-21 07:55:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly II</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Molly Needs a Number: When Molly is overwhelmed by Thanksgiving preparations and wedding planning, she asks Mike to help, with mixed results. Ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 07:55:00" d="2019-08-21 08:20:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly II</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Christmas Break: Molly receives some disappointing news at work and is thrown into a terrible mood that threatens to ruin Christmas. Ep11)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 08:20:00" d="2019-08-21 08:45:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>Hero Worship: Doug's uncle gives him money to fulfil his dream of setting up his own sandwich shop, but Carrie is worried about his business abilities</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 08:45:00" d="2019-08-21 09:10:00"><n>The King of Queens</n><e>R</e>    <k>Screwed Driver: Doug's parents visit when Carrie is away, prompting Doug to act like a child while Arthur invents a new type of screwdriver</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 09:10:00" d="2019-08-21 09:40:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Will: When Ray and Debra draw up their wills, their choice of replacement guardians for the kids doesn't go down well</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 09:40:00" d="2019-08-21 10:10:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Sister: Debra's hippie sister turns up unexpectedly at the house to announce that she has decided to become a nun</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 10:10:00" d="2019-08-21 10:40:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Semi-Decent Proposal: Frasier agrees to escort his former high school prom queen to her surprise birthday party but his goal is to spend time with her attractive friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 10:40:00" d="2019-08-21 11:10:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>A Passing Fancy: Frasier tutors Lorna's son Kirby in exchange for a date with Claire, while Roz gets a day off as a reward for taking Kirby to the prom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 11:10:00" d="2019-08-21 11:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Loobenfeld Decay: Leonard and Sheldon each tell a lie to avoid going to see Penny on stage singing in a production of Rent, but Sheldon's lie gets out of control</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 11:35:00" d="2019-08-21 12:00:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory I (11)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Pancake Batter Anomaly: Penny volunteers to nurse Sheldon when he's sick. However, his friends know how miserable he is when he's ill and stay well away from him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 12:00:00" d="2019-08-21 12:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Old Man and the Key: Grandpa borrows Homer's car to impress a new lady (Olympia Dukakis) at the Springfield Retirement Castle; but</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 12:30:00" d="2019-08-21 13:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Homer and Apu: Homer joins Apu on a trip of enlightenment to the first ever Kwik-E-Mart, in the Himalayas. Meanwhile, actor James Woods (guest starring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 13:00:00" d="2019-08-21 13:05:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 13:05:00" d="2019-08-21 14:05:00"><n u="A New Life in the Sun">A New Life in the Sun IV</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The inspectors descend on a Shropshire family's treehouse in France. In Spain a bistro gets a visit from a VIP, and will a Cambridgeshire couple in France</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 14:05:00" d="2019-08-21 15:10:00"><n>Posh Pawnbrokers</n><e>RF</e>    <k>In this episode, the pawnbrokers from London and Sheffield consider deals on a vintage trumpet, a replica Magna Carta and a gold pocket watch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 15:10:00" d="2019-08-21 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Dr Linda Papadopoulos is in Dictionary Corner with Susie Dent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 16:00:00" d="2019-08-21 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2018 &amp; 2019</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun
Gary and Linda live in Lincolnshire and have four children and three grandchildren between them. Danni Menzies is on</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 17:00:00" d="2019-08-21 18:00:00"><n u="The ?100K Drop">The ?100K Drop III</n>    <k>Davina McCall is joined by Ky and Anvir, friends from Birmingham and Leicester, and Becki and her father from Carlisle. Will either pair</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 18:00:00" d="2019-08-21 18:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n>    <k>The third host in and around Sheffield, is GP surgery manager Clare, who hopes to up the ante with a winter warmer menu. But food aficionado</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 18:30:00" d="2019-08-21 19:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Burns' Heir: Mr Burns decides he wants an heir and auditions Springfield's children for the position. When Bart wins, he must choose between his boring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 19:00:00" d="2019-08-21 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Sweetest Apu: Marge and Homer desperately try to get Apu and Manjula back together after she catches him cheating on her at the Kwik-E-Mart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 19:30:00" d="2019-08-21 20:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n>    <k>Breda is at a crossroads as she begs for God to give her a sign. Jack has gathered everyone at The Dog to try to establish who the serial killer is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 20:00:00" d="2019-08-21 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Includes sport and weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 21:00:00" d="2019-08-21 22:00:00"><n>Jamie Oliver: The Naked Chef Bares All</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Jamie Oliver: The Naked. 
. hef Bares All: Twenty years since Jamie exploded onto our screens, Davina McCall looks into his career: his rise to fame</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 22:00:00" d="2019-08-21 23:00:00"><n>Jade: The Reality Star Who Changed Britain</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Jade: The Reality Star Who. 
. hanged Britain. Told of her diagnosis for cancer during the Indian version of Big Brother, Jade Goody's life unravelled</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-21 23:00:00" d="2019-08-22 00:05:00"><n u="New: Naked Attraction">New: Naked Attraction V (1)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>A new series begins with 30-year-old Stephanie, a clumsy girl who never gets a second date, and first-time lesbian Bethany. Will Naked Attraction</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 00:05:00" d="2019-08-22 01:05:00"><n>The Sex Clinic</n><e>TF</e>    <k>Experts cut through taboos about young people's sexual health, offering sexual MOTs, STI tests, treatment and advice to anyone who walks through the clinic's doors. (Ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 01:05:00" d="2019-08-22 02:00:00"><n>Born Famous</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Born Famous: Michelle Mone
Entrepreneur Michelle Mone's daughter Bethany discovers what life could have been like if her mother wasn't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 02:00:00" d="2019-08-22 02:55:00"><n>Kathy Burke's All Woman</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Kathy explores motherhood, talking to actor Samantha Morton and comedian Katherine Ryan about their experiences, and attending a birth. (Ep2/3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 02:55:00" d="2019-08-22 03:50:00"><n>Train Your Baby Like a Dog</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Dog trainer and behaviourist Jo-Rosie Haffenden believes we should apply dog training reward techniques to our kids. She tests her method with a toddler</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 03:50:00" d="2019-08-22 04:40:00"><n>Undercover Boss USA</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Greg Adler, President and CEO of the off-road accessory empire 4 Wheel Parts, goes undercover to work in his own business, where his identity is closely</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2019-08-22 04:40:00" d="2019-08-22 05:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In north Wiltshire, über-confident businessman Sani hopes his African-inspired cuisine will win over party-loving pensioner Jane, 38-year-old Sharon</k>  </p>
</a>
