<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="35" t="2021-07-13 05:01:23"><p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 05:30:00" d="2021-07-20 06:25:00"><n u="Location, Location, Location">Location, Location, Location XXX (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Bournemouth, Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer help two single parents who want to bring their families together, and a family who are stuck in a rental rut</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 06:25:00" d="2021-07-20 06:50:00"><n u="Food Unwrapped">Food Unwrapped XVIII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>A trip to California reveals the secret to perfect walnuts. Matt finds out what makes sour sweets sour. And how do brewers make their trendy hazy beers cloudy? Ep2)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 06:50:00" d="2021-07-20 07:00:00"><n>Jamie's Comfort Food</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Jamie Oliver takes the nation's favourite dishes to the next level. In this episode, he cooks the perfect toasted cheese sandwich</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 07:00:00" d="2021-07-20 07:40:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Anne Robinson and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Grace Dent joins Susie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 07:40:00" d="2021-07-20 08:05:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly I</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Jim Won't Eat: When Peggy needs surgery, she surprises Molly by asking her to take care of her dog, Jim, while she's in hospital. Mike talks about where</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 08:05:00" d="2021-07-20 08:25:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly I</n><e>RF</e>    <k>First Valentine's Day: Mike makes special plans for his first Valentine's Day with Molly, but the romantic scheme is jeopardised when he accidentally meets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 08:25:00" d="2021-07-20 08:50:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Civil War: Ray volunteers for a Battle of Gettysburg re-enactment to spend some quality time with his father - but it turns out that they're fighting on opposite sides</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 08:50:00" d="2021-07-20 09:15:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Mia Famiglia: Ray's oldest living relative, his great aunt Sarina, turns up from Italy to help Ally with a school project about family trees</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 09:15:00" d="2021-07-20 09:40:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Marie's Meatballs: Ray asks Marie to teach Debra how to make her famous meatballs, to cure his wife's culinary inferiority complex. But Ray's plan has consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 09:40:00" d="2021-07-20 10:10:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Three Faces of Frasier: Frasier becomes obsessed with a caricature of him that hangs on the wall of a Seattle restaurant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 10:10:00" d="2021-07-20 10:40:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Dark Side of the Moon: Daphne buckles under the strain of planning her wedding, knowing deep down that it's because her true love is not her betrothed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 10:40:00" d="2021-07-20 11:10:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Spock Resonance: While he's being interviewed for a documentary about Star Trek character Mr Spock, Sheldon can't suppress his emotions about his split from Amy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 11:10:00" d="2021-07-20 11:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Mystery Date Observation: While Amy's out on a date with a mystery man, Sheldon enlists Howard and Raj to help him find a new girlfriend online</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 11:35:00" d="2021-07-20 12:05:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Platonic Permutation: At Thanksgiving, Sheldon and Amy hang out as friends at the aquarium, and Howard reluctantly agrees to volunteer at a soup kitchen</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 12:05:00" d="2021-07-20 12:35:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons VIII (14)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>87% The Itchy &amp; Scratchy &amp; Poochie Show: Homer gets a job on The Itchy &amp; Scratchy Show as the voice of hip-hop surfer dog Poochie, a character brought</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 12:35:00" d="2021-07-20 13:05:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons VIII (15)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>87% Homer's Phobia: When Bart befriends a gay shop owner (guest star John Waters), Homer decides to take his son hunting, but not everything goes according to plan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 13:05:00" d="2021-07-20 13:10:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 13:10:00" d="2021-07-20 14:10:00"><n u="Posh Pawnbrokers">Posh Pawnbrokers IV (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>In Penzance, bosses Larry and Neil do deals on unusual hand-painted unicorn sculptures and a rare gold disc by 1980s pop star Olivia Newton-John</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 14:10:00" d="2021-07-20 15:10:00"><n u="A New Life in the Sun">A New Life in the Sun VI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>A couple with a new B&amp;B row over renovations. A family of brewers from Kent dash across the Channel to beat lockdown. And a Skegness restaurateur's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 15:10:00" d="2021-07-20 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Anne Robinson and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Rachel Parris joins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 16:00:00" d="2021-07-20 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Michelle and Bernard love the Italian city of Lucca, with its Tuscan charm and beautiful countryside, and want their own holiday home there. Ben Hillman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 17:00:00" d="2021-07-20 18:00:00"><n>Mend It for Money</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>A vintage jukebox, a highly collectable antique gyrocycle, and a ship's porthole all need some TLC. But which restorers will be chosen to revive these tired items? (Ep11/20)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 18:00:00" d="2021-07-20 19:00:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Bournemouth, David and AJ plan a South African menu - with bread in every course. Vinnie and Alex serve South American dishes. And Andrea and Wayne's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 19:00:00" d="2021-07-20 19:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXVIII (6)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>87% There Will Be Buds: Homer gets roped into coaching the kids' lacrosse team with Milhouse's dad, Kirk, who desperately needs a friend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 19:30:00" d="2021-07-20 20:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Brody is in turmoil in the aftermath of the wedding, and things go from bad to worse as Summer continues her revenge. Nancy fears she might have forgiven Darren too soon. Warren is furious</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 20:00:00" d="2021-07-20 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 21:00:00" d="2021-07-20 22:00:00"><n u="Bake Off: The Professionals">Bake Off: The Professionals IV (9)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Bake Off: The Professionals
It's the semi-final and the four remaining teams bake batches of perfect petit fours, before creating a magical, teddy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 22:00:00" d="2021-07-20 23:00:00"><n u="24 Hours in A&amp;E">24 Hours in A&amp;E XXIV</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: 24 Hours in A&amp;E
New parents Danny and Jordan are worried that five-day-old Gracie may have an infected umbilical cord. They talk about life changes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 23:00:00" d="2021-07-21 00:00:00"><n>New: Torn Apart: Family Courts...</n><e>F</e>    <k>. ncovered: Dispatches: An unprecedented look at what's going on behind closed doors in family courts, including shocking personal testimony and footage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-21 00:00:00" d="2021-07-21 01:15:00"><n>Gold Diggers</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Walter Presents: Gold Diggers
Russian thriller set in a world of money, sex and power. In Moscow, Marina Levkoeva appears to have it all, but after</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-21 01:15:00" d="2021-07-21 02:10:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay travels to Baltimore, Maryland, to try to save the struggling Café Hon restaurant, which is suffering because its owner has alienated</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-21 02:10:00" d="2021-07-21 03:00:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Nottingham, three couples compete with holiday-inspired menus, in a week featuring a sweaty confession, an underwhelming paella and an alpha-male arm wrestle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-21 03:00:00" d="2021-07-21 03:30:00"><n u="This Way Up">This Way Up II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Aisling Bea's pin-sharp, poignant comedy-drama returns. Aine has a date with Etienne's dad, Richard. Shona struggles to settle in at home with her fiancé</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-21 03:30:00" d="2021-07-21 04:25:00"><n>Extraordinary Escapes with Sandi Toksvig</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Extraordinary Escapes with. 
. andi Toksvig: Sandi's joined by Sindhu Vee for some remarkable Scottish escapes, from a lighthouse keeper's cottage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-21 04:25:00" d="2021-07-21 05:10:00"><n u="Wife Swap USA">Wife Swap USA II</n><e>TF</e>    <k>A materialistic city lady who believes that appearance is everything swaps lives with a charity-minded farmer's wife. Ep10)</k>  </p>
</a>
