<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2020-05-28 04:38:39"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 05:05:00" d="2020-06-04 06:00:00"><n>Britain's Best Parent?</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Anita Rani hosts as parents aim to prove their parenting style is best. Joana has a gender-fluid approach. Kevin and Kerry are hands-off. Rin and Robin's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 06:00:00" d="2020-06-04 06:25:00"><n>Richard &amp; Judy: Keep Reading and Carry On</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Richard &amp; Judy: Keep Reading. 
. nd Carry On: Richard and Judy chat to David Walliams about his new book, Bernardine Evaristo reveals her top tips</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 06:25:00" d="2020-06-04 06:50:00"><n>Richard &amp; Judy: Keep Reading and Carry On</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Richard &amp; Judy: Keep Reading. 
. nd Carry On: Sue Perkins and Emilia Fox join Richard and Judy to review an all-time classic, Maggie O'Farrell discusses</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 06:50:00" d="2020-06-04 07:30:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Kate Adie is in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 07:30:00" d="2020-06-04 07:55:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers VII (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>How to Recede in Business: Evan Drake's replacement, Greg Stone, fires Rebecca as bar manager and promotes Sam. In a bid to curry favour, Sam plots to get her rehired</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 07:55:00" d="2020-06-04 08:20:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers VII (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Swear to God: One of Sam's exes tells him that he may be the father of her unborn child, so he swears he will abstain from sex for a year if his paternity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 08:20:00" d="2020-06-04 08:45:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Pat's Secret: Robert is shocked when he discovers Pat smoking, but not enough to refuse a drag on her cigarette. Then he proves that he can't be trusted with secrets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 08:45:00" d="2020-06-04 09:10:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Finale: In the last-ever episode of the US comedy series, events take a dramatic turn when Ray goes into hospital to have his adenoids removed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 09:10:00" d="2020-06-04 09:35:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly IV</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Weekend at Peggy's: Following a dramatic argument with Joyce over money, Mike and Molly make a hasty decision to move into Mike's childhood bedroom at Peggy's house. Ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 09:35:00" d="2020-06-04 10:00:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly IV</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Dips &amp; Salsa: Mike asks Carl to replace him as Molly's dance partner at a salsa class, but he gets jealous when he realises that they are having way too much fun. Ep10)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 10:00:00" d="2020-06-04 10:30:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>A Man, a Plan and a Gal - Julia: Daphne and Niles have an important announcement to make, but Frasier's girlfriend steals their thunder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 10:30:00" d="2020-06-04 11:00:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Doctor Is Out: The debonair conductor of the Seattle Opera (guest star Patrick Stewart) mistakenly believes that Frasier is gay and starts courting him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 11:00:00" d="2020-06-04 11:30:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Babysitter: It's a battle of the Cranes as Frasier and Martin fall for the same girl - the boys' childhood babysitter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 11:30:00" d="2020-06-04 12:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>Gloucestershire. Actor and otter conservationist Daphne, who's 80, hosts an entertaining and eventful evening featuring simple fare, furry friends</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 12:00:00" d="2020-06-04 12:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Gloucestershire. Youth worker Aisha serves up spicy Jamaican food with a side dish of hip hop. Will last night's dessert deserter Anne return? (Ep2/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 12:30:00" d="2020-06-04 13:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Gloucestershire. Hairdresser Debbie hosts a music-themed night. But James's opinions of her food cause consternation, and he offends Aisha when he shuts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 13:00:00" d="2020-06-04 13:05:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 13:05:00" d="2020-06-04 13:35:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Gloucestershire. Beauty product salesman James serves up a Canadian menu for his four female guests, but Debbie and Aisha are out for revenge. (Ep4/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 13:35:00" d="2020-06-04 14:05:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Gloucestershire. It's the last night, and Sarah Louise treats her guests to some family favourites, including 'roast chicken with a twist'</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 14:05:00" d="2020-06-04 15:10:00"><n u="A New Life in the Sun">A New Life in the Sun V</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Two ex-pat gite owners open for business in France. In Spain, a diving school deals with a very nervous customer. And there's a life-changing event</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 15:10:00" d="2020-06-04 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Kate Adie is in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 16:00:00" d="2020-06-04 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Now that she's retired, the time is right for Pat from Reading to buy a holiday home on the south-east coast of Cyprus. Can Scarlette Douglas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 17:00:00" d="2020-06-04 18:00:00"><n>Work on the Wild Side</n><e>F</e>    <k>Vets and volunteers rescue and rehabilitate animals in South Africa. Alison prepares to release an endangered penguin. Emily anaesthetises a cheetah</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 18:00:00" d="2020-06-04 19:00:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Brighton, Hannah and Luke give their guests a sneak peek of their wedding breakfast. There are jaw-dropping revelations on Karen and Mark's night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 19:00:00" d="2020-06-04 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>RF</e>    <k>The Devil Wears Nada: Marge and her friends raise money for charity by posing for a racy calendar, but Marge is too shy to show off her body, until</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 19:30:00" d="2020-06-04 20:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Pranks and Greens: Bart is determined to seek out the best prankster in Springfield Elementary's history to ask him all about his legendary practical jokes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 20:00:00" d="2020-06-04 21:05:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 21:05:00" d="2020-06-04 22:00:00"><n>Britain's Best Parent?</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Britain's Best Parent?
Anita Rani hosts as parents aim to prove their parenting style is best. Hannah takes a parent-centric approach</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 22:00:00" d="2020-06-04 23:05:00"><n u="First Dates Hotel">First Dates Hotel V</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: First Dates Hotel
It's the end of another summer of love, and Fred and his team are determined to go out on a high as cat-lover Zoe dates Joseph</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-04 23:05:00" d="2020-06-05 00:20:00"><n>America's Animal Hoarder:...</n><e>R</e>    <k>. orror at the Zoo: The true story of how 18 tigers, 17 lions and eight bears belonging to a private collector were found roaming the streets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 00:20:00" d="2020-06-05 01:25:00"><n u="Joe Lycett's Got Your Back">Joe Lycett's Got Your Back II</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Alison Hammond helps Joe discover how trustworthy Trustpilot is. Joe takes aim at a paintballing company's dubious practices and takes on the Google Play Store</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 01:25:00" d="2020-06-05 02:15:00"><n>Poker</n><t>S</t>    <k>PokerStars Players Championship
It's the penultimate day of the biggest High Roller of all time. Can amateur poker players Jackie Burkhart and Michael</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 02:15:00" d="2020-06-05 04:40:00"><n>Mulk</n><e>F</e>    <k>Rishi Kapoor stars as an elderly Muslim lawyer defending his family against the accusation that they groom terrorists, after his nephew is found</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 04:40:00" d="2020-06-05 05:35:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Gill and Mark, Matt and Derek, and Cat and Martin compete to host the best dinner party in Glasgow, in a week featuring an impromptu sing-song, a kitchen</k>  </p>
</a>
