<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2020-05-14 04:53:53"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 05:45:00" d="2020-05-21 06:35:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S III (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Little Black Corvette: Tim and Fuzz restore a 1974 Chevrolet Corvette Stingray that has been off the road for years, but it's a bigger job than they thought</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 06:35:00" d="2020-05-21 06:50:00"><n>Kirstie's Fill Your House for Free</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and the team help a Southbourne couple jazz up their living room, hall and bedroom</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 06:50:00" d="2020-05-21 07:30:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>R</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Colin Murray</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 07:30:00" d="2020-05-21 07:50:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Karaoke Christmas: Even while playing the role of Santa, Mike can't contain his frustration about Molly's extravagant Christmas spending</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 07:50:00" d="2020-05-21 08:15:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Fish for Breakfast: In an effort to boost their chances of getting pregnant, Molly encourages Mike to join her in her campaign to eat more healthily</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 08:15:00" d="2020-05-21 08:40:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers VI (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Paint Your Office: When Norm is unable to pay his bar bill, he settles his debt by painting Rebecca's office and believes he's discovered a heart under</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 08:40:00" d="2020-05-21 09:10:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers VI (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Last Angry Mailman: Developers announce they want to tear down Cliff's home and put up a shopping mall. The gang are curious when they hear about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 09:10:00" d="2020-05-21 09:35:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Slave: Ray and Debra inadvertently leave the twins home alone and are impressed with Ally when she takes care of them, so they offer her lots of other work</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 09:35:00" d="2020-05-21 10:05:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Whose Side Are You On?: After discovering that Debra places bets with the kids on his strange behaviour, Ray is disturbed to find out that his children</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 10:05:00" d="2020-05-21 10:35:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Love You Fake: Frasier and his neighbour Cam attempt to put an end to their feud because of their parents' supposed love affair</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 10:35:00" d="2020-05-21 11:00:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Cheerful Goodbyes: Frasier meets up with some of the old Cheers gang in Boston for Cliff's retirement party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 11:00:00" d="2020-05-21 11:30:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Frasier Has Spokane: When Frasier's radio programme is syndicated in Spokane, it replaces a local broadcaster's show, enraging his callers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 11:30:00" d="2020-05-21 12:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>Belfast. Mobile phone sales manager Steve hosts a banter-filled night of impersonations, romance and sausage talk. (Ep1/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 12:00:00" d="2020-05-21 12:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>Belfast. Flame-haired hairbrush executive Julie serves her own versions of takeaway classics, drawing on her experiences from living in Japan and China. (Ep2/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 12:30:00" d="2020-05-21 13:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>Belfast. Mobile barista Justin hopes to wow his guests (especially Julie!) with a barbecue extravaganza, including a barbecued dessert. But there's a tense atmosphere. (Ep3/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 13:00:00" d="2020-05-21 13:05:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 13:05:00" d="2020-05-21 13:35:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Belfast. Executive assistant Cushla plans to impress with scallops, venison and an exotic jus, but the night is dominated by dodgy impressions and Julie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 13:35:00" d="2020-05-21 14:05:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>The final host in Belfast is super-foodie fan of the Far East, Marty. But after a week of endless Bo' Selecta! impressions, Steve's starting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 14:05:00" d="2020-05-21 15:10:00"><n u="Sun, Sea and Selling Houses">Sun, Sea and Selling Houses II (20)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Joanne from Staffordshire wants to fulfil the holiday home dream that she shared with her late husband. But she doesn't know exactly what she's looking for</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 15:10:00" d="2020-05-21 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Margaret Mountford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 16:00:00" d="2020-05-21 17:00:00"><n u="A Place in the Sun 2018 -">A Place in the Sun 2018 - 2020</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun
Maggie and Alistair dream of swapping Scottish winters for the white sandy beaches of sunny Gran Canaria. Jasmine Harman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 17:00:00" d="2020-05-21 18:00:00"><n>Work on the Wild Side</n><e>F</e>    <k>Vets and volunteers rescue and rehabilitate animals in South Africa. Emma looks after an aardvark who needs five-hour walks every night, and Josie deals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 18:00:00" d="2020-05-21 19:00:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Lee and Tash, Judy and Will, and Jess and Dale compete to host the best dinner party in Stockport, in an edition featuring vanilla cured salmon</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 19:00:00" d="2020-05-21 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Summer of 4'2&quot;: Lisa uses the holiday as a chance to change her image and gets in with a cool crowd (including guest star Christina Ricci)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 19:30:00" d="2020-05-21 20:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Treehouse of Horror V: The Simpsons become winter caretakers at Mr Burns' mountain mansion, where Homer is driven mad by the lack of beer and TV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 20:00:00" d="2020-05-21 21:05:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 21:05:00" d="2020-05-21 22:00:00"><n>Spring at Jimmy's Farm</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Spring at Jimmy's Farm
In this concluding episode, we see how Jimmy Doherty and his small team continue to care for the animals while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 22:00:00" d="2020-05-21 23:00:00"><n u="First Dates Hotel">First Dates Hotel V</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: First Dates Hotel
Make-up artist Kiera hopes her hilariously bad luck in love is over as she meets Essex builder Jack. Online relationship</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 23:00:00" d="2020-05-22 00:05:00"><n>The Boy Whose Skin Fell Off</n><e>R</e>    <k>Frank and moving classic documentary about Jonny Kennedy, an extraordinary man with a terrible condition that makes his skin fall off at the slightest touch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 00:05:00" d="2020-05-22 00:10:00"><n>Ramadan in Lockdown</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Ramadan in Lockdown
This year, Britain's 2.6 million Muslims will observe Ramadan - up to 30 days fasting from sunrise to sunset - in lockdown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 00:10:00" d="2020-05-22 01:15:00"><n u="Joe Lycett's Got Your Back">Joe Lycett's Got Your Back II</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>MP Jess Phillips helps Joe as he investigates budget flights and tracks down Airbnb scammers. Plus: reducing our carbon footprint and ingenious</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 01:15:00" d="2020-05-22 02:10:00"><n>Poker</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>PokerStars Players Championship
It's bubble time in the Bahamas. The moment approaches when players in the biggest $25k poker tournament in history start</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 02:10:00" d="2020-05-22 03:00:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay visits Michon's, a family-run smokehouse eatery in Atlanta, Georgia, whose future is in doubt because of the owner's ill health</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 03:00:00" d="2020-05-22 05:05:00"><n>The Host</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Sci-fi drama starring Saoirse Ronan. A group of humans try to avoid succumbing to alien parasites that take over their hosts' personalities. With Diane Kruger. Violence</k>  </p>
</a>
