<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="40" t="2020-05-29 04:35:57"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 05:35:00" d="2020-06-05 06:25:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S V (7)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Mazda RX-7: Tim and Fuzz restore a Japanese sports car with an innovative and unusual rotary engine that belongs to charity worker Conor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 06:25:00" d="2020-06-05 06:50:00"><n>Beat the Chef</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>A talented amateur cook competes with professional chef Frederick Forster to make spicy pork tacos and guacamole. (Ep23)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 06:50:00" d="2020-06-05 07:30:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Kate Adie is in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 07:30:00" d="2020-06-05 07:55:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers VII (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Executive Sweet: Greg Stone is fired, and Rebecca gets a new boss - Martin Teal, a young hotshot who takes a liking to her and reinstates her as bar manager</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 07:55:00" d="2020-06-05 08:20:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers VII (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>One Happy Chappy in a Snappy Serape: The company sends Sam to open a new bar in Mexico, but Rebecca needs him to stay in Boston and pose as her fiancé</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 08:20:00" d="2020-06-05 08:45:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Pilot: Debra wants a peaceful birthday with Ray, so he tells his parents and brother that there's no party: a lie that has embarrassing consequences</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 08:45:00" d="2020-06-05 09:10:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>I Love You: Debra is upset that Ray has trouble saying 'I love you' - and she gets even more annoyed when he shares his problem with his interfering parents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 09:10:00" d="2020-06-05 09:35:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly IV</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Mind Over Molly: Molly grudgingly goes to see a therapist at Mike's urging, but as the sessions progress, her belief that the counselling is unnecessary is challenged. Ep11)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 09:35:00" d="2020-06-05 10:00:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly IV</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Open Mike Night: Molly offers her wisdom to Samuel, who aspires to be a stand-up comedian. And Molly's advice to Harry makes him challenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 10:00:00" d="2020-06-05 10:30:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Placeholder: Frasier feels like a gooseberry on a night out with Niles, Daphne, Martin and Ronee, so Roz convinces him to go on a date with her friend Ann</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 10:30:00" d="2020-06-05 11:00:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>I'm Listening: Frasier overhears his dad's girlfriend Ronee making a date with another man, but when Martin hears the news he accuses his son of eavesdropping</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 11:00:00" d="2020-06-05 11:30:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Maris Returns (Part 1/2): Niles' ex-wife Maris needs his help - can he keep her return secret from a pregnant and emotional Daphne?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 11:30:00" d="2020-06-05 12:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Berkshire. The first host, 54-year-old events organiser Sarah, hosts a French-themed evening, with her own pastry in her lemon tart, and some of Henley's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 12:00:00" d="2020-06-05 12:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Berkshire. Music merchandiser Rob serves his restaurant favourites, but puts his foot in it when he asks his guests to wear slippers. Later, there's</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 12:30:00" d="2020-06-05 13:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Berkshire. Self-professed super-mum Lydia serves a 'taste of the savannah' Kenyan menu. After she criticised Sarah and Rob's food, how will her guests react? (Ep3/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 13:00:00" d="2020-06-05 13:05:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 13:05:00" d="2020-06-05 13:35:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Berkshire. On the penultimate night, telecoms manager Susan serves up a spicy menu, including the intriguing chicken mole. (Ep4/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 13:35:00" d="2020-06-05 14:05:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Berkshire. John plans a Spanish fiesta for the final night. But there's a spat between Sarah and Lydia, Susan's table manners leave a lot to be desired</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 14:05:00" d="2020-06-05 15:10:00"><n u="A New Life in the Sun">A New Life in the Sun V</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>A horse-riding school in Spain has a chance to earn big money. In France, there's a jaw-dropping surprise for a gite owner. Ep15)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 15:10:00" d="2020-06-05 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Kate Adie is in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 16:00:00" d="2020-06-05 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Mandy and Paul from Sussex want to make a permanent move to the Spanish town of Dolores with their six cats and rescue dog. Jasmine Harman shows</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 17:00:00" d="2020-06-05 18:00:00"><n>Work on the Wild Side</n><e>F</e>    <k>Vets and volunteers rescue and rehabilitate animals in South Africa. Anna dehorns two rare and dangerous black rhinos. Jenna and Sean tackle the issue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 18:00:00" d="2020-06-05 19:00:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Brighton, David and Liz serve crowd-pleasers with a twist. James and Paul make their evening personal. And Martin and Lorena host a Spanish fiesta</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 19:00:00" d="2020-06-05 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Rednecks and Broomsticks: Homer spends time with Cletus and his pals when he discovers that they are making moonshine. Lisa gets to know three teenage Wiccans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 19:30:00" d="2020-06-05 20:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>RF</e>    <k>O Brother, Where Bart Thou?: Bart grows jealous of Lisa's relationship with Maggie and asks Homer if he can have a baby brother. Featuring Kim Cattrall</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 20:00:00" d="2020-06-05 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 21:00:00" d="2020-06-05 22:00:00"><n u="Joe Lycett's Got Your Back">Joe Lycett's Got Your Back II</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Joe Lycett's Got Your Back
Joe presents a special episode, featuring behind-the-scenes insights, never-before-seen moments, and his most outrageous</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 22:00:00" d="2020-06-05 23:00:00"><n u="Celebrity Gogglebox">Celebrity Gogglebox II</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Celebrity Gogglebox
Some of Britain's best-loved personalities hit the sofa to watch the week's biggest TV shows, including Zoe Ball, Harry Redknapp</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-05 23:00:00" d="2020-06-06 00:05:00"><n>The Last Leg</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Live: The Last Leg: Locked Down. 
. nder: Adam Hills, Josh Widdicombe and Alex Brooker host from their homes in Australia and the UK with their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 00:05:00" d="2020-06-06 00:35:00"><n u="The IT Crowd">The IT Crowd I (1)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>66% Yesterday's Jam: Award-winning sitcom. New recruit Jen is made head of the IT department, but her staff, Moss and Roy, soon discover that she knows nothing about computers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 00:35:00" d="2020-06-06 01:05:00"><n u="The IT Crowd">The IT Crowd I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>66% Calamity Jen: The team face a big test during Reynholm Industries' so-called 'war on stress'. The office is on fire, Roy has an attack of kleptomania</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 01:05:00" d="2020-06-06 01:35:00"><n u="The IT Crowd">The IT Crowd I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>66% 50/50: Jen has an admirer, but his romantic gesture goes badly wrong when Jen's inability to tell the truth results in a public humiliation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 01:35:00" d="2020-06-06 02:05:00"><n u="The IT Crowd">The IT Crowd I (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>66% The Red Door: What's behind the mysterious red door in the IT department? What has happened to Moss's new mug? And why is Roy in danger of becoming known</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 02:05:00" d="2020-06-06 02:30:00"><n u="The IT Crowd">The IT Crowd I (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>66% The Haunting of Bill Crouse: Moss goes to extraordinary lengths to help Jen escape the unwanted attention of potential suitor Bill Crouse, while</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 02:30:00" d="2020-06-06 03:00:00"><n u="The IT Crowd">The IT Crowd I (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RT</e>    <k>66% Aunt Irma Visits: Jen explains that she is subject to very powerful mood swings around a certain time every month. But then Moss and Roy start to display similar symptoms</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 03:00:00" d="2020-06-06 03:25:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Warwickshire. The first host, 50-year-old fitness instructor Liza, plans to impress her guests with a French menu and three well-oiled hunks. (Ep1/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 03:25:00" d="2020-06-06 03:50:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Warwickshire. Sailor and ladies' man Steve hosts a nautical evening. But what will his four female guests think when they discover the secrets of his love ship? (Ep2/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 03:50:00" d="2020-06-06 04:20:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Warwickshire. Talkative admin manager Emma lays on an Indian menu with a 'Bollywood or bust' dress code and dancing. But it's bottoms up for Steve</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 04:20:00" d="2020-06-06 04:45:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Warwickshire. PA Pinky plans to introduce her guests to the finer things in life with a night of sophistication and pageantry. But Liza doesn't think</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-06-06 04:45:00" d="2020-06-06 05:15:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Warwickshire. Eccentric driving instructor Alison hosts a 1980s disco-themed night that reaches a sticky end with a marshmallow competition. (Ep5/5)</k>  </p>
</a>
