<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="39" t="2020-05-15 04:54:29"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 05:05:00" d="2020-05-22 06:00:00"><n u="Grand Designs New Zealand">Grand Designs New Zealand III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>A mother-of-six from Helensville, north-west of Auckland, plans to recreate the historic villa she fell in love with as a child, but her husband wants a modern house. Ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 06:00:00" d="2020-05-22 06:50:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S III (10)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Vive La Citroën: Tim and Fuzz visit Eastbourne to rescue an iconic French front-wheel-drive car, a 1954 Citroën Traction Avant belonging to a former watchmaker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 06:50:00" d="2020-05-22 07:30:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Margaret Mountford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 07:30:00" d="2020-05-22 07:50:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Carl Gets a Roommate: Mike begins transforming the basement into a living area for himself and Molly, but the construction work is tricky. Carl invites</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 07:50:00" d="2020-05-22 08:15:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>The Princess and the Troll: Mike and Molly encourage Harry to take Victoria on a date. Carl convinces Samuel that the launderette is the perfect place</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 08:15:00" d="2020-05-22 08:40:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers VI (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Bidding on the Boys: Rebecca organises a bachelor auction for charity, with Sam and Woody among the prizes, but both men are less than thrilled about the winning bidders</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 08:40:00" d="2020-05-22 09:10:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers VI (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Pudd'n Head Boyd: Woody joins a theatre group and understudies for the role of Mark Twain. While wearing his costume and make-up in the bar, an older woman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 09:10:00" d="2020-05-22 09:35:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Lateness: Fed up with his wife's constant tardiness, Ray leaves Debra at home, rather than taking her to an awards ceremony</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 09:35:00" d="2020-05-22 10:05:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Party Dress: Ray and Debra disagree over whether they should buy an expensive dress for Ally to wear to a friend's formal 13th birthday party</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 10:05:00" d="2020-05-22 10:35:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Guilt Trippers: A birthday party held in Daphne's honour sets in motion some rather surprising and unexpected events</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 10:35:00" d="2020-05-22 11:00:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Moon Over Seattle: Niles finally convinces Daphne's hard-drinking father in England to return to her harpy-like mother in Seattle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 11:00:00" d="2020-05-22 11:30:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Ring Cycle: Niles and Daphne marry on an impulse while on holiday in Reno but are forced to hide their good news when they return to Seattle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 11:30:00" d="2020-05-22 12:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In and around Belfast. Chatty PR manager Claire plans a menu of her restaurant favourites. But she has a challenge on her hands, as she's never plucked</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 12:00:00" d="2020-05-22 12:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In and around Belfast. Carpenter Neil takes his guests on a weird and wonderful visit to the countryside, featuring country-style cuisine, farmyard animals</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 12:30:00" d="2020-05-22 13:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In and around Belfast. Debonair window-cleaning business owner Paul plans an evening of fancy food and fine dining. For some of his guests, it's uncharted territory. (Ep3/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 13:00:00" d="2020-05-22 13:05:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 13:05:00" d="2020-05-22 13:35:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>R</e>    <k>In and around Belfast. DJ and events organiser Ryan hosts a madcap evening of fun, with a hipster band playing in his living room and several crises in the kitchen. (Ep4/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 13:35:00" d="2020-05-22 14:05:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In and around Belfast. Final host Cailin throws a Eurovision extravaganza, with dishes from across Europe and full-on fancy dress</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 14:05:00" d="2020-05-22 15:10:00"><n u="Sun, Sea and Selling Houses">Sun, Sea and Selling Houses II (19)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Ian from Fife is looking for a holiday home for his family, but he's searching in Spain without them. Another holiday home-hunter dramatically increases her budget</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 15:10:00" d="2020-05-22 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Margaret Mountford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 16:00:00" d="2020-05-22 17:00:00"><n u="A Place in the Sun 2018 -">A Place in the Sun 2018 - 2020</n><t>S</t>    <k>A Place in the Sun
Sandra and Desmond are looking for their dream holiday home near Mar Menor's stunning beaches on Spain's Costa Calida</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 17:00:00" d="2020-05-22 18:00:00"><n>Work on the Wild Side</n><e>F</e>    <k>Vets and volunteers rescue and rehabilitate animals in South Africa. Harriet helps with an elephant wounded by a snare, and Debbie is</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 18:00:00" d="2020-05-22 19:00:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Bromley, Ryan and Julie's food fails to impress, with one guest comparing the main to vomit! Can Jo and Alex or Michelle and Craig do better with their</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 19:00:00" d="2020-05-22 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Lisa on Ice: Bart and Lisa's rivalry intensifies when she takes up ice hockey and their teams are scheduled to play each other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 19:30:00" d="2020-05-22 20:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Homer Badman: The babysitter accuses Homer of sexual harassment when he tries to pick a rare sweet off the back of her trousers</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 20:00:00" d="2020-05-22 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 21:00:00" d="2020-05-22 22:00:00"><n u="Joe Lycett's Got Your Back">Joe Lycett's Got Your Back II</n><t>S</t>    <k>New: Joe Lycett's Got Your Back
Joe exposes a money-making scheme and turns the tables on nuisance callers. Katherine Ryan brings hype to a struggling business</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 22:00:00" d="2020-05-22 23:00:00"><n u="Gogglebox">Gogglebox XV</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Gogglebox
Britain's sharpest armchair critics share more of their insightful, passionate and sometimes emotional critiques of the week's biggest and best shows. Ep14)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-22 23:00:00" d="2020-05-23 00:05:00"><n>The Last Leg</n><t>S</t>    <k>Live: The Last Leg: Locked Down. 
. nder: Adam Hills, Josh Widdicombe and Alex Brooker host from their homes in Melbourne, London and Huddersfield</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 00:05:00" d="2020-05-23 01:10:00"><n>Da Best of Ali G</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Another chance to see some of Ali G's most memorable interviews from The 11 O'Clock Show, plus a special guided tour of his hometown, including visits</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 01:10:00" d="2020-05-23 01:40:00"><n u="Da Ali G Show">Da Ali G Show I (2)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>77% Ali G Night: Da Ali G Show
Ali G says 'booyakasha' and 'respect' to his army of devotees in his own series. Mohamed Al Fayed raps. Borat finds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 01:40:00" d="2020-05-23 02:10:00"><n>Ali G in Da USAiii</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Ali G Night: Ali G in Da USAiii
Ali G leaves the Staines Massive behind to large it Stateside, keeping it real and addressing the big issues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 02:10:00" d="2020-05-23 02:40:00"><n>Ali G in Da USAiii</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Ali G Night: Ali G in Da USAiii
Ali G keeps it real Stateside. Ali speaks to prominent Republican Newt Gingrich, Borat tries his hand at acting</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 02:40:00" d="2020-05-23 03:10:00"><n>The Best of Borat</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Ali G Night: The Best of Borat
Kazakhstan's most celebrated journalist, the ever-enthusiastic Borat Karabzhanov, tries to make sense of British culture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 03:10:00" d="2020-05-23 03:35:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Treehouse of Horror V: The Simpsons become winter caretakers at Mr Burns' mountain mansion, where Homer is driven mad by the lack of beer and TV</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 03:35:00" d="2020-05-23 04:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>East Hampshire. Cabby Nik Christides hosts first, with some unusual ingredients and his favourite pub game: 'cheesy darts'. (Ep1/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 04:00:00" d="2020-05-23 04:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>East Hampshire. Mum-of-four Jax's 'Arty and Tarty' theme is misinterpreted by Natalie, who turns up dressed in black leather, but her life-drawing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 04:30:00" d="2020-05-23 04:55:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RF</e>    <k>East Hampshire. Natalie hosts an evening of tradition from her homeland, with Russian food, dancing and customs - including banning shoes inside the house. (Ep3/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-23 04:55:00" d="2020-05-23 07:55:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>East Hampshire. History buff Kyle asks his guests to dress up as historical characters, from Cleopatra to Vladimir Putin. And he needs their</k>  </p>
</a>
