<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="35" t="2020-04-09 04:33:41"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 05:05:00" d="2020-04-16 06:00:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer are in Kent, helping Robin and Gemma to find a family home after three years living in Singapore, and first-time buyers Gemma and Barney</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 06:00:00" d="2020-04-16 06:50:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S I (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Phoenix Jeep: Tim Shaw and Fuzz Townshend take on a renovation project to surprise the owner of a US Army Jeep that survived World War</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 06:50:00" d="2020-04-16 07:25:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Tom Kerridge joins Susie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 07:25:00" d="2020-04-16 07:50:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers IV (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Love Thy Neighbor: Diane is incensed by the way Sam refers to her during a radio interview. Norm is confronted with evidence of his wife's infidelity</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 07:50:00" d="2020-04-16 08:15:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers IV (9)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>From Beer to Eternity: Sam challenges rival bar Gary's Tavern to a bowling match, only to find the Cheers regulars are hopelessly bad at the sport</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 08:15:00" d="2020-04-16 08:40:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Young Girl: Robert is dating a 22-year-old woman. Debra and Marie think he's being foolish, but Ray and Frank aren't so sure. But is she really 22?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 08:40:00" d="2020-04-16 09:05:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Fighting In-Laws: Debra's parents come round for Thanksgiving dinner. Debra's so pleased that they're not like Frank and Marie - or are they?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 09:05:00" d="2020-04-16 09:35:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>To Tell the Truth: Niles hires Donny Davis (Saul Rubinek), a legal shark and Roz's ex-boyfriend, to represent him in the divorce case</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 09:35:00" d="2020-04-16 10:05:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Decoys: Niles discovers that Daphne is dating Donny, his divorce attorney, so he hatches a plan to try to get Donny back together with Roz</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 10:05:00" d="2020-04-16 10:35:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Dinner Party: Frasier and Niles decide to throw a dinner party, but can't agree on who they should invite</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 10:35:00" d="2020-04-16 11:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>The first host in and around Leeds, choir teacher Dionne, serves up a menu that combines European and Caribbean influences, with a carnival flourish thrown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 11:00:00" d="2020-04-16 11:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>On the second night in Leeds, finance director Jane serves up a fine dining menu of homemade ravioli, pork and panna cotta. But Denver is upset about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 11:30:00" d="2020-04-16 12:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>On day three in Leeds, drama teacher and DJ Denver serves a Spanish menu, with a prosecco van and stilt walkers to get the Ibiza feel. But Darren finds</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 12:00:00" d="2020-04-16 12:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>On day four in Leeds, local legend Billy serves up tried-and-tested dinner party favourites. The best is yet to come at the end of the night, with a Frank</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 12:30:00" d="2020-04-16 13:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>On the final night in Leeds, Darren plans to put a fancy twist on an apparently basic menu. But Billy is concerned about the amount of mustard Darren is using. (Ep5/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 13:00:00" d="2020-04-16 14:05:00"><n>The Steph Show</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Live: The Steph Show
Steph McGovern presents the brand-new daily programme live from her living room, featuring special guests and the latest information</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 14:05:00" d="2020-04-16 15:10:00"><n>Posh Pawnbrokers</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Charlie and Patrick face one of their biggest deals with ?600,000 worth of rare Lalique glass car mascots. Plus: a pair of running spikes signed by Usain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 15:10:00" d="2020-04-16 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Tom Kerridge joins Susie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 16:00:00" d="2020-04-16 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun 2018 &amp; 2019</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun: Home or Away
Rod and Margaret are selling up in London and want to buy a house in Dorset, near the seaside town of Weymouth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 17:00:00" d="2020-04-16 18:00:00"><n u="Escape to the Chateau: DIY">Escape to the Chateau: DIY IV</n><e>F</e>    <k>Wendy and Marcus prepare to host their first official booking. Amy and Marc turn their grounds into an escapist retreat. Ben and Billie start building</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 18:00:00" d="2020-04-16 18:30:00"><n>Four in a Bed</n><e>F</e>    <k>The final visit of the week is to In the Stix Glamping in Greetham, Rutland, but with one guest refusing to give it a go before even setting foot on site</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 18:30:00" d="2020-04-16 19:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Dave hosts on the fourth night in Manchester, with a leopard-print dress code and a song that he wrote for his wife. But tension soon resurfaces</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 19:00:00" d="2020-04-16 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Homer and Lisa Exchange Cross Words: Lisa enters a tournament after discovering that she has a knack for doing crosswords. But Homer thinks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 19:30:00" d="2020-04-16 20:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Mypods and Broomsticks: The family go to the mall to buy Lisa a Mypod, but Bart causes chaos when he interrupts tycoon Steve Mobbs' announcement</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 20:00:00" d="2020-04-16 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 21:00:00" d="2020-04-16 22:00:00"><n>New: Grayson's Art Club</n>    <k>Grayson Perry, one of Britain's leading artists, brings the nation together through art, making new works and hosting masterclasses set to unleash</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 22:00:00" d="2020-04-16 23:00:00"><n>Dispatches</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: The Truth About Traveller. 
. rime - Dispatches: Theft, vandalism, violence - some of the crimes linked to several Traveller communities in England</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-16 23:00:00" d="2020-04-17 00:05:00"><n u="999: What's Your Emergency?">999: What's Your Emergency? IX</n><e>RF</e>    <k>With a police officer assaulted every 20 minutes in England and Wales, this episode focuses on the growing lack of respect that officers face on the streets. Ep3)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 00:05:00" d="2020-04-17 01:10:00"><n>The Interrogation of Tony Martin</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Steve Pemberton, Daniel Mays and Stuart Graham star in this factual drama about the police interrogation of Tony Martin, the Norfolk farmer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 01:10:00" d="2020-04-17 01:55:00"><n u="Wife Swap USA">Wife Swap USA I</n><e>TF</e>    <k>A germophobe wife who attempts to run her house like a corporation swaps lives with the mother of a messy, cat-filled household in the US spouse-switch series. Ep7)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 01:55:00" d="2020-04-17 02:45:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>At Amy's Baking Company in Scottsdale, Arizona, Gordon Ramsay meets a husband and wife team with a shocking contempt for customer feedback</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 02:45:00" d="2020-04-17 03:10:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Treehouse of Horror XIX: In a Halloween special, Homer tries to vote for Barack Obama but the machine is rigged to place votes for John McCain</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 03:10:00" d="2020-04-17 03:40:00"><n>Feel Good</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Comedy about love and addiction. The arrival of George's male teenage crush exposes Mae's biggest insecurities. Can their relationship survive? (Ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 03:40:00" d="2020-04-17 04:35:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Essex and east London, Spencer and Sara kick off the competition with a simple Jewish feast. But will reserved Lauren and Jack be put off by Spencer's loud personality?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-04-17 04:35:00" d="2020-04-17 05:30:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer take on an epic challenge house-hunting in trendy east London, where homes can sell in days, often at open viewings</k>  </p>
</a>
