<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="37" t="2020-05-13 04:35:34"><p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 05:25:00" d="2020-05-20 06:15:00"><n u="Car S.O.S">Car S.O.S III (8)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Lancia Reborn: Tim Shaw and Fuzz Townshend restore a high-end car, a 1967 Lancia Flavia coupé, that has been rotting away for over 30 years in a garage in Rochdale</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 06:15:00" d="2020-05-20 06:40:00"><n>Beat the Chef</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>A home cook faces the dessert round and the challenge of making a tastier apple tart than chef Frederick Forster. Whose apples will be sweetest and whose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 06:40:00" d="2020-05-20 06:50:00"><n>Kirstie's Vintage Gems</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Paper-cutter extraordinaire Poppy Chancellor helps Kirstie Allsopp to create unique, personalised wedding invitations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 06:50:00" d="2020-05-20 07:30:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Margaret Mountford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 07:30:00" d="2020-05-20 07:50:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Thanksgiving Is Cancelled: When Mike is ill at Thanksgiving, Molly is secretly thrilled, because she won't have to cook, but then Vince invites his brother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 07:50:00" d="2020-05-20 08:15:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Mike Takes a Test: Molly encourages Mike to pursue a new job as a police detective, but the stress of studying for the qualifying examination takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 08:15:00" d="2020-05-20 08:40:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers VI (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Little Carla, Happy at Last (Part 2): Sam tries to act as peacemaker when Eddie cancels his wedding to Carla due to his mother's disapproval of the bride</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 08:40:00" d="2020-05-20 09:10:00"><n u="Cheers">Cheers VI (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Crane Mutiny: When Frasier and Lilith's relationship turns sour, the gang play a prank on Frasier and convince him that Rebecca's falling for him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 09:10:00" d="2020-05-20 09:35:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Jazz Records: When the children ruin Ray's dictionary, Frank tells them about the time that Ray wrecked his prized jazz record collection</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 09:35:00" d="2020-05-20 10:05:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Debra at the Lodge: When Debra accepts a position at Frank's lodge to help plan a recruitment party, Ray resents how much time she is spending away from home</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 10:05:00" d="2020-05-20 10:35:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Three Blind Dates: Frasier's family and friends set him up on dates with various women who they believe are guaranteed to sweep him off his feet</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 10:35:00" d="2020-05-20 11:00:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>War of the Words: Frasier's son wins a spelling bee, but there's trouble when the runner-up's parents find out that Frasier was mouthing the letters of the words</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 11:00:00" d="2020-05-20 11:30:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Deathtrap: Frasier and Niles make a return trip to their childhood home and reminisce about when they thought there had been a murder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 11:30:00" d="2020-05-20 12:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In and around Leeds. Digital account manager Alice hosts her first-ever dinner party, featuring gob-smacking revelations, cringe-worthy party tricks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 12:00:00" d="2020-05-20 12:30:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In and around Leeds. Company director Andy hopes to win the grand with fancy restaurant-inspired fare. But Alice and Danielle are more impressed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 12:30:00" d="2020-05-20 13:00:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In and around Leeds. Fun-loving student Danielle plans an indulgent, high-calorie menu - and dons her wedding dress to serve her pyramid of desserts. (Ep3/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 13:00:00" d="2020-05-20 13:05:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 13:05:00" d="2020-05-20 13:35:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In and around Leeds. Theatre technician Matt plays it safe with tried-and-tested family favourites. But despite Matt's juggling skills, Andy declares</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 13:35:00" d="2020-05-20 14:05:00"><n>Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In and around Leeds. Jeweller Lynne goes for gold on the final night, with a menu of her own creations and a sparkling karaoke performance. (Ep5/5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 14:05:00" d="2020-05-20 15:10:00"><n u="Sun, Sea and Selling Houses">Sun, Sea and Selling Houses II (18)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Diane and Tony from Nottingham are looking for a holiday home in Alicante, but while Diane likes modern properties, Tony wants a renovation project</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 15:10:00" d="2020-05-20 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Nick Hewer and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Margaret Mountford</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 16:00:00" d="2020-05-20 17:00:00"><n u="A Place in the Sun 2018 -">A Place in the Sun 2018 - 2020</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>A Place in the Sun
Jonathan and Stephen can't wait to buy a holiday home with spectacular sea views near glitzy Marbella, on Spain's sunshine coast</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 17:00:00" d="2020-05-20 18:00:00"><n>Work on the Wild Side</n><e>F</e>    <k>Vets and volunteers rescue and rehabilitate animals in South Africa. Emma has a poorly patient, and Anna hopes to help dehorn five white rhinos</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 18:00:00" d="2020-05-20 19:00:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Stockport, Ian and Lithuanian-born Loreta go back to their roots. 'Gemily' offer a taste of Morocco. Tim and Luan serve their favourite dishes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 19:00:00" d="2020-05-20 19:30:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Much Apu About Nothing: Homer helps Apu study for a naturalisation exam to prove that he's American enough to stay in the country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 19:30:00" d="2020-05-20 20:00:00"><n>The Simpsons</n><e>R</e>    <k>Homerpalooza: Homer goes on the road with alternative rock festival Hullabalooza in a sideshow where he has cannonballs fired at his belly. Guest stars</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 20:00:00" d="2020-05-20 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 21:00:00" d="2020-05-20 22:00:00"><n u="Location, Location, Location">Location, Location, Location XXXII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer help two couples with babies on the way to find new homes in a hurry in Surrey. Ep1)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 22:00:00" d="2020-05-20 23:00:00"><n>Old, Alone and Stuck at Home</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Old, Alone and Stuck at Home
As the UK prepares for lockdown to ease, the moving stories of the elderly and vulnerable who must bunker</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-20 23:00:00" d="2020-05-21 00:05:00"><n u="8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown">8 Out of 10 Cats Does Countdown XVII</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Jimmy Carr hosts as Sean Lock and Johnny Vegas take on guest captain Alan Carr and Lou Sanders. The Brett Domino Trio join Susie Dent in Dictionary Corner</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 00:05:00" d="2020-05-21 00:10:00"><n>Ramadan in Lockdown</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Ramadan in Lockdown
This year, Britain's 2.6 million Muslims will observe Ramadan - up to 30 days fasting from sunrise to sunset - in lockdown</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 00:10:00" d="2020-05-21 01:15:00"><n u="Celebrity SAS: Who Dares Wins">Celebrity SAS: Who Dares Wins II</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The remaining celebs face a punishing race across land and ocean before they plunge into an overnight pursuit by an elite hunter force across the Scottish Inner Hebrides. Ep5)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 01:15:00" d="2020-05-21 02:10:00"><n>Walking with Elephants</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>Levison Wood continues his epic journey following the migration of Botswana's elephants. After trekking to the edge of the Okavango Delta</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 02:10:00" d="2020-05-21 03:00:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>Gordon Ramsay travels to Austin, Texas, home to struggling Greek restaurant El Greco, where the owners have secretly recruited 'Chef Mike' the microwave</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 03:00:00" d="2020-05-21 03:55:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Competing to host the best party in Grimsby are straight-talking Mel and Patrick, seasoned ravers Vanessa and Steve and lovebirds Amber and Ryan, whose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 03:55:00" d="2020-05-21 04:50:00"><n>Location, Location, Location</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer help a pair of nervous first-time buyers in Leeds and a house-hunter who's looking for a new work/life balance in the Yorkshire Dales</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2020-05-21 04:50:00" d="2020-05-21 05:45:00"><n u="Grand Designs New Zealand">Grand Designs New Zealand III</n><e>RF</e>    <k>A remote home is built on Slipper Island, off the Coromandel Peninsula, but all the materials must travel by barge from the mainland past the dangerous Tairua sandbar. Ep3)</k>  </p>
</a>
