<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2021-07-12 04:58:17"><p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 05:35:00" d="2021-07-19 06:30:00"><n u="Location, Location, Location">Location, Location, Location XXX (2)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Reading, Kirstie and Phil help a dad and daughter trawl the trendy suburb of Caversham. And can teachers Richard and Jo find a family home before</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 06:30:00" d="2021-07-19 07:00:00"><n>Coach Trip: Road to Tenerife</n><t>S</t><e>TF</e>    <k>Coach Trip: Final Week: Road. 
. o Tenerife: After a heavy night on the town, Brendan takes the group for a gruelling beach boot camp, followed by mermaid school. (Ep39/40)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 07:00:00" d="2021-07-19 07:40:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Anne Robinson and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Grace Dent joins Susie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 07:40:00" d="2021-07-19 08:05:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly I</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Mike Goes to the Opera: When Mike becomes ill during a night out at the opera with Molly, his mother Peggy and Molly fall out over who can take better care of him. Ep12)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 08:05:00" d="2021-07-19 08:25:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly I</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Molly Makes Soup: When her mother's fiancé Vince tries to strike up a friendship with Mike by inviting him to a basketball game, Molly isn't pleased about</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 08:25:00" d="2021-07-19 08:50:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Gift: Ray buys his dad an expensive aquarium, just like the one in the Chinese restaurant, for his 65th birthday. At first Frank loves it, but then one fish dies</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 08:50:00" d="2021-07-19 09:15:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>High School: Ray accompanies Debra to a high school reunion, where he is unmasked as a former nerd. Worse still, Debra was one of the cool kids who used to tease him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 09:15:00" d="2021-07-19 09:40:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>The Letter: Debra decides to write a letter to Marie to tell her to stop interfering after ruining her Tupperware party, but a shocked Ray tries to intercept the note</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 09:40:00" d="2021-07-19 10:10:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Morning Becomes Entertainment: Frasier and Bebe fill in for a week on a morning TV chat show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 10:10:00" d="2021-07-19 10:40:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>To Thine Old Self Be True: Frasier tries to plan Donny's bachelor party and winds up handcuffed to a stripper, embarrassing himself in front of Regan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 10:40:00" d="2021-07-19 11:10:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (4)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The 2003 Approximation: Sheldon sulks when Penny and Leonard announce that they're moving in together. Howard and Raj form a band to play at the comic book shop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 11:10:00" d="2021-07-19 11:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Perspiration Implementation: The guys take fencing lessons from Barry Kripke. Stuart struggles to attract female customers to the comic book shop</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 11:35:00" d="2021-07-19 12:05:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory IX (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Helium Insufficiency: Sheldon and Leonard struggle to find the supplies they need for an experiment. Penny and Bernadette download a dating app for Amy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 12:05:00" d="2021-07-19 12:35:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons VIII (12)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>87% Mountain of Madness: An avalanche traps Homer and Mr Burns in a mountain cabin during a team-building exercise</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 12:35:00" d="2021-07-19 13:05:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons VIII (13)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>87% Simpsoncalifragilisticexpiala (Annoyed Grunt) cious: Supernanny Shary Bobbins comes to the rescue of Marge, who is so stressed that her hair has started to fall out</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 13:05:00" d="2021-07-19 13:10:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 13:10:00" d="2021-07-19 14:10:00"><n u="Posh Pawnbrokers">Posh Pawnbrokers III (14)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>At London Road Pawnbrokers in Sheffield, boss Dan tries to seal the deal on a unique caravan. At Gold Arts in Brighton, Doug Senior and Doug Junior</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 14:10:00" d="2021-07-19 15:10:00"><n u="A New Life in the Sun">A New Life in the Sun VI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>A family of brewers from Kent get more than they bargained for when they buy a French farmhouse. A former DJ from Skegness opens a bar in Portugal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 15:10:00" d="2021-07-19 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Anne Robinson and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Rachel Parris joins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 16:00:00" d="2021-07-19 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Scuba-diving couple Caitlin and Simon are hunting for a holiday home on the Greek island of Paros. With a ?140k budget and their hearts set on sea views</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 17:00:00" d="2021-07-19 18:00:00"><n>Mend It for Money</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>A dilapidated MGC sports car, a 1920s beer engine, and an unusual rotating bookcase are all ripe for restoration. Which restorers will be chosen to bring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 18:00:00" d="2021-07-19 19:00:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Bournemouth, confident Nikki and Steve deal with some boisterous guests. Experienced hosts Peter and Lyn serve up a surprise. And youngsters Nicki</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 19:00:00" d="2021-07-19 19:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXVIII (5)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>87% Trust But Clarify: Lisa and Bart investigate Krusty's new 'Krustaceans' candy. Homer wants a promotion at the nuclear plant and asks Marge to help him dress the part</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 19:30:00" d="2021-07-19 20:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>Wedding bells are chiming in Hollyoaks, but the bride-to-be has a devilish plan. Elsewhere, Warren is confronted, and Yazz and Tom struggle to get people</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 20:00:00" d="2021-07-19 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 21:00:00" d="2021-07-19 22:00:00"><n u="Devon and Cornwall">Devon and Cornwall I</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Fisherman Stephen reveals what life is like in the perfectly preserved coastal village of Clovelly. Handywoman Lynn completes last-minute preparations</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 22:00:00" d="2021-07-19 23:00:00"><n>New: Taken: Hunting the Sex...</n><e>F</e>    <k>. raffickers: The inside story of a secret police investigation into a human trafficking gang. Following an anonymous tip-off, the police resolve to bring</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-19 23:00:00" d="2021-07-20 00:05:00"><n>24 Hours in Police Custody</n><t>S</t>    <k>81% 24 Hours in Police Custody:. 
. urder in the Woods: The first episode in a two-part documentary goes behind the scenes of a police investigation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 00:05:00" d="2021-07-20 01:10:00"><n u="999: What's Your Emergency?">999: What's Your Emergency? XIII</n><t>S</t><e>TF</e>    <k>In South Yorkshire, a mother asks police to take her 15-year-old into custody as officers confront several painful cases of the fast-growing crime</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 01:10:00" d="2021-07-20 02:00:00"><n>Ramsay's Kitchen Nightmares USA</n><e>RT</e>    <k>In La Verne in southern California, Gordon Ramsay visits Italian bistro Charlie's, where the pasta's soggy, the lasagne's a liability and the chef can't</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 02:00:00" d="2021-07-20 02:50:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>On Merseyside, Sandra dishes out orders to her husband Graham, Joanne and Simon serve too much spice, and Helen and Adam plan a Michelin-star-inspired</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 02:50:00" d="2021-07-20 03:45:00"><n u="Bake Off: The Professionals">Bake Off: The Professionals IV (8)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>It's the quarter-final and the teams make Black Forest gateaux and mini roulades, before going back to the 70s as they create disco-inspired sugar</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 03:45:00" d="2021-07-20 04:35:00"><n u="Wife Swap USA">Wife Swap USA II</n><e>TF</e>    <k>A professional wrestler swaps lives with a devoted wife and mum whose disconnected husband prefers video games to family time. Ep9)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-20 04:35:00" d="2021-07-20 07:35:00"><n u="George Clarke's Amazing Spaces">George Clarke's Amazing Spaces V</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>George and Will's floating beach hut goes to sea. There's also a festival camper van made from an American school bus, and a family home in Germany built</k>  </p>
</a>
