<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="34" t="2021-07-09 07:02:09"><p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 05:30:00" d="2021-07-14 06:25:00"><n u="Location, Location, Location">Location, Location, Location XXIX (6)</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Edinburgh, Kirstie Allsopp and Phil Spencer help a couple who don't know what they want, and an American family with their hearts set</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 06:25:00" d="2021-07-14 06:50:00"><n>Coach Trip: Road to Tenerife</n><t>S</t><e>TF</e>    <k>Coach Trip: Final Week: Road. 
. o Tenerife: On Gran Canaria, Brendan takes the group sofa boating and for an afternoon class at clown school</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 06:50:00" d="2021-07-14 07:00:00"><n>Kirstie's Fill Your House for Free</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Kirstie Allsopp visits a stunning Georgian home in Brighton, and a house in Devon where the furniture was made for free</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 07:00:00" d="2021-07-14 07:40:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Anne Robinson and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Rory Bremner joins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 07:40:00" d="2021-07-14 08:05:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly I</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Mike's Apartment: When Mike invites Molly over to his apartment, his plans for romance are interrupted by an untimely call from his overbearing mother, Peggy. Ep6)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 08:05:00" d="2021-07-14 08:25:00"><n u="Mike &amp; Molly">Mike &amp; Molly I</n><e>RF</e>    <k>After the Lovin': After spending the weekend with Molly, Mike comes on too strong with his affections, so he takes Carl's advice to play it cool and tries</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 08:25:00" d="2021-07-14 08:50:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Boys' Therapy: The women pressure Ray and Frank to join Robert at one of his therapy sessions. Instead, they head to the racetrack</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 08:50:00" d="2021-07-14 09:15:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>Debra's Parents: Debra invites her divorced parents over for Thanksgiving. When Ray walks in on them making love, he and Debra mistakenly assume</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 09:15:00" d="2021-07-14 09:40:00"><n>Everybody Loves Raymond</n><e>R</e>    <k>A Job for Robert: Ray is jealous when Marie starts treating Robert better than him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 09:40:00" d="2021-07-14 10:10:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>They're Playing Our Song: Frasier goes all out when he's inspired to write a new theme tune for his radio show</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 10:10:00" d="2021-07-14 10:40:00"><n>Frasier</n><e>R</e>    <k>Big Crane on Campus: Frasier dates his old high school prom queen but discovers that beauty is only skin deep</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 10:40:00" d="2021-07-14 11:10:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Skywalker Incursion: When Leonard and Sheldon are invited to speak at Berkeley, they take a detour during the journey to try to meet one of their idols</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 11:10:00" d="2021-07-14 11:35:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (20)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Fortification Implementation: When Sheldon and Amy build a blanket fort, they come to a major crossroads in their relationship. Howard meets his half-brother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 11:35:00" d="2021-07-14 12:05:00"><n u="The Big Bang Theory">The Big Bang Theory VIII (21)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>The Communication Deterioration: Raj is asked to create a message for NASA to use if one of their missions finds alien life. Penny considers taking up acting again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 12:05:00" d="2021-07-14 12:35:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons VIII (6)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>87% A Milhouse Divided: When Milhouse's parents split up, his mum gets together with an American Gladiator called Pyro, his dad self-produces an album</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 12:35:00" d="2021-07-14 13:05:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons VIII (7)</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>87% Lisa's Date with Density: Lisa has a crush on Nelson the bully. But can she get him to change his ways?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 13:05:00" d="2021-07-14 13:10:00"><n>Channel 4 News Summary</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's midday news summary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 13:10:00" d="2021-07-14 14:10:00"><n u="Posh Pawnbrokers">Posh Pawnbrokers II (19)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>In Kent, Charlie and Patrick examine a Chinese vase that could be worth a small fortune. In Penzance, Larry and Neil deliver a shock when they value a very special violin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 14:10:00" d="2021-07-14 15:10:00"><n u="A New Life in the Sun">A New Life in the Sun VI</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>A couple launch a cycling business in Spain. In Portugal, a holiday village navigates murky waters. And a motorhome rental business in France handles</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 15:10:00" d="2021-07-14 16:00:00"><n>Countdown</n><e>F</e>    <k>Anne Robinson and Rachel Riley host as contestants race against the clock to pit their wits against vowels, consonants and numbers. Philippa Perry joins</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 16:00:00" d="2021-07-14 17:00:00"><n>A Place in the Sun</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>Alison and her daughter Paula are looking for a traditional holiday home in Spain. Jasmine Harman shows them five properties around Vélez-Málaga for their budget of ?60,000</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 17:00:00" d="2021-07-14 18:00:00"><n>Mend It for Money</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>A Santa-worthy sleigh, a wooden chest of surprises, and a double-barrelled shotgun are all ripe for restoration. Which restorers will be chosen to breathe</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 18:00:00" d="2021-07-14 19:00:00"><n>Couples Come Dine with Me</n><e>RTF</e>    <k>In Brighton, Hannah and Luke give their guests a sneak peek of their wedding breakfast. There are jaw-dropping revelations on Karen and Mark's night</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 19:00:00" d="2021-07-14 19:30:00"><n u="The Simpsons">The Simpsons XXVIII (3)</n><t>S</t><e>RF</e>    <k>87% The Town: After Homer catches Bart supporting Springfield's football rival, the Boston Americans, he plans a family 'hate-cation' trip to Boston</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 19:30:00" d="2021-07-14 20:00:00"><n>Hollyoaks</n><e>F</e>    <k>An unwelcome visitor causes Shaq to make a shocking confession. Captive Liberty is desperate to return home to her daughter. Martine finds it difficult</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 20:00:00" d="2021-07-14 21:00:00"><n>Channel 4 News</n><e>F</e>    <k>Channel 4's flagship news programme. Including the weather</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 21:00:00" d="2021-07-14 22:00:00"><n>Kirstie and Phil's Love It or List It</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: Kirstie and Phil's Love It. 
. r List It: Brilliant Builds - Kirstie and Phil look back on putting family front and centre, from a town house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 22:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:00:00"><n>Grand Designs</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>85% New: Grand Designs
Kevin McCloud revisits Adrian and Megan, whose dream home in East Sussex became a nightmare. With the house now fully complete</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 23:00:00" d="2021-07-14 23:30:00"><n u="This Way Up">This Way Up II (1)</n><t>S</t><e>F</e>    <k>New: This Way Up
Aisling Bea's pin-sharp, poignant comedy-drama returns. Aine has a date with Etienne's dad, Richard. Shona struggles to settle</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-14 23:30:00" d="2021-07-15 00:30:00"><n u="Celebrity Gogglebox">Celebrity Gogglebox III</n><t>S</t><e>R</e>    <k>Celebs including Ed Sheeran, KSI and Roman Kemp have been watching Love Island, America's Got Talent, Sex/Life, Clarkson's Farm, BBC News (England</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 00:30:00" d="2021-07-15 01:30:00"><n>Cruises, Trains, Holidays &amp; Flights from Hell</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Trains from Hell: Caught on Camera
From shocking near-misses and derailments to rush-hour rage and unique on-board entertainment, and from the funny</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 01:30:00" d="2021-07-15 02:25:00"><n>Murder in the Outback</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Murder in the Outback: The. 
. alconio and Lees Mystery: Bradley Murdoch was found guilty of killing British backpacker Peter Falconio. But other suspects</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 02:25:00" d="2021-07-15 03:20:00"><n>Kathy Burke: Money Talks</n><t>S</t><e>RTF</e>    <k>Are governments doing enough to tackle poverty? Kathy meets a man trying to build a community in one of Britain's most deprived towns and the founder</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="852" o="2021-07-15 03:20:00" d="2021-07-15 05:15:00"><n>Men, Women &amp; Children</n><e>RF</e>    <k>Drama. A group of parents and school pupils try to navigate the pitfalls of modern technology, with varying degrees of success. Frank sexual</k>  </p>
</a>
