<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2021-07-08 04:59:42"><p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-13 06:00:00" d="2021-07-13 07:30:00"><n>The Secret of the Bear</n>    <k>When a wild bear threatens their community, a man and his son venture into the mountains to hunt him down</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-13 07:30:00" d="2021-07-13 09:05:00" c="1"><n>Pressure Point</n><t>F</t>    <k>55% When his gambling debt is claimed by a match-fixing syndicate, Jermaine Slagter must do everything to keep his life from falling apart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-13 09:05:00" d="2021-07-13 10:25:00"><n u="An Innocent Man">An Innocent Man (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Based on true events. In 1899, a little girl is brutally murdered in a local village. In a climate of growing antisemitism, a young Jewish man named</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-13 10:25:00" d="2021-07-13 11:45:00"><n u="An Innocent Man">An Innocent Man (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A trial begins against Hilsner. This will become the most famous case in the history of the country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-13 11:45:00" d="2021-07-13 13:25:00" c="1"><n>The Time of Secrets</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% The last vacations for Marcel Pagnol (Pierre-François Martin-Laval) in his favorite Provence hills prove as delightful as challenging. It is the beginning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-13 13:25:00" d="2021-07-13 15:05:00"><n>The Time of Love</n>    <k>Overcoming disciplinary committee, Marcel (Pierre-François Martin-Laval) gets to stay at high school. He becomes a leader among his new classmates, firming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-13 15:05:00" d="2021-07-13 16:15:00"><n u="Fallen Empire">Fallen Empire (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Tired of how their country was run, two men decide to take refuge in Russia and build an exiled government. Soon they discover the price of their actions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-13 16:15:00" d="2021-07-13 17:40:00"><n u="Fallen Empire">Fallen Empire (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Patriotism is a willingness to sacrifice for your country. Two men did it and were sentenced to death for betraying the monarchy. They still managed to find independence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-13 17:40:00" d="2021-07-13 18:30:00"><n u="Shattered Destinies – Episode">Shattered Destinies – Episode 1</n>    <k>Vika dreams of becoming a successful fashion designer. Her parents run a small tailor shop and a spot at a market. When Vika’s father dies, his debts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-13 18:30:00" d="2021-07-13 19:20:00"><n u="Shattered Destinies – Episode">Shattered Destinies – Episode 2</n>    <k>Vika has support from only one person — Kostya, who starts helping Vika to understand the principles of trading at the market. Vika has other plans</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-13 19:20:00" d="2021-07-13 20:10:00"><n>Strike Force Season 1 Episode 9: Dirty money</n>    <k>To free Tessa (Lindsay Zwaan), Theo (Jeroen van Koningsbrugge) and Willem (Dennis van de Ven) need money from a drug dealer. In order to catch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-13 20:10:00" d="2021-07-13 21:00:00"><n>Strike Force Season 1 Episode 10: The price of freedom</n>    <k>Willem (Dennis van de Ven) is prepared to offer negotiator Freddy van Nuenen (Patrick Stoof) 35 million Euros in drug money to finally freed Tessa (Lindsay Zwaan)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-13 21:00:00" d="2021-07-13 22:30:00"><n u="Full Disclosure Episode">Full Disclosure Episode 3 I</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Elena (Antonia Liskova) is increasingly tormented by the memory of her old captor, Virgilio Sanna (Mirko Urania), while Pietro (Massimo Poggio) continues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-13 22:30:00" d="2021-07-14 00:05:00"><n u="Full Disclosure Episode">Full Disclosure Episode 4 I</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Elena (Antonia Liskova) wants the truth from Pietro (Massimo Poggio) about his role in her kidnapping and confronts him at gunpoint. His confession</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-14 00:05:00" d="2021-07-14 01:30:00"><n u="Dark Forest – Episode">Dark Forest – Episode 1</n>    <k>After twenty years, Nina Ferrari (Giulia Michelini) returns to the small provincial town where she was born. She has won a chair to teach psychology</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-14 01:30:00" d="2021-07-14 03:00:00"><n u="Dark Forest – Episode">Dark Forest – Episode 2</n>    <k>Nina (Giulia Michelini) is attacked by the mysterious hooded figure. To save herself, she dives into the river which runs through the woods</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-14 03:00:00" d="2021-07-14 04:30:00"><n u="Dark Forest – Episode">Dark Forest – Episode 3</n>    <k>Nina (Giulia Michelini) is alone and standing before the murderer in the woods. The hooded figure scrutinizes her for a while, then moves away, leaving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-14 04:30:00" d="2021-07-14 06:00:00"><n u="Dark Forest – Episode">Dark Forest – Episode 4</n>    <k>Nina's father is dead and she doesn't know what to think anymore: did her father really kill her mother? And why? Who murdered him?</k>  </p>
</a>
