<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="14" t="2019-08-09 01:36:04"><p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-15 06:00:00" d="2019-08-15 08:00:00"><n>From Rome with Love</n>    <k>Maya (Lola Ponche) is a beautiful young Argentine woman who leaves Buenos Aires and moves to Roma to take part in a talent show and thus realise her dream</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-15 08:00:00" d="2019-08-15 09:45:00"><n>Silent Fear</n>    <k>Sabine (Thekla Reuten) is looking for the truth behind the disappearance of her best friend twenty years ago. An encounter with the handsome Olaf (Daan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-15 09:45:00" d="2019-08-15 11:25:00"><n>Enticement</n>    <k>Jonathan Marescot has an obsession for stealing little objects. He loves not only possessing them, but also the thrill he gets from robbing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-15 11:25:00" d="2019-08-15 13:10:00"><n>The Perfect Stranger</n>    <k>Jonathan (Bruno Debrandt), an unhappy man who has just inherited a massive fortune, discovers that Anaďs (Audrey Fleurot), his wife, has been hospitalized</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-15 13:10:00" d="2019-08-15 15:00:00"><n u="Deadly Game Part">Deadly Game Part 1</n>    <k>Olivia (Michelle Bonev), a dedicated police officer, decides to help Natasha (Nadia Konakchieva), an Eastern European woman who has sacrificed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-15 15:00:00" d="2019-08-15 16:50:00"><n u="Deadly Game Part">Deadly Game Part 2</n>    <k>Olivia (Michelle Bonev), a dedicated police officer, decides to help Natasha (Nadia Konakchieva), an Eastern European woman who has sacrificed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-15 16:50:00" d="2019-08-15 18:30:00" c="1"><n>Deception</n><t>F</t>    <k>Paul Berthier, a public prosecutor, witnesses the accidental drowning of a young girl but does nothing to help. A decision that will change</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-15 18:30:00" d="2019-08-15 20:15:00"><n>The Evil Hands</n>    <k>Roxana (Sylvie Testud), a prominent violinist, has both hands crushed during an accident. After she undergoes a transplant by a prominent surgeon, whose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-15 20:15:00" d="2019-08-15 22:00:00"><n>Gone</n>    <k>When Caroline (Margot Faure), has a little affair and breaks a promise, the life of her husband changes forever. She disappears after a violent dispute</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-15 22:00:00" d="2019-08-15 23:45:00" c="1"><n>Wings of Steel</n><t>F</t>    <k>A former RAF captain (David Svehlík) returns home to his family in 1945 hoping for a happy life after surviving the horrors of war piloting combat aircrafts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-15 23:45:00" d="2019-08-16 01:25:00"><n>Mafia Millionaires</n>    <k>The rise and fall of a Camorra clan in Naples, told through the eyes of a crime boss and his family. Forty years of a man's life, forty years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-16 01:25:00" d="2019-08-16 03:10:00" c="1"><n>Wings of Steel</n><t>F</t>    <k>A former RAF captain (David Svehlík) returns home to his family in 1945 hoping for a happy life after surviving the horrors of war piloting combat aircrafts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-16 03:10:00" d="2019-08-16 04:35:00" c="1"><n>Perversion</n><t>F</t>    <k>Investigating the death of a young woman, a police inspector finds himself exploring the torrid and mysterious side of Roma’s night life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-16 04:35:00" d="2019-08-16 06:00:00"><n>The President's Mistress</n>    <k>Forbidden love affairs have their risks, especially in closed and conservative societies. Eurochannel welcomes you to the final years of the nineteenth</k>  </p>
</a>
