<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2020-04-09 04:31:33"><p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-16 06:00:00" d="2020-04-16 07:35:00"><n>Blood Brothers</n>    <k>Brice (Sylvain Dieuaide), the eldest son of the Lemeuniers, is accused of a quadruple murder. His brother Martin (Clément Chebli) will do whatever it takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-16 07:35:00" d="2020-04-16 09:10:00"><n>Forbidden Lust</n>    <k>Two young men work for The Master, a loan shark and illegal antiques dealer. They take care of the dirty work but both make the fatal mistake of falling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-16 09:10:00" d="2020-04-16 11:15:00"><n>The Counterfeiters</n>    <k>1920s Paris. When teenager Bernard (Jules-Angelo Bigarnet) discovers that the man who raised him is in fact not his father, he leaves the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-16 11:15:00" d="2020-04-16 12:00:00"><n u="Almirante Hotel">Almirante Hotel (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A corpse is found in a hotel room and all evidence points to a suicide. As the police investigate, they find a letter revealing clues about the tragedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-16 12:00:00" d="2020-04-16 12:45:00"><n u="Almirante Hotel">Almirante Hotel (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The main suspect is interviewed by the police but he denies having a close relationship with the deceased. He is trapped in a dark game of power and revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-16 12:45:00" d="2020-04-16 13:30:00"><n u="Almirante Hotel">Almirante Hotel (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The investigation reveals that the deceased was not as innocent as it appeared and her death is part of a bigger plan of resentment and payback</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-16 13:30:00" d="2020-04-16 14:15:00"><n u="Almirante Hotel">Almirante Hotel (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The story of Rosalía Leal and Javier Aldao comes to an end, revealing Aldao's hidden interest with Rosalía. His obscure intentions will cause</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-16 14:15:00" d="2020-04-16 15:45:00" c="1"><n>The Marvels of Rome</n><t>F</t>    <k>Rome, 1947. The war is over but in the eternal city is still open and obvious wounds of the conflict. In the maternity ward of a hospital, nine women wait to give birth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-16 15:45:00" d="2020-04-16 17:25:00"><n>The Skin of Sorrow</n>    <k>It's 1832, and 22-year-old Raphaël's (Thomas Coumans) gambling has driven him to the brink of suicide. He is about to throw himself in the Seine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-16 17:25:00" d="2020-04-16 18:40:00" c="1"><n u="Fallout Part">Fallout Part 1</n><t>F</t>    <k>An unfortunate gunshot intertwines the fates of seven people and changes their fate forever. Viktor shoots Jendric while defending his daughter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-16 18:40:00" d="2020-04-16 20:00:00" c="1"><n u="Fallout Part">Fallout Part 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>While helping to reconstruct Jendric’s family, Viktor also attempts to get closer to his daughter and former wife. This is his only opportunity for redemption</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-16 20:00:00" d="2020-04-16 21:35:00" c="1"><n>The Marvels of Rome</n><t>F</t>    <k>Rome, 1947. The war is over but in the eternal city is still open and obvious wounds of the conflict. In the maternity ward of a hospital, nine women wait to give birth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-16 21:35:00" d="2020-04-16 23:05:00"><n>Paris Undercover</n>    <k>The fate of two intriguing and deadly figures intertwine when a young petty tough is ordered to kill Mr Zhu, a senior man who has just arrived from China</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-16 23:05:00" d="2020-04-17 00:55:00"><n>Frozen Valley</n>    <k>A former human trafficker finds the murdered body of his nephew in a remote valley. As soon as the police start to investigate the murder case, he becomes the prime suspect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-17 00:55:00" d="2020-04-17 02:30:00"><n>True Intentions</n>    <k>Jana and Marika meet on a train and quickly become friends. They go to the countryside, a remote mountain area that holds a lot of secrets about Jana's past</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-17 02:30:00" d="2020-04-17 03:55:00" c="1"><n>Perversion</n><t>F</t>    <k>Investigating the death of a young woman, a police inspector finds himself exploring the torrid and mysterious side of Roma’s night life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-17 03:55:00" d="2020-04-17 04:55:00"><n u="Legacy">Legacy (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Strahinja suicides in his prison cell. Aleksandar finds call logs between Dejan and Nikola Kovacevic, Peca's father and minister in the Parliament</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-17 04:55:00" d="2020-04-17 06:00:00"><n u="Legacy">Legacy (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mirko and Aleksandar agree to arrest Dejan. Aleksandar reveals the connection between the police chief Obradovic, Jovan's wife, and Nikola Kovacevic</k>  </p>
</a>
