<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="15" t="2019-07-11 00:20:34"><p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-17 06:00:00" d="2019-07-17 07:50:00"><n>Silent Fear</n>    <k>Sabine (Thekla Reuten) is looking for the truth behind the disappearance of her best friend twenty years ago. An encounter with the handsome Olaf (Daan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-17 07:50:00" d="2019-07-17 10:05:00"><n>Broken Promise</n>    <k>Based on a true story of a Jewish boy in Western Slovakia who escaped deportation to a concentration camp thanks to his extraordinary soccer talent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-17 10:05:00" d="2019-07-17 11:45:00"><n>Beyond Suspicion</n>    <k>Valérie (Cristiana Réali) is an active and exemplary woman. Psychiatrist by profession, a mother, a wife and an irreproachable parishioner. Still, Valerie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-17 11:45:00" d="2019-07-17 13:30:00"><n>Dreams of Glory</n>    <k>Marko (Benjamin Krnetic) and his friends live in an ill-famed suburb. One mischievous night, they have a life-changing encounter with the police</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-17 13:30:00" d="2019-07-17 15:00:00"><n u="The Secret of Borgo Larici">The Secret of Borgo Larici (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Anita (Serena Iansiti) decides that it's time to go back to town and enjoy her romance with Francesco (Giulio Berruti), but Claudia (Nathalie Rapti Gómez)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-17 15:00:00" d="2019-07-17 16:30:00"><n u="The Secret of Borgo Larici">The Secret of Borgo Larici (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Francesco (Giulio Berruti) believes Fausto Ferraris (Nicola Pistoia) is involved in the mystery about his mother. Don Costante (Massimo Wertmuller)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-17 16:30:00" d="2019-07-17 18:20:00"><n u="The Salento Murders Part">The Salento Murders Part 1</n>    <k>A malevolent clan, probably from Calabria, has arrived in Salento to conquer the territory. Commissioner Pasquale Zagaria (Lino Banfi) is a policeman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-17 18:20:00" d="2019-07-17 20:15:00"><n u="The Salento Murders Part">The Salento Murders Part 2</n>    <k>A malevolent clan, probably from Calabria, has arrived in Salento to conquer the territory. Commissioner Pasquale Zagaria (Lino Banfi) is a policeman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-17 20:15:00" d="2019-07-17 21:05:00"><n u="Strike Force Season 4 : Live">Strike Force Season 4 : Live (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A very anxious man enters the studio of TV Brabant and demands a conversation with Theo (Jeroen van Koningsbrugge). When he arrives in the studio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-17 21:05:00" d="2019-07-17 22:00:00"><n u="Strike Force Season 4 : Trapped">Strike Force Season 4 : Trapped (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Willem (Dennis van de Ven) and Theo (Jeroen van Koningsbrugge) have to rescue politician from the hands of the serial killer. The politician who always</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-17 22:00:00" d="2019-07-17 23:40:00"><n>Gone</n>    <k>When Caroline (Margot Faure), has a little affair and breaks a promise, the life of her husband changes forever. She disappears after a violent dispute</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-17 23:40:00" d="2019-07-18 01:25:00"><n u="Only you">Only you (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Florist Carlo Gambardella (Giampaolo Morelli) and biologist Valentina Trevisol (Gaia Bermani Amaral) meet one day by chance and their lives change forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-18 01:25:00" d="2019-07-18 03:10:00"><n u="Only you">Only you (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Carlo (Giampaolo Morelli) tries to contact Valentina (Gaia Bermani Amaral) again but she, scared off by the discovery that he has five children</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-18 03:10:00" d="2019-07-18 04:50:00" c="1"><n>Deception</n><t>F</t>    <k>Paul Berthier, a public prosecutor, witnesses the accidental drowning of a young girl but does nothing to help. A decision that will change</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-18 04:50:00" d="2019-07-18 06:00:00" c="1"><n>Dancing Quietly</n><t>F</t>    <k>60% After many dark years of depression, Luca (Martina Schöne-Radunski) seeks to earn her high school diploma. Her little dog Mata helps her to find motivation</k>  </p>
</a>
