<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="17" t="2020-05-28 04:36:28"><p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-04 06:00:00" d="2020-06-04 07:40:00" c="1"><n>The Legend of Rita</n><t>F</t>    <k>69% The riveting true story of Rita Vogt (Bibiana Beglau), a 1970s West German terrorist who escapes to the East with the help of the Stasi</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-04 07:40:00" d="2020-06-04 09:25:00"><n>Silent Fear</n>    <k>Sabine (Thekla Reuten) is looking for the truth behind the disappearance of her best friend twenty years ago. An encounter with the handsome Olaf (Daan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-04 09:25:00" d="2020-06-04 11:00:00"><n>Enticement</n>    <k>Jonathan Marescot has an obsession for stealing little objects. He loves not only possessing them, but also the thrill he gets from robbing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-04 11:00:00" d="2020-06-04 12:50:00"><n>Frozen Valley</n>    <k>A former human trafficker finds the murdered body of his nephew in a remote valley. As soon as the police start to investigate the murder case, he becomes the prime suspect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-04 12:50:00" d="2020-06-04 14:20:00" c="1"><n>Suspicion</n><t>F</t>    <k>A lonely, trusting old woman fears that no-one needs her anymore. She suddenly meets a young man that claims to be a distant relative</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-04 14:20:00" d="2020-06-04 15:10:00"><n u="Lifeline">Lifeline (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Anton asks Oksana not to linger at the hospital - he plans to celebrate their anniversary but last minute problems at work do not allow her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-04 15:10:00" d="2020-06-04 16:00:00"><n u="Lifeline">Lifeline (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Oksana refuses to go to Anton's parents, who want to bless them for their upcoming marriage. Maxim looks for his daughter after she escapes from her grandparents' house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-04 16:00:00" d="2020-06-04 17:40:00"><n>Fallen from the sky</n>    <k>January 1943. France is under occupation. Louise is 70, and in her bar, everyone likes to forget about the war. Her serenity is disturbed, however</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-04 17:40:00" d="2020-06-04 19:20:00"><n>Enticement</n>    <k>Jonathan Marescot has an obsession for stealing little objects. He loves not only possessing them, but also the thrill he gets from robbing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-04 19:20:00" d="2020-06-04 20:10:00"><n u="Lifeline">Lifeline (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Anton asks Oksana not to linger at the hospital - he plans to celebrate their anniversary but last minute problems at work do not allow her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-04 20:10:00" d="2020-06-04 21:00:00"><n u="Lifeline">Lifeline (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Oksana refuses to go to Anton's parents, who want to bless them for their upcoming marriage. Maxim looks for his daughter after she escapes from her grandparents' house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-04 21:00:00" d="2020-06-04 22:40:00"><n>The Perfect Stranger</n>    <k>Jonathan (Bruno Debrandt), an unhappy man who has just inherited a massive fortune, discovers that Anaďs (Audrey Fleurot), his wife, has been hospitalized</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-04 22:40:00" d="2020-06-05 00:15:00"><n>Better Days</n>    <k>It’s New Year’s Eve and Gary (Cody Brotter) desperately tries to spark the interest of his ex-girlfriend, without letting his friends embarrass him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-05 00:15:00" d="2020-06-05 01:55:00"><n>Manon Lescaut</n>    <k>There is nothing we can do against the call of love. Even when a professional future might look brighter than the sun, sometimes the heart beats drive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-05 01:55:00" d="2020-06-05 03:15:00"><n u="Absolution">Absolution (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A shocked, twenty-year-old Lily, runs to her father's door to tell him that she killed her lover in self-defense. Her father, a police investigator</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-05 03:15:00" d="2020-06-05 04:35:00"><n u="Absolution">Absolution (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Richard knows his daughter is hiding something. An investigative journalist comes across evidence linking the murdered man with a shady firm</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-05 04:35:00" d="2020-06-05 06:00:00"><n u="Absolution">Absolution (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>An autopsy confirms to Richard that the victim was under the influence of sleeping drugs at the time of the killing, changing the direction</k>  </p>
</a>
