<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="20" t="2020-04-11 04:31:36"><p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-18 06:00:00" d="2020-04-18 07:25:00" c="1"><n>Babylon Sisters</n><t>F</t>    <k>The residents of a rundown building receive an eviction notice from their landlord. Led by little Kamla and professor Leone, this striving immigrant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-18 07:25:00" d="2020-04-18 08:50:00"><n>Double Trouble</n>    <k>Marek lives alternately with two women. He tells them both that he works in another city for part of the week. In reality, he stays in the same and moves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-18 08:50:00" d="2020-04-18 10:30:00"><n>Fallen from the sky</n>    <k>January 1943. France is under occupation. Louise is 70, and in her bar, everyone likes to forget about the war. Her serenity is disturbed, however</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-18 10:30:00" d="2020-04-18 12:05:00"><n>Blood Brothers</n>    <k>Brice (Sylvain Dieuaide), the eldest son of the Lemeuniers, is accused of a quadruple murder. His brother Martin (Clément Chebli) will do whatever it takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-18 12:05:00" d="2020-04-18 13:35:00"><n>Better Days</n>    <k>It’s New Year’s Eve and Gary (Cody Brotter) desperately tries to spark the interest of his ex-girlfriend, without letting his friends embarrass him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-18 13:35:00" d="2020-04-18 15:10:00"><n>Blind Fear</n>    <k>After a tragic car crash and losing the baby she was expecting, Betty seeks solace in a new job looking after a blind kid in a mountain house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-18 15:10:00" d="2020-04-18 16:35:00" c="1"><n>Babylon Sisters</n><t>F</t>    <k>The residents of a rundown building receive an eviction notice from their landlord. Led by little Kamla and professor Leone, this striving immigrant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-18 16:35:00" d="2020-04-18 18:05:00" c="1"><n>The Marvels of Rome</n><t>F</t>    <k>Rome, 1947. The war is over but in the eternal city is still open and obvious wounds of the conflict. In the maternity ward of a hospital, nine women wait to give birth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-18 18:05:00" d="2020-04-18 19:15:00"><n u="Red Line">Red Line (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Murderers are trying to sweep traces of the weapons stolen from Soviet military trains. It's a game of time as both sides try to put together a picture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-18 19:15:00" d="2020-04-18 20:25:00"><n u="Red Line">Red Line (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>It is New Year's Eve of 1992 - the last day of Czechoslovakia. In one room is a dead body, in the other is Rédl on the brink of death</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-18 20:25:00" d="2020-04-18 21:10:00"><n u="Almirante Hotel">Almirante Hotel (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A corpse is found in a hotel room and all evidence points to a suicide. As the police investigate, they find a letter revealing clues about the tragedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-18 21:10:00" d="2020-04-18 21:55:00"><n u="Almirante Hotel">Almirante Hotel (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The main suspect is interviewed by the police but he denies having a close relationship with the deceased. He is trapped in a dark game of power and revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-18 21:55:00" d="2020-04-18 22:40:00"><n u="Almirante Hotel">Almirante Hotel (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The investigation reveals that the deceased was not as innocent as it appeared and her death is part of a bigger plan of resentment and payback</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-18 22:40:00" d="2020-04-18 23:25:00"><n u="Almirante Hotel">Almirante Hotel (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The story of Rosalía Leal and Javier Aldao comes to an end, revealing Aldao's hidden interest with Rosalía. His obscure intentions will cause</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-18 23:25:00" d="2020-04-19 00:15:00"><n>The Hold-Up - E1</n>    <k>An ordinary morning, a bank robbery intertwines the lives of the branch director, a star restauranteur, a pregnant young cop, an old policeman and other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-19 00:15:00" d="2020-04-19 01:05:00"><n>The Hold-Up - E2</n>    <k>While Agnes (Blandine Bellavoir), a young cop, brings supplies to the hostages, Mino (Yaniss Lespert), one of the four robbers, is ill. He needs insulin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-19 01:05:00" d="2020-04-19 01:55:00"><n>The Hold-Up - E3</n>    <k>Alex (Arnaud Ducret) enters the vault containing a loot of eight million euros. The hostages are still tied to each other and their eyes are bandaged</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-19 01:55:00" d="2020-04-19 03:20:00"><n u="The Mine Inferno">The Mine Inferno (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Petr (Oskar Hes) drops out of the Mine Engineering College in Prague and moves back to the family home with a pregnant Jewish girlfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-19 03:20:00" d="2020-04-19 04:35:00"><n u="The Mine Inferno">The Mine Inferno (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Marie (Martha Issová) is falling apart. A collapsed Milan (Marek Taclík) shifts to a less paid job, while Jana (Antonie Formanová) betrays Marie’s darkest secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-19 04:35:00" d="2020-04-19 06:00:00" c="1"><n>Babylon Sisters</n><t>F</t>    <k>The residents of a rundown building receive an eviction notice from their landlord. Led by little Kamla and professor Leone, this striving immigrant</k>  </p>
</a>
