<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="16" t="2019-07-11 00:20:34"><p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-16 06:00:00" d="2019-07-16 07:40:00"><n>Mafia Millionaires</n>    <k>The rise and fall of a Camorra clan in Naples, told through the eyes of a crime boss and his family. Forty years of a man's life, forty years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-16 07:40:00" d="2019-07-16 09:20:00"><n>Chase</n>    <k>Luis (Nicolas Cazalé) is a somewhat clumsy money transporter. Against all odds, he steals his own van with five million euros. For Emma (Isabelle Carré)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-16 09:20:00" d="2019-07-16 10:50:00"><n>A Sicilian Dream</n>    <k>A poignant drama following the development of a young Sicilian boy, Ettore Corvaja (Corrado Fortuna), from the 1950s to 1960s. Yearning to become</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-16 10:50:00" d="2019-07-16 11:50:00" c="1"><n u="Haunted Part">Haunted Part 1</n><t>F</t>    <k>With the arrival of her last boarders, just before the winter closure of the cottage, Laura's (Marie Gillain) fragile balance is upset</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-16 11:50:00" d="2019-07-16 12:55:00" c="1"><n u="Haunted Part">Haunted Part 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>Laura (Marie Gillain) is now sure that Olivier (Andrei Aradits) is tracking her, since he has escaped from prison. She decides to resort to</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-16 12:55:00" d="2019-07-16 14:25:00"><n>Manhunt</n>    <k>After being wrongfully accused of a fatal hit-and-run, Michael Bellicher (Daan Schuurmans) finds himself hunted by cops and criminals alike as he attempts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-16 14:25:00" d="2019-07-16 16:05:00"><n>The Perfect Stranger</n>    <k>Jonathan (Bruno Debrandt), an unhappy man who has just inherited a massive fortune, discovers that Anaďs (Audrey Fleurot), his wife, has been hospitalized</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-16 16:05:00" d="2019-07-16 17:35:00"><n>The President's Mistress</n>    <k>Forbidden love affairs have their risks, especially in closed and conservative societies. Eurochannel welcomes you to the final years of the nineteenth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-16 17:35:00" d="2019-07-16 19:15:00" c="1"><n>Deception</n><t>F</t>    <k>Paul Berthier, a public prosecutor, witnesses the accidental drowning of a young girl but does nothing to help. A decision that will change</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-16 19:15:00" d="2019-07-16 20:05:00"><n u="Strike Force Season 4 : Live">Strike Force Season 4 : Live (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A very anxious man enters the studio of TV Brabant and demands a conversation with Theo (Jeroen van Koningsbrugge). When he arrives in the studio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-16 20:05:00" d="2019-07-16 21:00:00"><n u="Strike Force Season 4 : Trapped">Strike Force Season 4 : Trapped (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Willem (Dennis van de Ven) and Theo (Jeroen van Koningsbrugge) have to rescue politician from the hands of the serial killer. The politician who always</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-16 21:00:00" d="2019-07-16 22:35:00"><n u="The Secret of Borgo Larici">The Secret of Borgo Larici (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Anita (Serena Iansiti) decides that it's time to go back to town and enjoy her romance with Francesco (Giulio Berruti), but Claudia (Nathalie Rapti Gómez)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-16 22:35:00" d="2019-07-17 00:05:00"><n u="The Secret of Borgo Larici">The Secret of Borgo Larici (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Francesco (Giulio Berruti) believes Fausto Ferraris (Nicola Pistoia) is involved in the mystery about his mother. Don Costante (Massimo Wertmuller)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-17 00:05:00" d="2019-07-17 01:55:00"><n u="The Salento Murders Part">The Salento Murders Part 1</n>    <k>A malevolent clan, probably from Calabria, has arrived in Salento to conquer the territory. Commissioner Pasquale Zagaria (Lino Banfi) is a policeman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-17 01:55:00" d="2019-07-17 03:50:00"><n u="The Salento Murders Part">The Salento Murders Part 2</n>    <k>A malevolent clan, probably from Calabria, has arrived in Salento to conquer the territory. Commissioner Pasquale Zagaria (Lino Banfi) is a policeman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-17 03:50:00" d="2019-07-17 06:00:00"><n>Shanghai Dynasty</n>    <k>Lutvija Belmondo Mirga (Visar Vishka) narrates a story of four generations of a gypsy family. After finding success in trading goods, he plunges into crime</k>  </p>
</a>
