<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2020-06-01 04:32:50"><p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-08 06:00:00" d="2020-06-08 07:40:00"><n>The Killer Inside</n>    <k>A young and ambitious lawyer gets his first big case, the defense of brutal serial killer Peter Kuerten (Milan Knazko). But Kuerten and his wife begin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-08 07:40:00" d="2020-06-08 09:15:00"><n>True Intentions</n>    <k>Jana and Marika meet on a train and quickly become friends. They go to the countryside, a remote mountain area that holds a lot of secrets about Jana's past</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-08 09:15:00" d="2020-06-08 10:05:00"><n>The Hold-Up - E1</n>    <k>An ordinary morning, a bank robbery intertwines the lives of the branch director, a star restauranteur, a pregnant young cop, an old policeman and other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-08 10:05:00" d="2020-06-08 10:55:00"><n>The Hold-Up - E2</n>    <k>While Agnes (Blandine Bellavoir), a young cop, brings supplies to the hostages, Mino (Yaniss Lespert), one of the four robbers, is ill. He needs insulin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-08 10:55:00" d="2020-06-08 11:45:00"><n>The Hold-Up - E3</n>    <k>Alex (Arnaud Ducret) enters the vault containing a loot of eight million euros. The hostages are still tied to each other and their eyes are bandaged</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-08 11:45:00" d="2020-06-08 13:10:00"><n>Double Trouble</n>    <k>Marek lives alternately with two women. He tells them both that he works in another city for part of the week. In reality, he stays in the same and moves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-08 13:10:00" d="2020-06-08 14:40:00"><n>Better Days</n>    <k>It’s New Year’s Eve and Gary (Cody Brotter) desperately tries to spark the interest of his ex-girlfriend, without letting his friends embarrass him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-08 14:40:00" d="2020-06-08 16:05:00"><n u="The Mine Inferno">The Mine Inferno (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Petr (Oskar Hes) drops out of the Mine Engineering College in Prague and moves back to the family home with a pregnant Jewish girlfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-08 16:05:00" d="2020-06-08 17:20:00"><n u="The Mine Inferno">The Mine Inferno (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Marie (Martha Issová) is falling apart. A collapsed Milan (Marek Taclík) shifts to a less paid job, while Jana (Antonie Formanová) betrays Marie’s darkest secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-08 17:20:00" d="2020-06-08 19:00:00"><n>The Killer Inside</n>    <k>A young and ambitious lawyer gets his first big case, the defense of brutal serial killer Peter Kuerten (Milan Knazko). But Kuerten and his wife begin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-08 19:00:00" d="2020-06-08 20:00:00"><n u="Legacy">Legacy (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The young detective Jakovljevic and his partner investigate the murder of a young girl who was burned in a cornfield. The investigation leads to a company</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-08 20:00:00" d="2020-06-08 21:00:00"><n u="Legacy">Legacy (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Aleksandar and Mirko bring Strahinja into custody. During a raid at Strahina's place, they find an interesting photo that may be a possible clue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-08 21:00:00" d="2020-06-08 22:00:00"><n u="The Fury Season">The Fury Season 2 (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Kunes and Lupin finally meet Zeljek in Montenegro. The criminal has the advantage of his territory but the detectives have an ace behind their sleeves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-08 22:00:00" d="2020-06-08 23:15:00" c="1"><n u="Fallout Part">Fallout Part 1</n><t>F</t>    <k>An unfortunate gunshot intertwines the fates of seven people and changes their fate forever. Viktor shoots Jendric while defending his daughter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-08 23:15:00" d="2020-06-09 00:30:00" c="1"><n u="Fallout Part">Fallout Part 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>While helping to reconstruct Jendric’s family, Viktor also attempts to get closer to his daughter and former wife. This is his only opportunity for redemption</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-09 00:30:00" d="2020-06-09 01:30:00"><n u="The Fury Season">The Fury Season 2 (13)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Kunes and Lupin finally meet Zeljek in Montenegro. The criminal has the advantage of his territory but the detectives have an ace behind their sleeves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-09 01:30:00" d="2020-06-09 03:10:00"><n>The Killer Inside</n>    <k>A young and ambitious lawyer gets his first big case, the defense of brutal serial killer Peter Kuerten (Milan Knazko). But Kuerten and his wife begin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-09 03:10:00" d="2020-06-09 04:35:00" c="1"><n>Babylon Sisters</n><t>F</t>    <k>The residents of a rundown building receive an eviction notice from their landlord. Led by little Kamla and professor Leone, this striving immigrant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-09 04:35:00" d="2020-06-09 06:00:00"><n>A Sicilian Dream</n>    <k>A poignant drama following the development of a young Sicilian boy, Ettore Corvaja (Corrado Fortuna), from the 1950s to 1960s. Yearning to become</k>  </p>
</a>
