<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="17" t="2019-07-11 00:20:34"><p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-15 06:00:00" d="2019-07-15 07:55:00"><n>In Love with an Angel</n>    <k>Claudio (Raoul Bova) is a selfish 40-year-old man who enjoys all the pleasures in life. With a limitless bank account at his disposal and a charming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-15 07:55:00" d="2019-07-15 09:40:00"><n>Silent Fear</n>    <k>Sabine (Thekla Reuten) is looking for the truth behind the disappearance of her best friend twenty years ago. An encounter with the handsome Olaf (Daan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-15 09:40:00" d="2019-07-15 11:20:00"><n>Mafia Millionaires</n>    <k>The rise and fall of a Camorra clan in Naples, told through the eyes of a crime boss and his family. Forty years of a man's life, forty years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-15 11:20:00" d="2019-07-15 13:00:00"><n u="Mafia Undercover Season">Mafia Undercover Season 2 (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The mission isn’t over yet for Agent Solo (Marco Bocci), now infiltrated within the Corona crime family. Agata (Carlotta Antonelli), daughter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-15 13:00:00" d="2019-07-15 14:35:00"><n u="Mafia Undercover Season">Mafia Undercover Season 2 (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Unexpected news alter the course of destiny for Marco (Marco Bocci) and the old Boss; Bruno Corona (Peppino Mazzotta) is still alive and in prison</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-15 14:35:00" d="2019-07-15 16:15:00"><n u="Mafia Undercover Season">Mafia Undercover Season 2 (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Following Bruno’s (Peppino Mazzotta) escape from prison and Agata’s (Carlotta Antonelli) rescue from Albania, the Corona family is finally reunited again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-15 16:15:00" d="2019-07-15 17:55:00"><n u="Mafia Undercover Season">Mafia Undercover Season 2 (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Following Don Antonio’s (Renato Carpentieri) death, the alliance between Marco (Marco Bocci) and Bruno (Peppino Mazzotta) becomes increasingly fragile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-15 17:55:00" d="2019-07-15 19:25:00"><n>Manhunt</n>    <k>After being wrongfully accused of a fatal hit-and-run, Michael Bellicher (Daan Schuurmans) finds himself hunted by cops and criminals alike as he attempts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-15 19:25:00" d="2019-07-15 21:00:00"><n>Unfaithful</n>    <k>Eric (Frédéric Van Den Driessche) looks like a happy family man. But he also frequents two other women with one child each: Chloé and Hugo, whose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-15 21:00:00" d="2019-07-15 21:50:00"><n u="Strike Force Season 4 : Live">Strike Force Season 4 : Live (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A very anxious man enters the studio of TV Brabant and demands a conversation with Theo (Jeroen van Koningsbrugge). When he arrives in the studio</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-15 21:50:00" d="2019-07-15 22:40:00"><n u="Strike Force Season 4 : Trapped">Strike Force Season 4 : Trapped (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Willem (Dennis van de Ven) and Theo (Jeroen van Koningsbrugge) have to rescue politician from the hands of the serial killer. The politician who always</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-15 22:40:00" d="2019-07-15 23:35:00"><n u="Strike Force Season 4 : Now it's personal">Strike Force Season 4 : Now it's personal (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Harold (Daan van Dijsseldonk) discovers an old case that helps Willem (Dennis van de Ven) and Theo (Jeroen van Koningsbrugge) in their search</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-15 23:35:00" d="2019-07-16 00:30:00"><n u="Strike Force Season 4 : No way out">Strike Force Season 4 : No way out (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The serial killer tries to put Willem (Dennis van de Ven) in a tight spot by going after a childhood friend of his. Because of their painful past, Willem</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-16 00:30:00" d="2019-07-16 01:55:00"><n>The President's Mistress</n>    <k>Forbidden love affairs have their risks, especially in closed and conservative societies. Eurochannel welcomes you to the final years of the nineteenth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-16 01:55:00" d="2019-07-16 03:25:00"><n>Back to Mom's</n>    <k>François (Pierre Cassignard), divorced and unemployed, finds himself on the street. He returns to live with Alice (Annie Cordy), his mother, claiming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-16 03:25:00" d="2019-07-16 04:50:00" c="1"><n>The Perfect Match</n><t>F</t>    <k>The immature Wyne (Hannah van Lunteren) starts a football team to rebel against all her friends whose lives have become dull and boring since either giving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-07-16 04:50:00" d="2019-07-16 06:00:00" c="1"><n>Dancing Quietly</n><t>F</t>    <k>60% After many dark years of depression, Luca (Martina Schöne-Radunski) seeks to earn her high school diploma. Her little dog Mata helps her to find motivation</k>  </p>
</a>
