<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="17" t="2021-07-13 04:59:20"><p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-20 06:00:00" d="2021-07-20 07:25:00"><n u="An Innocent Man">An Innocent Man (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A trial begins against Hilsner. This will become the most famous case in the history of the country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-20 07:25:00" d="2021-07-20 08:55:00"><n u="The Shadow Killer">The Shadow Killer (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In the early 1970s, a series of bloody crimes targeted brunette women. As the police investigation rejects the possibility of a serial killer, murders multiply</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-20 08:55:00" d="2021-07-20 10:25:00"><n u="The Shadow Killer">The Shadow Killer (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The investigator finds herself puzzled by the evidence. As the case progresses, she discovers astonishing information leading to the existence of a serial killer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-20 10:25:00" d="2021-07-20 12:15:00" c="1"><n>Frozen Valley</n><t>F</t>    <k>A former human trafficker finds the murdered body of his nephew in a remote valley. As soon as the police start to investigate the murder case, he becomes the prime suspect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-20 12:15:00" d="2021-07-20 14:05:00" c="1"><n>The Greek Affair</n><t>F</t>    <k>1970. Antonio leaves Rome and drives to Greece longing to discover its many secrets. His summer adventure quickly turns into a romance when he falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-20 14:05:00" d="2021-07-20 15:55:00" c="1"><n>Wings of Steel</n><t>F</t>    <k>A former RAF captain (David Svehlík) returns home to his family in 1945 hoping for a happy life after surviving the horrors of war piloting combat aircrafts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-20 15:55:00" d="2021-07-20 17:40:00" c="1"><n>Mafia Millionaires</n><t>F</t>    <k>The rise and fall of a Camorra clan in Naples, told through the eyes of a crime boss and his family. Forty years of a man's life, forty years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-20 17:40:00" d="2021-07-20 18:30:00"><n u="Shattered Destinies – Episode">Shattered Destinies – Episode 3</n>    <k>Vika gets what she wants, but she does not know it is only the beginning of the challenges she and Kostya will have to face</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-20 18:30:00" d="2021-07-20 19:20:00"><n u="Shattered Destinies – Episode">Shattered Destinies – Episode 4</n>    <k>After an accidental meeting of Oleg and Kostya, everything changes. The men surprisingly notice they look the same. From now on, they are to reveal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-20 19:20:00" d="2021-07-20 20:10:00"><n>Strike Force Season 2 Episode 1: Risky Business</n>    <k>Willem (Dennis van de Ven) gets the shock of a lifetime when he hears that Theo (Jeroen van Koningsbrugge) has been shot down in his own apartment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-20 20:10:00" d="2021-07-20 21:00:00"><n>Strike Force Season 2 Episode 2: Bad Trip</n>    <k>After a bloody shoot-out, Theo (Jeroen van Koningsbrugge) and Willem (Dennis van de Ven) venture into Amsterdam’s night life. There, a cold-blooded hitman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-20 21:00:00" d="2021-07-20 22:30:00"><n u="Full Disclosure Episode">Full Disclosure Episode 5 I</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Pietro (Massimo Poggio) finds Aldo’s dead body on the beach outside his father-in-law’s house, and when Elena (Antonia Liskova) arrives on the scene</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-20 22:30:00" d="2021-07-20 23:55:00"><n u="Full Disclosure Episode">Full Disclosure Episode 6 I</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Arianna (Laura Adriani) is about to be killed by the men sent by Fiore (Luca Biagini). Pietro (Massimo Poggio) has seen everything from Gloria’s house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-20 23:55:00" d="2021-07-21 01:35:00" c="1"><n>The Good Neighbor</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% The budding friendship between two very different neighbors takes a tragic turn when David (Maxim Mehmet) runs over a young woman and causes her death</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-21 01:35:00" d="2021-07-21 03:30:00"><n>In Love with an Angel</n>    <k>Claudio (Raoul Bova) is a selfish 40-year-old man who enjoys all the pleasures in life. With a limitless bank account at his disposal and a charming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-21 03:30:00" d="2021-07-21 04:40:00"><n u="Fallen Empire">Fallen Empire (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Tired of how their country was run, two men decide to take refuge in Russia and build an exiled government. Soon they discover the price of their actions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-21 04:40:00" d="2021-07-21 06:00:00"><n u="Fallen Empire">Fallen Empire (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Patriotism is a willingness to sacrifice for your country. Two men did it and were sentenced to death for betraying the monarchy. They still managed to find independence</k>  </p>
</a>
