<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="16" t="2020-04-10 04:32:30"><p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-17 06:00:00" d="2020-04-17 07:30:00" c="1"><n>The Marvels of Rome</n><t>F</t>    <k>Rome, 1947. The war is over but in the eternal city is still open and obvious wounds of the conflict. In the maternity ward of a hospital, nine women wait to give birth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-17 07:30:00" d="2020-04-17 08:55:00"><n>Double Trouble</n>    <k>Marek lives alternately with two women. He tells them both that he works in another city for part of the week. In reality, he stays in the same and moves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-17 08:55:00" d="2020-04-17 10:20:00"><n>A Sicilian Dream</n>    <k>A poignant drama following the development of a young Sicilian boy, Ettore Corvaja (Corrado Fortuna), from the 1950s to 1960s. Yearning to become</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-17 10:20:00" d="2020-04-17 11:55:00"><n>The Evil Hands</n>    <k>Roxana (Sylvie Testud), a prominent violinist, has both hands crushed during an accident. After she undergoes a transplant by a prominent surgeon, whose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-17 11:55:00" d="2020-04-17 13:25:00"><n>True Intentions</n>    <k>Jana and Marika meet on a train and quickly become friends. They go to the countryside, a remote mountain area that holds a lot of secrets about Jana's past</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-17 13:25:00" d="2020-04-17 14:55:00" c="1"><n>Suspicion</n><t>F</t>    <k>A lonely, trusting old woman fears that no-one needs her anymore. She suddenly meets a young man that claims to be a distant relative</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-17 14:55:00" d="2020-04-17 16:25:00"><n>Paris Undercover</n>    <k>The fate of two intriguing and deadly figures intertwine when a young petty tough is ordered to kill Mr Zhu, a senior man who has just arrived from China</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-17 16:25:00" d="2020-04-17 18:00:00"><n>Breaking News</n>    <k>Maksim is so addicted to internet news and social media feeds that he barely notices his wife anymore. Until she surprises him with very personal and life-changing news</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-17 18:00:00" d="2020-04-17 19:25:00" c="1"><n>Babylon Sisters</n><t>F</t>    <k>The residents of a rundown building receive an eviction notice from their landlord. Led by little Kamla and professor Leone, this striving immigrant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-17 19:25:00" d="2020-04-17 21:00:00"><n>Blind Fear</n>    <k>After a tragic car crash and losing the baby she was expecting, Betty seeks solace in a new job looking after a blind kid in a mountain house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-17 21:00:00" d="2020-04-17 22:00:00"><n u="Legacy">Legacy (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Strahinja suicides in his prison cell. Aleksandar finds call logs between Dejan and Nikola Kovacevic, Peca's father and minister in the Parliament</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-17 22:00:00" d="2020-04-17 23:00:00"><n u="Legacy">Legacy (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Mirko and Aleksandar agree to arrest Dejan. Aleksandar reveals the connection between the police chief Obradovic, Jovan's wife, and Nikola Kovacevic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-17 23:00:00" d="2020-04-18 00:50:00" c="1"><n>The Greek Affair</n><t>F</t>    <k>1970. Antonio leaves Rome and drives to Greece longing to discover its many secrets. His summer adventure quickly turns into a romance when he falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-18 00:50:00" d="2020-04-18 02:30:00"><n>Blind Fear</n>    <k>After a tragic car crash and losing the baby she was expecting, Betty seeks solace in a new job looking after a blind kid in a mountain house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-18 02:30:00" d="2020-04-18 04:15:00"><n u="Injustice Part">Injustice Part 1</n>    <k>Barrister Will Travers (James Purefoy) is asked to defend old friend Martin Newall (Nathaniel Parker), accused of murdering his secretary</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-18 04:15:00" d="2020-04-18 06:00:00"><n u="Injustice Part">Injustice Part 2</n>    <k>The trial begins and Will (James Purefoy) puts on an effective defense. DCI Wenborn (Charlie Creed-Miles) desperately wants to arrest Will for the murder</k>  </p>
</a>
