<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="14" t="2019-08-10 01:37:47"><p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-16 06:00:00" d="2019-08-16 07:30:00"><n>A Sicilian Dream</n>    <k>A poignant drama following the development of a young Sicilian boy, Ettore Corvaja (Corrado Fortuna), from the 1950s to 1960s. Yearning to become</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-16 07:30:00" d="2019-08-16 09:05:00"><n u="The Heiresses">The Heiresses (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In 1945, Ottavio della Rocca (Jacques Weber), a wealthy Corsican landlord, is about to marry his favorite daughter, Vanina (Helena Soubeyrand)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-16 09:05:00" d="2019-08-16 10:45:00"><n u="The Heiresses">The Heiresses (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In 1945, Ottavio della Rocca (Jacques Weber), a wealthy Corsican landlord, is about to marry his favorite daughter, Vanina (Helena Soubeyrand)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-16 10:45:00" d="2019-08-16 12:25:00"><n>Blood Brothers</n>    <k>Brice (Sylvain Dieuaide), the eldest son of the Lemeuniers, is accused of a quadruple murder. His brother Martin (Clément Chebli) will do whatever it takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-16 12:25:00" d="2019-08-16 14:00:00"><n>The Evil Hands</n>    <k>Roxana (Sylvie Testud), a prominent violinist, has both hands crushed during an accident. After she undergoes a transplant by a prominent surgeon, whose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-16 14:00:00" d="2019-08-16 15:45:00" c="1"><n>Wings of Steel</n><t>F</t>    <k>A former RAF captain (David Svehlík) returns home to his family in 1945 hoping for a happy life after surviving the horrors of war piloting combat aircrafts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-16 15:45:00" d="2019-08-16 17:20:00" c="1"><n>Mont Blanc Murder</n><t>F</t>    <k>An inspector newly transferred to the small Mont Blanc region has been given a strange case, of a man whose body was trapped in the ice for 15 years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-16 17:20:00" d="2019-08-16 19:00:00"><n>The Skin of Sorrow</n>    <k>It's 1832, and 22-year-old Raphaël's (Thomas Coumans) gambling has driven him to the brink of suicide. He is about to throw himself in the Seine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-16 19:00:00" d="2019-08-16 20:50:00"><n>Obsession</n>    <k>Simone (Loes Haverkort) inherits a dilapidated country house in France and makes her way there with her husband Eric and their two children</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-16 20:50:00" d="2019-08-16 22:30:00"><n>Enticement</n>    <k>Jonathan Marescot has an obsession for stealing little objects. He loves not only possessing them, but also the thrill he gets from robbing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-16 22:30:00" d="2019-08-17 00:10:00"><n>Forbidden Lust</n>    <k>Two young men work for The Master, a loan shark and illegal antiques dealer. They take care of the dirty work but both make the fatal mistake of falling</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-17 00:10:00" d="2019-08-17 01:55:00" c="1"><n>Wings of Steel</n><t>F</t>    <k>A former RAF captain (David Svehlík) returns home to his family in 1945 hoping for a happy life after surviving the horrors of war piloting combat aircrafts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-17 01:55:00" d="2019-08-17 04:10:00"><n>Broken Promise</n>    <k>Based on a true story of a Jewish boy in Western Slovakia who escaped deportation to a concentration camp thanks to his extraordinary soccer talent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-17 04:10:00" d="2019-08-17 06:00:00"><n>Silent Fear</n>    <k>Sabine (Thekla Reuten) is looking for the truth behind the disappearance of her best friend twenty years ago. An encounter with the handsome Olaf (Daan</k>  </p>
</a>
