<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="16" t="2020-05-26 04:34:31"><p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-02 06:00:00" d="2020-06-02 07:35:00"><n>Manon Lescaut</n>    <k>There is nothing we can do against the call of love. Even when a professional future might look brighter than the sun, sometimes the heart beats drive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-02 07:35:00" d="2020-06-02 09:05:00" c="1"><n>Suspicion</n><t>F</t>    <k>A lonely, trusting old woman fears that no-one needs her anymore. She suddenly meets a young man that claims to be a distant relative</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-02 09:05:00" d="2020-06-02 10:45:00"><n>Gripsholm</n>    <k>59% Kurt (Ulrich Noethen) and Lydia (Heike Makatsch) are planning a relaxing vacation in Sweden. What Lydia does not know is that for Kurt, a well-known</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-02 10:45:00" d="2020-06-02 12:25:00"><n>Enticement</n>    <k>Jonathan Marescot has an obsession for stealing little objects. He loves not only possessing them, but also the thrill he gets from robbing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-02 12:25:00" d="2020-06-02 14:05:00"><n>Albert Camus</n>    <k>During the 1959 rebellion Albert Camus (Stéphane Freiss) wrote to his mother to convince her to leave Algeria and join him in France. He sees episodes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-02 14:05:00" d="2020-06-02 15:45:00"><n>Blind Fear</n>    <k>After a tragic car crash and losing the baby she was expecting, Betty seeks solace in a new job looking after a blind kid in a mountain house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-02 15:45:00" d="2020-06-02 17:25:00"><n>Fallen from the sky</n>    <k>January 1943. France is under occupation. Louise is 70, and in her bar, everyone likes to forget about the war. Her serenity is disturbed, however</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-02 17:25:00" d="2020-06-02 18:25:00"><n u="The Fury Season">The Fury Season 2 (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% The head of the local psychiatric hospital is found dead. The chief surgeon is at risk as well as many of the doctors. Will Kunes and his team arrive on time?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-02 18:25:00" d="2020-06-02 19:25:00"><n u="The Fury Season">The Fury Season 2 (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Zelejek escapes in the last minute before being captured. The town becomes more dangerous than ever as he plans his revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-02 19:25:00" d="2020-06-02 21:00:00"><n>Manon Lescaut</n>    <k>There is nothing we can do against the call of love. Even when a professional future might look brighter than the sun, sometimes the heart beats drive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-02 21:00:00" d="2020-06-02 22:15:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder">Anatomy of a Murder V (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Criminalist Marie Vyrová is approached by a woman who is convinced that 30 ago when she was spending her vacation as a 12-year-old girl in the countryside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-02 22:15:00" d="2020-06-03 00:05:00"><n>Obsession</n>    <k>Simone (Loes Haverkort) inherits a dilapidated country house in France and makes her way there with her husband Eric and their two children</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-03 00:05:00" d="2020-06-03 01:20:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder">Anatomy of a Murder V (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Criminalist Marie Vyrová is approached by a woman who is convinced that 30 ago when she was spending her vacation as a 12-year-old girl in the countryside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-03 01:20:00" d="2020-06-03 03:00:00" c="1"><n>The Marvels of Rome</n><t>F</t>    <k>Rome, 1947. The war is over but in the eternal city is still open and obvious wounds of the conflict. In the maternity ward of a hospital, nine women wait to give birth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-03 03:00:00" d="2020-06-03 04:45:00" c="1"><n>The Winds of Passion</n><t>F</t>    <k>In the climax of political turmoil in France between republicans and Catholics, a young teacher and a fierce activist fall in love and marry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-03 04:45:00" d="2020-06-03 06:00:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder">Anatomy of a Murder V (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Criminalist Marie Vyrová is approached by a woman who is convinced that 30 ago when she was spending her vacation as a 12-year-old girl in the countryside</k>  </p>
</a>
