<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="14" t="2019-08-13 02:08:56"><p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-18 06:00:00" d="2019-08-18 07:35:00"><n>Chase</n>    <k>Luis (Nicolas Cazalé) is a somewhat clumsy money transporter. Against all odds, he steals his own van with five million euros. For Emma (Isabelle Carré)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-18 07:35:00" d="2019-08-18 09:15:00"><n>The Skin of Sorrow</n>    <k>It's 1832, and 22-year-old Raphaël's (Thomas Coumans) gambling has driven him to the brink of suicide. He is about to throw himself in the Seine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-18 09:15:00" d="2019-08-18 10:55:00"><n>Such a Pretty Lie</n>    <k>Christine (Corinne Touzet), a dermatologist falls in love with Bruno (Francis Renaud), a 40-year-old comic strip writer, but she lies about her age</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-18 10:55:00" d="2019-08-18 12:50:00"><n>From Rome with Love</n>    <k>Maya (Lola Ponche) is a beautiful young Argentine woman who leaves Buenos Aires and moves to Roma to take part in a talent show and thus realise her dream</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-18 12:50:00" d="2019-08-18 14:35:00" c="1"><n>Wings of Steel</n><t>F</t>    <k>A former RAF captain (David Svehlík) returns home to his family in 1945 hoping for a happy life after surviving the horrors of war piloting combat aircrafts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-18 14:35:00" d="2019-08-18 16:15:00"><n>Mafia Millionaires</n>    <k>The rise and fall of a Camorra clan in Naples, told through the eyes of a crime boss and his family. Forty years of a man's life, forty years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-18 16:15:00" d="2019-08-18 18:00:00" c="1"><n>The Time of Secrets</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% The last vacations for Marcel Pagnol (Pierre-François Martin-Laval) in his favorite Provence hills prove as delightful as challenging. It is the beginning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-18 18:00:00" d="2019-08-18 19:40:00"><n>The Time of Love</n>    <k>Overcoming disciplinary committee, Marcel (Pierre-François Martin-Laval) gets to stay at high school. He becomes a leader among his new classmates, firming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-18 19:40:00" d="2019-08-18 21:20:00"><n>Enticement</n>    <k>Jonathan Marescot has an obsession for stealing little objects. He loves not only possessing them, but also the thrill he gets from robbing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-18 21:20:00" d="2019-08-18 23:00:00"><n>The Perfect Stranger</n>    <k>Jonathan (Bruno Debrandt), an unhappy man who has just inherited a massive fortune, discovers that Anaďs (Audrey Fleurot), his wife, has been hospitalized</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-18 23:00:00" d="2019-08-19 00:50:00" c="1"><n>Wings of Steel</n><t>F</t>    <k>A former RAF captain (David Svehlík) returns home to his family in 1945 hoping for a happy life after surviving the horrors of war piloting combat aircrafts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-19 00:50:00" d="2019-08-19 02:35:00"><n>Silent Fear</n>    <k>Sabine (Thekla Reuten) is looking for the truth behind the disappearance of her best friend twenty years ago. An encounter with the handsome Olaf (Daan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-19 02:35:00" d="2019-08-19 04:15:00"><n>Chesterfield</n>    <k>In 1945, &quot;cigarette camps&quot; were set up in Normandy to provide rest and recreation for American soldiers back from the front. They were hastily transformed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-19 04:15:00" d="2019-08-19 06:00:00" c="1"><n>Sexy Zazy</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Zazy (Ruby O. Fee) and her boyfriend stumble upon the truth behind a terrible accident, which they use to force Marianna (Petra van de Voort), a wealthy</k>  </p>
</a>
