<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="20" t="2020-05-30 04:34:52"><p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-06 06:00:00" d="2020-06-06 07:35:00"><n>The Perfect Stranger</n>    <k>Jonathan (Bruno Debrandt), an unhappy man who has just inherited a massive fortune, discovers that Anaďs (Audrey Fleurot), his wife, has been hospitalized</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-06 07:35:00" d="2020-06-06 09:20:00"><n>Frozen Valley</n>    <k>A former human trafficker finds the murdered body of his nephew in a remote valley. As soon as the police start to investigate the murder case, he becomes the prime suspect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-06 09:20:00" d="2020-06-06 11:00:00" c="1"><n>The Fugitive</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% The true story of a man’s life that turns into a never-ending nightmare as he tries to prove his innocence. After years behind bars and half a decade</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-06 11:00:00" d="2020-06-06 12:10:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder">Anatomy of a Murder IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Three bears are robbed from the local zoo, and the guard is murdered. All the clues lead to an illicit enterprise with rare animals involving a dangerous mafia group</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-06 12:10:00" d="2020-06-06 13:20:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder">Anatomy of a Murder IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A detective team of Captain Vyrová is summoned to investigate an unusual case: three bears mysteriously disappeared from the local zoo. Their initial clues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-06 13:20:00" d="2020-06-06 14:30:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder">Anatomy of a Murder IV (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>With the help of a retired police captain, the team connects the case of the stolen bears with a case of five dead dogs found in mysterious circumstances</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-06 14:30:00" d="2020-06-06 15:40:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder">Anatomy of a Murder V (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Criminalist Marie Vyrová is approached by a woman who is convinced that 30 ago when she was spending her vacation as a 12-year-old girl in the countryside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-06 15:40:00" d="2020-06-06 16:30:00"><n>Mute – E1</n>    <k>Nastya dreams to adopt a 7-year-old boy, Yegor, from an orphanage. However, the boy is not a simple kid: two criminals have been watching over him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-06 16:30:00" d="2020-06-06 17:20:00"><n>Mute – E2</n>    <k>The orphanage manager decides to cheat the thugs and find the money himself. To do this, he takes the boy away from the orphanage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-06 17:20:00" d="2020-06-06 18:20:00"><n u="Legacy">Legacy (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The young detective Jakovljevic and his partner investigate the murder of a young girl who was burned in a cornfield. The investigation leads to a company</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-06 18:20:00" d="2020-06-06 19:20:00"><n u="Legacy">Legacy (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Aleksandar and Mirko bring Strahinja into custody. During a raid at Strahina's place, they find an interesting photo that may be a possible clue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-06 19:20:00" d="2020-06-06 20:10:00"><n u="Lifeline">Lifeline (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Anton asks Oksana not to linger at the hospital - he plans to celebrate their anniversary but last minute problems at work do not allow her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-06 20:10:00" d="2020-06-06 21:00:00"><n u="Lifeline">Lifeline (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Oksana refuses to go to Anton's parents, who want to bless them for their upcoming marriage. Maxim looks for his daughter after she escapes from her grandparents' house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-06 21:00:00" d="2020-06-06 22:00:00"><n u="The Fury Season">The Fury Season 2 (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% The head of the local psychiatric hospital is found dead. The chief surgeon is at risk as well as many of the doctors. Will Kunes and his team arrive on time?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-06 22:00:00" d="2020-06-06 23:00:00"><n u="The Fury Season">The Fury Season 2 (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Zelejek escapes in the last minute before being captured. The town becomes more dangerous than ever as he plans his revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-06 23:00:00" d="2020-06-07 00:40:00"><n>Enticement</n>    <k>Jonathan Marescot has an obsession for stealing little objects. He loves not only possessing them, but also the thrill he gets from robbing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-07 00:40:00" d="2020-06-07 01:40:00"><n u="The Fury Season">The Fury Season 2 (11)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% The head of the local psychiatric hospital is found dead. The chief surgeon is at risk as well as many of the doctors. Will Kunes and his team arrive on time?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-07 01:40:00" d="2020-06-07 02:40:00"><n u="The Fury Season">The Fury Season 2 (12)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Zelejek escapes in the last minute before being captured. The town becomes more dangerous than ever as he plans his revenge</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-07 02:40:00" d="2020-06-07 04:20:00" c="1"><n>The Fugitive</n><t>F</t>    <k>61% The true story of a man’s life that turns into a never-ending nightmare as he tries to prove his innocence. After years behind bars and half a decade</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-07 04:20:00" d="2020-06-07 06:00:00"><n>The Evil Hands</n>    <k>Roxana (Sylvie Testud), a prominent violinist, has both hands crushed during an accident. After she undergoes a transplant by a prominent surgeon, whose</k>  </p>
</a>
