<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2020-04-15 04:31:25"><p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-22 06:00:00" d="2020-04-22 07:30:00" c="1"><n>The Marvels of Rome</n><t>F</t>    <k>Rome, 1947. The war is over but in the eternal city is still open and obvious wounds of the conflict. In the maternity ward of a hospital, nine women wait to give birth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-22 07:30:00" d="2020-04-22 09:00:00"><n>Paris Undercover</n>    <k>The fate of two intriguing and deadly figures intertwine when a young petty tough is ordered to kill Mr Zhu, a senior man who has just arrived from China</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-22 09:00:00" d="2020-04-22 10:30:00"><n u="Methanol">Methanol (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Rudolf (David Máj) is bound to be fired from the chemicals firm he works for. This drives him to try extra hard to impress Malota (Lukás Vaculík), a dodgy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-22 10:30:00" d="2020-04-22 12:05:00"><n u="Methanol">Methanol (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Captain Hálek (Vasil Fridrich) investigates a case with the highest number of victims and indictments since 1989. How quickly can he find the murderer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-22 12:05:00" d="2020-04-22 13:15:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder">Anatomy of a Murder III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The team of detectives under the leadership of Marie Vyrova has a new case - the murder of a man shot by a crossbow. The case takes a dramatic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-22 13:15:00" d="2020-04-22 14:45:00"><n>Executive Orders</n>    <k>In Northern Nigeria, two French scientists working for an environmental NGO disappear. Hugo Geoffroy (Laurent Lucas), leader of an emergency</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-22 14:45:00" d="2020-04-22 16:15:00"><n>Closed Circuit</n>    <k>Hired by a surveillance company to oversee the security of a hypermarket, Pierre Solvy (Thomas Jouannet) soon discovers that he is expected to do other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-22 16:15:00" d="2020-04-22 17:45:00"><n>Better Days</n>    <k>It’s New Year’s Eve and Gary (Cody Brotter) desperately tries to spark the interest of his ex-girlfriend, without letting his friends embarrass him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-22 17:45:00" d="2020-04-22 19:00:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder">Anatomy of a Murder III (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The team of detectives under the leadership of Marie Vyrova has a new case - the murder of a man shot by a crossbow. The case takes a dramatic</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-22 19:00:00" d="2020-04-22 20:00:00"><n u="Legacy">Legacy (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Aleksandar visits Jovan's wife and shows her compromising pictures of her, so she accepts to work for him. Peca tells his father that he opened</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-22 20:00:00" d="2020-04-22 21:00:00"><n u="Legacy">Legacy (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Aleksandar is arrested and tortured to admit that he was with Marjanovic that night. Jelena and Sava fake evidence to release Aleksandar form custody</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-22 21:00:00" d="2020-04-22 21:50:00"><n u="Chernobyl: Aftermath">Chernobyl: Aftermath (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lera arrives in Prypyat. When her passport is stolen, an army officer uses his influence and manages to help her retrieve it, aiming to win Lera's heart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-22 21:50:00" d="2020-04-22 22:40:00"><n u="Chernobyl: Aftermath">Chernobyl: Aftermath (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Chernobyl nuclear plant explodes, leaving the surrounding area in disarray. Vitas rushes to the site, but it's too late. Sveta perishes, leaving behind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-22 22:40:00" d="2020-04-23 00:05:00"><n>Double Trouble</n>    <k>Marek lives alternately with two women. He tells them both that he works in another city for part of the week. In reality, he stays in the same and moves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-23 00:05:00" d="2020-04-23 00:55:00"><n u="Chernobyl: Aftermath">Chernobyl: Aftermath (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lera arrives in Prypyat. When her passport is stolen, an army officer uses his influence and manages to help her retrieve it, aiming to win Lera's heart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-23 00:55:00" d="2020-04-23 01:45:00"><n u="Chernobyl: Aftermath">Chernobyl: Aftermath (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Chernobyl nuclear plant explodes, leaving the surrounding area in disarray. Vitas rushes to the site, but it's too late. Sveta perishes, leaving behind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-23 01:45:00" d="2020-04-23 03:10:00" c="1"><n>Babylon Sisters</n><t>F</t>    <k>The residents of a rundown building receive an eviction notice from their landlord. Led by little Kamla and professor Leone, this striving immigrant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-23 03:10:00" d="2020-04-23 04:35:00"><n>Trapped</n>    <k>On New Year’s Day, Kristen (Terence Schreurs) arrives at her father’s bar to clean up after the night before. Then a mysterious figure starts harassing her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-23 04:35:00" d="2020-04-23 06:00:00" c="1"><n>Parental Guidance</n><t>F</t>    <k>Trying to conceive a second child, Giulio (Adriano Giannini) discovers he is infertile and suspects his wife, Veronica (Serena Autieri)</k>  </p>
</a>
