<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2021-07-10 04:58:54"><p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-17 06:00:00" d="2021-07-17 07:10:00"><n u="Red Line – Episode">Red Line – Episode 2</n>    <k>The two students are dead and military prosecutor Roman Rédl knows that killers can strike again at any time</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-17 07:10:00" d="2021-07-17 08:20:00"><n u="Red Line – Episode">Red Line – Episode 3</n>    <k>Murderers are trying to sweep traces of the weapons stolen from Soviet military trains. It's a game of time as both sides try to put together a picture</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-17 08:20:00" d="2021-07-17 09:30:00"><n u="Red Line – Episode">Red Line – Episode 4</n>    <k>It is New Year's Eve of 1992 - the last day of Czechoslovakia. In one room is a dead body, in the other is Rédl on the brink of death</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-17 09:30:00" d="2021-07-17 10:50:00" c="1"><n>Unlocked</n><t>F</t>    <k>59% Lonely medical student Frank is pleased with his flat: a safe, quiet haven where he can relax. When he meets his intrusive neighbor Lotte, he realizes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-17 10:50:00" d="2021-07-17 12:25:00" c="1"><n>The Good Neighbor</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% The budding friendship between two very different neighbors takes a tragic turn when David (Maxim Mehmet) runs over a young woman and causes her death</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-17 12:25:00" d="2021-07-17 14:05:00" c="1"><n>The Time of Secrets</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% The last vacations for Marcel Pagnol (Pierre-François Martin-Laval) in his favorite Provence hills prove as delightful as challenging. It is the beginning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-17 14:05:00" d="2021-07-17 15:40:00"><n>The Time of Love</n>    <k>Overcoming disciplinary committee, Marcel (Pierre-François Martin-Laval) gets to stay at high school. He becomes a leader among his new classmates, firming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-17 15:40:00" d="2021-07-17 17:10:00" c="1"><n>Parental Guidance</n><t>F</t>    <k>Trying to conceive a second child, Giulio (Adriano Giannini) discovers he is infertile and suspects his wife, Veronica (Serena Autieri)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-17 17:10:00" d="2021-07-17 18:00:00"><n u="Twilight - Episode">Twilight - Episode 3</n>    <k>After the misfortune that befell Masha, Oleh realizes her salvation is in her work. At last, everything is fine in their life: they have a big family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-17 18:00:00" d="2021-07-17 18:50:00"><n u="Twilight - Episode">Twilight - Episode 4</n>    <k>One after another, Masha is befallen by misfortunes that are not accidental. Oleh is worried about what is going on and tries to protect his family but fails</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-17 18:50:00" d="2021-07-17 19:40:00"><n>Strike Force Season 1 Episode 9: Dirty money</n>    <k>To free Tessa (Lindsay Zwaan), Theo (Jeroen van Koningsbrugge) and Willem (Dennis van de Ven) need money from a drug dealer. In order to catch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-17 19:40:00" d="2021-07-17 20:30:00"><n>Strike Force Season 1 Episode 10: The price of freedom</n>    <k>Willem (Dennis van de Ven) is prepared to offer negotiator Freddy van Nuenen (Patrick Stoof) 35 million Euros in drug money to finally freed Tessa (Lindsay Zwaan)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-17 20:30:00" d="2021-07-17 22:05:00" c="1"><n>Manon Lescaut</n><t>F</t>    <k>59% There is nothing we can do against the call of love. Even when a professional future might look brighter than the sun, sometimes the heart beats drive</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-17 22:05:00" d="2021-07-17 23:40:00"><n u="Full Disclosure Episode">Full Disclosure Episode 3 I</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Elena (Antonia Liskova) is increasingly tormented by the memory of her old captor, Virgilio Sanna (Mirko Urania), while Pietro (Massimo Poggio) continues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-17 23:40:00" d="2021-07-18 01:15:00"><n u="Full Disclosure Episode">Full Disclosure Episode 4 I</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Elena (Antonia Liskova) wants the truth from Pietro (Massimo Poggio) about his role in her kidnapping and confronts him at gunpoint. His confession</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-18 01:15:00" d="2021-07-18 02:05:00"><n>Strike Force Season 1 Episode 9: Dirty money</n>    <k>To free Tessa (Lindsay Zwaan), Theo (Jeroen van Koningsbrugge) and Willem (Dennis van de Ven) need money from a drug dealer. In order to catch</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-18 02:05:00" d="2021-07-18 02:55:00"><n>Strike Force Season 1 Episode 10: The price of freedom</n>    <k>Willem (Dennis van de Ven) is prepared to offer negotiator Freddy van Nuenen (Patrick Stoof) 35 million Euros in drug money to finally freed Tessa (Lindsay Zwaan)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-18 02:55:00" d="2021-07-18 04:25:00"><n u="Methanol">Methanol (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Rudolf (David Máj) is bound to be fired from the chemicals firm he works for. This drives him to try extra hard to impress Malota (Lukás Vaculík), a dodgy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-18 04:25:00" d="2021-07-18 06:00:00"><n u="Methanol">Methanol (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Captain Hálek (Vasil Fridrich) investigates a case with the highest number of victims and indictments since 1989. How quickly can he find the murderer</k>  </p>
</a>
