<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="17" t="2021-07-09 06:52:12"><p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-15 06:00:00" d="2021-07-15 07:20:00"><n u="An Innocent Man">An Innocent Man (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A trial begins against Hilsner. This will become the most famous case in the history of the country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-15 07:20:00" d="2021-07-15 08:50:00"><n>The Climb</n>    <k>A climbing champion is pushed to her limits when she takes on a perilous new route to the summit of the Alps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-15 08:50:00" d="2021-07-15 10:20:00"><n>To Die For</n>    <k>Shy law student Martin falls for his mysterious landlady, Simone, who lives next door behind a thin wall. While trying to find out if she is responsible</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-15 10:20:00" d="2021-07-15 11:30:00"><n u="Fallen Empire">Fallen Empire (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Tired of how their country was run, two men decide to take refuge in Russia and build an exiled government. Soon they discover the price of their actions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-15 11:30:00" d="2021-07-15 12:55:00"><n u="Fallen Empire">Fallen Empire (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Patriotism is a willingness to sacrifice for your country. Two men did it and were sentenced to death for betraying the monarchy. They still managed to find independence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-15 12:55:00" d="2021-07-15 14:30:00"><n>Against their will</n>    <k>France 1943. Two pretty and different girls, Alice (Flore Bonaventura) and Lisette (Louise Herrero), 17, are torn from their families by the Nazis</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-15 14:30:00" d="2021-07-15 16:05:00" c="1"><n>The Good Neighbor</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% The budding friendship between two very different neighbors takes a tragic turn when David (Maxim Mehmet) runs over a young woman and causes her death</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-15 16:05:00" d="2021-07-15 17:40:00"><n>The Secret of the Bear</n>    <k>When a wild bear threatens their community, a man and his son venture into the mountains to hunt him down</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-15 17:40:00" d="2021-07-15 19:20:00" c="1"><n>Last Chance for Love</n><t>F</t>    <k>57% Edoardo, an Italian composer, faces a mid-life crisis. He takes a break in Valencia, where fate puts him in charge of the town’s choir. There he meets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-15 19:20:00" d="2021-07-15 20:10:00"><n u="Shattered Destinies – Episode">Shattered Destinies – Episode 3</n>    <k>Vika gets what she wants, but she does not know it is only the beginning of the challenges she and Kostya will have to face</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-15 20:10:00" d="2021-07-15 21:00:00"><n u="Shattered Destinies – Episode">Shattered Destinies – Episode 4</n>    <k>After an accidental meeting of Oleg and Kostya, everything changes. The men surprisingly notice they look the same. From now on, they are to reveal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-15 21:00:00" d="2021-07-15 22:25:00"><n u="The Shadow Killer">The Shadow Killer (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In the early 1970s, a series of bloody crimes targeted brunette women. As the police investigation rejects the possibility of a serial killer, murders multiply</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-15 22:25:00" d="2021-07-15 23:55:00"><n u="The Shadow Killer">The Shadow Killer (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The investigator finds herself puzzled by the evidence. As the case progresses, she discovers astonishing information leading to the existence of a serial killer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-15 23:55:00" d="2021-07-16 01:45:00" c="1"><n>The Money Trail</n><t>F</t>    <k>Amidst Argentina's worst economic crisis, Jordi pursues a multimillion-dollar contract with the government. To get it, he must put his ethics aside</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-16 01:45:00" d="2021-07-16 03:25:00"><n>A Private Affair</n>    <k>An investigative journalist enters a steamy affair with Ben, a prominent New York banker to get the secrets of the shady finance world. When he becomes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-16 03:25:00" d="2021-07-16 04:35:00"><n u="Fallen Empire">Fallen Empire (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Tired of how their country was run, two men decide to take refuge in Russia and build an exiled government. Soon they discover the price of their actions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-16 04:35:00" d="2021-07-16 06:00:00"><n u="Fallen Empire">Fallen Empire (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Patriotism is a willingness to sacrifice for your country. Two men did it and were sentenced to death for betraying the monarchy. They still managed to find independence</k>  </p>
</a>
