<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="14" t="2019-08-13 02:09:00"><p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-19 06:00:00" d="2019-08-19 07:55:00"><n>In Love with an Angel</n>    <k>Claudio (Raoul Bova) is a selfish 40-year-old man who enjoys all the pleasures in life. With a limitless bank account at his disposal and a charming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-19 07:55:00" d="2019-08-19 09:40:00"><n>Silent Fear</n>    <k>Sabine (Thekla Reuten) is looking for the truth behind the disappearance of her best friend twenty years ago. An encounter with the handsome Olaf (Daan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-19 09:40:00" d="2019-08-19 11:30:00"><n u="Only you">Only you (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Florist Carlo Gambardella (Giampaolo Morelli) and biologist Valentina Trevisol (Gaia Bermani Amaral) meet one day by chance and their lives change forever</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-19 11:30:00" d="2019-08-19 13:15:00"><n u="Only you">Only you (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Carlo (Giampaolo Morelli) tries to contact Valentina (Gaia Bermani Amaral) again but she, scared off by the discovery that he has five children</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-19 13:15:00" d="2019-08-19 14:55:00"><n u="Only you">Only you (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Carlo (Giampaolo Morelli) tries to make it up to Valentina (Gaia Bermani Amaral) after Antonio's farce at the hospital. But she seems intent on staying</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-19 14:55:00" d="2019-08-19 16:40:00"><n u="Only you">Only you (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Unable to resign himself to the fact that Valentina (Gaia Bermani Amaral) is out of his life, Carlo (Giampaolo Morelli) looks for her where she usually</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-19 16:40:00" d="2019-08-19 18:30:00"><n u="Only you">Only you (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The reconciliation between Valentina (Gaia Bermani Amaral) and Carlo (Giampaolo Morelli) proves to be short-lived; after Tommaso (Flavio Montrucchio) tells</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-19 18:30:00" d="2019-08-19 20:15:00"><n u="Only you">Only you (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Valentina (Gaia Bermani Amaral) struggles to be accepted by Carlo’s family. While Mr. and Mrs. Trevisol meet the Gambardella family, Gaetano (Pietro</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-19 20:15:00" d="2019-08-19 21:50:00"><n>Unfaithful</n>    <k>Eric (Frédéric Van Den Driessche) looks like a happy family man. But he also frequents two other women with one child each: Chloé and Hugo, whose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-19 21:50:00" d="2019-08-19 23:35:00"><n>The Killer Inside</n><t>S</t>    <k>A young and ambitious lawyer gets his first big case, the defense of brutal serial killer Peter Kuerten (Milan Knazko). But Kuerten and his wife begin</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-19 23:35:00" d="2019-08-20 01:20:00" c="1"><n>Wings of Steel</n><t>F</t>    <k>A former RAF captain (David Svehlík) returns home to his family in 1945 hoping for a happy life after surviving the horrors of war piloting combat aircrafts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-20 01:20:00" d="2019-08-20 02:55:00" c="1"><n>Deception</n><t>F</t>    <k>Paul Berthier, a public prosecutor, witnesses the accidental drowning of a young girl but does nothing to help. A decision that will change</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-20 02:55:00" d="2019-08-20 04:35:00" c="1"><n>Sexy Zazy</n><t>F</t>    <k>65% Zazy (Ruby O. Fee) and her boyfriend stumble upon the truth behind a terrible accident, which they use to force Marianna (Petra van de Voort), a wealthy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-20 04:35:00" d="2019-08-20 06:00:00"><n>The President's Mistress</n>    <k>Forbidden love affairs have their risks, especially in closed and conservative societies. Eurochannel welcomes you to the final years of the nineteenth</k>  </p>
</a>
