<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2020-05-17 04:33:02"><p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-24 06:00:00" d="2020-05-24 07:35:00"><n>Beyond Suspicion</n>    <k>Valérie (Cristiana Réali) is an active and exemplary woman. Psychiatrist by profession, a mother, a wife and an irreproachable parishioner. Still, Valerie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-24 07:35:00" d="2020-05-24 09:05:00" c="1"><n>Suspicion</n><t>F</t>    <k>A lonely, trusting old woman fears that no-one needs her anymore. She suddenly meets a young man that claims to be a distant relative</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-24 09:05:00" d="2020-05-24 10:40:00"><n>The Evil Hands</n>    <k>Roxana (Sylvie Testud), a prominent violinist, has both hands crushed during an accident. After she undergoes a transplant by a prominent surgeon, whose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-24 10:40:00" d="2020-05-24 12:05:00" c="1"><n>Babylon Sisters</n><t>F</t>    <k>The residents of a rundown building receive an eviction notice from their landlord. Led by little Kamla and professor Leone, this striving immigrant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-24 12:05:00" d="2020-05-24 13:40:00" c="1"><n>Deception</n><t>F</t>    <k>Paul Berthier, a public prosecutor, witnesses the accidental drowning of a young girl but does nothing to help. A decision that will change</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-24 13:40:00" d="2020-05-24 15:20:00"><n>The Skin of Sorrow</n>    <k>It's 1832, and 22-year-old Raphaël's (Thomas Coumans) gambling has driven him to the brink of suicide. He is about to throw himself in the Seine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-24 15:20:00" d="2020-05-24 16:45:00"><n>Double Trouble</n>    <k>Marek lives alternately with two women. He tells them both that he works in another city for part of the week. In reality, he stays in the same and moves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-24 16:45:00" d="2020-05-24 18:10:00"><n>Burlesque</n>    <k>A young, full-figured high school teacher gets the chance to become attractive despite her ample figure by dancing in a burlesque bar. The world around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-24 18:10:00" d="2020-05-24 19:20:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder">Anatomy of a Murder IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Three bears are robbed from the local zoo, and the guard is murdered. All the clues lead to an illicit enterprise with rare animals involving a dangerous mafia group</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-24 19:20:00" d="2020-05-24 20:30:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder">Anatomy of a Murder IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A detective team of Captain Vyrová is summoned to investigate an unusual case: three bears mysteriously disappeared from the local zoo. Their initial clues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-24 20:30:00" d="2020-05-24 22:40:00"><n>The Counterfeiters</n>    <k>1920s Paris. When teenager Bernard (Jules-Angelo Bigarnet) discovers that the man who raised him is in fact not his father, he leaves the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-24 22:40:00" d="2020-05-24 23:40:00"><n u="The Fury Season">The Fury Season 2 (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Danger lurks in the city when a murderer is on the loose. When he is finally found, the investigation takes a dark turn as he is discovered lifeless</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-24 23:40:00" d="2020-05-25 00:45:00"><n u="The Fury Season">The Fury Season 2 (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% A prominent politician and his son are found dead and all their valuables have been stolen. It is up to Kunes and his unit to discover the truth behind this tragedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-25 00:45:00" d="2020-05-25 01:35:00"><n>Lifeline – S1E1</n>    <k>During a heart transplant operation, Oskana has to resolve an emergency after an argument with a young doctor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-25 01:35:00" d="2020-05-25 02:30:00"><n>Lifeline – S1E2</n>    <k>Oksana is late for work because of Anton's fault. Oksana invites Tatiana to work as a senior nurse but Tanya hesitates so a former paramedic lover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-25 02:30:00" d="2020-05-25 03:20:00"><n>Mute – E1</n>    <k>Nastya dreams to adopt a 7-year-old boy, Yegor, from an orphanage. However, the boy is not a simple kid: two criminals have been watching over him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-25 03:20:00" d="2020-05-25 04:15:00"><n>Mute – E2</n>    <k>The orphanage manager decides to cheat the thugs and find the money himself. To do this, he takes the boy away from the orphanage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-25 04:15:00" d="2020-05-25 06:00:00" c="1"><n>Wings of Steel</n><t>F</t>    <k>A former RAF captain (David Svehlík) returns home to his family in 1945 hoping for a happy life after surviving the horrors of war piloting combat aircrafts</k>  </p>
</a>
