<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2021-07-12 04:56:24"><p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-19 06:00:00" d="2021-07-19 06:50:00"><n u="Shattered Destinies – Episode">Shattered Destinies – Episode 3</n>    <k>Vika gets what she wants, but she does not know it is only the beginning of the challenges she and Kostya will have to face</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-19 06:50:00" d="2021-07-19 07:45:00"><n u="Shattered Destinies – Episode">Shattered Destinies – Episode 4</n>    <k>After an accidental meeting of Oleg and Kostya, everything changes. The men surprisingly notice they look the same. From now on, they are to reveal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-19 07:45:00" d="2021-07-19 08:55:00"><n u="Fallen Empire">Fallen Empire (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Tired of how their country was run, two men decide to take refuge in Russia and build an exiled government. Soon they discover the price of their actions</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-19 08:55:00" d="2021-07-19 10:20:00"><n u="Fallen Empire">Fallen Empire (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Patriotism is a willingness to sacrifice for your country. Two men did it and were sentenced to death for betraying the monarchy. They still managed to find independence</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-19 10:20:00" d="2021-07-19 12:15:00" c="1"><n>Time of Honor</n><t>F</t>    <k>67% Spain, 1944. Lucia returns to her rural village home and reconnects with Manuel, a member of the local resistance against Franco. Despite the risks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-19 12:15:00" d="2021-07-19 14:10:00"><n>In Love with an Angel</n>    <k>Claudio (Raoul Bova) is a selfish 40-year-old man who enjoys all the pleasures in life. With a limitless bank account at his disposal and a charming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-19 14:10:00" d="2021-07-19 15:45:00" c="1"><n>The Good Neighbor</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% The budding friendship between two very different neighbors takes a tragic turn when David (Maxim Mehmet) runs over a young woman and causes her death</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-19 15:45:00" d="2021-07-19 17:25:00" c="1"><n>Last Chance for Love</n><t>F</t>    <k>57% Edoardo, an Italian composer, faces a mid-life crisis. He takes a break in Valencia, where fate puts him in charge of the town’s choir. There he meets</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-19 17:25:00" d="2021-07-19 19:10:00" c="1"><n>Wings of Steel</n><t>F</t>    <k>A former RAF captain (David Svehlík) returns home to his family in 1945 hoping for a happy life after surviving the horrors of war piloting combat aircrafts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-19 19:10:00" d="2021-07-19 21:00:00" c="1"><n>The Greek Affair</n><t>F</t>    <k>1970. Antonio leaves Rome and drives to Greece longing to discover its many secrets. His summer adventure quickly turns into a romance when he falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-19 21:00:00" d="2021-07-19 21:50:00"><n>Strike Force Season 2 Episode 1: Risky Business</n>    <k>Willem (Dennis van de Ven) gets the shock of a lifetime when he hears that Theo (Jeroen van Koningsbrugge) has been shot down in his own apartment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-19 21:50:00" d="2021-07-19 22:40:00"><n>Strike Force Season 2 Episode 2: Bad Trip</n>    <k>After a bloody shoot-out, Theo (Jeroen van Koningsbrugge) and Willem (Dennis van de Ven) venture into Amsterdam’s night life. There, a cold-blooded hitman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-19 22:40:00" d="2021-07-20 00:15:00"><n>A Private Affair</n>    <k>An investigative journalist enters a steamy affair with Ben, a prominent New York banker to get the secrets of the shady finance world. When he becomes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-20 00:15:00" d="2021-07-20 01:35:00"><n u="An Innocent Man">An Innocent Man (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Based on true events. In 1899, a little girl is brutally murdered in a local village. In a climate of growing antisemitism, a young Jewish man named</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-20 01:35:00" d="2021-07-20 03:00:00"><n u="An Innocent Man">An Innocent Man (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A trial begins against Hilsner. This will become the most famous case in the history of the country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-20 03:00:00" d="2021-07-20 03:50:00"><n>Strike Force Season 2 Episode 1: Risky Business</n>    <k>Willem (Dennis van de Ven) gets the shock of a lifetime when he hears that Theo (Jeroen van Koningsbrugge) has been shot down in his own apartment</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-20 03:50:00" d="2021-07-20 04:40:00"><n>Strike Force Season 2 Episode 2: Bad Trip</n>    <k>After a bloody shoot-out, Theo (Jeroen van Koningsbrugge) and Willem (Dennis van de Ven) venture into Amsterdam’s night life. There, a cold-blooded hitman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-20 04:40:00" d="2021-07-20 06:00:00"><n u="An Innocent Man">An Innocent Man (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Based on true events. In 1899, a little girl is brutally murdered in a local village. In a climate of growing antisemitism, a young Jewish man named</k>  </p>
</a>
