<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2020-05-16 04:49:39"><p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-23 06:00:00" d="2020-05-23 08:10:00"><n>The Counterfeiters</n>    <k>1920s Paris. When teenager Bernard (Jules-Angelo Bigarnet) discovers that the man who raised him is in fact not his father, he leaves the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-23 08:10:00" d="2020-05-23 09:40:00"><n>Double Trouble</n>    <k>Marek lives alternately with two women. He tells them both that he works in another city for part of the week. In reality, he stays in the same and moves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-23 09:40:00" d="2020-05-23 11:25:00"><n>Fallen from the sky</n>    <k>January 1943. France is under occupation. Louise is 70, and in her bar, everyone likes to forget about the war. Her serenity is disturbed, however</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-23 11:25:00" d="2020-05-23 13:05:00"><n>Blood Brothers</n>    <k>Brice (Sylvain Dieuaide), the eldest son of the Lemeuniers, is accused of a quadruple murder. His brother Martin (Clément Chebli) will do whatever it takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-23 13:05:00" d="2020-05-23 14:35:00"><n>Better Days</n>    <k>It’s New Year’s Eve and Gary (Cody Brotter) desperately tries to spark the interest of his ex-girlfriend, without letting his friends embarrass him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-23 14:35:00" d="2020-05-23 16:10:00"><n>Blind Fear</n>    <k>After a tragic car crash and losing the baby she was expecting, Betty seeks solace in a new job looking after a blind kid in a mountain house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-23 16:10:00" d="2020-05-23 17:40:00" c="1"><n>Babylon Sisters</n><t>F</t>    <k>The residents of a rundown building receive an eviction notice from their landlord. Led by little Kamla and professor Leone, this striving immigrant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-23 17:40:00" d="2020-05-23 18:30:00"><n>Mute – E1</n>    <k>Nastya dreams to adopt a 7-year-old boy, Yegor, from an orphanage. However, the boy is not a simple kid: two criminals have been watching over him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-23 18:30:00" d="2020-05-23 19:20:00"><n>Mute – E2</n>    <k>The orphanage manager decides to cheat the thugs and find the money himself. To do this, he takes the boy away from the orphanage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-23 19:20:00" d="2020-05-23 20:10:00"><n>Lifeline – S1E1</n>    <k>During a heart transplant operation, Oskana has to resolve an emergency after an argument with a young doctor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-23 20:10:00" d="2020-05-23 21:00:00"><n>Lifeline – S1E2</n>    <k>Oksana is late for work because of Anton's fault. Oksana invites Tatiana to work as a senior nurse but Tanya hesitates so a former paramedic lover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-23 21:00:00" d="2020-05-23 22:00:00"><n u="The Fury Season">The Fury Season 2 (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Danger lurks in the city when a murderer is on the loose. When he is finally found, the investigation takes a dark turn as he is discovered lifeless</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-23 22:00:00" d="2020-05-23 23:00:00"><n u="The Fury Season">The Fury Season 2 (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% A prominent politician and his son are found dead and all their valuables have been stolen. It is up to Kunes and his unit to discover the truth behind this tragedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-23 23:00:00" d="2020-05-24 00:40:00" c="1"><n>Gone</n><t>F</t>    <k>When Caroline (Margot Faure), has a little affair and breaks a promise, the life of her husband changes forever. She disappears after a violent dispute</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-24 00:40:00" d="2020-05-24 01:40:00"><n u="The Fury Season">The Fury Season 2 (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Danger lurks in the city when a murderer is on the loose. When he is finally found, the investigation takes a dark turn as he is discovered lifeless</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-24 01:40:00" d="2020-05-24 02:40:00"><n u="The Fury Season">The Fury Season 2 (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% A prominent politician and his son are found dead and all their valuables have been stolen. It is up to Kunes and his unit to discover the truth behind this tragedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-24 02:40:00" d="2020-05-24 04:20:00" c="1"><n>Deception</n><t>F</t>    <k>Paul Berthier, a public prosecutor, witnesses the accidental drowning of a young girl but does nothing to help. A decision that will change</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-24 04:20:00" d="2020-05-24 06:00:00"><n>The Skin of Sorrow</n>    <k>It's 1832, and 22-year-old Raphaël's (Thomas Coumans) gambling has driven him to the brink of suicide. He is about to throw himself in the Seine</k>  </p>
</a>
