<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="14" t="2019-08-15 22:39:00"><p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-22 06:00:00" d="2019-08-22 08:15:00"><n>Broken Promise</n>    <k>Based on a true story of a Jewish boy in Western Slovakia who escaped deportation to a concentration camp thanks to his extraordinary soccer talent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-22 08:15:00" d="2019-08-22 10:05:00"><n>Dogs Five-Star Hotel</n>    <k>Sara and Luca are in love and have a plan for their future: the best hotel for dogs the world has ever seen. With no option but to ask their parents</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-22 10:05:00" d="2019-08-22 11:50:00"><n>Silent Fear</n>    <k>Sabine (Thekla Reuten) is looking for the truth behind the disappearance of her best friend twenty years ago. An encounter with the handsome Olaf (Daan</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-22 11:50:00" d="2019-08-22 13:30:00"><n>Mafia Millionaires</n>    <k>The rise and fall of a Camorra clan in Naples, told through the eyes of a crime boss and his family. Forty years of a man's life, forty years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-22 13:30:00" d="2019-08-22 15:10:00"><n>The Perfect Stranger</n>    <k>Jonathan (Bruno Debrandt), an unhappy man who has just inherited a massive fortune, discovers that Anaďs (Audrey Fleurot), his wife, has been hospitalized</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-22 15:10:00" d="2019-08-22 16:50:00"><n>Enticement</n>    <k>Jonathan Marescot has an obsession for stealing little objects. He loves not only possessing them, but also the thrill he gets from robbing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-22 16:50:00" d="2019-08-22 18:35:00"><n>Gone</n>    <k>When Caroline (Margot Faure), has a little affair and breaks a promise, the life of her husband changes forever. She disappears after a violent dispute</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-22 18:35:00" d="2019-08-22 20:15:00"><n>Blood Brothers</n>    <k>Brice (Sylvain Dieuaide), the eldest son of the Lemeuniers, is accused of a quadruple murder. His brother Martin (Clément Chebli) will do whatever it takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-22 20:15:00" d="2019-08-22 22:00:00"><n>The Skin of Sorrow</n>    <k>It's 1832, and 22-year-old Raphaël's (Thomas Coumans) gambling has driven him to the brink of suicide. He is about to throw himself in the Seine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-22 22:00:00" d="2019-08-22 23:35:00"><n>Silence of Death</n>    <k>Julie (Mélusine Mayance) lives with her mother (Pascale Arbillot) in an isolated house. She invents imaginary friends in the scary manga comics she draws</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-22 23:35:00" d="2019-08-23 01:10:00"><n>Blood Brothers</n>    <k>Brice (Sylvain Dieuaide), the eldest son of the Lemeuniers, is accused of a quadruple murder. His brother Martin (Clément Chebli) will do whatever it takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-23 01:10:00" d="2019-08-23 02:45:00"><n>Silence of Death</n>    <k>Julie (Mélusine Mayance) lives with her mother (Pascale Arbillot) in an isolated house. She invents imaginary friends in the scary manga comics she draws</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-23 02:45:00" d="2019-08-23 04:10:00" c="1"><n>Perversion</n><t>F</t>    <k>Investigating the death of a young woman, a police inspector finds himself exploring the torrid and mysterious side of Roma’s night life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-23 04:10:00" d="2019-08-23 06:00:00"><n>In Love with an Angel</n>    <k>Claudio (Raoul Bova) is a selfish 40-year-old man who enjoys all the pleasures in life. With a limitless bank account at his disposal and a charming</k>  </p>
</a>
