<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="20" t="2020-05-10 04:32:02"><p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-17 06:00:00" d="2020-05-17 07:25:00"><n>A Sicilian Dream</n>    <k>A poignant drama following the development of a young Sicilian boy, Ettore Corvaja (Corrado Fortuna), from the 1950s to 1960s. Yearning to become</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-17 07:25:00" d="2020-05-17 08:50:00" c="1"><n>Parental Guidance</n><t>F</t>    <k>Trying to conceive a second child, Giulio (Adriano Giannini) discovers he is infertile and suspects his wife, Veronica (Serena Autieri)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-17 08:50:00" d="2020-05-17 10:20:00" c="1"><n>Babylon Sisters</n><t>F</t>    <k>The residents of a rundown building receive an eviction notice from their landlord. Led by little Kamla and professor Leone, this striving immigrant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-17 10:20:00" d="2020-05-17 11:55:00"><n>Breaking News</n>    <k>Maksim is so addicted to internet news and social media feeds that he barely notices his wife anymore. Until she surprises him with very personal and life-changing news</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-17 11:55:00" d="2020-05-17 12:45:00"><n u="Heart to Heart">Heart to Heart (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Yevenia lives a fairytale: she is young and beautiful, she has a wonderful career and a man of her dream. A doorbell ring changes everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-17 12:45:00" d="2020-05-17 13:35:00"><n u="Heart to Heart">Heart to Heart (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Zenya thinks the boy was sent by some of her rivals. However, Vera, the woman who raised the boy has Leo’s DNA test results, which prove Zhenya is his biological mother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-17 13:35:00" d="2020-05-17 14:25:00"><n u="Heart to Heart">Heart to Heart (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Zenya gets enmeshed in her own lies, which she made up to get Vadim’s attention. Her relations with her fiancé worsen due to Irena, her fiancé’s mother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-17 14:25:00" d="2020-05-17 15:20:00"><n u="Heart to Heart">Heart to Heart (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Eventually, Zenya realizes she loves the boy. She is afraid to admit she has fallen in love with Safronov. Can she refuse her “celebrity life”?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-17 15:20:00" d="2020-05-17 16:10:00"><n u="Chernobyl: Aftermath">Chernobyl: Aftermath (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lera arrives in Prypyat. When her passport is stolen, an army officer uses his influence and manages to help her retrieve it, aiming to win Lera's heart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-17 16:10:00" d="2020-05-17 17:00:00"><n u="Chernobyl: Aftermath">Chernobyl: Aftermath (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Chernobyl nuclear plant explodes, leaving the surrounding area in disarray. Vitas rushes to the site, but it's too late. Sveta perishes, leaving behind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-17 17:00:00" d="2020-05-17 17:50:00"><n u="Chernobyl: Aftermath">Chernobyl: Aftermath (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>It's been 30 years after the Chernobyl tragedy and Lera tries to live a normal life. When she is asked to partake on a charity event, Igor walks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-17 17:50:00" d="2020-05-17 18:45:00"><n u="Chernobyl: Aftermath">Chernobyl: Aftermath (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Vitas Jr. is in critical condition. His only hope is an organ transplant from his father. Thirty years of confusion have passed for Lera and Vitas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-17 18:45:00" d="2020-05-17 20:00:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder">Anatomy of a Murder IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Three bears are robbed from the local zoo, and the guard is murdered. All the clues lead to an illicit enterprise with rare animals involving a dangerous mafia group</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-17 20:00:00" d="2020-05-17 21:20:00" c="1"><n u="Fallout Part">Fallout Part 1</n><t>F</t>    <k>An unfortunate gunshot intertwines the fates of seven people and changes their fate forever. Viktor shoots Jendric while defending his daughter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-17 21:20:00" d="2020-05-17 22:40:00" c="1"><n u="Fallout Part">Fallout Part 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>While helping to reconstruct Jendric’s family, Viktor also attempts to get closer to his daughter and former wife. This is his only opportunity for redemption</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-17 22:40:00" d="2020-05-17 23:40:00"><n u="The Fury Season">The Fury Season 2 (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% The unit's pathologist is missing but the team is busy investigating the finding of a burnt corpse near the quarry. Again, there is only one witness</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-17 23:40:00" d="2020-05-18 00:40:00"><n u="The Fury Season">The Fury Season 2 (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% After a wild party on a ship, a river brings the corpse of an unknown woman. Kunes and Lupinek follow the ship to the country's border, but it might be too late</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-18 00:40:00" d="2020-05-18 02:25:00"><n u="Deadly Game Part">Deadly Game Part 1</n>    <k>Olivia (Michelle Bonev), a dedicated police officer, decides to help Natasha (Nadia Konakchieva), an Eastern European woman who has sacrificed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-18 02:25:00" d="2020-05-18 04:10:00"><n u="Deadly Game Part">Deadly Game Part 2</n>    <k>Olivia (Michelle Bonev), a dedicated police officer, decides to help Natasha (Nadia Konakchieva), an Eastern European woman who has sacrificed</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-18 04:10:00" d="2020-05-18 06:00:00"><n>In Love with an Angel</n>    <k>Claudio (Raoul Bova) is a selfish 40-year-old man who enjoys all the pleasures in life. With a limitless bank account at his disposal and a charming</k>  </p>
</a>
