<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2020-05-11 04:30:54"><p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-18 06:00:00" d="2020-05-18 07:40:00"><n>The Skin of Sorrow</n>    <k>It's 1832, and 22-year-old Raphaël's (Thomas Coumans) gambling has driven him to the brink of suicide. He is about to throw himself in the Seine</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-18 07:40:00" d="2020-05-18 09:20:00"><n>Blood Brothers</n>    <k>Brice (Sylvain Dieuaide), the eldest son of the Lemeuniers, is accused of a quadruple murder. His brother Martin (Clément Chebli) will do whatever it takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-18 09:20:00" d="2020-05-18 10:10:00"><n u="Chernobyl: Aftermath">Chernobyl: Aftermath (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lera arrives in Prypyat. When her passport is stolen, an army officer uses his influence and manages to help her retrieve it, aiming to win Lera's heart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-18 10:10:00" d="2020-05-18 11:00:00"><n u="Chernobyl: Aftermath">Chernobyl: Aftermath (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Chernobyl nuclear plant explodes, leaving the surrounding area in disarray. Vitas rushes to the site, but it's too late. Sveta perishes, leaving behind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-18 11:00:00" d="2020-05-18 11:50:00"><n u="Chernobyl: Aftermath">Chernobyl: Aftermath (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>It's been 30 years after the Chernobyl tragedy and Lera tries to live a normal life. When she is asked to partake on a charity event, Igor walks</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-18 11:50:00" d="2020-05-18 12:45:00"><n u="Chernobyl: Aftermath">Chernobyl: Aftermath (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Vitas Jr. is in critical condition. His only hope is an organ transplant from his father. Thirty years of confusion have passed for Lera and Vitas</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-18 12:45:00" d="2020-05-18 14:10:00"><n u="The Mine Inferno">The Mine Inferno (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Petr (Oskar Hes) drops out of the Mine Engineering College in Prague and moves back to the family home with a pregnant Jewish girlfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-18 14:10:00" d="2020-05-18 15:25:00"><n u="The Mine Inferno">The Mine Inferno (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Marie (Martha Issová) is falling apart. A collapsed Milan (Marek Taclík) shifts to a less paid job, while Jana (Antonie Formanová) betrays Marie’s darkest secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-18 15:25:00" d="2020-05-18 16:40:00" c="1"><n u="Fallout Part">Fallout Part 1</n><t>F</t>    <k>An unfortunate gunshot intertwines the fates of seven people and changes their fate forever. Viktor shoots Jendric while defending his daughter</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-18 16:40:00" d="2020-05-18 18:00:00" c="1"><n u="Fallout Part">Fallout Part 2</n><t>F</t>    <k>While helping to reconstruct Jendric’s family, Viktor also attempts to get closer to his daughter and former wife. This is his only opportunity for redemption</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-18 18:00:00" d="2020-05-18 19:30:00"><n>True Intentions</n>    <k>Jana and Marika meet on a train and quickly become friends. They go to the countryside, a remote mountain area that holds a lot of secrets about Jana's past</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-18 19:30:00" d="2020-05-18 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Babylon Sisters</n><t>F</t>    <k>The residents of a rundown building receive an eviction notice from their landlord. Led by little Kamla and professor Leone, this striving immigrant</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-18 21:00:00" d="2020-05-18 22:00:00"><n u="The Fury Season">The Fury Season 2 (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Danger lurks in the city when a murderer is on the loose. When he is finally found, the investigation takes a dark turn as he is discovered lifeless</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-18 22:00:00" d="2020-05-18 23:00:00"><n u="The Fury Season">The Fury Season 2 (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% A prominent politician and his son are found dead and all their valuables have been stolen. It is up to Kunes and his unit to discover the truth behind this tragedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-18 23:00:00" d="2020-05-19 00:35:00"><n>Blood Brothers</n>    <k>Brice (Sylvain Dieuaide), the eldest son of the Lemeuniers, is accused of a quadruple murder. His brother Martin (Clément Chebli) will do whatever it takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-19 00:35:00" d="2020-05-19 01:35:00"><n u="The Fury Season">The Fury Season 2 (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Danger lurks in the city when a murderer is on the loose. When he is finally found, the investigation takes a dark turn as he is discovered lifeless</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-19 01:35:00" d="2020-05-19 02:35:00"><n u="The Fury Season">The Fury Season 2 (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% A prominent politician and his son are found dead and all their valuables have been stolen. It is up to Kunes and his unit to discover the truth behind this tragedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-19 02:35:00" d="2020-05-19 04:25:00" c="1"><n>The Greek Affair</n><t>F</t>    <k>1970. Antonio leaves Rome and drives to Greece longing to discover its many secrets. His summer adventure quickly turns into a romance when he falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-19 04:25:00" d="2020-05-19 06:00:00" c="1"><n>Suspicion</n><t>F</t>    <k>A lonely, trusting old woman fears that no-one needs her anymore. She suddenly meets a young man that claims to be a distant relative</k>  </p>
</a>
