<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="16" t="2020-05-12 04:33:22"><p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-19 06:00:00" d="2020-05-19 07:25:00"><n u="The Mine Inferno">The Mine Inferno (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Petr (Oskar Hes) drops out of the Mine Engineering College in Prague and moves back to the family home with a pregnant Jewish girlfriend</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-19 07:25:00" d="2020-05-19 08:40:00"><n u="The Mine Inferno">The Mine Inferno (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Marie (Martha Issová) is falling apart. A collapsed Milan (Marek Taclík) shifts to a less paid job, while Jana (Antonie Formanová) betrays Marie’s darkest secret</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-19 08:40:00" d="2020-05-19 10:15:00"><n>The Evil Hands</n>    <k>Roxana (Sylvie Testud), a prominent violinist, has both hands crushed during an accident. After she undergoes a transplant by a prominent surgeon, whose</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-19 10:15:00" d="2020-05-19 12:05:00"><n>In Love with an Angel</n>    <k>Claudio (Raoul Bova) is a selfish 40-year-old man who enjoys all the pleasures in life. With a limitless bank account at his disposal and a charming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-19 12:05:00" d="2020-05-19 13:45:00" c="1"><n>Deception</n><t>F</t>    <k>Paul Berthier, a public prosecutor, witnesses the accidental drowning of a young girl but does nothing to help. A decision that will change</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-19 13:45:00" d="2020-05-19 15:35:00" c="1"><n>The Greek Affair</n><t>F</t>    <k>1970. Antonio leaves Rome and drives to Greece longing to discover its many secrets. His summer adventure quickly turns into a romance when he falls</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-19 15:35:00" d="2020-05-19 17:15:00"><n>Blood Brothers</n>    <k>Brice (Sylvain Dieuaide), the eldest son of the Lemeuniers, is accused of a quadruple murder. His brother Martin (Clément Chebli) will do whatever it takes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-19 17:15:00" d="2020-05-19 18:15:00"><n u="The Fury Season">The Fury Season 2 (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% Danger lurks in the city when a murderer is on the loose. When he is finally found, the investigation takes a dark turn as he is discovered lifeless</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-19 18:15:00" d="2020-05-19 19:15:00"><n u="The Fury Season">The Fury Season 2 (8)</n><t>S</t>    <k>75% A prominent politician and his son are found dead and all their valuables have been stolen. It is up to Kunes and his unit to discover the truth behind this tragedy</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-19 19:15:00" d="2020-05-19 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Wings of Steel</n><t>F</t>    <k>A former RAF captain (David Svehlík) returns home to his family in 1945 hoping for a happy life after surviving the horrors of war piloting combat aircrafts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-19 21:00:00" d="2020-05-19 22:15:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder">Anatomy of a Murder IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A detective team of Captain Vyrová is summoned to investigate an unusual case: three bears mysteriously disappeared from the local zoo. Their initial clues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-19 22:15:00" d="2020-05-19 23:55:00"><n>Beyond Suspicion</n>    <k>Valérie (Cristiana Réali) is an active and exemplary woman. Psychiatrist by profession, a mother, a wife and an irreproachable parishioner. Still, Valerie</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-19 23:55:00" d="2020-05-20 01:10:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder">Anatomy of a Murder IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A detective team of Captain Vyrová is summoned to investigate an unusual case: three bears mysteriously disappeared from the local zoo. Their initial clues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-20 01:10:00" d="2020-05-20 03:00:00"><n>In Love with an Angel</n>    <k>Claudio (Raoul Bova) is a selfish 40-year-old man who enjoys all the pleasures in life. With a limitless bank account at his disposal and a charming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-20 03:00:00" d="2020-05-20 04:40:00" c="1"><n>Deception</n><t>F</t>    <k>Paul Berthier, a public prosecutor, witnesses the accidental drowning of a young girl but does nothing to help. A decision that will change</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-20 04:40:00" d="2020-05-20 06:00:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder">Anatomy of a Murder IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A detective team of Captain Vyrová is summoned to investigate an unusual case: three bears mysteriously disappeared from the local zoo. Their initial clues</k>  </p>
</a>
