<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="15" t="2019-08-11 01:34:35"><p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-17 06:00:00" d="2019-08-17 07:45:00"><n>Obsession</n>    <k>Simone (Loes Haverkort) inherits a dilapidated country house in France and makes her way there with her husband Eric and their two children</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-17 07:45:00" d="2019-08-17 09:25:00"><n>Gone</n>    <k>When Caroline (Margot Faure), has a little affair and breaks a promise, the life of her husband changes forever. She disappears after a violent dispute</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-17 09:25:00" d="2019-08-17 11:00:00" c="1"><n>Deception</n><t>F</t>    <k>Paul Berthier, a public prosecutor, witnesses the accidental drowning of a young girl but does nothing to help. A decision that will change</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-17 11:00:00" d="2019-08-17 12:35:00"><n>Enticement</n>    <k>Jonathan Marescot has an obsession for stealing little objects. He loves not only possessing them, but also the thrill he gets from robbing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-17 12:35:00" d="2019-08-17 14:10:00"><n>The Perfect Stranger</n>    <k>Jonathan (Bruno Debrandt), an unhappy man who has just inherited a massive fortune, discovers that Anaďs (Audrey Fleurot), his wife, has been hospitalized</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-17 14:10:00" d="2019-08-17 15:50:00" c="1"><n>Hit and Run</n><t>F</t>    <k>One rainy night, a woman is killed in a hit and run accident. Her sudden death will forever change the life of the city’s mayor as an investigative</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-17 15:50:00" d="2019-08-17 17:25:00"><n>Chase</n>    <k>Luis (Nicolas Cazalé) is a somewhat clumsy money transporter. Against all odds, he steals his own van with five million euros. For Emma (Isabelle Carré)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-17 17:25:00" d="2019-08-17 19:00:00" c="1"><n>Murdered</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% Cathy (Patricia Kaas) has been preparing herself since early morning. She is about to celebrate her daughter Eva’s 20th birthday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-17 19:00:00" d="2019-08-17 20:45:00" c="1"><n>Wings of Steel</n><t>F</t>    <k>A former RAF captain (David Svehlík) returns home to his family in 1945 hoping for a happy life after surviving the horrors of war piloting combat aircrafts</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-17 20:45:00" d="2019-08-17 22:25:00"><n>Mafia Millionaires</n>    <k>The rise and fall of a Camorra clan in Naples, told through the eyes of a crime boss and his family. Forty years of a man's life, forty years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-17 22:25:00" d="2019-08-18 00:00:00" c="1"><n>Deception</n><t>F</t>    <k>Paul Berthier, a public prosecutor, witnesses the accidental drowning of a young girl but does nothing to help. A decision that will change</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-18 00:00:00" d="2019-08-18 01:35:00"><n>Enticement</n>    <k>Jonathan Marescot has an obsession for stealing little objects. He loves not only possessing them, but also the thrill he gets from robbing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-18 01:35:00" d="2019-08-18 03:00:00" c="1"><n>Perversion</n><t>F</t>    <k>Investigating the death of a young woman, a police inspector finds himself exploring the torrid and mysterious side of Roma’s night life</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-18 03:00:00" d="2019-08-18 04:30:00"><n>Back to Mom's</n>    <k>François (Pierre Cassignard), divorced and unemployed, finds himself on the street. He returns to live with Alice (Annie Cordy), his mother, claiming</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-18 04:30:00" d="2019-08-18 06:00:00"><n>Unfaithful</n>    <k>Eric (Frédéric Van Den Driessche) looks like a happy family man. But he also frequents two other women with one child each: Chloé and Hugo, whose</k>  </p>
</a>
