<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2021-07-09 06:52:05"><p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-14 06:00:00" d="2021-07-14 07:35:00"><n u="Full Disclosure Episode">Full Disclosure Episode 3 I</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Elena (Antonia Liskova) is increasingly tormented by the memory of her old captor, Virgilio Sanna (Mirko Urania), while Pietro (Massimo Poggio) continues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-14 07:35:00" d="2021-07-14 09:10:00"><n u="Full Disclosure Episode">Full Disclosure Episode 4 I</n><t>S</t>    <k>58% Elena (Antonia Liskova) wants the truth from Pietro (Massimo Poggio) about his role in her kidnapping and confronts him at gunpoint. His confession</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-14 09:10:00" d="2021-07-14 10:35:00"><n u="The Shadow Killer">The Shadow Killer (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>In the early 1970s, a series of bloody crimes targeted brunette women. As the police investigation rejects the possibility of a serial killer, murders multiply</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-14 10:35:00" d="2021-07-14 12:00:00"><n u="The Shadow Killer">The Shadow Killer (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The investigator finds herself puzzled by the evidence. As the case progresses, she discovers astonishing information leading to the existence of a serial killer</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-14 12:00:00" d="2021-07-14 13:20:00" c="1"><n>Unlocked</n><t>F</t>    <k>59% Lonely medical student Frank is pleased with his flat: a safe, quiet haven where he can relax. When he meets his intrusive neighbor Lotte, he realizes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-14 13:20:00" d="2021-07-14 14:50:00"><n u="Dark Forest – Episode">Dark Forest – Episode 1</n>    <k>After twenty years, Nina Ferrari (Giulia Michelini) returns to the small provincial town where she was born. She has won a chair to teach psychology</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-14 14:50:00" d="2021-07-14 16:20:00"><n u="Dark Forest – Episode">Dark Forest – Episode 2</n>    <k>Nina (Giulia Michelini) is attacked by the mysterious hooded figure. To save herself, she dives into the river which runs through the woods</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-14 16:20:00" d="2021-07-14 17:50:00"><n u="Dark Forest – Episode">Dark Forest – Episode 3</n>    <k>Nina (Giulia Michelini) is alone and standing before the murderer in the woods. The hooded figure scrutinizes her for a while, then moves away, leaving</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-14 17:50:00" d="2021-07-14 19:20:00"><n u="Dark Forest – Episode">Dark Forest – Episode 4</n>    <k>Nina's father is dead and she doesn't know what to think anymore: did her father really kill her mother? And why? Who murdered him?</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-14 19:20:00" d="2021-07-14 21:00:00" c="1"><n>The Winds of Passion</n><t>F</t>    <k>In the climax of political turmoil in France between republicans and Catholics, a young teacher and a fierce activist fall in love and marry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-14 21:00:00" d="2021-07-14 21:50:00"><n u="Shattered Destinies – Episode">Shattered Destinies – Episode 3</n>    <k>Vika gets what she wants, but she does not know it is only the beginning of the challenges she and Kostya will have to face</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-14 21:50:00" d="2021-07-14 22:40:00"><n u="Shattered Destinies – Episode">Shattered Destinies – Episode 4</n>    <k>After an accidental meeting of Oleg and Kostya, everything changes. The men surprisingly notice they look the same. From now on, they are to reveal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-14 22:40:00" d="2021-07-15 00:15:00"><n>The Climb</n>    <k>A climbing champion is pushed to her limits when she takes on a perilous new route to the summit of the Alps</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-15 00:15:00" d="2021-07-15 01:35:00"><n u="An Innocent Man">An Innocent Man (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Based on true events. In 1899, a little girl is brutally murdered in a local village. In a climate of growing antisemitism, a young Jewish man named</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-15 01:35:00" d="2021-07-15 03:00:00"><n u="An Innocent Man">An Innocent Man (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A trial begins against Hilsner. This will become the most famous case in the history of the country</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-15 03:00:00" d="2021-07-15 03:50:00"><n u="Shattered Destinies – Episode">Shattered Destinies – Episode 3</n>    <k>Vika gets what she wants, but she does not know it is only the beginning of the challenges she and Kostya will have to face</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-15 03:50:00" d="2021-07-15 04:40:00"><n u="Shattered Destinies – Episode">Shattered Destinies – Episode 4</n>    <k>After an accidental meeting of Oleg and Kostya, everything changes. The men surprisingly notice they look the same. From now on, they are to reveal</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2021-07-15 04:40:00" d="2021-07-15 06:00:00"><n u="An Innocent Man">An Innocent Man (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Based on true events. In 1899, a little girl is brutally murdered in a local village. In a climate of growing antisemitism, a young Jewish man named</k>  </p>
</a>
