<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="14" t="2019-08-13 02:09:04"><p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-20 06:00:00" d="2019-08-20 07:40:00"><n>Mafia Millionaires</n>    <k>The rise and fall of a Camorra clan in Naples, told through the eyes of a crime boss and his family. Forty years of a man's life, forty years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-20 07:40:00" d="2019-08-20 09:20:00"><n>Chase</n>    <k>Luis (Nicolas Cazalé) is a somewhat clumsy money transporter. Against all odds, he steals his own van with five million euros. For Emma (Isabelle Carré)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-20 09:20:00" d="2019-08-20 10:50:00"><n>A Sicilian Dream</n>    <k>A poignant drama following the development of a young Sicilian boy, Ettore Corvaja (Corrado Fortuna), from the 1950s to 1960s. Yearning to become</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-20 10:50:00" d="2019-08-20 12:15:00"><n>The President's Mistress</n>    <k>Forbidden love affairs have their risks, especially in closed and conservative societies. Eurochannel welcomes you to the final years of the nineteenth</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-20 12:15:00" d="2019-08-20 13:55:00"><n>The Perfect Stranger</n>    <k>Jonathan (Bruno Debrandt), an unhappy man who has just inherited a massive fortune, discovers that Anaďs (Audrey Fleurot), his wife, has been hospitalized</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-20 13:55:00" d="2019-08-20 15:35:00" c="1"><n>Deception</n><t>F</t>    <k>Paul Berthier, a public prosecutor, witnesses the accidental drowning of a young girl but does nothing to help. A decision that will change</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-20 15:35:00" d="2019-08-20 17:25:00"><n u="The Salento Murders Part">The Salento Murders Part 1</n>    <k>A malevolent clan, probably from Calabria, has arrived in Salento to conquer the territory. Commissioner Pasquale Zagaria (Lino Banfi) is a policeman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-20 17:25:00" d="2019-08-20 19:20:00"><n u="The Salento Murders Part">The Salento Murders Part 2</n>    <k>A malevolent clan, probably from Calabria, has arrived in Salento to conquer the territory. Commissioner Pasquale Zagaria (Lino Banfi) is a policeman</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-20 19:20:00" d="2019-08-20 21:00:00" c="1"><n>Murdered</n><t>F</t>    <k>52% Cathy (Patricia Kaas) has been preparing herself since early morning. She is about to celebrate her daughter Eva’s 20th birthday</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-20 21:00:00" d="2019-08-20 22:45:00"><n u="Mafia Undercover Season">Mafia Undercover Season 2 (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Following Bruno’s (Peppino Mazzotta) escape from prison and Agata’s (Carlotta Antonelli) rescue from Albania, the Corona family is finally reunited again</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-20 22:45:00" d="2019-08-21 00:25:00"><n u="Mafia Undercover Season">Mafia Undercover Season 2 (4)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Following Don Antonio’s (Renato Carpentieri) death, the alliance between Marco (Marco Bocci) and Bruno (Peppino Mazzotta) becomes increasingly fragile</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-21 00:25:00" d="2019-08-21 02:40:00"><n>Broken Promise</n>    <k>Based on a true story of a Jewish boy in Western Slovakia who escaped deportation to a concentration camp thanks to his extraordinary soccer talent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-21 02:40:00" d="2019-08-21 04:25:00" c="1"><n>The Time of Secrets</n><t>F</t>    <k>68% The last vacations for Marcel Pagnol (Pierre-François Martin-Laval) in his favorite Provence hills prove as delightful as challenging. It is the beginning</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2019-08-21 04:25:00" d="2019-08-21 06:00:00"><n>The Time of Love</n>    <k>Overcoming disciplinary committee, Marcel (Pierre-François Martin-Laval) gets to stay at high school. He becomes a leader among his new classmates, firming</k>  </p>
</a>
