<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="19" t="2020-05-29 04:35:01"><p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-05 06:00:00" d="2020-06-05 07:45:00"><n>Obsession</n>    <k>Simone (Loes Haverkort) inherits a dilapidated country house in France and makes her way there with her husband Eric and their two children</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-05 07:45:00" d="2020-06-05 09:25:00"><n>Albert Camus</n>    <k>During the 1959 rebellion Albert Camus (Stéphane Freiss) wrote to his mother to convince her to leave Algeria and join him in France. He sees episodes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-05 09:25:00" d="2020-06-05 11:15:00"><n u="Caribbean Thunder">Caribbean Thunder (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>After a multimillion-Euro diamond robbery in Italy, Chiara (Vittoria Belvedere), Giorgia (Martina Stella) and Laura (Camilla Ferranti), a multi-task police</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-05 11:15:00" d="2020-06-05 13:05:00"><n u="Caribbean Thunder">Caribbean Thunder (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Chiara (Vittoria Belvedere), Giorgia (Martina Stella) y Laura (Camilla Ferranti) contiue their search for Giovanni Rossetti. In the verge of bringing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-05 13:05:00" d="2020-06-05 14:55:00"><n u="Caribbean Thunder">Caribbean Thunder (3)</n><t>S</t>    <k>After an attempted murder, Gavi (Michael Reale) is put in security. He is the only one who can exonerate Chiara's father. But the investigation</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-05 14:55:00" d="2020-06-05 15:45:00"><n>Mute – E1</n>    <k>Nastya dreams to adopt a 7-year-old boy, Yegor, from an orphanage. However, the boy is not a simple kid: two criminals have been watching over him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-05 15:45:00" d="2020-06-05 16:35:00"><n>Mute – E2</n>    <k>The orphanage manager decides to cheat the thugs and find the money himself. To do this, he takes the boy away from the orphanage</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-05 16:35:00" d="2020-06-05 17:25:00"><n>Mute – E3</n>    <k>Nastya and Andrei follow the manager, who takes Yehor to his hometown. This is where the money is hidden. They are all followed by the thugs</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-05 17:25:00" d="2020-06-05 18:15:00"><n>Mute – E4</n>    <k>Nastya and Andrei start falling in love with each other, but they must first find Yegor. The thugs find the manager, kill him and take Yegor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-05 18:15:00" d="2020-06-05 19:05:00"><n u="Lifeline">Lifeline (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Anton asks Oksana not to linger at the hospital - he plans to celebrate their anniversary but last minute problems at work do not allow her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-05 19:05:00" d="2020-06-05 19:55:00"><n u="Lifeline">Lifeline (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Oksana refuses to go to Anton's parents, who want to bless them for their upcoming marriage. Maxim looks for his daughter after she escapes from her grandparents' house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-05 19:55:00" d="2020-06-05 21:30:00" c="1"><n>Suspicion</n><t>F</t>    <k>A lonely, trusting old woman fears that no-one needs her anymore. She suddenly meets a young man that claims to be a distant relative</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-05 21:30:00" d="2020-06-05 22:30:00"><n u="Legacy">Legacy (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The young detective Jakovljevic and his partner investigate the murder of a young girl who was burned in a cornfield. The investigation leads to a company</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-05 22:30:00" d="2020-06-05 23:30:00"><n u="Legacy">Legacy (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Aleksandar and Mirko bring Strahinja into custody. During a raid at Strahina's place, they find an interesting photo that may be a possible clue</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-05 23:30:00" d="2020-06-06 00:20:00"><n u="Lifeline">Lifeline (5)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Anton asks Oksana not to linger at the hospital - he plans to celebrate their anniversary but last minute problems at work do not allow her</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-06 00:20:00" d="2020-06-06 01:10:00"><n u="Lifeline">Lifeline (6)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Oksana refuses to go to Anton's parents, who want to bless them for their upcoming marriage. Maxim looks for his daughter after she escapes from her grandparents' house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-06 01:10:00" d="2020-06-06 02:40:00"><n>Better Days</n>    <k>It’s New Year’s Eve and Gary (Cody Brotter) desperately tries to spark the interest of his ex-girlfriend, without letting his friends embarrass him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-06 02:40:00" d="2020-06-06 04:20:00"><n>Albert Camus</n>    <k>During the 1959 rebellion Albert Camus (Stéphane Freiss) wrote to his mother to convince her to leave Algeria and join him in France. He sees episodes</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-06-06 04:20:00" d="2020-06-06 06:00:00"><n>Fallen from the sky</n>    <k>January 1943. France is under occupation. Louise is 70, and in her bar, everyone likes to forget about the war. Her serenity is disturbed, however</k>  </p>
</a>
