<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="18" t="2020-05-13 04:33:26"><p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-20 06:00:00" d="2020-05-20 07:25:00"><n>A Sicilian Dream</n>    <k>A poignant drama following the development of a young Sicilian boy, Ettore Corvaja (Corrado Fortuna), from the 1950s to 1960s. Yearning to become</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-20 07:25:00" d="2020-05-20 08:50:00"><n>Burlesque</n>    <k>A young, full-figured high school teacher gets the chance to become attractive despite her ample figure by dancing in a burlesque bar. The world around</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-20 08:50:00" d="2020-05-20 10:15:00"><n>Double Trouble</n>    <k>Marek lives alternately with two women. He tells them both that he works in another city for part of the week. In reality, he stays in the same and moves</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-20 10:15:00" d="2020-05-20 11:25:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder">Anatomy of a Murder IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Three bears are robbed from the local zoo, and the guard is murdered. All the clues lead to an illicit enterprise with rare animals involving a dangerous mafia group</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-20 11:25:00" d="2020-05-20 12:35:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder">Anatomy of a Murder IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A detective team of Captain Vyrová is summoned to investigate an unusual case: three bears mysteriously disappeared from the local zoo. Their initial clues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-20 12:35:00" d="2020-05-20 14:05:00" c="1"><n>Suspicion</n><t>F</t>    <k>A lonely, trusting old woman fears that no-one needs her anymore. She suddenly meets a young man that claims to be a distant relative</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-20 14:05:00" d="2020-05-20 15:30:00" c="1"><n>Parental Guidance</n><t>F</t>    <k>Trying to conceive a second child, Giulio (Adriano Giannini) discovers he is infertile and suspects his wife, Veronica (Serena Autieri)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-20 15:30:00" d="2020-05-20 17:05:00"><n>Enticement</n>    <k>Jonathan Marescot has an obsession for stealing little objects. He loves not only possessing them, but also the thrill he gets from robbing</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-20 17:05:00" d="2020-05-20 18:40:00"><n>Better Days</n>    <k>It’s New Year’s Eve and Gary (Cody Brotter) desperately tries to spark the interest of his ex-girlfriend, without letting his friends embarrass him</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-20 18:40:00" d="2020-05-20 19:50:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder">Anatomy of a Murder IV (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Three bears are robbed from the local zoo, and the guard is murdered. All the clues lead to an illicit enterprise with rare animals involving a dangerous mafia group</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-20 19:50:00" d="2020-05-20 21:00:00"><n u="Anatomy of a Murder">Anatomy of a Murder IV (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>A detective team of Captain Vyrová is summoned to investigate an unusual case: three bears mysteriously disappeared from the local zoo. Their initial clues</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-20 21:00:00" d="2020-05-20 21:50:00"><n>Lifeline – S1E1</n>    <k>During a heart transplant operation, Oskana has to resolve an emergency after an argument with a young doctor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-20 21:50:00" d="2020-05-20 22:40:00"><n>Lifeline – S1E2</n>    <k>Oksana is late for work because of Anton's fault. Oksana invites Tatiana to work as a senior nurse but Tanya hesitates so a former paramedic lover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-20 22:40:00" d="2020-05-21 00:20:00" c="1"><n>Gone</n><t>F</t>    <k>When Caroline (Margot Faure), has a little affair and breaks a promise, the life of her husband changes forever. She disappears after a violent dispute</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-21 00:20:00" d="2020-05-21 01:10:00"><n>Lifeline – S1E1</n>    <k>During a heart transplant operation, Oskana has to resolve an emergency after an argument with a young doctor</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-21 01:10:00" d="2020-05-21 02:05:00"><n>Lifeline – S1E2</n>    <k>Oksana is late for work because of Anton's fault. Oksana invites Tatiana to work as a senior nurse but Tanya hesitates so a former paramedic lover</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-21 02:05:00" d="2020-05-21 04:00:00"><n>Frozen Valley</n>    <k>A former human trafficker finds the murdered body of his nephew in a remote valley. As soon as the police start to investigate the murder case, he becomes the prime suspect</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-05-21 04:00:00" d="2020-05-21 06:00:00"><n>In Love with an Angel</n>    <k>Claudio (Raoul Bova) is a selfish 40-year-old man who enjoys all the pleasures in life. With a limitless bank account at his disposal and a charming</k>  </p>
</a>
