<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<a p="17" t="2020-04-16 04:31:47"><p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-23 06:00:00" d="2020-04-23 07:30:00"><n>Closed Circuit</n>    <k>Hired by a surveillance company to oversee the security of a hypermarket, Pierre Solvy (Thomas Jouannet) soon discovers that he is expected to do other</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-23 07:30:00" d="2020-04-23 09:10:00"><n>Fallen from the sky</n>    <k>January 1943. France is under occupation. Louise is 70, and in her bar, everyone likes to forget about the war. Her serenity is disturbed, however</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-23 09:10:00" d="2020-04-23 10:45:00" c="1"><n>Suspicion</n><t>F</t>    <k>A lonely, trusting old woman fears that no-one needs her anymore. She suddenly meets a young man that claims to be a distant relative</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-23 10:45:00" d="2020-04-23 13:05:00"><n>Broken Promise</n>    <k>Based on a true story of a Jewish boy in Western Slovakia who escaped deportation to a concentration camp thanks to his extraordinary soccer talent</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-23 13:05:00" d="2020-04-23 14:35:00"><n>Paris Undercover</n>    <k>The fate of two intriguing and deadly figures intertwine when a young petty tough is ordered to kill Mr Zhu, a senior man who has just arrived from China</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-23 14:35:00" d="2020-04-23 16:15:00" c="1"><n>The Winds of Passion</n><t>F</t>    <k>In the climax of political turmoil in France between republicans and Catholics, a young teacher and a fierce activist fall in love and marry</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-23 16:15:00" d="2020-04-23 17:55:00"><n>Mafia Millionaires</n>    <k>The rise and fall of a Camorra clan in Naples, told through the eyes of a crime boss and his family. Forty years of a man's life, forty years</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-23 17:55:00" d="2020-04-23 19:20:00" c="1"><n>Parental Guidance</n><t>F</t>    <k>Trying to conceive a second child, Giulio (Adriano Giannini) discovers he is infertile and suspects his wife, Veronica (Serena Autieri)</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-23 19:20:00" d="2020-04-23 20:10:00"><n u="Chernobyl: Aftermath">Chernobyl: Aftermath (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Lera arrives in Prypyat. When her passport is stolen, an army officer uses his influence and manages to help her retrieve it, aiming to win Lera's heart</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-23 20:10:00" d="2020-04-23 21:00:00"><n u="Chernobyl: Aftermath">Chernobyl: Aftermath (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>The Chernobyl nuclear plant explodes, leaving the surrounding area in disarray. Vitas rushes to the site, but it's too late. Sveta perishes, leaving behind</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-23 21:00:00" d="2020-04-23 21:50:00"><n u="Heart to Heart">Heart to Heart (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Yevenia lives a fairytale: she is young and beautiful, she has a wonderful career and a man of her dream. A doorbell ring changes everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-23 21:50:00" d="2020-04-23 22:40:00"><n u="Heart to Heart">Heart to Heart (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Zenya thinks the boy was sent by some of her rivals. However, Vera, the woman who raised the boy has Leo’s DNA test results, which prove Zhenya is his biological mother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-23 22:40:00" d="2020-04-24 00:15:00"><n>Blind Fear</n>    <k>After a tragic car crash and losing the baby she was expecting, Betty seeks solace in a new job looking after a blind kid in a mountain house</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-24 00:15:00" d="2020-04-24 02:20:00"><n>The Counterfeiters</n>    <k>1920s Paris. When teenager Bernard (Jules-Angelo Bigarnet) discovers that the man who raised him is in fact not his father, he leaves the family</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-24 02:20:00" d="2020-04-24 03:10:00"><n u="Heart to Heart">Heart to Heart (1)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Yevenia lives a fairytale: she is young and beautiful, she has a wonderful career and a man of her dream. A doorbell ring changes everything</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-24 03:10:00" d="2020-04-24 04:00:00"><n u="Heart to Heart">Heart to Heart (2)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Zenya thinks the boy was sent by some of her rivals. However, Vera, the woman who raised the boy has Leo’s DNA test results, which prove Zhenya is his biological mother</k>  </p>
<p id_tv="998" o="2020-04-24 04:00:00" d="2020-04-24 05:00:00"><n u="Legacy">Legacy (7)</n><t>S</t>    <k>Aleksandar visits Jovan's wife and shows her compromising pictures of her, so she accepts to work for him. Peca tells his father that he opened</k>  </p>
</a>
